Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
With high hopes, humans
leave Earth...
...to begin a new life in
the space colonies.
But the United Earth Sphere
Alliance gains military power...
...and in the name of
Justice and Peace...
...seizes control of one
colony after the other.
The year is After Colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
To counter the Alliance's
tyranny, rebel colonists...
...bring new arsenals
to the Earth...
...disguising them as
shooting stars.
But the Alliance headquarters
catches on to this operation.
Where are you, Father?!!
Relena...
Father!
Your real name is
Relena Peacecraft.
What're you saying?
Party Night
- Here she is!
- This way!
Get the camera rolling!
Miss Darlian!
Miss Relena Darlian!
Any comments on Minister
Darlian's assassination?!
Should we consider this
a declaration of war?!
Is this the start of a war?!
Don't push! Step back!
Relena!!
How could they ask that?
None of them has any idea why
Father was actually assassinated.
I'm home, Mother.
Relena...
I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to save Father.
Don't be.
I'm just glad that you
weren't injured.
I knew something like this
would happen one day.
Relena...
Your real name is
Relena Peacecraft.
You're the daughter of
the Peacecraft family...
...who once advocated
Complete Pacifism.
Did he say anything
before he passed away?
No, he didn't say a thing.
I have something to
tell you, Relena.
Mother!
Relena?!
You're my real mother!
You'll always be my mother!
Relena...
Now that Minister Darlian
is dead...
...there are no diplomats
acting as a bridge...
...between Earth and
the colonies.
Right.
He was quite the individual.
Just the type of person who
is sacrificed to a new era.
Oh, by the way Lady Une.
You're not planning on
returning here yet?
No, I still have something
to take care of.
I need a little more time.
To get Darlian's daughter.
You don't usually make mistakes.
I'd like your permission to
head to the J.A.P. Point...
...with some mobile suits.
Take five mobile suits.
That many?
A dark shadow seems to
follow us wherever we go.
You mean the Gundams.
The Gundams have only been
attacking our facilities...
...and the new type of
mobile suit.
Think of it as a precaution.
But if a Gundam should attack...
...five suits might not
be enough.
We'll be late for the party!
Wait for me!
Delete files on Heero Yuy
at the Saint Gabriel Institute.
Transfer procedures complete.
Hurry, hurry!
I'm not involved.
Look, it's Relena!
Was her father assassinated
by colony terrorists?
Yeah, the press is all over it!
Relena!
I'm so sorry to hear
about your father.
I wish I were anywhere
but at a party.
All this festivity just
makes me sadder.
That's kind of you both.
But I can't be sad forever.
Let's try our best to be stronger.
Father wouldn't want me
feeling sorry for myself.
Relena...
Transferring?!
Heero is?!
But he hasn't even been
here for a month yet!
Are you off to fight again?!
Where's your next mission?
I met Dr. J.
So even you can be surprised.
Since we met, you're the one
who's always surprising me.
If you killed me now it'd
cause quite a commotion.
I don't think you want that.
The school's holding a party.
Might as well enjoy it.
At least until the dance
is over.
They finally made it.
This fog would slow
anyone down.
We'll be moving the mobile suits
to the hangar at once.
Right!
What's that?!
Look!
A Gundam!!
You let the enemy penetrate
a little too easily.
You can only blame yourselves
for poor security.
Where is that dimwit?!
He's up!
He's right over there.
You're late, Trowa!
Why can't you just stay here
and wait like everyone else?!
I made it here on time.
That's good enough.
Pardon?!
We're up next!
- The audience is waiting!
- Yeah, sure!
Just leave it to me.
All you have to do
is stand still.
Ladies and Gentlemen!
Our next performance is
by Catherine Bloom...
...the knife-throwing star
of the circus!
What a babe!
There she is!
Here goes, Trowa.
Go for it girl!
Look a little scared.
Otherwise I won't have
any fun, my little doll.
Wh-What is it?
He's not afraid of anything!
It's death...
He's begging for his death.
I don't understand!
You wanna die, Trowa?
No, that can't be!
T-Trowa...
Trowa!
Why didn't you dodge it?!
I'm not paid to dodge.
You looked just like
a wild beast.
With eyes like that lion's.
Oops, I guess I insulted him.
You'd look better out there
if you smiled a bit.
You're good looking, and
I'm not just saying that!
Uh-oh, I forgot the most
important thing!
Trowa! I'm sorry I hit you.
I told you, it's my job.
Trowa! How about that smile?!
Look! It's Relena!
She must be feeling better.
But it's a shame her dress
wasn't ready for the party.
I can imagine it.
I can picture her dress.
Heero, I know too much.
You still gonna kill me?
Yeah.
Before, I didn't want to die
without any answers.
But now it's different.
Now I know how you
feel when you fight.
And now I'm fighting with you.
With me?
What's that?!
That's an OZ mobile
suit carrier!
They've discovered this place!
Heero!
Don't stop at anything.
It'll be reported as a terrorist
attack against the Alliance.
I don't feel great about this.
Attacking a defenseless
civil facility.
Then stay behind!
Someone else can lead!
B- But why?!
That attitude risks your
life and the others'!
I can't have that in a leader!
Forgive my insubordination!
I'll carry out the mission!
Very well. Get on with it!
Roger!
We'll descend immediately!
You need to relax, Lady...
Right, let's go!
Roger!
What's that?!
Watch out! It's the enemy!
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Has the war started?!
The colony's attacking!
Run!!
Oh no!
The military's mobile suits!
Why would they be
fighting here?!
Relena!
Leo, Aries, both confirmed
as standard suits.
I'll get them!
Why's the enemy out here?
He's coming!
We're fighting off an
enemy mobile suit!
What kind of suit is it?
I have no idea!
I've never seen it before!
Colonel Treize predicted this.
So it's probably them.
But why did it show up here?
Capture that unconfirmed suit!
Dispatch the remaining
Aries suits!
Just as I thought.
Others are attacking OZ
facilities besides me.
I know one of them's Trowa,
but are there others too?
Other Gundam pilots like me?
Wish I could meet them all.
This is good stuff!
Nothing like a good drink
after work!
You got that right!
Hey Duo! Duo!!
What's up Duo?
What's up?
Just thinking how beautiful
the moon looks from Earth.
You bet; it's a beauty.
From the colony the moon
is just too close.
It's just like a graveyard.
Yeah? A graveyard?
Wonder how long I'll be able
to see the moon like this.
I doubt if that guy even
looks at the moon.
He should enjoy life, rather
than trying to outsmart me.
While he's alive, that is.
I know what you're saying,
but it's not that simple.
It's just human nature.
What's that guy doing?
He's unreal!
His suit is more agile
than ours could ever be!
It's a flight model! Ascend!
You're too heavy!
It's okay!
Stop crying and run!
O-Okay!
It'll be all right! Just hurry!
We will!
Relena...
Heero?
What am I thinking?!
I'd be better off if she died!
Why's he stopped?!
What?!
The Gundam's protecting
Darlian's daughter?!
Yes! No mistake about it.
It's the girl we're after;
Relena Darlian!
What's she got to do
with the Gundam's pilot?
Heero... is that you?
Why?
Why can't I...
Why can't I?!
All our suits are destroyed!
What?! Then I'll go!
Colonel Treize is on the line!
What?!
Lady Une.
Cancel the mission.
Return at once.
But Colonel Treize!
I've decided to let Darlian's
daughter live.
Why?! The mission was to...
Lady...
We were met by an
unexpected enemy.
Don't think of it as a failure.
Come back.
Right. I understand.
Thank you very much,
Colonel Treize.
I'm sure Lieutenant Zechs
will be pleased.
Zechs has always gone out
of his way to help me.
Saving Relena is the least I can
do to thank him for his efforts.
Give Lieutenant Zechs
my regards.
Yes, sir!
So the rumors were true.
Zechs still has a living
blood relative.
He could've said something.
I see.
You'd rather live here?
Heero, that's you, right?!
Answer me! Heero!
Why did you rescue me?!
Yeah-why did I save her?
She knows too much!
Weren't you gonna kill me?!
Answer me, Heero!
Heero...
How come I can't kill her?!
Heero!!
Don't run away.
Please, Heero.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Leaders of the Alliance
Military gather...
...at the New Edwards Base to
discuss armament reduction...
...and Treize Khushrenada,
OZ's leader...
...skillfully lays a trap to
attract the Gundam pilots.
The Alliance Military is
destroyed by the Gundams.
Treize's trap opens the gates
to a new era of bloodshed.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 7,
Scenario for Bloodshed
"Scenario for Bloodshed".