I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
What do we do now? We can't go
up any higher. Do you have a plan?
I'm thinking about it.
Is that so?
Ouch!
This is where the real fight begins!
She's headed your way!
Did you get her?
I dunno.
Be careful.
Yeah.
Got you! Yes I did!
Oh! I thought I'd be able
to take your head off.
That voice tells me it's
the nun that got caught.
It's your turn, Sawyer!
Damn it!
Shit!
Revy, the knife-wielder's
just a distraction.
The real attacker is her.
Hurry and get her.
Of course. Helping you won't
earn me a single penny.
- Bye.
- Shit.
- Get through this.
- Yeah.
Feint operation is a success.
Miss hostage nun.
Hey, listen up, slut!
Throw away your gun and come out!
You'll go to hell if you let a
nun die! That's not a good thing!
Revy! Don't worry
about me and shoot her!
Nice acting, nun. The slut's not inside.
- Now...
- Hey, hey, hey!
Wait! Wait! Give me a sec.
Listen to what I hafta say.
I'm not stupid. I'm not
letting you buy time.
I thought you'd go to hell for killing a nun.
I'm an atheist. Your religion
has nothing to do with me.
Goodbye, nun!
You fool. The hell express is here
for you a lot faster than you think.
Look behind you!
She's here! She's here! She's here!
Do something about her!
Wait, hold on.
This is no time to panic.
No time to panic? Are you stupid?!
Then what else do you suggest we do?
But a pitfall? That's just stupid!
Don't call it stupid! The wood below the
roof between us is conveniently rotten.
Now I got you.
We're almost in port. We'll be
close enough to see them soon.
So? Can you see anything?
Not yet. Just the Buddha by the
inlet and the city's lights.
Why, that's... Damn it!
Aw, shit! Fucking wonderful!
What's wrong, Dutch?
Is Roanapur under nuclear attack?
That would be a lot
better than this. Damn it!
Then I wouldn't be the
only one who's at a loss.
Some idiot's started a huge
ass bonfire at my dock!
It hurts, damn it!
Eda, you stupid bitch! I can't believe you
gave away that I was sneaking up on her.
- Sorry.
- I've been skewered!
- You whore.
If I hadn't distracted her, I wouldn't
have been able to drill bullets in her.
But that's not important right now.
What's going on above?
The ladder's no good. That ghost
woman cut it down. Damn, this hurts!
What's going on? Who told you to
start a Valencian fire festival?
Torch! My orders were to capture Jane,
not to burn anything!
They're on the roof.
The fire's so fierce, I can't get up there.
Now come on. Come right this way.
Straight over here.
She seems to be in a really
good mood for some reason.
Usually I just dismember
and my job's over.
Jobs like this are nice,
every once in a while.
I won't kill you today.
What are you gonna do?
She started talking!
But, I might help myself...
...to a couple of your hands and feet.
I'm a cleaner.
Always cleaning up after people.
But today is different. Today, I'm
stepping over everyone to reach higher.
I'm playing the position of the Forward.
Now, shall we begin?
- Take responsibility for this.
- How?
It's all right. I had my throat slit...
...but I'm still alive.
What now?!
The fire got to the high-octane
gasoline in the dock! Damn it!
She's still smiling!
She's gonna start talking all
creepy again and cut me up!
- Do something!
- Don't be ridiculous!
What?
What is it?
What's going on? Explain this!
How should I know! I have no
idea what's going on either.
Oh no!
Rock! Are you all right? What
happened to that ghost woman?
Ah, well... She's here.
I'm having trouble comprehending
the situation. What did you do?
Nothing really comes to mind.
It's true. She dropped her voice machine
and suddenly started acting like that.
She's one of those.
I bet she's got emotional issues.
I've seen people like this before.
- This is a problem.
- Hey. Ghost woman.
Idiot. This is what you get for
doing stuff you're not used to.
Revy. You're hurt.
I'm all right. It's not
as deep as it looks.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! Isn't
this building collapsing?
The dock's breaking up in the fire!
- Can you see Revy and the others?
- I can't confirm it.
But if we do something, she'll work in
sync. She has a knack for doing that.
Benny! Rush in and pull a 180
just before we get to the pier!
All right! I'm pretty good at docking.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- What's going on?!
I am here to take your life! I have
my reasons for joining this hunt!
My name is Wizard!
Lotton the Wizard! While I
have no grudge against you...
Damn it. It's been completely destroyed.
Damn it.
It's our boat!
About time.
Good. It's coming in. Get to the pier!
There they are! It's them! After them!
Stop!
Touchdown, Dutch!
Go, Benny!
Roger!
Wait!
Damn it! A few got onto the boat!
Rock! Get that girl inside!
Over here!
Oh, you're alive too.
You're extremely lucky.
- Were you watching?
- Yeah. Well, mostly.
Did I look good?
You looked no better
than the king of idiots.
I suggest you stop making
entrances like that.
Are you all right?
Do I look like I'm in shape
to do the Lion Dance to you?
Next time, you should
wear a bulletproof vest.
It's assuring to have, just in case.
A real weapon is one of offense.
Either way, there won't be
a next time with this wound.
I'll take you to a doctor.
I can't allow a girl to
die right in front of me.
You're not cut out to be
killing in a city like this.
You'd make a great host at a bordello.
I am much too clumsy for that.
If she's alive, let's take her with us.
She's lucky too.
Lobos! Where's that shit-head Lobos?!
You called?
Where's Russell?! Why
hasn't he come back yet?!
You can't ask for the impossible.
Naturally, he's having trouble.
Damn you!
How do you explain the mud pasted all
over my face in front of Don Geralamo?
I understand how you feel, but...
You bastard!
If you've got a head capable
of understanding anything...
...start requesting soldiers
from our homeland!
But that'll start a war with the
Russians and Chinese in this city.
Fine by me! Take me
to a phone right now!
- I'm making an international call!
- Please give me a moment.
There's a door here. I'm going down.
You guys get rid of their gunmen.
Roger.
Damn it. I'm going back to the controls.
We're shorthanded here, Dutch!
I'll take them on a rodeo. Even Tuff
Hedeman would be scared of this bull.
Sounds like fun, Dutch. Let me
know when you're about to go wild.
- Oww.
- Are you all right? Sorry for rushing you.
Yeah, thanks to you, I fell in face-first.
I let Dutch take over the driving.
Is this our guest?
Welcome aboard the Lagoon.
Just call me Benny.
Janet Bhai. Call me Jane.
We've actually got some
uninvited guests on board.
So relax in my room. We're
downsizing our defense line.
Oh, and please don't
touch the hardware.
Not a single thing.
We're about to start the
rough stock. You ready?
Wait. Eda. Hang onto this.
- What are you up to?
- All right, make this bull dance!
What do you think, Eda?! You happy?!
What the hell?!
Die!
I have a question. Is this
boat always driven like this?
Only today, just by chance.
For a second, I thought your real
job was to kill customers this way.
Bastard! Don't get so excited, you punk!
That was careless of you,
Revy. You're outta bullets?
- I'll earn my wings when I get rid of you.
- Revy. Use this.
How did you like that rodeo?
Great. It was a lot of fun.
You've gotta be kidding me. I never
wanna go through that again. Revy?
I'll take care of this one.
We've got one more that
snuck into the engine room.
Eda. Take care of that one.
Sure thing, partner.
What is this place?
Jane! Where are you?!
How long before we reach
the port we're headed to?
I'd say roughly eight hours.
All right. That's plenty of time. Mr.
Japanese, get my laptop from my bag.
I don't have any bag.
You don't? Why not? Are you
stupid?! What do you mean by that?!
How should I know?
If it was so important, why didn't
you take care of it yourself?!
You don't get it!
Get what?!
Don't get rough.
You'll damage the electronics.
I can't do anything without my things!
If I don't have my laptop computer,
if I can't access the web...
Computer?
Jane! Where are you?! Hey!
Come out! Shit! Shit! Shit!
There's no path from here to
the front. How dare it mock me.
I'll show you, stupid engine! When this is
over, I'll drink until I get sick of it!
I'll run all over Rawhide and I'll fuck
expensive women until my balls hurt!
You're really excited about this.
Way to go cowboy. You're a true stud.
But before you do that, why don't
you give God a call and ask...
...if you should be worried about your
balls being blown to heaven first.
Dutch. He's blocking my field
of vision with his fire.
That's a pain.
I need another bull ride.
Can you do it? That guy's
pretty quick for a fatso.
I'll signal you once
I lure him to his grave.
All right. That should be easy
enough. What are your chances?
It depends on your timing. Here I go!
Don't get in my way, you damned nun!
I'm sick of dealing with you guys!
Like I care, country bumpkin!
Then get off this boat!
- I can't do that!
- Shut up!
The plates are mine, shithead!
You don't have the plates?
The plates are in the ocean of the web.
All that was left was for us to
collect all the engineering data...
...scattered around the
world and create them.
But because the data manager
died, I can't get to it.
The encryption is automatically
changed every day. I give up.
We've already been paid by the
Ripoff Church, so we're fine, but...
The problem is Eda.
The moment she finds
out that you don't have the plates...
...she'll find a new way to crucify you
that would impress even Jesus Christ.
That's a joke, right?
Roanapur is the kind of place where all
jokes of a violent nature come true.
- Right.
- Then...
...will you let me use your
machines, just for a short time?!
I refuse.
Why not?! Stingy, stingy, stingy!
I won't lend them to you
no matter what you say.
I'd rather drink a pint of castor
oil than let anyone use my machines.
But as long as I'm using them,
that's a different story.
I'm a little interested in
what tricks your operator used.
Don't disappoint me.
If it's something a junior high
school student could've come up with...
...I'll charge you a fee for my time.
Oh my. I get a kick outta playing
chase with a young lady like you.
But frankly, my body just can't keep up.
How about you give up and be burned?
It'll only take an instant. My
wife didn't even take five minutes.
I'll be content as long as I can smell
the scent of your skin charring.
The weather is perfect, young lady.
It's a perfect day for a barbecue party.
Dutch! Ride!
You're a rocket man, baby!
I understand. This boat
really is out to kill me.
- No, it's just by chance. By chance.
- Is that so.
Well, at least let me see
the data before I die.
It's not an IFSR or an exchange code.
My gut tells me it's a GOST type.
We could also cause a buffer
overflow, and take control quickly.
But using force isn't very elegant.
Who cares about elegance?
Don't rush it. I'm running six
paths in parallel against the GOST.
If one of the indicators on the screen is
a hit, it'll start downloading, any moment.
Sounds like my partner just
took care of the fatso.
You're the only one left, cowboy.
If you resist, I'll blow your head
off and toss you in the ocean.
I got it. I got it. Damn it.
This isn't even funny.
How can I possibly go back to the boss?
There's no need to do that.
Lobos will take care of him.
He knows very well how
things work in Roanapur.
That Lobos guy? Finish Mr. Elvis?
Like he could do that...
What?
Wait a second. I've seen
you before. In Florida?
No, I know. It was Dirty City,
Washington D.C. I'm sure of it!
Is that so? I don't know you. I was
born in Alabama. I've never been to D.C.
Then I'll rephrase that and say
a woman who looked just like you.
You've been wearing those
sunglasses and that outfit...
...so I didn't realize it until now.
Damn, when was it? It was when
Don Geralamo was in D.C., so...
It was him. That man!
Hey.
You'd better stop there, cowboy.
You've got the wrong person, anyway.
I remember! That stupid
senator, Jack Bonham!
Tally ho! It was a GOST!
Your operator was skilled,
but he wasn't thorough enough.
I'm as great as Kevin
Mitnick. Yeah! I'm amazing!
There. I won the bet. What's my prize?
You know, you're so cute and sexy.
That woman was wearing
a navy blue suit, right?
She was having a dinner meeting with
the senator and several other men.
At a French restaurant
called the Fontainebleau.
That's right! The Fontainebleau!
But why were you with a senator?
At that time, she and her
superiors were talking about...
...contact with foreign countries
within the EAEC that opposed NAFTA...
...and how to deal with them.
You wouldn't be...
You're mistaken.
She's someone else. I'm just a
damned nun from the Ripoff Church.
But I'll tell you one thing that's true.
I wasn't born in Alabama.
My hometown is Langley, Virginia.
You're CIA?!
Hey, it sure took you long enough.
Yeah.
Did you send him off to hell?
We're almost in port. Let's take it easy.
Sure thing. God's in heaven
and all's well in the world.
Next Episode
Okay. I won't be too long.
After that I'm leaving, Partner.