Asia!
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
I'm Gonna Defeat My Ex-Girlfriend!
Episode 5
I have been craving this power for many years!
With this power I can conquer love!
Absolute power!
I can now become the supreme fallen angel!
I can now pay back those who insulted me!
Don't give me that crap!
You devil!
We will destroy you!
Fuck off! I don't have time to deal with you!
Damn you!
Kiba? Koneko-chan?
Thanks, guys!
Asia!
Asia.
This is your reward for getting this far.
Asia!
Asia, are you all right?
Issei-san?
I'm here for you.
Hang in there.
Yes.
You can have her.
Stop messing with me!
Give back her Sacred Gear!
Don't be ridiculous.
I even lied to my superiors to carry out this plan.
And unfortunately, you guys are witnesses to that.
But dying together with her is not so bad, is it?
Hyoudou-kun!
We're at a disadvantage here!
You were my first girlfriend...
Yeah... I was amazed you were so innocent!
It was fun teasing a guy
who's inexperienced with girls.
I was going to cherish our relationship!
You became so caring when I looked even slightly troubled.
But that was all only pretense!
To see your silly face when confused
and at your wits' end!
Yuuma-chan, I really loved you,
and I carefully planned out our first date.
I was determined to make it a fantastic one.
Oh, yeah.
Nothing could've gone wrong with that date.
But that also made it freaking boring.
Yuuma-chan!
Not bad!
But we'll see how long that fragile barrier can last.
The magical barrier only made things worse for you.
Or were we supposed to let the others go because of it?
No, no. We won't let you escape.
Your servants should be in for a beating by now, too.
Especially the perverted kid that fell in love with Reynalle-neesama!
I'm sure he's long been—
Don't underestimate Issei.
He is my strongest pawn, after all.
"Yuuma."
I chose that name because
I was going to kill you at dusk.
That's pretty cool, right?
But, you survived and made this blonde your girlfriend immediately afterwards.
That's really mean, Issei-kun!
Did you take her on a boring as hell date too?
Oh, it might have been interesting for a country bumpkin like her.
I don't know, maybe she was like:
"I've never had so much fun in my life!"
Reynalle!
Don't just say my name so casually, you brat!
You're defiling it!
She's the one acting like a devil!
Kiba?
Koneko-chan?
Hyoudou-kun, run!
Koneko-chan and I will hold them back!
Go!
We'll handle this!
Hurry up and run.
But...!
Just go, Hyoudou-kun!
Kiba, Koneko-chan, start calling me "Issei" once you're back!
Promise me!
Got it? We're a team!
"Pawn"?
Oh, right, you depict your servants as chess pieces.
Pawns are the ones lining up on the front, aren't they?
So, they're basically sacrificial lambs.
Oh my, our club president
would never sacrifice any pieces!
Asia, hang in there!
You'll be free once we get out of here!
We can have fun together, always!
It wasn't for long,
but I'm so happy I was able to make a friend.
What are you saying?
There are so many more places I want to show you!
Karaoke bars, amusement parks, bowling alleys...
We'll also get more Racchu-kuns!
And that's not all.
You know, things like... Yeah!
Right, I should introduce you to my friends as well.
Matsuda and Motohama.
They're a bit perverted, but they're really nice guys.
I'm sure they'll be your friends, Asia!
And we'll have a huge party!
A ridiculously huge one!
If I had been born here
and had gone to school with you,
it would've been so wonderful...
Let's go.
No, you are coming.
I'll take you.
You're crying for me.
I couldn't ask for more...
Thank you.
Asia?
Why?
Why did you have to die?
You were a kind girl who'd cure
anyone who was injured, even devils!
Hey, God, I know you're there!
Don't take her!
Please, I beg you!
She didn't do anything!
She just wanted some friends!
Won't you listen because I'm a devil?!
Does her life mean nothing
because she became friends with a devil?!
Please, God!
A devil, repenting in a church?
That's one nasty joke.
Reynalle!
You seem to be thinking that kid's so capable,
but he doesn't stand a chance against
Reynalle-sama, no matter how good he is.
She's his ex-girlfriend, after all!
Reynalle-sama told us about what she did to him.
It was hilarious!
Don't go there, Mitelt.
Just thinking about it makes me laugh out loud!
Well, I have to admit it was really funny!
President!
It bounced off of her?!
You made fun of...
You made fun of my servant.
Oh my,
you shouldn't have made her upset,
you silly angels.
Look, the knight boy did this to me on the way here.
Where are Kiba and Koneko-chan?
Isn't this wonderful?
It can heal everything.
It's a wonderful ability for us fallen angels
since we no longer have divine protection.
This firmly secures my status as a fallen angel.
I can assist the great
Azazel-sama and Shemhaza-sama!
Like I'd care.
She never discriminated
between fallen angels and devils!
This is the destiny of the chosen ones:
those endowed with a Sacred Gear.
That's no destiny!
She could've lived a peaceful life!
No, she couldn't.
What?!
Sacred Gears are too much for a human to handle.
No matter how wonderful they are,
unusual powers are bound to be
feared and their wielders shunned.
I was branded a heretic because
I had the power to even heal devils.
I don't have any friends, you see.
That's simply the way it is.
That's just how humans are.
Even with such a wonderful power!
But I...
I'm Asia's friend!
I tried to protect her as a friend!
But she died!
That girl's dead!
What you tried is irrelevant.
You failed to protect her back then and now as well!
I know!
That's why I can't forgive
either of us.
I can't forgive any of it!
Use your brain.
Sacred Gear is activated by its owner's will.
Give her back.
The greater your willpower, the more...
Give Asia back!
...powerful it will become.
Dragon Boost!
Like I said,
twice nothing is still nothing.
Boost!
You may have gotten a little stronger.
Light is deadly poison to devils!
Just coming into direct contact with it burns them!
It causes devils sharp, excruciating pain,
especially if they're low-class devils like you.
So what?
Compared to Asia's suffering, this is...
nothing at all!
Boost!
That's quite impressive.
You did well for a low-class devil.
I commend you.
My power...
But that's your limit.
A typical low-class devil would've died long ago.
You're a tough guy.
Lord...
I guess that won't work.
Since I'm a devil, it'd have to be the Satans.
I'm sure there's one.
I'm a devil,
so can you grant me a favor?
What are you babbling about?
Did the pain make you insane?
Please.
I don't need anything else.
Impossible! You've got to be kidding me!
So give me the power
to punch this bitch!
You shouldn't be able to stand.
The light must be burning your
entire body from the inside out.
A low-class devil without the ability to alleviate light
should be unable to take it.
Yeah, it hurts.
It really hurts.
I feel like I'll lose consciousness any second.
But...
I'm so pissed off at you that
it doesn't matter in the slightest!
Explosion!
A mid-class shockwave?
No, even stronger?
N-No way!
That Sacred Gear is just a Twice Critical. How?!
It's impossible!
You're not going anywhere, bitch!
I'm... I'm the supreme...
Die, damned angel!
Serves you right.
I didn't expect you to defeat a fallen angel on your own.
You're late, handsome prince.
The President ordered me to not get in your way.
She did?
I did.
I knew you could defeat her.
President!
I was done with my business,
so I teleported to the basement here.
Once there, I saw Yuuto and Koneko
fighting a whole bunch of priests.
We wouldn't have made it without her.
Damn, I shouldn't have worried about you.
President, I brought her.
Nice to meet you, fallen angel Reynalle.
My name is Rias Gremory,
heiress apparent of the Gremory family.
So, you're the girl from the Gremory family!
Nice to meet you,
though it won't be for long.
Also...
I blasted away your friends.
The three who came visiting.
Blasted away?
The President is known as
"Crimson-Haired Ruin Princess",
or "Princess of Destruction".
Destruction?
I never knew I was serving such a master.
Oh my, you made such a mess.
Gremory girl, how dare you...
When Donnasiege attacked Issei,
I figured there were fallen angels in this town, and I knew you were scheming something.
We wouldn't have interfered if
you hadn't caused us trouble, but...
President, was this for me then?
Issei, that Sacred Gear!
I don't know when, but its shape changed.
A red dragon...
Oh, I get it now.
Fallen angel Reynalle,
this kid's, Hyoudou Issei's,
Sacred Gear is not a mere Twice Critical.
What?
Known to double its holder's power every ten seconds;
allowing any who possess it to surpass
even a Satan or God in power temporarily...
It is one of the thirteen Longinus:
the Gauntlet of the Emperor of Red Dragon, Boosted Gear.
A kid like him has the ominous Sacred Gear known to bring ruin even to God?!
It may be potent, but it takes time
to power up, so it's not almighty.
You only won because your enemy let her guard down.
Begone, fallen angel.
Issei-kun!
Help me!
I said mean things, but I had no choice! It was my duty as a fallen angel!
Yuuma-chan?
Look, I still have this! It's proof of what I said!
You remember this, right?
You bought it for me.
Why do you still have that?
I just couldn't throw it away,
because I...
This is bad, Koneko-chan!
Save me, Issei-kun!
You are so...
President, please.
Don't try to seduce my adorable servant.
Get out of my sight.
U-Um, would you mind going out with me?
Please go out with me!
Let's return this to her.
Yes...
President, I'm sorry.
After talking big,
even with help from all of you,
I couldn't save Asia.
It's okay.
You just lacked experience as a devil.
No one will blame you.
But... But I...
It's unheard of, but it's worth trying.
What do you think this is?
A chess piece?
A bishop, to be exact.
Akeno-san?
A bishop's task is to support
other devils in the household.
Her healing abilities would
make her a capable bishop.
President, do you mean...
I will try resurrecting this nun as a devil.
I, Rias Gremory, hereby order you:
Heed me, Asia Argento.
Bring your soul back to this world,
and become my servant devil.
You shall become my bishop
and rejoice in your newfound life!
President, how's Asia?
Quiet!
Asia?
Huh?
President?
I only resurrected her because
I wanted her ability to heal even us devils.
You'll be taking care of her
as her senior devil.
Issei-san?
U-Um, I...
Let's go back, Asia.
Hey! It's morning! Wake up now!
Watch where your hand—
Good morning!
Oh, you managed to come.
How are your wounds?
Well, completely cured
thanks to Asia's healing ability.
She's already doing her job as a bishop, eh?
No wonder the fallen angels wanted it.
Um, President...
What is it?
There's an Evil Piece for
each chessmen on the board, right?
Yes.
Then will there be seven more pawns like me?
But having more rivals would be a little...
Oh, I'm joking!
It was just a joke!
You're my only pawn, Issei.
That's...
When a human is resurrected as a devil,
the number of Evil Pieces consumed
depends on the abilities of the human.
Consumed?
The only pieces I had left were a knight, a rook, a bishop,
and eight pawns.
I had to use all of my eight pawns,
so you could be ressurected as a devil.
You used all eight just for me?
I decided to make you my servant once I saw that.
Humans with that much potential are very rare.
I bet on that potential.
It was because you have Boosted Gear,
one of the thirteen Longinus.
Boosted Gear, the Gauntlet of the Emperor of Red Dragon.
Crimson-Haired Ruin Princess and
Gauntlet of the Emperor of Red Dragon...
Both are red, so it's a perfect match.
Indeed.
Aim to be the mightiest pawn.
You should be able to be it.
You're my adorable servant, after all.
The mightiest pawn...
It has such a nice ring to it!
I'm now one step closer to my dream—
It's a good luck charm. Grow strong!
The status quo is boring,
saenai desho konnanja
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
watashi kimi no haato wo shidou shichau yo
President, I'll do my best!
I shouldn't cuddle you like this anymore.
I don't want the newcomer to grow jealous.
J-Jealous?
I-Issei-san?
A-Asia?
Well, since Rias-san...
How amazing is the real you?
dore dake sugoi no honto no tokoro wa
I mean, President Rias is beautiful,
s-so it's no wonder you're attracted to her.
Naked soul, wake up.
You might not look all that appealing,
imaichipoin dakedo damasarete agenai
No, no! I shouldn't be thinking like that!
God, please forgive my sinful soul—
but you won't fool me!
genzaishinkoukei yaru shika nai desho
Wh-What's the matter?
My head hurts all of a sudden!
Don't you know? Baby
Of course.
I mean, my heart started throbbing
datte ima kyun to shite
You've become a devil.
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
sanbyougo no hoshou wa nai no
Right.
I'm a devil now.
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
yosougai kyacchi shita shigunaru
Do you regret it?
You still don't know anything.
kimi wa nani mo shiranai
No, I'm very grateful!
I'm happy to be close to Issei-san like this,
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
tokimeki eto shinka shite iru no wa
NO-NO-NO top secret
no matter what I am!
and keep it to myself.
naisho naisho desu
No way I can tell you that!
ieru wake ga nai
Wait, those clothes...
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STUDY NOW! renaiteki karikyuramu
Do they look good on me?
Are you transferring to this school?
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuumonhen de tsumazukanaide
My father is involved with the school's management,
It's not something erasers can erase.
keshigomu ja kesenai yo
so it wasn't a problem.
It's written directly on my heart!
mune ni choku de kaichau no
I-I never knew.
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
tenkai wa kibun shidai kakugo shite
Morning, Issei-kun!
Good morning, Issei-senpai.
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
aishou nante shinjinai
It's the real seconds that count!
shunkan ga daiji nanda
Oh my, you're all here.
STUDY X STUDY
We'll be having a party to welcome our newest member!
I want more of it!
motto shitai na
BOY MEETS GIRL
This must be destiny.
kitto unmei
Issei.
Yes?
STUDY X STUDY
You were the best.
Love's unpredictable.
koi wa kimagure
BOY MEETS GIRL
Th-Thank you.
Let's get together
saa goissho ni
and begin!
hajimeyo!
That was a great final episode...
Just kidding.
Next Episode
Do you want to touch my breasts?
Her breasts! Her breasts!
Please... Please make me a magical girl!
Episode 6
I'm A Devil, Hard At Work!
That's a crime, Issei-senpai.