Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
In the year After Colony 175...
...the leader of the colonies
was assassinated.
Five Gundams were sent
to Earth to take revenge.
However, since OZ's activities
in space...
...took the form of cooperation
rather than control...
...the colonies decided
to accept OZ.
The year After Colony 195.
As OZ moves to take over
both Earth and outer space...
...Gundams are labeled rebels
and are isolated from society.
With no place to return...
...the Gundams and
their pilots...
...must fight for a reason to
exist in the changing world.
Stop!
This one's for the peace
of the colony!
I'm fighting for the peace
of the colony as well.
Got him!
We're both fighting for
the colonies!
Then why are we enemies?!
The Gundam They Called Zero
We're 90% finished attaching
the satellite drive mechanism.
How much longer will it take?
Two days should be enough.
I see.
So that would mean a total
of about ten days...
...to move to OZ's power zone.
Contact Colonel Une so I can
give her a progress report.
Sir!
An unidentified shuttle
is headed this way!
A shuttle?
Yes, but it's quite small
for a shuttle.
Its lines?
They're open.
I've tried contacting them,
but they still won't respond!
Get hold of security and have
them guard our defense line.
Sir!
This is OZ Unit 171.
Approaching shuttle,
consider this a warning!
Change your course at once!
If you come any closer,
we'll open fire!
This is not a bluff,
it's a warning!
Go ahead, open fire!
The flying object has
been destroyed.
Mission com...
What...
It's a mobile suit!!
It's transforming!
A Gundam!!!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Enemy mobile suit hit!
It's off balance!
You fool!
If it's really a Gundam...
Then it wouldn't fall
this easily!!
So I'm too lenient am I,
Chief Engineer?
No.
I'm saying it's too risky
to depend on those pilots.
Those associated with
the Gundams...
...are still valuable.
The pilot of Zero One has already
mastered the Mercurius.
Unfortunately, no OZ pilot
has skills exceeding his.
But it's still too risky!
Don't worry.
With the colonies arming
themselves, they're isolated.
They can't make any
careless moves.
Preparations to mass-produce
the Vayeate and Mercurius...
...at the Lunar Base is
under way, as arranged.
They're not needed any longer.
Mr. Tubarov, why do you
dislike them?
Jealous?
That's not something to
be proud of.
Absurd.
Why would I be jealous?
Colonel!
We've received an
urgent message!
A natural resource satellite at
point 07 U 1 has disappeared!
What, an enemy?!
Yes, a new Gundam that
we have no data on!
A Gundam?
The satellite and the troops
and units on it have vanished!
How do you know
a Gundam did it?!
We heard from someone
we think is the enemy pilot.
He said he'd destroy the
civilian colony at point 06E.
He sent us this secret
blueprint.
Probably that of Gundam Zero Four!
Is this a declaration of war?
Okay.
Send the Vayeate and
Mercurius to Colony 06E.
Lady Une.
Let's send out the
Taurus mobile dolls.
We'll keep using them
to guard the Lunar Base.
Send out the Vayeate
and Mercurius!
But...
The firepower of both
the Vayeate and Mercurius...
...surpasses that of the Tauruses.
- Send out the orders.
- Uh, right.
They keep fighting.
The young men responsible
for changing the times.
Something's going on.
They're sure panicking.
An unidentified Gundam...
...has declared its plans
to destroy a colony.
Unidentified?
Yes, it's a new model.
What about its specs
and weapons?
Don't you have any
detailed information?
They know it's associated...
...with the Gundam Zero Four, Sandrock.
Is it Quatre?
Could be.
The other thing is that...
...it has the power to wipe out
a natural resource satellite.
I'll go confirm what they know.
The blueprint you left behind?
I don't know the size of the
resource satellite...
...but such destructive power
points to that blueprint.
Five of us designed the
original Gundam.
Someone has completed it.
I sense something dangerous.
Even a layman knows that
much power's unnecessary.
But the fact that the
pilot's using it...
...proves he's either ignorant
or reckless.
Then he's doing something
even we hesitated to do.
A couple of colonies are
gonna disappear.
Get out, No. 1.
Why him again?
I'm a better pilot than
No. 1!
Let me in on the next battle!
Not in your shape.
Even a Gundam pilot might
get himself killed this time.
Because you're up against
a Gundam.
What?
Apparently it's a new model.
He wiped out a whole OZ
division with just one suit.
What are its specs and
weapons?
No wonder you're a secret agent.
The engineers asked the
same questions.
Okay, let's go.
With the red one, the Mercurius,
this should be quite a fight.
You're coming; like it or not.
So you'll just stand
back and watch...
...as two Gundam pilots fight!
Hey, No. 1!
Don't do it!
It's probably a suit
performance test!
Don't help them out!
You guys keep quiet.
You'll get your turn eventually.
That was no act.
He might have betrayed us.
We don't need to worry
about that.
We can trust him.
How do you know?
Because a traitor wouldn't
bring us a gift like this.
Hey!
Duo Maxwell and
Wu Fei Chang.
Master O gave me this.
Use it to kill time.
What a guy.
See?
What's this?
The carrier for the
Vayeate and Mercurius.
We've got these two.
And Duo and Wu Fei's
Gundams have been upgraded.
I'm sure the pilot of the
new Gundam is Quatre.
The time may have come.
Once we join up with Quatre,
we'll attack OZ!
How do you know
he's our ally?
Assumptions lead to mistakes.
Besides, we're piloting
OZ's mobile suits.
We may be forced to
battle with him.
If he's a strong ally...
...we might have the force
needed to fight OZ.
But if his Gundam is
lacking in power...
...we'll end up destroying it!
It'd be more advantageous
for you...
...to keep hiding within OZ
until you can defeat Treize.
You knew.
Either way, we'll know
after this battle.
You're right.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
We've evacuated the civilians.
The enemy could show up
anywhere!
Be on the lookout!
Section 1: Everything's
under control!
Section 2: Under control!
The outside of the colony is
equipped with beam cannons.
The colony can defend itself
no matter what enemies approach.
Calling Colony 06E3.
I'm about to eliminate
your colony.
No sense retaliating.
Leave the colony at once.
I repeat.
The Gundam is here!
Attack!
Prepare to fire the outer
beam cannons!
Fire!!
You're afraid of dying,
aren't you?
Then you shouldn't be
fighting in the first place!
That's funny.
I have tears in my eyes.
But I'm not sad at all.
You're awake.
Are we there?
That was quick.
Our destination just changed.
We were too late to
save that colony.
Was it him?
Yeah.
He said he'd be destroying
a colony in this area next.
This carrier sticks out.
We'll proceed in the
mobile suits.
Our objective is to find out
how powerful the Gundam is.
We'll fight only if necessary.
Got it?
It's Quatre we're up against.
So we don't need to worry.
Trowa, be cautious.
Something isn't right.
What's the matter?
Remember, he just destroyed
a colony.
We'll lure the enemy in.
Mercurius, move in alone.
Attack the enemy on sight.
Roger.
Officer Trowa.
Aren't you giving that former
Gundam pilot too much freedom?
Don't worry about it.
I've got the switch to his
self-detonation device.
Besides...
...he's completely focused
on the Gundam right now.
He sees it as an enemy.
This is pretty awesome.
I hear it'll be completed
in one month.
Now that Quatre is back,
we're going to be busy again.
I won't consider an
unconfirmed Gundam an ally.
But the Gundam is defeating
OZ's troops.
It's gotta be an ally.
I certainly hope so...
But I've got a bad feeling.
Good job.
Sir!
Is this where the air supply
for the cells is controlled?
Yes, it's controlled here.
Oh?
Mr. Tubarov!
What are you doing?!
Just cutting off the air
supply to the prisons.
I haven't received such orders!
Are these orders from
Colonel Une?!
I'm giving out these orders.
Don't worry.
You're just doing
as ordered, that's all.
That Lady Une's a little
too soft for her own good.
Oh, I must be getting old.
My knees are feeling weak.
You fool, they've cut off
our air.
Shucks, you already noticed.
Then my efforts were wasted.
I didn't want you old men
worrying too much.
We've got thirty minutes
at the most.
I regret that we
couldn't complete...
...our upgrade of the
Deathscythe and Shenlong.
If you wanna die then
hurry up and die.
You're wasting air.
You know they hate
persistent old men.
But you've gotta be persistent
to get anything out of life.
Damn!
What a dinky way
to kill us off!
I wish I could've gone
to battle, instead of Heero.
What are you doing, Wu Fei?
There's no sense studying
that now.
Stay calm if you want
to live a little bit longer.
We're out of luck unless
something drastic happens.
I'm doing everything I can...
...in case "something drastic"
does happen.
Wu Fei!
Sorry, but I'm gonna
throw in the towel.
Oh, this is such a lame
way to die!
This is so "not cool"!
The motion sensor detects
nothing outside.
Do you really think he's here?
Couldn't he have already
gone to a different area?
No...
I'm sure the Gundam's here.
The colony doesn't need
things like these.
It's here!
The Gundam!
It's in the colony!
What the colony really
needs is a war!!
Three suits in the
colony are down!
The Gundam's coming out!
Quatre, go ahead.
Show me what that
Gundam can do!
So this is the new Gundam.
Heero, there's no worry.
This Gundam is unparalleled!
Quatre, this is Trowa.
Do you read me, Quatre?
I read you, Trowa.
Don't come any closer, Trowa.
What did I just say?!
Don't get any closer!!
Quatre.
What's going on?
Trowa.
Outer space has gone mad
so I'll destroy it all.
I must destroy all the weapons
that have accumulated here.
The colonies are becoming
armed, right?
That's why the colonies
must also be destroyed!!
What's the matter, Quatre?
This isn't like you.
Tell the others for me.
Tell them to stay away.
Otherwise...
...I'll kill them.
I'm telling you not
to get any closer!!
Is that all you've got
to say?!
If everything has gone mad...
...then I'll just fight,
believing in myself.
Quatre, I'm gonna kill you.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The mobile doll project
is another step toward...
...the Romefeller Foundation's
conquest.
Treize opposes this...
...and steps down from
his position as OZ leader.
The Gundam pilots cause
a blood bath in space...
...as they continue their
mortal battle.
During the battle, Trowa
is thrown out of his suit...
...and drifts into the
silent depths of space.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 25,
Quatre vs. Heero
"Quatre vs. Heero".