Let's fight one-on-one, Sairaorg!
Any time.
Bastard!
What the hell?!
Now it's my turn.
A-Amazing...
So this is the power of the number one amongst young devils.
I should mention that, even though his opponent Zephyrdor is a substitute, he is not weak.
Substitute?
His family's original successor died in an accident.
A magic circle?
Astaroth.
Huh?!
Good day, everyone. I am Diodora Astaroth.
so
no
mu
If you listen to the voice of your heart
You'll be born anew again and again
born
born
new
mo
u
ko
I can't hide it anymore
The purported salvation is but a mirror paradox
Trying to come to terms with myself
I realized my soul must lie with my wishes
The moment we met, the warmth of the tears
de
ta
shun
shun
ta
kan
shun
Falling off your palm ignited my heart
And we understood the DxD each other felt
I've been waiting
What's there to be gained amid all the despair?
It's not bliss but rather a good feeling
feel
feel
ing
so
no
mu
Until I reach deep inside your heart
I'll call out your name again and again
your
name
your
name
Episode
The Night Before Battle!
Allow me to get straight to the point.
I would like to trade bishops.
No! Does he mean me?!
No, of course not.
You desire to take Asia, I presume?
You are quick on the uptake.
It'll be a reasonable trade.
After all, I am offering—
Sorry. I have no interest in trading.
Asia is a valuable devil in my peerage.
I also think of her as my little sister.
President!
Trying to obtain the woman you proposed to through a trade...
Do you even know how to court someone?
President's about to blow a fuse!
That's understandable. I would, too!
I understand.
I will return for today, but I will not give up.
What?!
Our meeting and our reunion were fate.
Even if everything in this world gets in our way,
I will overcome all of those obstacles.
I love you, Asia.
Huh?!
What are you doing to Asia?!
Do not touch me.
I cannot stand being touched by a filthy dragon such as yourself.
B-Bastard!
Please do not talk about Issei-san that way!
I see. I understand.
Red Dragon Emperor, Hyoudou Issei,
I will defeat you in the next Game.
After that, Asia, I hope you will accept my love.
There's no way I'd lose to you, Diodora Astaroth!
I'll show you the power of the dragon that you called filthy!
Are Issei-san and Koneko-chan still doing their devil work?
Yes. They suddenly got requests.
Being a devil sure is a lot of work.
Even Rias-san?
She is currently planning for the Rating Game in her room.
Asia, don't worry.
Issei will definitely protect you.
Indeed. We have Issei-kun on our side.
Y-Yes! You're right!
Everyone really trusts Issei-kun, huh?
It's no exaggeration to say that we're all here now because of Issei.
Exactly.
I feel bad that we haven't really thanked him for all he's done.
Then, you should thank him now!
Thanks for having us!
Morisawa-san suddenly requested both of us out of the blue.
It was fun doing a devil comedy duo with you, Issei-senpai.
Sorry, Koneko-chan.
I can travel through magic circles now,
but it seems everyone still expects me to show up on a bike.
That's fine. This is fun in its own way.
Issei-senpai!
This presence!
Long time, no see!
Kuroka-neesama!
You're here to take Koneko-chan again?!
Your face has become a lot more valiant since I last saw you.
Is it because you reached Balance Breaker?
Or have you felt the warm embrace of a woman?
What are you saying?!
Huh?
Hmm. You still taste like a child.
Th-That's none of your business!
Hey! Hey, hey! Want to try making children with me?
What?
I want a dragon's child.
Nee-sama, Senpai's... Um, I-I won't let you have it.
You should ask Vali for that kind of thing!
I turned her down.
Vali!
Boost!
Looks like you're itching to fight.
You're the one who unleashed Loki on us!
Loki did that on his own.
We only escorted him to the underworld.
In fact, I think you should be thanking us.
We saved you all from Fenrir.
You bastard, how dare you...
I hear you're participating in a Rating Game.
Your opponent is the heir to the Astaroth family.
Be careful around him.
What?
I'm sure Rias Gremory won't give ear to any advice I give her.
So at the very least, I thought I'd warn you.
My, my. Issei-kun, welcome home!
A-Akeno-san, why are you dressed like that?!
You don't like it?
The opposite! It's the best!
W-Welcome home, Issei-san.
Welcome home, Issei.
Wh-What's going on?
This was my idea.
Issei-kun, they all wanted to thank you.
You did this?
I didn't think they'd go to this extreme, though.
Should it just be a show?
Or should we make it a touching event?
A touching event!
It's transparent!
I can see straight through it all!
Boobs!
I knew you'd enjoy this.
Everyone, what's going on?
Oh, Rias.
We're all trying to make Issei-kun happy right now.
P-President?
Is she mad that she was left out?
I'll go check up on her.
P-President!
Look, Issei. Doesn't this look good on me?
Yes. Very much so!
Issei, I'm well aware of your tastes.
My, my. You haven't won, yet!
What?!
Issei-kun, don't you love clothes that show a lot of skin the most?
Then, point with your finger upward.
L-Like this?
Th-This is...
Amazing!
S-So soft!
Huh? Huh?!
Yes!
Just as I thought, my breasts become so hot when Issei touches me!
I won't lose to you!
Neither will I!
My figure suits Issei-kun's tastes much better than yours.
No! Issei finds my type much more attractive!
That's not true! Rias, you idiot!
Akeno, you half-wit!
Rias, you dunce!
They started to fight.
Akeno, you moron!
Nobody can stop a fight between those two.
Rias, you—
Issei-senpai.
Do I look good in this?
This... really packs a punch!
Seriously, I can't believe Akeno.
Um, I guess it was my fault.
It's fine. It was a good way to relieve stress.
Vali's more important right now!
Unbelievable! How dare he fool around in my territory!
But he didn't look like he came to stir up trouble.
Just in case, I'll report this to my brother and Azazel.
I don't plan on taking Vali's words at face value,
but Diodora's carefree attitude certainly bothers me.
It doesn't matter how strong he is!
If it's for Asia, I'll definitely—
President?
Do you still blame yourself for dragging Asia into this world?
Yes, but Asia told me that she's happy with this life.
And that should be all there is to it.
But... even so, I...
With you, me, and everyone else in my peerage, we can be sure to make her happy.
But you and the others have to find happiness, too.
President!
Otherwise, I'll end up being sad.
Oh, that's right!
I got a request for you from an underworld TV show to make a guest appearance.
Guest appearance?
Why me?
Dunno.
It'll probably be after the Rating Game,
so focus on winning first.
I will, President!
I was hoping to eliminate both
Sirzechs and Odin by using Loki.
But it appears that a heathen god can only get so far.
Then again, he is one of the main Norse gods.
I find it hard to believe he was sealed away without much resistance.
Oh, Issei?
I noticed the lights were on.
The Game is fast approaching.
Weren't you training pretty hard even before the sun went down?
Well, I'm even weaker than Kiba.
I hate to admit it, but Kiba has
a lot more innate talent than me.
In my eyes, you and Kiba are both amazing.
Thanks.
All right!
Ascalon!
Blade!
Huh?!
Use it.
But...
It may not be as strong as Durandal,
but it's better than a wooden sword, right?
Are you okay with this?
Yeah!
If you need it, ask me any time.
We're all comrades here.
Comrades...
Hey.
You're eventually going to leave the president and go out on your own, right?
In order to rise to the top.
Huh? Yeah, someday.
I want President to see me as a man and her equal.
Asia said that she would follow you when that happens.
Yeah. We promised each other we'd always be together.
Take me with you as well.
You, too?
You're entertaining to be around, Issei.
Entertaining, huh?
All right! I'll think about it.
I feel like talking to you calmed my nerves.
Huh?
I was thanking you. Would you have preferred your lips?
No, that's fine!
Your point definitely got through!
Is that so?
All right, good night!
That really surprised me.
Oh, Issei-san!
Asia, Koneko-chan!
We were waiting for you in bed.
I was talking to Xenovia.
She's working really hard.
Issei-san, if we lose the Game, will I...
That guy can say whatever he wants.
We won't hand you over to anyone, Asia-senpai.
Koneko-chan.
Asia, don't worry about losing.
We're definitely going to win.
That's right!
Let's win the Rating Game
and the three-legged race at the sports festival while we're at it!
Okay!
Sorry for not speaking to you in person, Sirzechs.
Regarding the accidental death of the heir to the Glasya-Labolas family
and Diodora Astaroth's sudden increase in demonic power...
So they are related?
Most likely.
Then it seems that Rias' report on Vali's warning
should not be taken lightly.
It's not like they're a hivemind where everyone thinks alike.
It seems we'll have to put your plan in motion.
Michael and old man Odin have agreed as well.
Though I do feel bad doing this to those kids.
Take care.
Try your best.
Well, then. We should head out, too.
Michael-sama ordered me to go with you to the underworld, but...
Why are we keeping it a secret from the others?
If nothing happens, we can just say
it's a surprise visit to cheer them on.
If something does happen...
Well, I'll have to take the blame.
Are we there?
Is this the main battle area?
How strange.
There's no announcement from the referee.
Wh-What if there was a problem?
A magic circle?!
That's not the crest of Astaroth.
Be careful!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
If I remember correctly, this crest...
They are devils loyal to the
Old Satan Faction in the Khaos Brigade.
So they're terrorists?
The despicable fake Satan family, Gremory.
We shall eliminate you here.
What the hell is going on?!
Asia!
Diodora!
You bastard!
Hi, there. I'll be taking Asia Argento.
What are you doing to Asia?!
What is the meaning of this?!
You are all going to be murdered here by the Khaos Brigade.
As I feared, you've sided with the Khaos Brigade!
You're the worst kind of person!
And you defiled the sanctity of the Rating Game!
You deserve nothing less than death!
Most of all, you dared to touch my cute Asia!
Well, enjoy your final struggle against your innumerable opponents.
I will be united with Asia at that temple in the meantime.
Do you understand what I mean, Red Dragon Emperor?
Issei! Pass me Ascalon!
Yeah!
Ascalon!
Asia is my friend! I won't let you have your way with her!
You coward!
Asia!
Dammit!
I'll protect Asia?! Again, I—
I've—
Issei-kun!
Focus on the enemies surrounding us first!
We'll go save Asia after that!
Yeah. That's right.
You're right!
We're vastly outnumbered.
I'm not sure if Akeno and I can shield against their attacks completely.
Hmm. What a nice ass.
This youthful resilience is irresistible.
Old Man?!
Odin-sama?! When did you get here?!
We discovered that Diodora Astaroth was making backroom deals with these malcontents.
Come now!
I am the Great Father of the Norse!
If you take my head, you will become infamous!
That brat Azazel wanted to take care of them all in one fell swoop.
Then, this Game was...
We were used as bait.
Hurry up and go.
This old geezer will hold the front lines for you.
You should count yourselves lucky.
But we can't let you fight all alo—
A baby who's barely lived more than a decade
is a thousand years too young to worry about me!
Gungnir!
A-Amazing!
Odin-sama. We shall take you up on your offer.
No worries. Even an old man like me needs to get some exercise once in a while.
Let's run to the temple!
Yes, President!
You all right?
Azazel-sensei!
I'm sure there are plenty of things you want to tell me, but listen for now!
It's not just the field. The area around the VIP room
is also under attack from the Old Satan faction.
Of course, we planned for this.
Planned, huh?
Various units we've placed in the area are fighting back.
Due to the battle plan, I couldn't compromise the mission by giving you intel.
Wh-What if something had happened to us?!
I'm the strategist of this battle.
I'd take responsibility.
Well, my head alone might not be enough to make up for it.
Then...
...you were prepared to die...
...when you used us.
Anyway, stay hidden until the battle ends.
We'll take care of the terrorists.
Sensei, you're in the battlefield, too?
I'm on the same field as you.
But the area is huge, so I'm pretty far away from you guys.
We can't hide!
Asia... Asia was kidnapped by Diodora!
What did you say?!
We have to go save Asia right now!
Sensei, Asia is my comrade!
She's my family!
I... I never want to lose her ever again!
We will go and save Asia.
I have to teach him how foolish it is to steal someone from my peerage!
Well, I expected as much.
I'll take care of the rest!
Go rampage your hearts out!
Sensei!
Thank you, Azazel-sensei.
Listen, Issei!
Show that betraying brat the power of the Red Dragon Emperor!
Make sure to bring Asia back!
You got it!
sou daitai no koto nante
Well, yeah, I do think that
mou wakatte wa iru na tte
I've got this stuff mostly figured out
omou yo dakedo ne
But still, you know
kokoro wa bannou ja nai
Feelings on their own can only get you so far
daiji na koto bakka ishin fudenshin
The stuff that matter isn't getting across
saishuuteki ni wa analog tsuushin
So we have to rely on analog communication
dakara ima sugu
That's why, right now
motto chanto katachi ni shite yo
I want you to be more concrete
kimi ga
Do it
ijiwaru na voice
With your flirty voice
give me kikasete yo
Give me, just tell me
chotto dake de ii no
Just a little hint is fine
aimai na no wa yada na
Don't leave me hanging
no secret sansei
No secrets, yeah?
do you do you know
Do you know?
answer todokete ne
Give me your answer
kowaku nante nai shi
I'm not afraid to hear it
ienai kedo nee wakaru desho
I don't have to actually tell you, right?
wakatte yo
Take the hint
tell me heart tell me heart
Tell me your heart
subete wo kaeru no wa
If you want to take it to the next step
give me word give me word
Give me your word
itsu de mo kimi dakara
The power is in your hands
Next Episode:
I gobbled both of them up!
All of you, stop this now!
How dare you ignore me and fight over a man!
One who attacks first, wins.
Worldly desires, release! Max imagery!
Episode
We will Save Asia!
I can't believe you!
Success!