I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
It should be daybreak there soon.
The sea at daybreak.
Only worthless students find
that sort of thing appealing.
But, I do agree that this
winter sky is disgusting.
Right now, Okajima is
in the Sea of Heaven.
Would you prepare two plane tickets?
S-Sure. A business trip, sir?
Let us go there as well,
to the Sea of Heaven.
Damn it! Why the hell
should I suffer like this?!
Rock! You bastard! How much
do you think a gun costs?!
They came here to kill me.
Why do I have to go through this...
...for something the Department
Manager's involved in?
I think you're missing something.
They wanna destroy that data
disk, right? You're life is just...
M y life is just an accessory? Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
You realize there's a torpedo in there.
Shut up! Shut up!!
Don't you find something
odd about this, Benny?
Yeah, something's not right, Dutch.
They've totally stopped firing at us.
They could've easily turned
us into Swiss cheese.
I agree. Something's not right.
Dutch! What's going on?
Where'd those guys go?
Benny-boy.
Yeah.
They've retreated to a distance
of about 5,000 meters behind...
...and have been following us
while keeping that distance.
What are they after?
Yeah, there's gotta
be a reason.
Damn it.
It's this waterway.
That's it! The waterway!
The path ahead to Belawan is
filled with rocks and mangroves.
As we proceed, the waterway
will continue to narrow.
In the end we won't be able to
make any evasive maneuvers.
- There's no shame in running.
- I agree.
Don't tell me I suck at this.
Well, guess I can't blame
you if you did tell me so.
I wouldn't say such a thing.
I had no choice but to
evade to the right.
I know that.
Did we just enter the mouth of
a river? This is a river, right?
If we continue, we'll eventually
run out of options to escape.
We already know that.
We've become completely trapped.
The enemy's behind us again.
He's looking down on us from
behind, 5,000 meters from us.
Look at that. A sunken ship.
What a bad omen.
This is fine. This'll be our spot.
Go on, go on. Go on and
keep showing me your ass.
But you know, you guys
will come back to me.
And then you'll hafta
face me. Hurry on back!
And let's put an end to this.
Dutch, they've stopped by the sunken
ship. They're not chasing us anymore.
It's no longer necessary for them
to waste their energy chasing us.
That's what that means.
Damn it!
A dead end?
Looks that way.
Damn it!
Hey, Meyer.
Sir?
I get so excited just imagining how
they'll react in a crisis like this!
They have no chance of beating us.
We'll honeycomb the ship
with our superior weaponry.
That's exactly why I can't
wait to see how they'll react.
If they're the boring type
who won't try to fight back...
...then we'll just torture them to death.
There's no road ahead of us.
We'll have to turn around and go back.
But, he'll be waiting for us.
M y gut tells me they have
purposely set up this ring.
They wanna finish this face to face.
So, who's going to ring the bell?
Sometimes you'll find them around.
So-called ancient bastards
who think they're gunmen.
Wait a second! So the
only choice is to die?!
Well calm down, calm down, Rock.
Let's call the local police!
That's better than getting...
You're not helping one
bit. Calm down, will you?
Panicking isn't gonna solve anything.
If you wanna survive, use your head.
Dutch. How about waiting
for them to run outta fuel?
The bastards are from E.O. They'll come
to finish us off before that happens.
Damn!
Why did this have to happen?
Not this one.
I'd like a business paper. I want
to check on the stock prices.
Right away, Mr. Kageyama.
How bad is the damage to the ship?
Not too bad, so far. I'm more
worried about that thing.
If even a single bullet hits the torpedo,
we'll end up flying to the moon.
It's your own fault for keeping
that thing on the ship, you dumbass.
I thought I might have been
able to use it for something.
It's a waste, but maybe we
should throw it overboard.
Guess we have no choice.
What a waste.
Wait. Dutch. Listen to me.
You go back to sleep.
I understand something, now that
I've had time to think. Hear me out.
If you disturb my thought process
I'll let Revy nail you this time.
Let's have a shoot out, face to face.
Are you an idiot?
How can we have a shoot out?
At most we have an anti-tank rifle.
They've got rocket missiles!
It looked like the chopper
had infra-red homing missiles.
We don't even come close.
You think so? We
do have something.
Revy. What did you give
him to drink?
I did nothing.
To put it simply, it's a
head on chicken race, right?
This ship's speed and
armaments, that sunken ship...
...we have everything we need.
What...
...do you have in mind?
What you guys were just talking about.
Let's give them
a flight to the moon.
Impossible. There's no
way we can pull that off.
In theory, this ship is designed
to hydroplane...
At full speed we're only
in the water this much.
Dutch. It's not as if we've
got an alternate plan. I'm in.
The plan won't work unless
they're right in front of us.
Can we count on that happening, Rock?
They're having a blast
chasing us around.
Despite having a complete advantage.
So what's the reason for them
to restart the whole fight?
You said it yourself.
He's the type who imagines
himself to be a gunman.
If we lure him into a chicken race,
he'll be more than happy to do it.
I can't guarantee you anything. From
this point on, it's up to you as Captain.
This guy we picked up is completely
out of his mind. He's gotta be insane.
But this is exciting.
And being excited is an important
thing, Rock. Let's do it!
The radar's picked up something,
Captain. They're on the move.
Let's accept their challenge.
Rock! You know what
needs to be done, right?!
If they launch a rocket, I fire the
signal flare away from the ship.
That's correct!
I can see the idiot. Revy! It's a
chicken race! Send them an invitation!
They're firing at us!
Of course they are!
Great! I accept the challenge!
Rock! They're coming! Fire
the infrared flare gun!
It worked!
We're on the alpine course.
Both of you, get back into the cabin!
They plan to use the
sunken ship as a shield?
Well, that's useless. Hey Meyer!
Yes, sir!
When we cross paths we'll
get them with a single shot.
We're gonna put an end to this duel!
Get ready to get fucked, baby!
300 more feet.
150 more.
One hundred!
Fire number one! Fire number two!
You got fucked!
My head's still attached.
My sunglasses aren't broken.
Amen, hallelujah, peanut butter.
Fucking Christ has saved us this
time. But I'll never do that again.
Benny, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm alive, somehow. But
all our machinery is smashed up.
We need to fix it up. We're...
Hey! How about Rock?!
He's right over there, passed out.
He yelled out as we hit.
Like one of William Holden's
lines from The Wild Bunch.
Look at him. He looks so
comfortable passed out like that.
Yeah, no kidding.
When that moment passed...
...all the excitement the body's
adrenaline causes...
...disappeared somewhere.
And my boiling blood returned to normal.
Where am I, and what am I doing here?
Good job.
I love smart work, Dutch.
But I've gotta tell you,
you guys look terrible.
We're not going to a formal party.
We'll dress however we want.
Now, Mr. Kageyama. We, from Hotel
Moscow, have a code of honor.
Oh? I thought you were from the
Bougainvillea Trade Company.
We followed through in our own way.
There shouldn't be any grudges.
The world is full of things
that cannot be helped.
Now it's your turn to follow
through in your own way.
We'll go over details at the hotel.
Very well.
Thanks for the good work,
Okajima. Now, let's go.
Okajima. What are you
waiting for? Come on.
Boss. Don't you remember?
You know, I'm already dead.
You told me so.
My name is...My name is Rock.
Is that so? Then do as you wish.
Let's get going, Fujiwara.
Y-Yes sir.
Rock.
Sorry for making you
talk with those idiots.
But I'd consider it a great waste for
a tough guy like you stay a Japonski.
Come to us anytime if
you ever need help.
Goodbye.
Okajima...
He's no longer an employee.
Those eyes weren't the eyes of someone
who could take on a managerial role.
But, how'd things end up like
this in such a short time?
I don't really care.
So, Rock. What will you do now?
I'm no longer a hostage.
And I've got nowhere to go.
Hey. I know a place that
could use a sailor.
Would you be interested?
It's a delivery company...
At times they may take part
in illegal activity. Right?
What's wrong?
There's a boat that's blocking our way.
We've been blowing our
horn but it won't move.
What is that?
Well, the amount of information
that did get out was inevitable.
But we were prepared for that much.
That was a job well done, Kageyama.
Thank you very much.
Ah, testing, testing...testing...um...
Good morning, everybody
aboard the St. Joan. Ah...
Why won't you wear that aloha
shirt I got for you at the market?
Because we're working right now.
That's right. This is my job now.
Everybody aboard the St. Joan, I
apologize for the sudden request...
...but I ask you to please stop your ship.
My personal opinion is that...
...complying with the request as
quickly as possible would be...um...
...the best course of action!
Dutch. The St. Joan has
opened up its communications.
We've finally made contact.
And what did they say?
Ah, "Unless you get out of our way,
we will force our way through".
Guess it can't be helped.
Okay, Benny. Revy.
That was an awfully long wait.
Time's up for being gentlemen.
Okay!
Everyone, please take cover!
These moments make my
prehistoric blood awaken.
What in the world?!
They have a rocket launcher!
Hand that over!
Wait!
Listen carefully, you dimwits!
My rockets are faster than mayday calls!
If you don't want to end up
as a ghost ship full of blood...
...then stop the ship, you bastards!
Benny-boy.
Give notice to the guys at Lyun E.
Pan that we've taken the St. Joan...
...and that they'd better come get
it before anyone starts a ruckus.
Roger.
I'm home.
Hey, John. Good boy.
Takanori. How are things?
Your studies for your entrance exams.
Not too good.
Oh, you're home today.
About your daughter. She's been
getting home late recently.
She's only eighteen. Could
you please talk to her?
That's your responsibility.
Stocks.
Hey, Daddy?
What color was the sea of that
southern country...
...you went to on your business trip?
Color of the sea? I can't really
say. Daddy's been busy with work.
Maybe no one will believe me...
...but I've become a pirate
of the South Seas.
That huge ship was today's prey.
Okay, let's get back to port before lunch.
The China bowl at Kao Han...
...sure sells out quickly.
Next Episode
We're being targeted by pirates?!
Dutch! What's the background
on our client?