I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Once a businessman in Tokyo...
...I now work for a shipping
company in the South China Sea.
With that one, we're done transferring
the crates. Would you please sign this?
Um, could somebody please sign this?
There's nothing special about it.
We're just a mediocre shipping company.
At times, we even brush up against
the law to put food on the table.
So everything's okay, Rock?
All okay, and I even got them to sign.
We should also have cargo from them
for us to take back. Did you get it?
About that...
Well yeah, I did get it.
Is there a problem?
If not, ask them to use the crane again
and get down here with the shipment.
Roger.
So the troublemaker is being useful.
Well, I'd like to say that,
but nothing's changed.
It's just that his white collar look
was perfect for this job.
Yeah, so far.
Is he worried about the cargo
we're taking back?
Looks that way.
He's helpless. It's just some cheap job
from the Manisarera cartel.
I counted the crates we delivered
like you wanted me to...
...and I brought the shipment
we're taking back, too.
But are you sure he's it?
Once we arrive at Hat Yai, we hand
him over to a buyer carrier...
...designated by the Colombian Mafioso.
Revy, put him in a cabin for now.
Right.
Now, come here.
Don't you fight back. This way.
Hey. Come on. Get in this hole.
He looked like he was gonna puke.
He's still not a pro.
Rock.
We're a shipping company.
We take shipments to their
designated destinations.
That's where our responsibilities end.
Understand?
I understand.
I won't get too attached to the boy.
Good boy.
Bring it on!
- Rock.
- Want to see what you had for breakfast?!
Sorry, but would you trade
babysitting duties with Revy?
- Her professionalism is a problem.
- Get over here! You!
We can't deliver
a shipment full of holes.
- Taking advantage of my kindness!
- Hey, Revy!
- What are you looking at?!
- That's enough!
He doesn't need something
as good as a cabin.
We ought to chain him up and throw
him in storage. That brat.
We're in the middle of the sea.
He can't escape. We don't need chains.
Shut up!
Well, you know, it'll only be for a little
while, but we'll be traveling together.
You can at least stop throwing
food at me.
That friendly talk will rot your mouth.
Saint Maria can see through it, villain.
Well, I'm aware that my words
may not be appropriate...
...since I'm helping these guys out.
You're different from the tattooed
woman or the big black man.
You seem like a normal person.
It must seem like it.
I'm just a villain in training.
The people who put me on the boat
didn't tell me anything.
I'm gonna be sold off
somewhere, aren't I?
Are you worried?
I'll be fine. I know my father will save me.
Father? But aren't you an orphan?
Who told you that? The cartel?
They're big liars.
My father is a member of one of
the great thirteen families...
...of South America.
He's Diego Jose San Fernando Lovelace,
the eleventh head of the household.
I'm Garcia Lovelace, his only son
and the next head of the family.
If you're looking for pity,
you won't find it here.
If you're gonna lie you should
come up with a better one.
Pity? Don't be stupid. What could
I gain from lying now?
You're a pretty unlikable kid.
Where did you hear
the name Lovelace, anyway?
It's the lowest noble house
of the thirteen families.
Though that makes it a little
more believable.
Well, things haven't been going well
lately. But we've been getting by.
My father is kind of old fashioned.
He never got involved
in unnecessary side businesses.
Our business wasn't going well,
but the plantations were stable.
- Until the mafia came, that is.
- And that's who kidnapped you.
You have a gift for making up stories.
They came to buy our land by force.
A geological test showed that
lanthanides could be found there.
When my father refused,
they showed their true nature.
They began harassing our farms.
But father still wouldn't nod his head.
That's why I'm here.
Lanthanides?
It's also called rare earth.
Don't you know your periodic table?
Well... Where did you learn
a word like that?
You still don't believe me.
That's fine then.
Well, it's not that easy.
What can I do to make you believe me?
What else do you know about
rare earth... lanthanides?
Lutetium, atomic number 71,
was found on our land.
It's used as a fixing agent for
ceramics. How's that?
No good, huh?
Then the next question.
The Lovelace household has a dog.
About that dog. What do you know?
That's easy. That dog became a member
of our family six years ago.
His name is Lazlo, a Volpino Italiano
with a white coat.
Revy. Rock is taking too long.
He's probably getting himself
emotionally worked up.
He'll probably give us a sad story
and ask us to let him go.
What did I tell you?
With eyes just like that.
That's odd. I don't like how this feels.
Even after we dock, I think we should
wait before handing him to the mafia.
The cartel was lying.
If they're lying, there must be trouble.
Rock.
You can't have pity for our cargo.
You'll become depressed...
...if you try to imagine where people
who are sold will end up.
But as long as there's a profit for
our company, there's no problem.
Understand? There's no problem
from that point on.
The world will keep turning
even if there is no justice.
I'd be lying if I said I didn't pity him.
But I'm also concerned
that our client lied.
I used to be in the resource procurement
department of my company.
I know a lot about rare earth
and rare metals.
And he's correct in what he says
about the Lovelace family.
I remember seeing reports from
our South American division.
Family structure and whatnot.
Impressive. That's impressive, Rock.
You're a very brilliant businessman.
I'll have to get you some of Mama's
homemade cherry pie as a reward.
Either way, it's up to Dutch.
I'll go with what he says.
I just don't get it. The moment
they had the kid...
...they could've demanded a ransom
and accomplished their goal.
Is there any reason for them to keep it
a secret and sell him off?
I don't know why they'd
keep it a secret.
But selling him off has a simple and
clear logic. They were pissed off.
There's nothing mafias
and cartels hate worse...
...than having shit rubbed
in their faces. Right?
Hey Revy...
...if their face is what's at stake
then this is gonna be a hassle.
I'm gonna put a little insurance on
our shipment before we deliver it.
I'll ask Balalaika to check
behind the scenes.
Oh, my. It's rare to have you
asking a favor, Dutch.
I need details about the relationship
between the Manisarera cartel...
...and the Lovelace family.
Can you prepare that for us?
Oh?
We actually just received a job
concerning Manisarera.
Your timing's great, Dutch.
Thanks. I owe you one.
But since we're still just
setting up insurance...
...can I ask that
you don't stir things up?
Well, that's impossible.
What?
In our business, if things get stirred,
they get stirred up like a typhoon.
Just do your best, do it cool.
Very well. Shall I get back
to you at your office?
No. We'll be waiting at the Yellow Flag
having a drink.
All right then, Rock. There's one more
thing we need to check out.
About the Lovelace father.
Is he really the type to use mercenaries
to rescue hostages, like the kid implied?
I can't imagine so.
Financially speaking, they can barely
afford to keep one servant.
A servant? What kind?
An ordinary house maid.
Think the maid's gonna rush in to save
the little prince? That would be fun.
What did you just say?
I am just a lonely soul who has come
all the way from South America.
I am in search of a place where I can
find my fellow countrymen.
By fellow countrymen, you mean
from your country?
Yes, of course.
This little lady's countrymen?
Hey, could she mean...
But there are no other "countrymen"
of her's in this area.
We really can't tell you ourselves.
Then who may I ask that could tell me?
Miss. There is a place where you
might be able to find out.
But that place is like a den of gangsters.
Please do not worry. So long as I can
find out about my countrymen there.
I really wouldn't recommend
that place, Miss.
Please do not worry.
We're here. We're on land.
Would you get moving?!
That's not the disposition of an adult.
You used to be a brat too, remember.
Then pay me for my work as a babysitter.
This isn't even funny.
Revy.
Hurry up!
Hey, that's enough.
What? You too?
You gonna treat him nice and get a job
at his house? Guess that makes sense.
You'd be better off as
a white-faced butler than a sailor.
Yeah, yeah. Whatever you say.
Asking, "Master, would you like
some Mint Julep?"
Just like Old Black Joe, must be nice
to be surrounded by dozens of servants.
Like I told you before,
we only have one servant.
A maid named Roberta.
And even though she's a maid,
she's no good at cleaning or chores.
We don't serve milk here.
Then may I have a glass of water?
I only arrived here today and
I do not know my way around.
I am in search of a Colombian friend...
This is a bar. Order a real drink.
You dumbass.
I only arrived here today and
I do not know my way around.
I am in search of
a Colombian friend of mine.
Might you know where the
proper authorities are?
Lady, does this look like the tourist
or employment agency to you?
No.
She's really clumsy. She can't clean
or do chores, but...
Roberta is much stronger than you!
Of all the damned things to say!
She's not gonna throw
a teacup at me, is she?
If what you say is true...
...I'd even believe it if you said Jesus
tore across Route 66 on a chopper!
Have you seen her when she was strong?
I haven't. But I remember one thing.
We lived at my father's house.
The three of us, my father,
Roberta and I, lived peacefully.
I didn't have many friends to play with,
so Roberta would play with me.
I especially loved
to arm wrestle with her.
Because I could beat Roberta every time.
Roberta lost every single time.
She was arm wrestling me
on that day, too, when...
...they came.
To threaten my father.
She knew what was going on
long before I did.
The moment she sensed that they
were coming, she stiffened.
I tried to beat her with
my usual strength, but...
Her arm was like steel.
Roberta always lost to me on purpose.
I realized then, that she had a reason...
...to always act like a weak maid.
Fallen nobility. The wife
died four years ago.
The ones pictured are the head,
Diego, his only son, Garcia...
...and their only servant, the house maid.
I don't like this. This isn't good.
Yes?
Comrade Sergeant. Take a look
at her eyes. Don't you notice anything?
The eyes of a soldier.
That is correct, Sergeant.
And that's not all. She's one
hell of a rabid dog.
Woman. I've got business with you.
I heard a woman in a strange
maid's outfit...
...is looking for the Colombian mafia.
In a crazy outfit that you'd only see
in Hollywood movies.
Any idiot would remember someone
in clothes like that.
You called us here. What are you after?
Who the hell are you?!
It was my intention to have you find me.
You are from the
Manisarera cartel, correct?
I am a servant of the Lovelace family.
I have a few things I would like to ask.
I hope you'll excuse me, but I am afraid
I may have to be rude.
Did you hear that?
"Be rude", she says. This bitch!
- She makes me laugh!
- What are you gonna do?!
I am afraid I will not be able to hold back.
Please pardon me.
Well then, enjoy yourselves.
Roberta!
Next Episode
Impossible!
I believe it.
That's a killer robot from the future!