Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
The attacks by the Gundams
sent by the Space Colonies...
...reflected the colonies'
retaliatory intentions.
OZ has masked its identity
in the Alliance Military...
...and the Gundams' mission
is to attack them.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite soldiers
at his command...
...Treize Khushrenada plans to
destroy the Alliance Military.
The battle between OZ and the
mobile suits sent to Earth...
...causes serious repercussions
on the Earth.
Don't you think your life's
too valuable for that?!
Self-detonate?
What are you thinking?!
What would your parents think...
I said this before.
The way to live a good life
is to act on your emotions.
The Order to Destroy 01
Take better care.
Yeah.
Of your body, I mean.
Here...
That's Sylvia Noventa.
She's in Marseilles.
Sure you wanna start there?
Yeah.
Looks like we'll make it.
What's the matter?
The display of Leos, huh.
They've been the main force
of the Alliance and OZ.
Why was Romefeller so
set on using mobile suits?
Because people tend
to fear large machinery.
But at the same time they
have a strong admiration for it.
Mobile suits walk upright, too.
The Foundation must've preferred
a human looking battle...
...rather than one played out
with buttons and switches.
There's no difference when
it comes to killing men.
If there were, it'd be as a game
that toyed with people's lives.
In war, a frenzied death is
the most honest way.
Only a few know that the
chaos caused by OZ...
...is according to the
Romefeller Foundation's plans.
An assembly of the Romefeller
Foundation and invited guests...
...was being held on the
outskirts of Bremen.
The Romefeller Foundation was
formed from European royalty.
With their enormous financial
power and connections...
...the aristocrats poured their
energy into weapons development.
They provided mobile suits
to the Alliance...
...and became powerful enough to
pull off the latest coup d'etat.
What's wrong?
You'll have to forgive me.
I can't blame you, considering
what I did last time.
Beyond that door are people...
...responsible for the death of
your father and Sanc Kingdom.
But today you mustn't
do anything...
I understand.
I promise to act appropriately
for a sovereign...
...of the peace-oriented
Sanc Kingdom.
In the past, the United Earth
Sphere Alliance...
...requested considerable funds
and assistance for world peace.
We didn't hesitate to cooperate
with them for world peace.
But the Alliance started seeking
peace through dialogue alone.
Earth has too many disputes that
dialogue alone can't settle.
Isn't a system of control what
humanity truly needs?
That's precisely how control
will be exercised now.
This is how peace
can be maintained.
The Alliance lacked the
necessary talent.
Many responsibilities are
required to rule.
But they attempted to run away
from those responsibilities.
We have the traditions
needed to rule an era.
The world was corrupted...
...with imperfect ideas
like equality and freedom.
The time's arrived where we
must once again take control.
I can't believe OZ's using these
methods to take over the world.
The Romefeller Foundation
kept such ideas to itself...
...while hiding its presence and
agendas within the Alliance.
OZ took advantage
of the situation...
...saying they'd achieve world
peace, if the Alliance couldn't.
So the war will continue, then?
OZ must keep winning in
order to continue ruling.
The rewards of victory and
OZ's success go hand in hand.
OZ's dissolution of former
policies...
...was a revolution against the
system's misrule and poverty.
The nations in the
Romefeller Foundation...
...will want to take part only
in wars they're certain to win.
So OZ needs the strongest mobile
suit troops in order to exist.
But the Gundams can defeat OZ.
OZ sees the Gundams
as a serious menace.
By threatening to directly
attack the colonies...
...OZ completely silenced
the Gundams.
The Romefeller Foundation is
trying to destroy the Gundams...
...as soon as they're able.
They'll sacrifice lives
in order to gain rule.
But Heero sacrificed
his own life to save others.
They'd never understand.
I'd like to introduce you to
the conqueror of the Alliance.
This gentleman is a brave
knight fighting for us...
...in his endless quest
to attain world peace.
A member of Romefeller
and OZ's chief commander!
Treize Khushrenada!
Some think OZ's military power
and mobile suit forces...
...may result in excess rule.
"Rule" is commonly associated
with oppression and arrogance.
I think it's a way to keep
ambitions under control.
God let humanity run free.
So what humanity needs is
a system over and above God's.
God couldn't have predicted this
world with never-ending wars.
I'm sure God would understand
the steps we're taking.
Let's leave.
There's no point staying.
These people see wars through
rose-colored glasses.
Nothing we say will change that.
Relena? Relena?
You're all very mistaken.
And the Gundams will come
to rectify your mistakes.
On behalf of those who're
trampled by this whitewash!
Relena, stop this!
No, I'm not finished yet!
I'm begging you Relena.
Talking to them is useless!
Thank you, Lieutenant
Lucrezia Noin.
My apologies, Your Excellency.
Excuse us.
Forgive me; she's the younger
sister of a friend I invited.
What on earth was she
trying to get at?
She must've sensed our
anxiety toward the Gundams.
She's saying "be confident".
Speaking of the Gundams, I want
a word about Zechs Merquise.
I know his skills, but you're
giving him too much freedom.
Meaning exactly?
I hear he's rebuilding the
self-detonated Gundam...
...in Lake Victoria.
It's insane to be fixing
the mobile suit...
...that we considered a menace!
That Gundam should be destroyed
as a warning to the colonies!
I understand what you're saying.
If the Foundation decides to...
...I'll tell Colonel Zechs
to destroy the Gundam at once.
I'm surprised that rumors about
the Gundams were so widespread.
It shows the significance of the
damage they've rendered to OZ.
His Excellency didn't seem
to agree, though...
Can't help it, if they're
orders from above.
Will you follow orders
and destroy the Gundam?
How's Relena?
She's a ball of energy.
It's hard to escort her.
How much does she know?
It seems that Mr. Darlian,
her foster father...
...told her a lot before
he passed away.
I told her you're a respectable
and trustworthy soldier...
...who was brought up
in Sanc Kingdom.
I also said you alone were there
when Gundam Zero One self-detonated.
And that you're reconstructing
the Gundam.
Which makes Relena believe
that the Gundam pilot...
...Heero Yuy, must've
somehow lived.
Heero Yuy... so that's
the pilot's name.
Relena has some connection
with him, much like yourself.
I understand.
Thanks for the update, Noin.
Wouldn't you tell
her about yourself?
Over and out.
How could I do that?!
I'm Zechs Merquise,
from the organization...
...responsible for this
blood bath.
I could set fire to this castle
and burn it down right now.
But God would never forgive
me if I did such a thing.
Perhaps I'll be punished
for my profanity toward God.
Then an appropriate
punishment must be planned.
God's merely an imaginary
figure created by humans.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Marshal Noventa of the United Earth
Sphere Alliance...
...objected to armament
expansion, to deter rebels.
He passed a request for arms
reduction and disarmament...
...to the Earth's nations
and the colonies.
But his untimely death
put an end to it.
OZ chose that day as
the dawn of a new era...
...and tricked the Gundams into
shooting down Noventa's shuttle.
But I won't let it obstruct
our peace proposal.
M-Marshal!!
Don't be rash now, young man!
As a result of this tragedy...
...the road to peace may
have been lost forever.
Sylvia.
You must escape at once!
I appreciate your concern,
Captain.
Many soldiers from the United
Earth Sphere Alliance...
...are still here in Marseilles.
OZ will probably carry out
plans to attack us.
I thought the city
could be protected...
...because the Alliance
has a base here.
But now the base poses the
greatest threat toward the city.
It'll be a battleground.
Yes, I know.
But leaving my memories
of life with my grandfather...
...has taken longer
than I thought.
Marshal Noventa was
a fine person.
He always thought about how
to help achieve world peace.
Grandfather's no longer here,
but his heart still remains.
I'll live my life remembering
that he's here in our hearts.
Sylvia...
I'm sorry.
Captain, we're under attack!
Is it OZ?
Yes! Ten Aries suits!
They think they can capture this
place with 10 mobile suits?!
Captain!
Don't worry, we won't
give up that easily.
Get yourself to a safe place.
Keep the Aries from residential
areas, and commence attack!
Leos, return fire!
It's like a guerrilla attack!
We'll destroy all those Leos!
After them!
What've I done?!
What?!
The Alliance's Leos are retreating
to the underground channels!
Probably they're the main forces.
All Aries, assemble at once!
The underground channels.
Pretty obvious decision.
Don't worry about me.
I'd get in your way
with this arm.
We can't let OZ find out
we've got a Gundam in town.
There's just a few of us left!
Are we doomed?
Hurry to point 211
of the channels!
Yes, sir!
Sylvia Noventa!
Who're you?
Aries suits have entered
the channels!
No choice but to surrender.
Commander!
What's this?
It's a Gundam.
What's it doing here?
The Aries are only a block away!
We'll stop retreating and
fire as they come!
Commander?!
Probably can't buy much time...
...but we'll resist until
the pilot returns.
We'll manage.
Are we protecting the Gundam?
Yeah; it'll be our backup!
Continue fire!
Don't ease up!
He's here.
The rest is up to you, Gundam.
All Leos in the channels
are destroyed!
We're heading out!
It's a Gundam!
Why's it here?!
I'll get rid of you before
the others catch on.
I won't get involved in a battle
between OZ and the Alliance.
But I can't afford to have
anyone see the Gundam!
Five Aries suits destroyed!
Is this a miracle?
Who could this unidentified
mobile suit be?
Whoever it is, I'm
extremely grateful!
Heero?
You said your name
was Heero Yuy?
Heero Yuy, huh.
This is my grandfather's grave.
You wanted to talk to me?
I was the one who killed
Marshal Noventa.
Huh?!
I made a mistake.
I accidentally shot down
Marshal Noventa's shuttle.
Killing him and other people
who'd advocated peace.
How could you?!
How?!
This is the only thing I can
do for you right now.
Sylvia Noventa...
I can't undo my mistake.
I hope the anger felt by
the Marshal's loved ones...
...and the regrets of
the Marshal's soul...
...can be somewhat eased
if you pull that trigger.
You're such a coward!
You obviously just wanna
take the easy way out of this!
This is the only answer
I can offer you now.
You coward!
Understand that I didn't
come here to make you suffer.
I'm going to pay a visit
to your grandmother.
I heard she's in Sicily.
Yes.
This is where it starts.
He goes to every family member,
seeking their verdict.
Everything he does is thorough
and well thought out.
Everything Heero Yuy does.
Wars are nothing but
repulsive killings!
How can you be so
clear-cut about it all?!
It's the only way I can live.
Do it!
Gundam Zero One has been destroyed
as per orders, Inspector Acht.
I saw the explosion.
But would you object if
I collected the remains?
You're not satisfied with the
documents we submitted?
I'd rather confirm the remains
with my own two eyes.
Since I need to prepare
a document of my own...
...to satisfy the hard-liners
of the Romefeller Foundation.
As you wish.
I don't imagine I'll find
anything out of the ordinary.
Zechs Merquise isn't likely
to be careless with details.
There weren't any Gundam parts
left at the Lake Victoria base.
Zechs is fond of mobile suits.
I can't see him changing his
ways for a request from us.
What will he gain by opposing
the Romefeller Foundation?
I dunno what he's thinking.
But Romefeller's taking
over this era.
To move into the top ranks...
...we just need to prove Zechs
betrayed his official orders.
The Inspector is just trying
to find faults with you...
...so he can score some points
with the Romefeller Foundation.
He won't find anything different
from the documents.
Sorry I had to involve you
in my little performance.
I figured it'd be a real waste
to destroy the Gundam Zero One...
...at this point in the game.
But we've destroyed most of
the Tallgeese's spare parts.
In that case I'll just have
to be more careful with it.
No pilot can harm the
Tallgeese and Colonel Zechs.
Not true. There is at least
one man.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
A war is supposed to
be heartless.
But Heero places his own destiny
in the hands of Mrs. Noventa.
Zechs longs for a decisive
battle as a warrior.
Noin invites Heero to Antarctica
where Zechs awaits.
Inspector Acht pursues them
with his own forces.
The Gundam revival is about
to ignite its own new blaze.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 15,
To the Battleground, Antarctica
"To the Battleground, Antarctica".