I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
The noose hanging at
the entrance of the city...
...warns all who wish to go further...
...that if you pass through this gate...
...you will automatically be
marked as a reckless one.
The worst of the worst villains
from around the world gather here...
...butting heads with each other.
This place was born in
the midst of the Cold War.
It was nurtured by a continent that
uses drugs as its secret weapon.
An evil city
The end of this world.
A crucible of hypocrisy.
The stomping grounds for people...
...whose souls have been
destroyed and sent to hell.
The only reason I'm surviving...
...is because I'm recognized as a member
of the well-known Lagoon Company.
The name of this city is spoken of
amongst the villains of the world.
But many of those who come to
make a name for themselves...
...never set foot on their home soil again.
A cruel fate awaits any
halfhearted, small-time crook...
...stepping foot into Roanapur.
Right now, there is a sacrificial
lamb who has wandered into this city.
Okay guys!
The night's just right to make our way...
...to our clownish one-grand-a-person job.
Let's get going!
Hey. What in the world
are we waiting here for?
By my calculations, a total
of about one million dollars.
As if there really is such a great deal.
It's just another gun fight.
A gunfight's coming.
I'd be grateful for a gunfight. That rotten
nun is just blinded by her own greed.
So who's gonna come? No one's coming.
Don't get all pumped up just
because you're bored, Revy.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Right, handsome boy?
But it's gonna be a gunfight, right?
Come on, Rock, it's not like you're
gonna get holes drilled in your body.
Hey, Eda. Mind if I crack your jaw?
Oh my, jealousy isn't like you.
Well, it's about the right time.
I guess I can tell you what's going down
right now in a certain place in Roanapur.
You bitch!
First of all, that certain
place is the Ramsap Inn.
The place I introduced that girl to.
But you know what? Right about now...
...a bunch of useless thugs
are rushing into the place.
It's going something like this...
But the room they raid will
be the one next to hers.
Why would something
convenient like that happen?
That's because I gave them
the room number next to hers.
That stupid woman will be scared
outta her bed because of the gunfire...
...and run to the hallway
to see what's going on.
Well, she naturally would
in that situation.
That woman's instincts
are devastatingly bad.
Right?
Especially given the fact that her room
is the only one behind a fireproof wall.
The moment she opens the door she'll
be facing off with those bastards.
And the guys probably
wouldn't have guessed...
...that there's a room
behind the fireproof wall.
You've gathered all the "ifs"
in the world for this story.
Come on now. If she gets
killed now, then so be it.
But normally, one would be alert
enough to close that fireproof door.
Although it's not much,
it'll still buy her time.
And when the guys break through
the door and burst into the room...
...it'll be empty.
How come? As if things will fall into
place for you like that, you dumb ass.
I've given her a way out, you see.
If you stretch out on that bed even
once, you should be able to see it.
Although you'll only understand
its meaning when the time comes.
That's way too simple.
That's like graffiti in bathrooms.
Look up. Look down. Jack-ass.
And that's fine.
It's better to keep it simple!
Anyway, after that, she'll be able to
make a touchdown like Brett Favre.
As long as she escapes according
to the route marked by the signs.
How's that sound?
I shouldn't have
come with you.
Oh?
Let's go home, Rock.
Turn the ignition.
Right.
Hold up, Revy. That room's
worked four times outta seven!
- What?!
- See?! See?! What did I tell you?! Bingo!
Rock, after her!
Hey, young lady.
Jogging this late at night?
That's very impressive.
You! You tricked me!
That's not nice. How can you talk
like that to your guardian angel?
What do you expect!
I thought I was gonna die!
Oh, really? Well, whatever.
Do you want us to save you?
Think hard. If you don't wanna hand over
the plates, I guess we have no choice.
I suggest you run to a mosque
next time. What do you think?
You are the worst. Really.
Thirty thousand dollars!
Rock, it's almost my bedtime.
Take me back to the church.
You monster! Ten thousand!
Hand it over at no charge!
Look, they're after you.
Okay fine! I'll accept your conditions!
All right, contract complete.
If you don't actually
save me, I'll haunt you!
Don't worry. If I went on with my evil
ways, I'd only scare away my customers.
Hey, Eda! What are you doing here?!
Hi! What's up? You guys out
for a late night walk too?
We have business with that woman!
A senseless one-grand-a-person job!
That's a nice way to get pocket change.
Isn't it? So how about it, Eda. You want...
You bitch!
What do you mean "bitch", you bastards?
I'm on a big million-dollar job.
From here on in, she's ours.
We're her recently purchased
getaway driver and body guard.
- Revy, eat 'em up!
- Right on!
Bring the cars around!
After them! Get 'em!
- We're coming out to the main road!
- This is our job, Rock! Head for the ocean!
Damn it!
Looks like things are getting complicated.
Complicated is an understatement.
It's the Ripoff Church
and Lagoon's gun-woman.
This isn't the same as going
after a single amateur.
Deer hunting just turned into
tiger hunting.
What are you doing?! Will you
hurry up and go after them?!
Cowboy! The situation's changed.
Unless you pay us 30 grand a head,
we're leaving.
What?! You serious?! I did hear
that two punks are now on her side!
But thirty grand for that?!
You're all unbelievable cowards!
Cowboy, this is no Florida. It's Roanapur.
Understand what I'm telling you?
Our opponents are not
like the punks you know...
...that get off by scribbling
on walls. And neither are we.
We make a living by killing
and offering to kill.
If you wanna continue being cheap,
then go at it alone with your own men!
Understand what I'm telling you?
So you're full of confidence. I pray it's
not just bravado. But wait a second!
The way you're telling me,
it sounds like you know them.
Of course we know them. Anyone who
doesn't know about those two fools...
...can't be from this city.
Get my point, Cowboy?!
You better hurry and call Lobos. Got it?!
Call him and you'll know
exactly what I mean.
Where now? Where are you taking
me now?! Is this another trap?!
- Even if you try to up the price, I...
- I wouldn't do anything so roundabout.
I'll take you right into the getaway pod.
Once you're on, you can say goodbye
to this wonderful Roanapur.
As soon as you can, please.
Eda, you promised me payment up front.
Yeah, I've got it here.
The ocean? A port?
A boat?! Is it fast?
Why don't you ask the
handsome man in the tie?
Eda.
You'll see in a minute.
Get this, it's a torpedo boat...
I hate to say it, Eda,
but you won't see the boat.
Hey, hey! Hey! This isn't at
all how it's supposed to go!
The most important thing isn't here!
Yeah, we're receiving a shipment.
We got a rush job a short while ago.
Want something to drink?
You've only got piss.
I see that you've got Ardbeg
Providence. Gimme that.
Are you nuts? That's Dutch's.
You even lick that once, I'll throw you
around and shove a beer up your ass.
Stingy bitch.
Will Jim Beam do?
We have plenty of this.
If you're gonna be picky then you can
help yourself to toilet water, you idiot.
Revy, is Eda there too?
Yeah, she is. Sorry to interrupt.
That's fine. Now back to where we left off.
So the situation is neither
good nor bad, right?
Okay, we've got all the goods.
Yeah, that's right. We have
Eda and we have weapons.
I've also taken the two
useless ones into account.
All right. Wait a sec. Benny's here.
I suggest we dump what
we just picked up.
That'll get us to the port a little quicker.
I guess we'll have to. We'll also need
to compensate for breaking the deal.
I'll contact Isaac about that from here.
Anything and everything will be
covered by the Ripoff Church.
Oh well, fine. It's not much.
By the way, what's that girl up to?
Her? She's been in the storage
room ever since we got here.
She hasn't come out for about an hour.
Space. Scan with box.
TSIG root-authority.
Auto one. 192, 168. DNS server?
Is this it?
No good. The port shell's being booted.
I feel so foolish not being
able to get into my own bank.
Way to go, Theo. I'm in big trouble,
thanks to your valuable skills.
Sorry Dutch, I'm really sorry.
Yeah, Lobos.
He's from my country but I'm
having trouble with him, too.
They don't realize they're like countrymen
from afar in this lawless world.
I guess not. Roanapur is where the
worst of the worst villains gather.
Hell, even we've been
thoroughly tainted by it.
Those guys need to be refined
by true villainy as well.
So please, give me more time.
All right.
- Benny-boy, did you hear that?
- Yeah, every word.
There are men playing with fire,
unaware of the demonic
energy of this city.
It's dangerous. Anyway, let's hurry.
Of course!
So, everyone is tainted by the
villainy of this city, huh?
I had always thought Rock
and I were exceptions.
What are you saying, Benny?
I've sensed it all along.
Even what's deep down within you guys.
Thanks a lot.
Shit! Damn it! How long will this
take you?! Would you hurry and...
One more try. TSIG, root-authority.
It's from here that...
- You forgot to say, "good evening".
- You idiots.
Damn it! What's up with that?!
- They're using our car as a shield!
- Sorry for your loss.
Damn it! They just finished fixing
it after that damn maid tore it up!
Hey, it's leaking gas!
- Oops, you've done it.
- Rock!
Yeah!
Damn it, more guys?!
Rock! Can you make
it to the back door with that girl?
I'll give it a try! As long
as you hold them there.
Leave it to me!
All right, let's go!
- Wait!
- Come on!
That's pretty manly of him!
He's still got a ways to go.
This way!
- We can't go this way! Revy!
- What's wrong, Rock?!
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and shoot her!
I can't! I don't have a gun!
Are you stupid or something?!
I was thinking the same thing.
Rock!
- Rock! Damn it.
- Hey, Revy!
Rock! Damn it. Are you all right, Rock?!
Don't have an answer for you.
No! Come back! That door
leads down to the dock!
You've gotta be kidding! If I stay up
here, it wouldn't matter how many lives...
Hi. I've got one favor to ask.
Will you let me get past you?
Do you like grill parties, young lady?
Rock!
Rock, get away from her!
Shoot! Shoot 'em all!
Revy! The guys across the street
are being a nuisance!
Can't you do anything?!
Hey! Girl! Give that box to her!
What's this?
If you've got something this nice,
bring it out to begin with, you monkey.
- It was for sale!
- Doesn't matter! We've only got one life!
Damn.
Now, hurry!
Revy, you too!
Go ahead, Rock!
Shit. If we stick our heads out,
we'll be targets at a firing range.
It's the same with the front door.
There are two or three snipers
positioned out there.
Oh? Something smells burnt.
Gimme a break. That just isn't fair.
Some idiot set fire to the dock exit.
We really have no choice
but to go to the roof.
Bad idea. That'll be our last stop.
I know. But our enemy
shares the same concerns.
Unless they do something,
the moneymaker they're after...
...will perish along with the building.
So what would you do if you were them?
That's obvious. I'd force my way in
and take out the guards, of course.
And the timing?
They'll spray us all
at once any second now.
Once we're pinned to a spot,
they'll rush in to this second floor.
But we're not just gonna sit and wait.
Revy!
Is that you, Shen Hua?!
Oh, good guess!
Who's that? You know her?
Yeah.
She's the worst to face as
part of their shock troops.
"Yes it is" lady! Is your partner here?!
Oh, Leigharch?
He relaxed too much and finally
couldn't make it back home from Mars.
He's living happily with his live-in nurse!
That's a shame!
- Eda. Listen up. Say "Hi" to him for me!
- Okay!
She's using the duct as a foothold.
Yeah, but knowing that
isn't gonna help us much.
That fire down below isn't
a joking matter anymore.
Damn it. It's a matter of time. This
place isn't gonna last much longer.
I hate endurance contests. I'll draw
her out before she draws us out.
I'll chase out that female fox on the
duct to the front. Can you nail her?
Of course, blockhead. If
you just draw her out...
...I can easily do my part.
- Then here I go.
- Got it.
She's headed your way!
What do we do now?
I'm thinking about it.
We can't go up any higher.
Do you have a plan?
- I'm thinking about it.
- So that's your plan?
Oh, how dependable of you. Let's see...
Shall we pray and pray
and pray our hearts out...
...until a golden chain
comes down from above?
Shut up.
I'm thinking about it.
Next Episode
I am here to take your life!
My name is Wizard! Lotton the Wizard!