I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Have you heard this one?
There's this joke I heard.
How many Polaks does it take
to change a light bulb?
One to hold the light bulb,
ninety-nine to turn the house.
L-Let's see...
How about this, The Pope says
to a homeless guy...
"Stay outta my sight, you're
an eyesore." You idiot.
Just shut up and drive, you moron.
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired!
Why am I stuck playing
errand boy with you?
Damn Dutch! I hope he dies!
What? Me?
I have to work on the boat.
Benny's working on the mechanics.
Oh, right. Revy's just lying around
in her room. Take her with you.
Take Revy?
You have a problem with that?
No.
But she's not gonna want to.
That's an issue you two
need to deal with.
It has nothing to do with me, or the job.
Start with the closer places.
First head to Rowan "Jackpot" Pigeon's
place on Rachiada Street.
Welcome Rebecca. I thought
you gave up on me.
So you've finally decided to work here as
a dancer for the S&M show, right?
That's it, isn't it, baby?
Give me a break, Rowan.
I only came here because
my job brought me here.
I don't wanna be tied up
or tie anyone else up.
You're as hard to get as always.
You're so fine you'd fit either part.
It's a shame. So, what brings
you here today?
Um... About the goods from the firm...
You ordered booze for this place, right?
There are 1,500 bottles in warehouse
five of the harbor bureau.
Now, this really helps.
Wow! Tax sure has gone up on these!
I can't stand it.
By the way, who's that guy
standing over there?
Oh, him. He's a newbie at our place.
He's got nowhere else to go, so we had
no choice but to take care of him.
You're in for a rough ride, brother.
If you ever need any help,
feel free to come to us.
Later, Rowan. Don't forget
about the money.
So the shipment's gonna be late?
You could've told me that by phone,
but you came all the way here?
Tell that to Dutch.
That's fine. I've gotta finish
fifteen of these today.
I should've gotten a part-timer to do it.
This is driving me crazy.
I have a meeting tonight, too.
Some idiots are selling drugs without
permission. It's such a nuisance.
Hey sis, is that in her ass?
Yeah, that's in her ass.
Oh. If you hear anything about that,
let me know.
I'll thank you properly if you do.
Yeah, if we hear anything. We'll come
again, sis. Good luck with the rest.
I want to die.
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired!
Why am I stuck playing
errand boy with you?!
W-Well, one more
and we're done. Let's see.
Receive firearms on order from Sister
"PW" Deegan of the Ripoff Church.
Hey, you old bitch!
It's Rebecca from the Lagoon Company!
Would you hurry and open up,
old bitch! Hello?!
Hello! Hello! Hello!
- Hello! Hello! I'll kill you! Hello!
- Hey!
You're too damned loud.
Just put those in the shed.
But these are cleaned items.
It's okay. It's what the sister said.
Hey, Two Hands, that's the chapel.
If trash like you walks through there,
you'll be punished by the heavens.
Over here. Follow me.
Oh my.
It certainly is a surprise...
...that Dutchy-boy would send
you on an errand.
That's not your problem. Do you have
the goods that we ordered, Sister?
Yes. New items from Eastern Europe,
arriving here by way of Cambodia.
Except for one item.
Unfortunately we're still waiting for
the Arwin 37 revolving grenade launcher.
Don't kid around, Sister.
We ordered everything through you
because we need them for the next job.
Actually, we do have the item.
It's just that another customer...
...is saying they need it immediately.
However, as Lagoon is a very good
customer of ours...
...I wouldn't mind handing it over to you.
Anyway, it will either have to be a better
deal or a discount on your services.
Don't trifle with us, Sister.
If you just play this by the book
then everyone will be happy.
You wouldn't wanna count your money
with your feet, would you?
I wouldn't make idle threats, Miss.
If you insist, why don't you bring
Dutchy-boy around?
That's all I have to say.
There's nothing else beyond that.
Move it, Eda, you second-rate gunman.
Want me to teach you how to smoke
through your forehead?
This is very good tea, Sister.
Sister... Um...
It's Yolanda, young man.
It's been a long time since I've had tea
that wasn't from a teabag.
Is this W&M? Or perhaps
Fortnum and Mason?
Oh, my. You're very
knowledgeable, young man.
It's W&M. I just love tea.
Yes. It's a flavor that a company...
...with dedication and history
will deliver without fail.
Rock. Shut up!
That's true with any company even
if the products differ, am I right?
I don't see it. What are
you getting at, young man?
Do you mean it's also true
for illegal firearms?
You won't have much of a negotiation
if you get too hasty.
What if I mean drugs? That's what
I'm talking about, Sister.
Did you know drugs are being distributed
outside the agreed routes lately, Sister?
Hotel Moscow and other
mafia in the city...
...have put a lot of effort
into finding the culprits.
They've looked everywhere
they could think of.
Yet, the culprits
still haven't been found.
That's because there's a blind-spot in a
place where they shouldn't have to look.
For example, those who can easily cross
borders for religious activities.
These legitimate NGO members...
...who don't know they're being used as
couriers are being overlooked.
Sister Eda.
Why did you put the big bags
of sheets into the shed?
Aren't cleaned items normally
taken to the living quarters?
Young man. You can't make statements
based on conjecture.
You make it sound like the stuff's
coming out of this place.
It's just a hypothesis.
Also, the number of weapons
leaving and entering this place...
...don't match up.
It's easy to figure out with a little
research. It is dangerously easy to see.
One more thing.
The Lagoon Company is on friendly
terms with Hotel Moscow...
...but we do not necessarily
work together.
Improve your timing on
when to say what...
...and you'll really take shape. Eda.
Yes?
He's a bit rough, but he passes.
Add the launcher to the list.
Yes.
Dutchy-boy has a good eye.
It's almost time for mass. I apologize,
but you'll have to be on your way.
Young man. Come visit us again.
Hey. You got lucky.
Get the hell outta here.
Miss!
You could learn from that young man.
You can't do good business by
just waving your gun around.
Shut up, bitch!
Aw man... We should've timed this
a little better. It's crowded.
Let's eat before it gets cold.
I don't wanna eat.
Eat.
You'll feel better if you do.
Gimme the keys. I'll go back alone.
But then, I can't get back.
Why don't you walk?
That's not gonna happen.
You ought to go back home to Japan.
You're not cut out for this.
You're the one who invited me.
That was a big mistake.
I wonder. Who kept the church
from becoming a bloodbath?
It's just like that old lady said.
You can't solve everything with a gun.
Hey...
You'd better watch what you say.
You've been this way
ever since the submarine.
- Is it about that conversation?
- Who cares?
I told you never to talk about that again.
Revy.
I'm not gonna apologize anymore.
I think I misheard you. I thought I just
heard you fucking with me.
Is that so?
In that case... I'll say it again!
I'm not wrong, and I've got nothing
to apologize about!
That's what I'm saying!
That's a shame.
You just stepped on a non-negotiable,
non-defusing, big ass landmine.
It's a real shame.
I'll ask you one last thing.
What should I write on your tombstone?
Write, "There's no medicine
for violent idiots".
Goodbye, Rock.
See ya.
See? There are some things
you can't solve with a gun!
B-Bastard!
Don't call me "Bastard"!
My name is Rock!
Got that?! Damn it!
I've had more than enough of this!
I won't take any more!
I thought I was done kissing
my superiors' asses.
Now I'm at the end of the Earth
kissing some woman's ass?
What kinda sick joke is this?!
- You impudent son of a bitch! You're-
- The name's Rock!
Impudent?! Get real, you damn fool!
What about you?
You're an outlaw, a wild pirate!
But as soon as you open your mouth
it's "Money, money, money"?
You think you're a villain
after a big prize...
...but you end up
scavenging off of corpses!
There's a limit to how greedy
you can be!
Don't you have any pride
in that head of yours?!
Don't try and gloss this over
you white-collar!
What do you know about me?!
What the hell do you know?!
Tell me! A guy like you,
with a sheltered life...
...can't understand
what I've been through!
That's right. There's no way
I could know. I'm not you.
But let me ask you.
What do you know about me?
No matter how you live,
you'll encounter suffering.
Right?
You have no intention of
understanding that.
And when you can't answer, you
conveniently become the tragic heroine.
That's the most cowardly
thing about you!
Shut up! You're the one
looking at this conveniently!
God damn it. This isn't like those cheap
Hollywood picaresque films you admire!
What's this about pride?
Screw that! Look around! It's a pile
of shit in every direction!
Robin Hood doesn't
exist anywhere, dumbass!
If there's no Robin Hood,
then become Robin Hood!
It's a much better way of life
than crying and bitching!
Shut up! Shut up, damn it! I'm serious!
I'm gonna kill you!
Sure, then do it. Keep running
around in circles like a dog.
If you kill me here, it'll just prove that.
That's all I know how to do!
Did you forget, Revy?
The reason I'm here. My bosses
calmly cut my life away.
To protect their dirty money...
...and their place to eat.
When you invited me, it was like
something blew through me.
Like I was freed.
My life was the rush hour commute,
the fake laughing...
...lowering my head and risking my life
to maintain a good score.
It was fine as long as I had a place
to drink and a batting cage to go to.
But then, none of that mattered anymore!
The one who taught me that...
The one who invited me...
It was you, Revy.
The reason I'm concerned...
...is that the woman who taught me this
is acting like those who betrayed me.
I can't stand that!
I don't know what you mean, damn it.
Hell with it. You're a real pain in the ass.
You won't live long, idiot.
Well, we're both suffering idiots!
You're a bigger idiot than I am.
- Super idiot.
- You're pissing me off!
Good! Let me take a look at how
you dance around!
- Hey! You two!
- What the hell do you want?
Gimme a break.
I hear someone's making a ruckus in the
market and it turns out to be you again.
Revy. This isn't some prize
in a bag of snacks.
Shooting off like that without concern
for who's watching.
Put yourself in the shoes of those who
have to put the fire out after you.
But that's why you
collect those fat envelopes, right?
That's your job, Chief Watsap.
I'm not saying don't do it, just do it where
no one is gonna see you.
As long as you do that...
...I won't care if you go and kill,
or play hide-the-apple for that matter.
As long as there's no trouble, I don't
have to cancel my golfing plans.
Anyway, I'm bringing you in. We've got
paperwork to take care of on our side.
Yeah, yeah.
Damn engine is giving me trouble.
Have a cold one.
Yeah.
Hey chief, don't steal our car.
Who would want that piece of junk?
Pick it up on your way home.
Hey, Rock.
Just one thing. Let me ask this,
and there will be no more trouble.
Which side do you wanna be on?
Me?
I am where I'm standing. Nowhere else.
Rock. Give me a light.
Light? The cop's got the lighter.
What are you talking about?
You've got one in your mouth.
What a terrible day.
No kidding.
Damn.
I'm so tired. I wanna go home and sleep.
Yeah.
Next Episode
I'm gonna be sold
off somewhere, aren't I?
The world will keep turning
even if there's no justice.