Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
With high hopes, humans
leave Earth...
...to begin a new life in
the space colonies.
But the United Earth Sphere
Alliance gains military power...
...and in the name of
Justice and Peace...
...seizes control of one
colony after the other.
The year is After Colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
To counter the Alliance's
tyranny, rebel colonists...
...bring new arsenals
to the Earth...
...disguising them as
shooting stars.
But the Alliance headquarters
catches on to this operation.
You and I shouldn't be
fighting each other!
Put your hands down.
I was the first one to surrender
and come out, remember.
The Victoria Nightmare
We have word on
the Corsica Factory.
The enemies left before the
reinforcements arrived...
...and 55% of the facility
is destroyed.
Walker.
Thanks for filling me in on
another two enemy machines.
Lieutenant Zechs, Victoria Base
is on the line.
It's been a while,
Lieutenant Zechs.
Looking good, Noin.
I hear you're pretty busy
these days.
Rumors about the
"Lightning Count"...
...have made it down
here to Victoria.
I don't appreciate the rumors.
Enemies target me, and allies
expect more than I can handle.
Rumors are great.
Heard any rumors about me?
I hear you've done well
training pilots for outer space.
Also that you're a superior
all-round soldier.
But Noin.
You used to hate wars.
What's with all this effort?
I'm honored that you
remember so much about me.
My efforts stem from
my love of outer space.
100 meters below surface!
Zero G!
Right!
Commence final testing for
space mobile suit operations.
Roger!
What are you doing?!
You shouldn't have
problems at this speed!
Sense the movements
of your ally craft!
Lieutenant Zechs is coming!
Don't embarrass yourselves!
Lieutenant Zechs is coming?!
Ma'am! I'll do my best!
Good!
Zechs...
It's been one year and
twenty-two days.
So we've lost him?
Yes.
It's the only mobile suit we've
confirmed the location of...
...and it vanished past
the equator.
He's headed for the Taurus
suits at Noin's base.
The military's too imprudent.
Even civilian children know
the Taurus space mobile suits...
...are manufactured
at the Victoria Base.
And I'm on my way over there.
Noin's the only one who'll
welcome an annoying lieutenant.
You two were old schoolmates
there, weren't you?
I'm surprised you knew.
Of course I do.
Everyone knows the top two
students of all graduates...
...from the Lake Victoria
Military Academy.
I also know that you
were the top student.
She was always trying
to be second.
To make me look better.
She might be helping
me once again.
Zechs Merquise.
Or rather, Peacecraft.
Come here and lean on me.
Today's your last day
of training.
You've followed my
strict command.
Today you'll become a member
of the elite Specials force.
The enemy's after your
space mission Taurus suits!
And your first mission
as a member of OZ...
...is to get your suits
off the base!
Isn't that a job for
the transport crew?
The men I trained can take
care of their own machines.
Prepare to leave immediately!
Get a move on!
Yes, ma'am!
When will we slip
the Tauruses out?
0700 hours tomorrow.
That's cutting it close.
I heard the enemies
won't show on radar.
We've got extra soldiers
on the lookout.
That's the best strategy.
Good thinking.
I appreciate the compliment,
Lieutenant Zechs.
Call me Zechs, Noin.
This room sure is cheery.
Most of my soldiers are
young and restless.
This suits them.
Don't get too attached
or parting will be hard.
Thanks for being so concerned.
But my soldiers aren't ever
gonna be killed in battle.
They've been trained not
to overdo things.
To me, there's no comparing
the value of life versus war.
My soldiers have died.
Noin, I disagree with
your philosophy.
Battles that risk men's lives
are pure miscalculations!
I pity the soldiers
who get killed.
Noin here.
Zechs, you've got a call
from Lieutenant Otto.
The technicians are
just as surprised.
This suit is far more superior
than initially predicted.
It should be ready sooner
than expected.
Even so, it'll take
another month or two.
I see; sounds good.
Keep me posted.
What's happening?!
We're under attack!
The pilot trainee dormitory
was hit the worst!
What?!
Th-This is terrible!
I-Instructor...
I wanted to go to outer
space so badly.
Find the enemy and
attack them on sight!
Destroy them!
We're expecting a mobile
suit battle.
Leos, lead the pack!
The enemy should be close by!
How's Lieutenant Zechs?
He's safe at the south hangar
and now coming over here.
Good!
The enemy's come to
destroy the Taurus suits!
Assume positions!
It'll take 30 minutes to load
all the suits for transport.
Okay!
Hold the enemy off
for 30 minutes!
I'll command the
mobile suit troops!
No sign of the enemy!
No enemies at the east gate!
No problems at the water
pressure generator!
No sign of the enemy!
Where's the enemy hiding?!
Bring up the heat
sensor images!
There he is!
Get some Aries over here!
Only those closest by!
We're going after him!
Stop! Stop or I'll shoot!
He'll never escape!
Has he got backup?!
A Gundam!!
A Gundam might be waiting
where the enemy's headed!
Bring out the space laser!
But we can't fully deploy the
heat when it's used on Earth!
Doesn't matter!
- We just need one shot!
- Yes ma'am!
Noin's in enemy pursuit?!
He's heading for the
bushes up ahead.
It's a dead end!
You coward, attacking soldiers
instead of mobile suits!
Call yourself a man?!
You sound like a real
know-it-all.
He's practically a baby!
A kid did all that damage to
the base by himself?!
Hm? A woman...
Now it makes sense.
He attacked the base
on his own.
But he only looks about 14.
He's there!
Target in sight!
Fire!!
Don't shoot!
Why not, Lieutenant Noin?!
Because she's a woman!
Damn you!!
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Hurry!
Lift off as soon as we get
all six Taurus suits loaded!
Orders from Lieutenant Noin!
Hurry!
The enemy isn't headed
this way.
Don't panic.
We'll handle things at the base.
Just move your aircraft out
from in front of Transport No. 1!
I don't care if you're following
Instructor Noin's orders.
The enemy isn't coming,
so don't move the Taurus suits.
Never mind!
Get Transport No. 2 out!
Lieutenant Zechs, I could
get you court-martialed.
I'm much more composed
than you right now.
If one makes a decision
with a cool head...
...he won't regret
his decision later on.
Move!!
What's wrong with you, Aries?!
Th-The Taurus suits!
Woman!
Are you listening?!
You underestimated me
because I'm a kid.
You're a weak soldier.
I don't kill bleeding hearts
or women.
Damn!
Damn it!!
Insulation section 2600.
Repairs are possible.
Hey, you!
I'm calling you!
Why won't you even
acknowledge our kindness?
I'm being Mr. Nice Guy
offering to fix your suit...
...but you brush me off!
I don't want anybody
touching my mobile suit.
That's all.
That's a joke; you haven't
even got the parts.
The best engineers in the world
can't do repairs without parts.
Mechanics need repair parts;
not like you with your leg.
See what I'm saying?
Why did I bother to rescue
this guy in the first place?
He's anti-social, thinks he's
Evel Knievel, and hardly speaks.
I can't take it!
You're so gloomy; why not
stop pretending to be human?
Hey!
What?!
You're too late to come
asking for my help!
Could you keep it down?
Yeah, sure.
Forgive me for interrupting.
What is it?!
A mission.
An enemy carrier's transporting
Gundanium alloy.
Roger.
I'll do it tomorrow morning.
How do you plan to work
with your suit in this shape?!
You're talking miracles!
It'd take a miracle for you.
But I can handle it.
Well excuse me for being
a mere mortal!
If you screw up you'll
be blown to bits.
Your missions have no
room for failure.
Just like mine; the similarities
are uncanny!
Heero!
I'm right over here so
hurry and come kill me!!
According to reports from
Colonel Treize...
...they're made of
Gundanium alloy.
Very interesting...
"Treize?!"
Treize Khushrenada of
the Specials?!
I've heard that Gundanium
alloy can only be refined...
...in outer space.
We should conclude that
these mobile suits...
...came from the colonies!
That'd mean disarming my
military would be delayed.
No, we should be increasing
our presence.
We'd be glad to direct our
country's space forces...
...to Lagrange Point and
support General Septem's troops.
Our nation has already made
arrangements to do so.
I think it's unwise to interpret
the actions of a few...
...as reflecting all
the colonies.
The real problem is how to deal
with these Gundam attacks.
We know what the problem is!
General, give orders to attack!
More than anyone else,
the colonies are hoping...
...for peace in the Earth
Sphere Alliance!
We want peace as well.
The colonies' actions aren't
stemming from some jealousy?
Absolutely not!
Until now hostilities have only
been sparked by attempts...
...of the Alliance Military
to take control.
Your true feelings are
finally emerging!
You're a spy and have been
colluding with the colonies!
That's ridiculous!
We've heard everything
you have to say.
I'd like you to leave the room
now, Vice Foreign Minister.
Isn't it about time you
people realized...
...that you're posing the
greatest threat of all!
Silence! We've had enough!
So tension returns at
La Grange Point.
That's the way it should be.
The leak worked well this time.
My hat's off to Zechs.
He really did a fine job.
By the way, Lady Une.
Yes?
About Vice Foreign
Minister Darlian...
I'll see to it.
And I'll have rose fragrance
ready for your next bath.
Sounds good.
Man, what's he thinking?
I'm sacking out.
What's going on?!
I don't believe it!
That guy's incredible; he
fixed his suit over night!
Oh no!!
We've been had!
He took his parts
from this suit!
What?!
I was just complimenting him!
Traitor!!
Target confirmed.
It's almost fixed!
They're a similar make,
so it was pretty easy.
So similar it's freaky!
Right boss?
Yeah.
That's why Master Quatre
is so concerned.
I'm just relieved that this guy
who can fight like Quatre...
...isn't an enemy.
Noin, you all right in there?
Yeah.
Just feeling a little beat up
inside and out.
Noin...
I'm just happy you're alive.
Because if I died I'd get
promoted over you?
You've got nothing to worry
about with that sense of humor.
Zechs, you've gotta let me
fight the enemy with you!
I wanna get stronger!
I've been through hell
with that Gundam as well.
But next time they won't be
getting off so easily.
Zechs...
I'd be happy if you
worked with me, Noin.
I'd like that, Zechs.
Get out of my sight,
you weaklings!!
Fighting a weak enemy leaves
me feeling so empty afterward.
Damn it!!
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
With the Gundams' arrival,
the true battle has begun.
But is it what the
colonies desire?
Vice Foreign Minister Darlian
leaves for the colonies again...
...taking Relena with him.
But OZ's Lady Une plans
the Minister's assassination.
With Minister Darlian's
dying breath...
...Relena learns the secrets
surrounding her birth.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 5,
Relena's Secret
"Relena's Secret".