Did you know?!
Your pretty face is getting all messed up.
It's starting to look like it was made to be the prey of this Holy Sword, Excalibur!
Shut your hole!
That's a dirty mouth for such a pretty face.
Right?!
Holy Eraser!
Yeah, that's not gonna work.
Sorry!
I was just testing your sword.
I had to see if it was real.
Now, I won't hesitate to break you and your sword!
Goodness!
Did I forget to tell you?
This sword was made for killing you Devil shits.
Capiche?
I know!
As if I'd ever forget!
You cheater!
Devilish, aren't I?
Touché.
Huh?
Someone's calling me!
Well, smell ya later!
Stand up once again
Tomo ni mou ichido tachiagare
To protect a single life
Mamore hitotsu no inochi tayasanu yo ni
Waking up to another dawn
Futatabi otozureta yoake ni me ga samete
I was dreaming about you
Kimi wo omoi dasu yume no tochuu
I still see your afterimage and can't move on
Me no mae no zanzo susumanai ashidori
I still see your afterimage and can't move on
Me no mae no zanzo susumanai ashidori
Powerless, I drift away
Toozakatte yuku hiriki na boku
What is most precious to me?
Taisetsu na mono wa doko ni aru?
If you believe in the future, never forget
Ashita wo shinjiru nara wasurenaide
Now is the time to risk your life and move on
Ima koso saa inochi wo kakete susumi dasu toki
The stronger your will, the stronger you will be
Omoi ga tsuyoi hodo tsuyokunaru
A faint, fragile dream will never last long
Hengen suru tsugihagi darake no risou dewa
A faint, fragile dream will never last long
sugu ni kiete shimau kara
Let's make an eternal promise
Towa e tsuzuku kawasu chikai
From the bottom of our shivering bodies
Furue dashita karada no soko kara
Episode 2
The Holy Sword Is Here!
Good morning! Splash!
Just kidding!
My chest feels heavy.
Morning, Issei.
Good morning, Issei-san.
Wh-What's going on?
You fell asleep on us last night.
So we decided to each take one of your arms as a pillow.
That's right!
This can't be right...
I need to make breakfast soon!
Oh, my!
I'll see you later, Issei.
Thanks for having us, Issei-san.
President's influence is making Asia do dirty things...
not like that's bad or anything!
No, it is!
I have to protect Asia!
Protecting her while she's being dirty is...
even better!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
But if I ever did anything with
President, Asia would get mad.
I'm stuck in limbo!
HAREM
KING
According to my simulations...
Who should I please today?
Issei-san!
Me!
Please give me your blessing!
P-Please...
Give me your blessing!
If you insist...
You must be crazy, Issei!
I-I'm sorry!
Listen to me, Issei.
I cannot live without you.
Now, get over here and satisfy me.
President!
I called him first!
I always go first!
Wha—
Aw, man.
It's a pity there's only one of me.
I know. Why don't you play
rock-paper-scissors to decide?
I'm not going to lose!
Nor will I!
Bring it on!
Anytime!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'm the Harem King!
Scissors!
If only life could be so sweet...
Reality, why are you so cruel?!
Yeah, I saw President's boobs...
touched 'em, too! But...
anything beyond that seems light-years away!
I'm so unlucky!
Hey, partner.
Sorry to interrupt your thoughts.
Forgot my voice, partner?
Ddraig?
You never stop thinking about women, huh?
Shut it!
I'm just at that stage of my life!
You're the one that barged in on me!
Stop complaining.
I've gone out of my way so I could warn you.
Warn me?
Hey, Asia,
how do you like this?
It's delicious!
President-san, how do you make such good miso soup?
I have felt a strong force around you lately.
I put in a secret ingredient.
I have a hard time sleeping.
Yeah, President's been fooling around with me all the time...
with her body, that is!
If that force were one of your friends, I wouldn't give a damn.
Then you're saying it's an enemy?
I'm just telling you to be careful.
You never know when the white one could attack you.
The white one?
I remember you talking about it before.
The white dragon:
Vanishing Dragon.
Vanishing Dragon?
We're known as the Two Heavenly Dragons,
but we never got along.
The hosts of the Heavenly Dragons are destined to fight one another.
Hosts?
You mean there's another guy with a Sacred Gear like mine?
There is.
And I have to fight him sometime in the future?
Most likely.
First, you barge into my body, and now this?!
You got a dragon's powers in exchange, didn't you?
It's not like I've forgotten that.
I couldn't have saved President without it.
But you know what, Ddraig? Let me tell you something.
What?
Ahem.
Listen carefully.
I want to become a High Class Devil and become Harem King!
I'm going to have countless girls as my servants,
and create my very own hottie brigade!
That is my dream!
First time I've ever had a host with a dream like that!
D-Does that make me weird?
It's definitely achievable.
Dragons' powers subjugate and mesmerise those around them.
Although some consider it repulsive,
many women become charmed and are drawn to it.
S-Seriously?!
Sure.
My hosts have always been swarmed with women.
I didn't know you were such an amazing piece of Sacred Gear!
Talk about a change of heart.
All right!
My goal for the time being is to conquer President's boobs!
I appreciate your help!
You're going to grope them?
No...
Kiss 'em.
I'm helping a guy suckle, huh?
I wonder when I fell so low.
Well, I guess I'm in for a fun ride.
Don't forget about my warning, though!
The strong...
force?
Chairwoman?
A Holy Sword...
Karaoke?
It's been a while!
The one in front of the station not only has insert songs,
but character songs, too!
What was that about inserting?
Kiryuu?!
Goodness gracious. Another morning spent talking about sex?
We were just talking about karaoke!
Karaoke?
Sounds nice.
I'd love to go.
Wouldn't you, Asia?
Hey! You can't just...
Yes, I would!
Really?!
Wow, it's got a mirror finish!
Yeah, gotta love
that mirror finish!
Huh?
What's up?
What's that room down there?
Oh, that room's always been closed.
We call it the "Forbidden Room."
Now that the building's spotless,
we can start anew.
Wait, where's Kiba?
Yuuto-senpai is absent from school.
He is?
President, could this have anything to do with our talk yesterday?
Please tell me, President.
What has Kiba got to do with the Holy Swords?
I told you that Yuuto is a survivor of the Holy Sword Experiment, right?
Yes.
There were many more children conditioned to be compatible with Excalibur.
That's because there are seven swords known as the Holy Sword, Excalibur.
Seven?
The original Excalibur was shattered in combat long ago.
The Church found those pieces
and used alchemy to create seven new swords.
Does that mean Kiba can use them?
Yuuto, along with the other test subjects,
failed to become compatible with the Excaliburs.
The experiment was a failure.
A failure?
Consequently, the leader of the experiments decided to dispose of all test subjects.
Dispose of...
You can't mean...
He was nearly dead.
However, he was the only one to escape, and with his short life flashing before his eyes,
he passionately desired vengeance.
Seeing his strong determination, I wanted him to put it to good use as a Devil.
And that's when you made Kiba a Devil?
That's why, when he saw that photo, he...
We'll just keep an eye on him for now.
My, my. We're all gathered already?
Akeno! You're late.
I've brought guests.
Excuse us.
The Student Council Chairwoman and...
Vice-Chairwoman?
She has some very urgent business with President.
Yes.
Rias, would you please accompany me to my house?
No one will be able to interfere there.
This sounds like serious business.
Yes, quite serious.
Any idea what's going on?
They both looked so serious.
No idea...
What do you think, Koneko-chan?
Nothing.
President always does the right thing.
However...
I am concerned about Yuuto-senpai.
To be honest, so am I.
President told us to leave him alone,
but I can't do that.
Not because we're a family...
but because we're friends.
Yes.
Goodbye. See you tomorrow.
See ya, Koneko-chan.
Bye! See you tomorrow!
Koneko-chan, Akeno-san...
Huh?
I wonder if they have a story behind their rebirths.
You know, like us, or like Kiba.
I haven't been here in a while.
Did you come here often?
Rias and I often talked about things in secret here.
I had this sauna built for my personal use.
This dimension is connected only to Sona-sama's home.
Once we close that passage, nobody can come in.
And what exactly were those "secrets", hmm?
Whining about our strict parents,
and other silly gossip like that.
I think Sona talked about her sister all the time.
My, my.
I didn't know that side of you two.
We were young.
So...
I presume we're not here to gossip.
This morning, I was in contact with two affiliates of the Church.
The Church?
I haven't seen them in this city for a while.
And what were they here for?
They asked to talk to you, Rias.
Church affiliates want to meet a Devil?
You must be joking.
In any case, this can't be good.
So, how did you reply to them?
I accepted.
After school tomorrow, they will visit your club room.
However, there's something that worries me.
These two affiliates had a Holy Sword with them.
A Holy Sword?!
Church affiliates with a Holy Sword?
In this city, of all places?
Perhaps an affiliate of this city's church?
Could it be...
I-I'm getting chills.
Yeah, I feel it, too.
Actually, I've had this feeling before.
You've felt it before?!
When I met you and went to that church.
And...
Mom!
Excuse us, Sona.
We must go back immediately.
Issei and Asia are in danger.
Mom!
Yes, that's right!
And this is when he tore his swim trunks in the pool!
Mom?
Oh, Issei. Welcome home!
Why do you look so shocked?
That feeling must've been these two!
Long time no see, Issei-kun.
Don't you remember me?
It's me!
Uh...
Look, this girl here!
Shidou Irina-chan!
Wh-What?!
But...
She was such a tomboy back then,
but now she's just the opposite!
I almost didn't recognize her!
Seriously?!
I really thought she was a boy.
That's really rude, you know?
N-No, I—
I can understand.
I was pretty boyish back then.
Oh, I... Sorry.
But it looks like a lot's happened while we were apart.
Huh?
You can never really tell how people will change!
I'm so glad you're safe!
I'm so sorry.
I should've been more wary of what was going on.
I came back prepared for the worst.
I'm just so glad.
I'll take much, much better care of you two from now on.
President...
Yes?
Your boobs...
All right.
Issei, you're such a demanding boy.
Oh boy!
No!
Figures.
They were talking to your mother?
Yes.
I gave Asia an excuse to come up here,
but they seemed to know that we were Devils.
Well, that's fine.
I don't know what they came for,
but I'll be meeting them tomorrow, anyway.
T-Tomorrow?!
After school tomorrow, they'll be coming to the club room.
I can't believe my childhood friend is part of the Church.
I'm worried about tomorrow.
What's wrong, Devil-kun?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just thinking about things.
A Devil shouldn't look so gloomy.
Life's problems tend to sort themselves out.
I don't find any point in worrying about every little thing that lies ahead.
Huh?
Oh, Devil-kun,
you got a bite.
Wh-Whoa!
We appreciate your cooperation.
I am Xenovia.
I'm Shidou Irina.
For what reason would servants of God desire to meet a Devil?
Although one is yet to be found,
the six remaining Excaliburs have been kept by three divisions of the Church.
Three of those have been stolen by Fallen Angels.
Stolen?!
The ones that we have are this, the Holy Sword of Destruction, Excalibur Destruction...
...and my Holy Sword of Mimicry, Excalibur Mimic!
So, what do you want from us?
This particular problem is between us and the Fallen Angels.
We can't afford to deal with the Devils of this city.
You're awfully condescending.
You thought we would side with the Fallen Angels to do something to the Holy Swords?
Devils despise Holy Swords.
You're in the same position as the Fallen Angels.
President's getting pissed!
If we must, we will completely destroy you,
even if you are the sister of a Satan.
If you know that much already,
then let me tell you something else:
I will never side with a Fallen Angel.
In the name of the Gremorys,
I swear I will never do anything to humiliate the Satans.
I am glad to hear that.
That was just what our headquarters were after.
I am sure the sister of a Satan would not be so foolish.
Then you must know that I will not side with you and your God either, correct?
Of course.
We simply would like you to pledge non-intervention in this ordeal.
Understood.
Thank you for your time.
Won't you stay for some tea?
I am sorry, but we cannot befriend Devils.
We shall take our leave now.
I've been wondering this since I visited Hyoudou Issei's house.
Are you Asia Argento?
Y-Yes.
I never thought I'd see a witch here.
Oh, you're that ex-nun who became a witch?
I did hear that you were exiled, because you could even heal Devils and Fallen Angels,
but I never knew you'd become a Devil!
Um... I...
Asia...
To think that a saint has become a Devil...
Nobody's perfect, I suppose.
Hey!
Shut the hell—
Issei-senpai.
That's right.
I know that I can't cause a scene with these two right now,
but still...
Do you still believe in our God?
Xenovia, she's a Devil.
Still, some blasphemers feel some guilt and retain a little of their faith.
I can sense that from her.
Oh, really?
Hey, Asia-san, do you still believe in the Lord, even though you're a Devil?
I-I just can't quite let it go.
I believed in him all my life.
In that case, let us kill you now.
Whatever sins you have committed,
God will always forgive you.
I will punish you...
in the name of God.
That's enough.
If you are going to belittle my servant...
I wasn't belittling her.
This is my duty as a woman of faith.
Issei!
You mustn't!
Issei-san!
Did you call Asia a witch?!
I believe it's a term fit for her.
Like hell it is!
You're the ones that started calling her a saint.
Asia was...
always alone!
Issei-san...
A saint needs only God's love.
Those seeking more love or friendship are not worthy of sainthood.
Screw faith...
and God.
You're all idiots for not understanding Asia's kindness!
What are you to Asia Argento?
Her family!
Her friend!
Her ally!
If you do anything to Asia,
I won't be afraid to fight every last one of you!
May I take that as a challenge to the entire Church?
What a bold statement from such a feeble Devil.
Issei, stop it.
Very well.
I will be your opponent.
Who are you?
Your senior.
Yuuto?
Let us begin.
Is this really okay?
Should we be fighting Church affiliates on our own accord?
This is simply an unofficial sparring match.
If either of our higher-ups knew, we'd be in big trouble!
We'll do our best not to kill you.
You're laughing?
Indeed, because I finally found what I've been wanting to destroy.
Sword Birth...
I remember now.
It was said one subject from the
Holy Sword Experiments escaped disposal.
Hyoudou Issei-kun!
Wh-What?
I can't believe my old friend become a Devil during our years apart.
Is destiny toying with us to cause such tragedy?!
What?!
I finally became compatible with a Holy Sword and even flew over the sea thinking that I could be of use!
Is this another of the Lord's trials?!
Although, overcoming this will bring me one step closer to him!
She's completely lost in her faith.
Come, Issei-kun.
Let me use my Excalibur to punish you for your sins!
Amen!
I don't understand what's going on, but...
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Even for fated couples
unmeiteki ni mo hakarishirenai
The equation of love is complicated
koi no houteishiki
Love isn't always justifiable
ai ni riyuu wa iranai
The answer lies inside your heart
kotae wa kimi no kokoro ni aru kara
After worrying and hesitating
nayande mayotte
My brain stops functioning
shikou teishi
I keep writing then erasing stuff
kaite wa keshite wo kurikaeshi
I'm running a simulation of you in my head
atama no naka de anata simulation
It's unpredictable
yosoku fukanou
Will this work? How about this?
kou kana kou kana
But you never follow my calculations
keisan de ugokeba ii no ni
"Look, it's the beach!" "It sure is."
umi ne sou ne
I can't tell if you love me because you're so innocent
junsui na hodo futoumei
Don't be so kind to every girl
yasashisa wo furimaku na
You'll end up breaking many hearts
tsumitsukuri da wa
Why can't you just be normal?
futsuu ni misete
It's so unfair
zurui hito
zu
It's so unfair
ru
i
hi
to
Then you leave!
jaa kaeri na
I shouldn't let my rivals take you away from me
raibaru ni ukkari ki mi toraretara
I need a hint!
hinto ga hoshii
Quick, I need one!
hayaku hoshii
ha
Quick, I need one!
As I imagine a lovey-dovey future
love hidai na mirai
love
As I imagine a lovey-dovey future
My expectations only go up
takamatta kitai
ta
My expectations only go up
What should I try as the coefficient?
keisuu wa nan ni shiyou
There are too many variables
michisuu sugiru
To your feelings
kimi no kimochi
Rather than just work on the left-hand side
hidari yori mo daisuki
Look ahead to the other side of the equal sign
ikooru no saki wa
Although I'm not sure what it does
wakaranai kedo michibiku
It leads to the correct answer every time
kotae wa itsumo seikai deshou
I'll get over my worries and prove my love for you
nayande mo kono ai wo shoumei suru yo
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
We're up against two hotties with Holy Swords!
It's time to break out my signature move!
Next Episode:
I'll Destroy the Holy Sword!
Episode 3
The boobs are getting hot!