I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
What's with those eyes?
You had all that done to you and
you act like nothing's wrong.
Go on. Keep looking down on us.
You know, after we've gotten
rid of your sword-boy...
...and if we have trouble
finding a buyer for you...
I'll let you have fun with this
pervert I know, shooting drugs...
...from dawn till dusk every day.
This guy can't get a hard-on
unless it's hardcore S&M.
Have him get you hooked on drugs,
shake your ass, and eat his shit...
...and I'm sure you'll
see things differently.
Right? But don't worry.
When the video comes out,
I'll be sure to buy a copy.
Dumbass. You can't win
that much with Mahjong.
Shut up! You wanna fight? Huh?
Hey, any of you got Zippo oil?
Oh, by the way, did you hear?
About the guy who pulled off
a robbery at Shin-Okubo?
Yeah, the news about the Iranian...
...being chased by a guy with
knife in hand, right?
Well there's a warrant out
for the guy's arrest, and...
What the hell?
Keep it down over there!
Wow, so you really did show up.
I don't understand you.
Well, my dear Revy,
what are you doing here?
So you did wanna fuck, eh? Cool!
Gin. Gin!
You've really gone
overboard this time.
Do you wanna see
my sword that badly?!
You'll all make the
march to hell together!
Kill 'em all, baby!
Look! Look at this!
I've never seen such a fight!
Hey guys! Don't hide!
Show some balls!
Come on! Run! Run!
He's all yours.
Wow! Amazing! I'd better get
serious or I could be in trouble.
Hey, Yuki! Come here!
Miss!
Come on! Try catching up with me!
- Ow! Ow!
- Amazing! That woman's amazing!
I never thought I'd have the chance
to do it with her in a place like this!
I'd better prepare the stage
if I'm gonna do this right! Right, Yu...
God damn it! Who did this?
Cleaning fluid?
Hey!
It's a strike!
W-Wait! I give up! I really give up!
I give! Give! You know, give, give, give!
Give? Give me what?
I-I cannot speak... ah...
You're gonna give me
something, right?
Well, come on, what the fuck
are you trying to say?
W-Well, give up, so give!
Seriously! I give, give! Give!
Quit yapping, you goofball.
You gonna give it to me or not? C'mon!
Hey Jumbo! The game's up.
Boy we made a mess, all we got
left is to mop up the place.
Let's split up and look for
our princess and that sack o' shit.
Pool
Men's
Lockers
Women's
Restaurant
We'll go around the corridor
and meet at the pool, okay?
Women's
Lockers
If you see Rock, bring him with you.
If we're lucky,
he may be with the princess.
All right.
I'm counting on you, partner.
What a stubborn guy.
Let's see...
You've run outta luck.
I pity you guys.
No one's getting outta here alive.
Not a single one of you.
This is Hell's Motel.
Run away, if you can...
...or the boogeyman's
gonna eat you up!
Perfect.
Time to live forever, baby.
I don't hear anything.
Mr. Chaka, have the other guys...?
Um, Mr. Chaka!
I can hear you! Shut up. What was that?
I'd say they're probably dead.
What the hell, you bastard?!
How can you say that?
I'm tired of following you!
If you've got time to bitch,
go look for the girl.
What are you going to do?
The plan's screwed.
Come on now!
What? You're running from me?
Fine then!
Damn it!
Wow, what a surprise.
You shot your own subordinates.
I've never seen such despicable scum.
Seeing that you're
still running around...
...I guess you haven't met up
with Jumbo yet.
Well, who cares?
I've been wanting to meet you.
I've never met
a female gunman before.
The opportunity has finally come.
Sleep with me, Revy.
A-ha, yeah. So that's it.
What a joker.
The moment this can hits the
floor is our signal, kitty-cat.
Ready?
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
Huh?
You wanted to challenge me as
a gunman? Don't make me laugh.
I'm not about to duel against a...
...below-third-rate sack o' shit
like you, punk.
I do have a desire to kill you.
But if you're happy to die,
then it's a different story.
I'll let Jumbo finish you off.
How dare you. Stop, bitch!
Sack o' shit.
Hey! Wait! Wait, damn it!
Wait!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Jumbo.
I brought you your prom date.
This isn't funny.
You get on my nerves, sword man.
The Miss isn't here any more.
Because I shot her.
So you're done here, right?
I suggest...
...you go home and cook
some octopus dumplings.
There's no way a pathetic
little dog like you...
...would ever drop your own
wallet with cash in it.
Am I right?
A-All right then, you bastard!
Now, show me how good you are.
Draw in any manner you wish.
You bastard! I'll kill you, bastard!
I'll kill you!
It's gotten quiet.
I bet Revy and Gin are
getting their job done.
Let's stay here a little longer,
just in case.
Mr. Okajima, why are you here?
I couldn't leave you alone...
...because I found out that you were...
...being dragged into this
incident, our job.
I see. So you didn't know.
I get it. You just said that
I was being dragged into this.
You're mistaken, Mr. Okajima.
I'm... I'm the person at
the core of this incident.
And... you are my enemy.
I'll say it again. You are my enemy.
- Yukio! What are you saying?
- Mr. Okajima...
...I have accepted the position of
fourteenth Washimine Clan deputy.
In other words...
...right now I hold the highest rank
within the Washimine Clan.
I... I wasn't dragged into this.
I am at the core of it all.
And you are... my enemy.
You're...
You knew what kind of world this is,
and yet you stepped in?!
You've seen it, right?!
They're filled with evil and
don't have a shred of decency!
This is a world where people like
that betray and kill one another!
Mr. Okajima. I'll ask you again.
Why did you come here?
I said it before.
I couldn't just watch you
get dragged into this.
Couldn't just watch?
I believe Mr. Bando's
cause of death was suicide.
You must have been there too.
When your clan's
lost its driving force...
...and the parent clan is
neglecting you.
When it's necessary to stand
up against a stronger power.
Suppose you're the only one...
...who can save the clan from
that predicament. Then what?
To renew the brotherhood...
...only someone from the direct bloodline
will be recognized as a successor.
That was the rule.
But...
You don't have to say it. I know.
It's an old tradition that
no one's bothered to change.
But no matter how
ridiculous it sounds...
...we only know how to live
within those guidelines.
That's the order we abide by.
But that's crazy!
Then what happens to your life?
Nobody wanted this!
Not Mr. Bando,
not Mr. Gin, and not you!
Everyone was desperate to keep you
away from the fighting, right?
They were keeping you from
standing here!
If I had been standing here sooner...
...this would not have happened.
No! It's the Kousa Clan
who is to be blamed!
You are... You are forcefully trying
to bear this burden by yourself.
That's the only way I see it.
Do you remember what we
talked about at the café?
People are like dice.
A certain Frenchman said
that people are like dice.
You throw yourself in the
direction of your choice.
I wasn't forced. I chose this.
I'm doing all I can for my father
and the people who loved him.
No! You didn't have a choice!
If you lose sight of that...
...you'll be forced to live with a burden
that you don't have to carry!
- You are in the twilight.
- What?
You can say these things because
you've stayed in the twilight like this!
I had no choice but to come here!
I cannot have resolve unless
I believe that I chose this!
If someone's life, honor,
and future depends on me...
What else can I do
but fight for them?!
Like tonight! If I didn't believe
that I had chosen this responsibility...
...I couldn't have endured
what I went through!
Revy.
Well, I believed in God...
...right up to the day cops beat the hell
outta me for something I didn't do.
So the next time you try telling
me what's proper...
...you'll no longer be one of us.
Nothing's changed since then.
Revy.
In the midst of this night
that she has experienced...
...I am completely powerless.
I have no words to give this
girl before me...
...who's stumbling
towards your side.
I...
I am where I'm standing.
Nowhere else.
That's a lie.
I'm not standing anywhere!
You bastard!
You devil!
This is too easy a way for you to die,
but the style suits you.
I decided that it would be acceptable
for me to carry it all on my shoulders...
...if it means
saving Gin and the others.
Y-Y-Yukio, do you...
Mr. Okajima. Answer me.
Why did you try to
make a stand here?
To be honest I couldn't...
...understand what you were
talking to me about in the café.
But I think I can say
this clearly now.
The reason you
submerged yourself...
...in the southeast Asian
underworld is possibly because...
...you were seeking something different
from Japan. Different from your daily life.
But in the end,
you haven't chosen anything.
You're not returning to your
casual life under the sun yet you...
...refuse to sink further into
darkness where the evil roams.
You just remain
standing where you are.
N-No... I...
You said it earlier,
that you wanted to save me.
Then save me!
Save the Washimine Clan!
Save Gin, the members, everyone!
There's no way you can. Because you
don't actually want to save me.
You don't want to lose that normal
life that you thought you threw away.
That's all.
If you sit back and watch me die...
...you lose the very last of
your recollections of Japan.
But you don't want to lose anything.
You still have yearnings for
that which you've thrown away.
Who could you possibly protect,
feeling like that?
With you like that, who could
you possibly save?! Answer me!
Answer me now!!
I wanted to live a normal life.
I should be in
the same place as you...
...a guy who chose
not to live a life of pain.
Yukio...
Stay away.
I know. But I'm upset.
I can't help but be upset about it.
And that's why I hate you.
Wait a sec.
You did something amazing.
The bullet, baby. You cut the bullet.
Could you show that to me again?
Come on. Please?
Being short tempered
won't do you any good.
I owe you and the interpreter.
There's no need to waste that.
If you're lucky...
Or rather, if you're unlucky, there will
be other opportunities for us to fight.
Yukio.
Thank you for tonight.
But I pray...
I pray we never meet again.
Rock still hasn't
returned to his room.
Where could he be
wasting his time?
It's just as well. There's nothing
for him to do for a while anyway.
The assault on the Washimine
Group will begin at 0750 hours.
Form two squads to go in and
destroy their headquarters...
...offices and all confirmed hideouts.
The attack team
has already moved out.
We shall destroy all of the Washimine
forces thoroughly and immediately.
Teach these Japanese the
etiquette of war.
Next Episode
I don't know what you're thinking...
...but you should not wish for the
same way of life as his.