Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
The Heroine of the Battlefield
The Romefeller Foundation's
enforced rule...
...has caused disputes to
spring up around the world.
Our country has declared
itself a peaceful nation...
...and we've been trying
to avoid resistance.
We'd be guaranteed peace
if we let them control us.
But you couldn't really
call that true peace.
It'd be a method of oppression.
It'd lead to a new despotic
rule and more disputes.
I certainly hope that we're
making the right decisions.
Over the ages, the world
has had many countries...
...many races, and many
ways of thinking.
Perhaps we should
accept the fact...
...that some disputes in
the past were unavoidable.
Freedom is a right given
to all people.
But we must realize that people
can't be given complete freedom.
What we need in order
to attain harmony...
...is to be thoughtful
to others.
A peaceful future
doesn't lie in fighting.
It's our job to learn
from our past...
...and use that experience to
build a new and correct future.
I was afraid that our
nation alone...
...couldn't act against the
Romefeller Foundation.
So was I.
But Total Pacifism...
...as advocated by the
late King Peacecraft...
...is well rooted here in
the Sanc Kingdom.
Its presence is a
strong support.
I'm aware that my speech
and behavior...
...seem impudent despite
the fact...
...that I'm following
my father's teachings.
But it's my sincere hope
that more countries...
...and more people can
one day attain true peace.
To that end I ask for
your assistance.
Let us work together!
For true peace!
The meeting ended
without a hitch.
It's not as if we're watching
every move you people make.
It's just that your meeting
ended so soon.
We're determined to
get our way.
That's probably why the
meeting didn't take long.
We'll be on our way,
since we're not needed.
We're ruining the view.
We don't necessarily dislike
the Romefeller Foundation.
We just want you to rectify
your mistakes.
And do it before many
people lose their lives.
Count Townsend!
We've found two space suits.
It appears that only
the two landed here.
Roger.
There's no reason for caution.
- You may return.
- Yes, sir.
The Space Colonies and
Romefeller have joined forces.
The Gundam pilots'
missions are over.
Orders are out to execute
the Gundam pilots.
Executing them would be easy.
Although our country is
under Romefeller's rule...
...I'd rather not
get rid of them yet.
Not big on animals, Quatre?
I love them.
Then play with the dogs.
It seems they'd rather
play with you anyway.
Animals have the natural ability
to sense kindness in people.
Is kindness necessary in a war?
No.
Not while you're fighting.
But kindness is probably
needed the rest of the time.
This isn't the time to fight.
Thanks for the meal.
Sorry to trouble you.
Especially considering there
are orders to execute us.
Fortunately headquarters
contacted us and will be...
...picking up you Gundam pilots.
I'm glad; it means I don't
have to carry out the orders.
But I'll still have to hand
you over to them...
...when the time comes.
We can't trouble you any
more than we already have.
It's your job to hand us over.
You're gonna surrender
without a fight?
We won't know what we'll do
till the time comes.
But we won't die aimlessly.
You guys are certainly strong.
We're involved in Romefeller's
control policies...
...but we have doubts.
Getting involved was our only
choice to avoid futile battle.
You made the correct decision,
to protect the people's lives.
I think that's the same decision
our people in space made.
To the Romefeller Foundation...
...we Gundam pilots are
a mere obstruction.
Anyone who's after our
lives is an enemy.
We have to fight to survive.
That's the one and only thing...
...that we can and must
carry out.
It's that simple.
If you don't wanna die,
that is.
Attention, carrier!
Surrender at once!
We have orders to shoot
you down!
I repeat.
Surrender at once.
The sea's gotta be cold
at a latitude of 50.
But still, I can't simply give
the craft up to OZ!
There it is.
Get a move on!
Sally Po.
Just be thankful you
got a fireplace.
The new OZ is a warm-
hearted organization.
You're only treating me like
a special guest...
...until you confirm what's
in the carrier, I suppose?
We were told to watch
for rebels...
...who would help the Gundam
pilots once they took action.
But we didn't expect to
get our hands on a Gundam!
So it's true that the Gundam
pilots have returned to Earth.
I've gotta make sure
I deliver it to them.
Damn.
More and more nations are
taking sides with Romefeller.
It's gonna be a rocky road.
The metal detector won't be
able to pick up the Gundam.
But it'll pick up the carrier,
so find it.
Yes, sir!
- What's wrong?!
- Enemies?!
Who are you?
I want the truth.
Is that the real thing
at the bottom of the sea?
I might tell a lie
so that you'll free me.
I wanna retaliate against
Romefeller...
...so I need the Gundam.
You're fighting the
same enemy.
So decide if you
wanna negotiate.
My time's run out!
Let's go!
So it IS real then.
That's why the enemy
built up so fast.
It's the one OZ referred
to as Zero One.
You said you wanted the
Gundam to save yourselves.
What country are you from?
I can't tell you yet.
I will say that it's
resisting Romefeller.
So it could be attacked
any time.
The ruler of the nation is
indispensable for the future.
And is capable of bringing
true peace to this world.
Do you expect to win
against Romefeller...
...with just the Gundams?
I'm confident in its pilot.
He'd defeat Romefeller's
ambitions.
As acquaintances of
the Gundam pilots...
...you and I tend to
overdo things.
It's risky to depend
on them too much.
But at the moment
I want their help.
Nobody wants to get
involved in wars.
But those who have the
ability to fight should fight.
At least that's what I think.
I'm reluctant to use
the word "righteous".
But the word suits those kids.
Calling them righteous
might really be a sad thing.
Since it forces them to
act like modern heroes.
I want to follow them.
If I do, it's unlikely that
I'll take a wrong path.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Plans to wipe out the Gundams
are progressing in two places.
One is here.
Could the other be the
Gundam you left behind?
I think that might be.
They're calling it "Zero One".
Heero, have you heard
of the Sanc Kingdom?
It comes up in Romefeller's
confidential data...
...as a problematic nation.
The Sanc Kingdom...
They're covering their tracks.
But they're very interested
in finding Zero One.
And also its pilot.
Wouldn't you like to go?
I'm sure we could be
of some help to them.
That's a good boy.
These two dogs are the only
ones guarding us now.
They're telling us to leave.
This nation isn't looking
for any battles.
But we're like time bombs
and will bring trouble.
The commander here has
a weak point, to boot.
It's his kindness.
Let's go, Quatre.
Sure thing.
Something's headed our way.
Any word from Count Townsend?
Nothing.
- Check at once.
- Sir.
What?
They're heading straight
for Romefeller's forces?!
Why wouldn't they be escaping?
We have an urgent message
from those forces...
...demanding information
on the approaching craft!
Count Townsend.
- This was left behind.
- By the Gundam pilots?
Count, what is it?
Please inform them at once
that we've escaped.
We can't cause you any more
trouble than we already have.
That is...
Thank you, Count.
We'd be wiser just to run away.
But we always end up fighting.
Wherever I go it's the same.
Because fighting is
all I can do!
I feel sorry for them.
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
It's being raised.
Let's go!
Roger.
See ya later.
Enemy in sight!
Launching torpedoes!
What's this? An attack?!
This is nuts but
it's the only way!
I knew it was crazy!
I want them, for the sake
of the Sanc Kingdom!
Hands up!
No funny stuff!
Advise the other ships too.
I don't want to make things
worse than they are.
Better do what my partner
tells you.
Personally, I would have
already opened fire.
Actually I just want you
to leave us alone.
But I don't figure
you can allow that.
Heero, where should we
head to now?
There isn't any place
I wanna go.
There are lots of kind people
right here on the Earth.
But we'd be causing them
a great deal of trouble...
...by doing nothing more
than meeting them.
We have no place to go,
do we?
Quatre...
It's because you're trying
to forget the battle.
As long as Earth's a war zone,
I'm gonna fight.
You have no choice but
to fight either.
Because we're Gundam pilots.
The battlefield is the only
place we're allowed to live.
For us, I guess the meaning
of life is to survive battles.
Sally here.
The surface is under control.
How're things?
It's like meeting a long
lost friend.
Use it to protect your country.
I can't thank you enough.
My name is Lucrezia Noin.
The country I'm serving is...
Noin, it's okay.
You don't have to tell me.
I trust you.
I'm just honored to
help a nation...
...that's trying to oppose
Romefeller.
Sally...
I'm gonna go and
look for another Gundam.
If you hear about one
I'd welcome your help.
It'd be great to have
two or three pilots.
You can count on my help.
It'll be a chance
to earn your trust.
I give you my word, in the
name of God and our nation.
The guards for the Peace Nations
Assembly are leaving.
So I rushed here for nothing.
And I was positive they'd
take this opportunity...
...to invade the Sanc
Kingdom, too.
Well, the mobile dolls
just won't do the job.
Those dinky things don't have
a chance against the knights...
...protecting their precious
Princess.
Miss Relena.
Are you all right with that
new student arriving today?
Why do you ask, Pagan?
I heard she was a blood
relative of Duke Dermail...
...the central figure of the
Romefeller Foundation.
I know I mustn't make
assumptions.
But given that the Foundation...
...doesn't think highly of the
Sanc Kingdom's pacifism...
...I can't help thinking
it's a trick.
The Romefeller Foundation
said they wish to learn more...
...about educational policies
on building a peaceful nation.
That's why they wanted to send
a student to our kingdom.
There's nothing to worry about.
I have problems believing
everything the Foundation says.
Doubting people won't
get you anywhere.
Besides there's nothing mistaken
about what we're doing here.
I think this'd be a great chance
to make them understand that.
I'm Relena Peacecraft,
Director of this institution.
Welcome to the Sanc Kingdom.
I wasn't aware that the Princess
of the Sanc Kingdom...
...was also the Director
of the institution.
Once again, my name is
Dorothy Catalonia.
It's an honor to meet you.
I'm still powerless to do
anything on my own.
I'm learning Total Pacifism
that my father advocated.
Just as everyone else is.
As you're aware...
...I've come here on behalf
of the Romefeller Foundation.
The Foundation is surrounded
with weapons...
...in this war-torn world.
I have a great interest in the
policies of the Sanc Kingdom.
Especially in what you'd do...
...if the forces decided to
invade.
This beautiful scenery would
disappear in an instant.
And the hearts that cherish this
beauty would also be lost.
Nobody in their right mind
would want to hand over...
...the Kingdom to such
foolish barbarians.
So what would you do then?
I don't believe there are any
foolish people in this world.
People reach an understanding
by talking things over.
I believe such discussions
will bring peace...
...to all people.
Miss Relena.
I'm a foolish person myself.
I love wars.
I really do.
I guess I'd only be a nuisance
by staying in this country.
Not at all.
The main objective of the
Sanc Kingdom...
...is to provide a place for
these discussions.
I welcome more talks like
this, Miss Dorothy.
But please call me Dorothy,
Miss Relena.
And you can just call
me Relena.
I couldn't.
You are the heroine of
our times.
I myself feel a great
admiration for you.
Dorothy Catalonia.
She's the same age
as Miss Relena.
I expected her to be brainwashed
by Romefeller's oppressive ideas.
But that doesn't seem
to be the case.
But we must be cautious.
Keep an eye on her.
I even had this ready
just in case.
But Dorothy seems tougher
than I thought.
What do you mean?
Miss Dorothy truly gets
enjoyment out of battles.
At this time, when Miss Relena
is rejecting battles...
...I'm worried that Dorothy
could exhaust Miss Relena.
Relena's thoughts are
commendable.
She knows that her actions
are highly risky now.
Our mission is to protect her
in operation.
Even if that means getting
some weapons?
That's right.
We can't afford to let
Relena get killed...
...like the assassinated King
of this country.
We're confronted
by a part of history...
...that could easily be
repeated, but must not.
I'll protect Relena, even if
it means using foul play.
I'll live my life in the
shadows of this kingdom.
Hurry up and start a war!!
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Romefeller's military power
grows...
...as they violently attack
areas of dispute.
Heero recklessly participates
in the battle...
...as a mercenary of the Treize
Faction's retaliating troops.
Quatre begins doubting the
heroism of finding answers...
...within battles.
He learns of a resisting
nation promoting Total Pacifism.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 30,
The Reunion with Relena
"The Reunion with Relena".