You want to observe others working?
Yes.
Asia and I want to see if we are doing our jobs as demons properly.
True. It could be beneficial to the two of you since you're new.
D-Do we have permission, then?
But only if...
you don't interfere with their work.
Don't trouble the client either.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am!
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 14 "I Seek Boobies!"
Oh?
If it isn't Hyoudou-shi!
Good evening, Morisawa-san.
It's been a while.
How come you're here too?
Please excuse me. I'm here to observe today.
Observe?
Oh, I won't interfere.
I'd be much obliged if you just let me sit in a corner and watch.
I don't mind, but...
Who's that girl?
Do I get a girl in nun cosplay as a special bonus?
N-No, I'm also here to observe.
Oh, so you're also new to the business.
Nice to meet you.
I-I'm Asia Argento.
What is your request?
Oh yeah.
We'll play this!
Hyper Road Warrior
Oh, Hyper Road Warrior 4!
Oh, you know this game?
It's an insanely tough fighting game with challenging controls; it's impossible for beginners!
Hardcore gamers love it so much that they even hold tournaments!
Impressive as always, Hyoudou-shi.
You see, I've been digging the arcade edition too.
Everyone at my local arcade knows me as Mori, the player who transcends tier listings!
All right, let's battle, Koneko-chan!
KO!
Impossible! She totally crushed every one of my characters!
Your reflexes are lacking.
K-Koneko-chan, I didn't know you were so good at gaming!
An hour of gaming a day.
That's old.
So you came, Kiba-kun.
I'm glad.
Long time no see, Mika-san.
Is your business doing well?
Yeah, it's doing great.
Two new demons are here with me today to observe.
Do you mind their presence?
Not a problem.
Make yourselves at home, guys.
Kiba-kun, could you do the usual?
"Th-The usual"?!
Kiba, don't tell me you've been providing those kinds of services!
Sure.
Do we have the ingredients?
I-Ingredients?!
Right over there.
I'll be taking a nap now. I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me, ma'am.
She seems really tired.
Mika-san's always like that when she's had a busy day at work.
So I come here and cook her supper.
All right, it's done!
Mika-san!
Mika-san, wake up.
Your udon's ready.
This isn't what I expected.
Guess I got mad over nothing when I heard you're summoned by beauties all the time.
I imagined something sexual.
Oh, just saying legit requests like this are the right job for Kiba!
It's delicious.
Thanks as always, Kiba-kun.
My pleasure.
Akeno-kun, thanks for coming today.
Oh, President.
How may I serve you today?
It seems I must ask for a favor again.
The usual, then?
As you wish.
What kind of favor would the president of a large company request?
C-Could it be...
assassinating a high executive of a rival company?!
Th-That'd indeed be a job for a demon!
Oh my.
Th-That sounds so scary, but I'd like to watch and learn from it!
Come on.
O-Oh my god!
R-Right there!
Perfect!
Oh my.
You must be very exhausted, Mr. President.
I'll give you a great time tonight.
Her finger work is absolutely divine!
This is it! Her massage really hits the spot!
It hurts!
But it feels good!
But it still hurts!
Whenever he's overloaded with workplace stress, he asks me for a foot massage to defuse all of it.
More!
What's up with that getup, though?
I'll knead you all you want.
You're such a helpless president!
What would your employees think if they saw you like this?
More! Stretch me more!
Oh, you're so adorable.
Th-They seem to be having fun.
It's the perfect job for a sadist like Akeno-san.
Playing games together, making supper, and performing a massage?
I get summoned a lot for stuff like playing cards, too.
It just goes to show how peaceful demons' lives and jobs are nowadays.
Are they really?
But you are in luck.
I've been commissioned to do some substantial work tonight.
It'll be a great opportunity for you.
We get to observe you, President?
If they asked her personally, it must be a pretty big deal!
B-But is it really all right?
Of course.
Tag along.
Where are we?
A museum.
Oh, Gremory-san.
Good day, Professor.
I am here to fulfill your request.
Oh, it's much appreciated!
This is Professor Nishiura.
He researches ancient civilizations from around the world.
What's that?
Looks like an ancient sarcophagus.
It's a valuable historical artifact we
excavated from some ancient ruins.
It's giving me the shivers!
Indeed, the coffin is emitting a certain aura.
Not a good one, at that.
I knew it!
The truth is, people who have been involved with this have
come down with unknown diseases, got into mysterious accidents,
or met misfortune in some shape, way or form.
Oh my, that's a disaster.
It might be the curse of the coffin.
That's so scary!
Really? It's cursed?!
Take a look at those hieroglyphs.
I see two circles.
They remind me of a pair of boobs!
Wait, what am I thinking?
I shouldn't seek erotica in hieroglyphs!
Let me tell you what it says.
"Only a beautiful demon woman with large breasts shall awaken me!"
It needs the breasts of a beautiful demon woman?
To summarize,
he wants to be awoken by a beautiful female demon with big boobs!
That's way too short!
Well, it makes sense that he wants to be awakened by a beautiful demon with big boobs, though.
It makes sense to you?
It's Issei-senpai we're talking about here.
By the way, the researchers who've been cursed were all dirty middle-aged men.
Meaning middle-aged men can't touch the coffin.
That makes sense too.
In any case, let me examine it.
What's happening?!
Oh, just as I thought!
The coffin opens when a female demon gets close enough!
Wh-What's going on?!
A-A mummy?
Be careful, Issei.
What's wrong?
Who roused me from my slumber?
Issei?
What the hell is going on? My body won't move!
He must've taken over your body.
Wh-What?!
I'm the one who woke you up.
Good day, mummy man.
My name is Unas!
As a noble priest, I perform ceremonial magic!
I must thank you for waking me!
I see you cast your consciousness into my cute underling's body and took over.
You've got some guts.
Leave his body immediately!
I am afraid I cannot abide by your request!
What?!
I would withdraw if my soul could rest in peace upon returning to this cursed body,
but, alas, it can not!
Just give back my body, you mummy!
It's kind of pathetic that a sorcerer would get cursed.
Silence!
It happened when I attempted to summon a high-ranking demon to advance my sorcery!
A high-ranking demon?
Who was it?
You'll be surprised when you hear this.
It was a female relative of Grand Duke Agares!
What?
Grand dukes are second in authority, right below kings.
But before I could even negotiate,
that demon sealed my body along with most of my powers!
Thus I had no choice but to enter a long slumber!
You got cursed instead?
I wonder how that happened.
As long as I am under the curse,
I won't return this body!
Hey, I have nothing to do with this!
Well, fine.
I can't afford to let you take the body of my precious underling.
President!
Sorcerer Unas, I will lift your curse!
I take it that you're quite a powerful demon yourself.
Then I shall rely on you, red-haired lady.
So what specifically do I have to do?
There are three curses placed on me.
The power of a beautiful demon is necessary to lift it.
Take this!
Put on this costume and dance before me!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Very well.
I just need to put that on and dance, yes?
Th-This is irresistible!
M-Marvelous!
I'm getting suspicious.
That's the crest of Grand Duke Agares, all right.
Looks like one of Agares' curses has been lifted!
There's still two to go.
Lifting the next curse requires the kiss of a female demon.
What?!
You small lady over there!
You've been watching me intently for a while.
I was trying to figure out whether it was your stare
or the possessed Issei-senpai's stare that was so lustful.
That's why I was observing closely.
I don't think so!
I felt it!
You looked at me with romantic interest!
Therefore, I'd like you to lift the next curse!
Come! Give me a kiss as intense as that stare!
Wait, at this rate I'll end up kissing Koneko-chan!
Actually, before that,
Koneko-chan will punch me!
But there's still a chance, however faint!
She may listen to his wish and kiss me!
Stay away from me.
I knew it.
Issei-san!
It was an accident, but Asia kissed me on the cheek!
I'm a lucky guy!
Anyway, looks like we cleared the second one.
One more! Just one more and I can fully revive!
R-Revive?!
This guy...
The last curse will be the most difficult to lift.
The most difficult?
Indeed.
To be exact...
I must motorboat a girl with huge breasts!
M-Motorboat?!
You sure know your slang for an ancient mummy!
No, no, wait!
Don't get in my way!
Your release is just a step away!
You're messing with us!
You said you wanted to rest in peace,
but you're actually trying to revive!
What are you talking about?!
I can hear everything!
Everything you're thinking!
And you're unbelievably perverted!
I bet you were a useless sorcerer!
The boobs are waiting for me!
I will indulge in those boobs and fully revive!
Because the boobs... the boobs are there!
What incredibly powerful lust!
Enough to rival mine!
Oh my, how troublesome.
I mean, no! Don't let him touch your boobs, Akeno-san!
Boy, imagine the sheer bliss you'll experience from rubbing your face in those boobs!
What?!
Just imagine! It'll be true ecstasy that'll take you to heaven!
I-I need to stop getting tempted!
I will win her boobs on my own someday!
Imagine that delightful moment!
Oh my, Issei-kun's so bold.
I'm in heaven!
That wicked aura grew stronger.
I'm the great sorcerer, Unas!
I have now revived!
Well done, demons!
That Agares' woman...
After a millennium the curse has been lifted.
I will see to my vengeance!
You bastard!
He used us to revive himself!
I expected that to be the case.
President!
Could I ask you one thing?
What is it?
How did you get a curse placed on you?
The demon I summoned was stunningly beautiful,
so I told her my wish to marry...
I mean, to have her as my slave!
That's pretty ridiculous.
When you're dealing with a grand duke's relative,
you need an appropriate wish and reward.
No wonder she burst into a rage.
Shut up, demon! I shall bring you down first!
Koneko-chan! Issei-kun!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Geez.
Professor, this mummy man is dangerous.
Can we eliminate him?
That'd be a waste, but it looks like there's no option.
B-But I'd appreciate it if you could at least leave the coffin intact.
We can do that. We'll leave the coffin alone and destroy only him.
Your arrogant attitude reminds me of the annoying female demon from back then!
Take this!
Oh my.
Not this again.
Why do our enemies always love to entangle the girls?
Though I'd love it too.
Let's go, Kiba!
Don't move!
If you move, the girls will be squeezed to death!
P-President!
This is no ordinary bandage. I poured energy into it for many years.
It will not come off easily!
This is a bit problematic.
But you chose the wrong demons to mess with!
Issei!
Yes, ma'am!
Use that!
Oh right!
Got it, President!
Let's go, Boosted Gear!
Explosion!
Wh-What are you trying to do?
Koneko-chan, forgive me!
Dress...
Break.
What a sight!
I'm saving all your nudes to my neural HDD!
I'm so thankful!
No looking.
Are you all right, Issei-san?
Wh-What a truly wonderful technique!
You impressed me, demon boy!
Lawless one who attempts to do vulgar things to demon ladies.
Your crime warrants nothing but death.
In the name of Duke Gremory,
I'll blast you away.
W-Wait!
Oh my.
I know you've just awakened from a long slumber,
but we'll have to punish you for misbehaving!
Damn you!
Perish!
So in the end, I guess it's fine to live and work as we have been?
Demons live for a long time,
so you can take your time to think about it.
Right!
Yeah, Asia?
Yep!
Lord, please watch over me so that I'll become a fine demon!
President?
We received a request to investigate a coffin recovered from some ancient Chinese ruins this time.
Could it be another perverted sorcerer?!
Could you ask another high-class demon to take care of it?
The last one was so not worth the trouble.
I'm not taking any more fishy requests.
That'll be for the best.
Really? You're getting another demon to do it?!
As perverted as always.
I know. I'm sorry.
I-Issei-san.
Oh my.
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Boobiliciously Premiering July 2013!
'Sup? I'm Hyoudou Issei!
Driven by friendships, burning passions, and plenty of carnal desires,
the romantic school comedy battle fantasy, will be back for another season, wilder and crazier than ever!
Episode one, "An Ominous Feeling, Once Again!"
Episode 1 "An Ominous Feeling, Once Again!"
Let's boobs!