Here ya go!
Dragon Shot!
Issei-kun!
You guys okay?!
We understand the situation.
Onii-sama, please look after Gasper.
All right.
Here comes another wave.
We've just gotta hold them off till the gate closes, right?
Boost!
The only one who can create a
defensive barrier that powerful is Rias.
It's my fault...
President!
I...
President Rias!
Issei-senpai!
I...
I... want to be a man like you, Senpai.
I want to live up to your expectations, President.
So...
I'm...
I'm going to fight for my friends!
Stop that!
Onii-sama, please stop Gasper!
Onii-sama!
I am... I am...
a man!
Gasper!
My puny arrogance came back to me
Takaga shireteta terai ga uzumaite
and I couldn't go to you for help
Oisugaru koto mo dekizu ni ita yo
I couldn't tell you why I was crying
Namida no wake kimi ni ienai mama de
and always frowned up to the sky
Kuchibiru wa itsumo sora wo nirande ita
You dug through the darkness to cross this line
Uzumoreteta yami yori kimi ga koete kita kyoukaisen
The world's out of changes to make
Sekai system wa kakumeigire
Pleasure, pain, destruction, creation
Kaikan itami hakai souzou
I'm going to change my own weaknesses
Kaete yuku watashi no yowasa wo
All I can make are appeals to emotion
Ima oshiyoseru kanjouron
Love's not easy with my life on the line
Inochi gake no ai wa amakunaiwa
Stronger, even stronger
Tsuyoku motto tsuyoku
No matter what lies I face
Donna uso ga matteita to shitemo
I've already chosen which signs to follow
Eranda michibiki shinjite
The devil smiles at me, telling me to be myself
Furumau koto wa nai to yasashii akuma no hohoemi wa
and shines a faint light on the world
Hakanaku subete wo terasu no
Clash of the Twin Sky Dragons!
Final Episode
My, my.
What happened?
I do not know.
Sona-chan, welcome back!
O-Onee-sama?!
Did Gasper regain control of his powers and dispel his magic?
The enemy's gate has been disabled, too.
That's one less thing to worry about, then.
You did it!
Way to go, Gasper!
What's going on?
There's no time to explain now.
I need you all to lend me your strength!
Yes, President!
Lightning!
Tsubaki!
Yes, Chairwoman!
Now, then...
Let's quit playing around, shall we?
What is that?!
Something much more fun than war: my hobby.
This is the Downfall Dragon Spear,
an artificial Sacred Gear I made myself.
Balance...
Break.
What's that?!
Armor of the Fallen Dragon:
Downfall Dragon, Another Armor.
Dragon Armor...
A Balance Breaker?!
Come on, bring it.
Damn you!
A new world is coming,
and it has no place for you!
If it means I can slaughter the leader of one of the three great factions,
I don't mind throwing my life away!
Going to self-destruct?
Doesn't look like fun.
This is a small price to pay!
An arm...
is all you're worth.
I guess there's still some room for improvement.
Stick with me a little longer,
Dragon King, Fafnir.
His own arm...
He's insane!
Anyway, we just need to mop up the rest.
All right!
Ascalon!
Blade!
All done, huh?
What the...
Ow...
I must be getting old.
Vali?
Forgive me, Azazel.
This side seemed more interesting.
Vali!
So you were the one who betrayed us?!
Hey, Vali.
I want to ask you something.
Shemhaza, my Governor,
noticed that rebels from the three great factions were banding together.
The "Khaos Brigade," was it?
Khaos Brigade?
A group of rebels?!
There aren't many who can
control a bunch of guys like that...
And their leader is
the Uroboros Dragon, Ophis.
Ophis?!
It can't be!
A Dragon?
The Dragon God of Infinity.
Feared by even God himself, he's the greatest Dragon of all.
Indeed, I am working with Ophis,
but neither of us want to rule the world.
Some idiots came after us for our power.
That explains a thing or two.
I thought you'd gotten all
buddy-buddy with Cattleya...
because neither of you could become a Satan.
Neither of you?!
What do you mean?
My name is Vali Lucifer.
What?!
Lucifer?!
He can't be!
I am a descendant of a previous Satan.
Sired by the son of a pure-blooded Satan,
and birthed by a human woman,
I'm a half-Devil.
No...
It can't be!
A half-Devil...
No wonder we had not heard of you.
Even though he shares blood with a Satan,
his human half allowed him to host the Vanishing Dragon.
It's hard to believe you even exist.
Perhaps I epitomize the word "miracle."
Those wings...
O Lord...
Of all the hosts of the Emperor of White Dragon,
past, present, and future,
this man is, without a doubt, going to be the most powerful.
The most powerful...
Hyoudou Issei.
Fate is a cruel thing, is it not?
What?
With the power of a Satan and a Dragon,
I am the mightiest being of all.
Meanwhile, you are a mere human.
Until you were reborn as a Devil, you were
nothing more than an average high school boy.
That is to say, without your
Boosted Gear, you are nothing.
So pitiful...
So laughably pitiful!
Our Sacred Gears are fated enemies,
and yet our abilities are worlds apart.
Too many worlds apart...
What of it?!
I know!
How does this sound?
You devote yourself to revenge...
after I kill your parents.
If a man like me were to kill your parents,
you ought to be willing to face your fate.
I'm sure it will be a much more exciting end for your parents
than letting their lives slowly peter out.
It's brilliant!
That's too cruel!
Issei...
I'm gonna kill this asshole.
Issei!
What have my parents' lives got to do...
with your goddamn ego?!
Welsh Dragon, Overbooster!
You will never kill my parents, you son of a bitch!
A Balance Breaker?!
Look, Albion.
Hyoudou Issei's power just grew exponentially.
A Sacred Gear's strength comes from its wielder's will.
He's consumed with blind rage against you.
Rage, of all feelings,
is the most effective in powering a Dragon.
If that's the case,
he's a more suitable host for a Dragon than I.
Shut your damn mouth already!
Ascalon!
Blade!
A Dragon Slayer...
Even a single hit will cause severe damage.
Then all I have to do is dodge.
Issei!
Let go of me, Onii-sama!
Their auras have exceeded your limits.
You'll burn to death if you approach them.
But...
I can't just watch them.
So weak...
Too weak...
Divide.
My power...
I almost forgot.
That guy absorbs the power from anyone he touches.
Issei!
I'm all right, President!
Don't worry about me!
Issei-senpai, don't lose!
Yeah...
President is watching.
I'm gonna win!
Boost!
I see.
What the hell?!
He's discarding the power he can't contain through his wings.
That allows him to maintain maximum power.
Even the strongest hosts have their limits, huh?
I just remembered.
You fought Kokabiel to protect your friends.
Should I kill your friends before I do your parents?!
Asia!
Over here!
Fucker!
I've had enough of your shit, asshole!
Hate me! Loathe me!
Use your strength to entertain me,
Hyoudou Issei!
Issei!
Ddraig!
Transfer our power to the Ascalon!
Transfer!
Gotcha!
He's transferring power to Vali?!
I'll enhance your absorption and emission
and put an excessive load on your system!
So much that your wings will give in!
We're going into overdrive. It's best we back off and regain our footing.
Take the power of the Dragon Slayer!
Impressive...
You blew my Sacred Gear apart.
Not bad at all.
You truly are my rival.
That's crazy...
Are you serious?
It's not over until the host can no longer stand.
That's how we fight.
What's wrong?
That armlet's time is almost up.
My weakness is holding me back again?!
We can't let time be the limiting factor.
Running's your only option!
I can't run away and leave everyone behind!
Ddraig,
you told me that a Sacred Gear can
evolve to satisfy its wielder's will, right?
Interesting.
Are you willing to die for it, though?
I don't want to die.
I haven't taken President's virginity yet!
But... I'll take all the pain for it!
That's my boy.
I'll do whatever you want!
I am the the manifestation of pure power, the Emperor of Red Dragon!
Let's make it through this alive, partner!
Ready, Hyoudou Issei?!
Yeah!
What are you up to now?
Vanishing Dragon, Vali!
I'll be taking your power!
Issei!
Wh-What's happening?
It hurts! It hurts!
Those spears of light are nothing compared to this!
You're trying to absorb my power?
Kiba was able to put the holy and the demonic together!
So I'm going to take your power of annihilation
and give it to my Sacred Gear!
How foolish.
We are polar opposites.
That is only going to kill you.
Albion, if there's anything I learned from this host,
it's that if a fool is foolish enough,
he'll achieve the impossible!
Call me a fool!
If I don't have any other talent,
I might as well be the greatest fool of all!
Evolve to my will!
Vanishing Dragon, Power is Taken!
I guess you could call it the Dividing Gear!
Impossible...
That's impossible!
You just slashed a huge chunk off your lifespan,
even though, as a Devil, you practically had eternal life.
I don't need to live that long!
There're plenty of things I still need to do, though.
Vali, I've got your power now!
You-
Most intriguing.
It's time that I showed you my true power!
Half Dimension!
What the hell is he doing?!
He is bending space.
He is extremely dangerous!
He's mad!
The hosts of Dragons...
are always mad in some way or another.
It's worth trying to use that.
Let's poke at what the other one's mad about.
Hey, Emperor of Red Dragon,
Hyoudou Issei.
What do you want?
I'll give you a simple explanation of his ability.
That ability halves everything around it.
It halves things?
Which means...
it's going to halve Rias Gremory's bust as well.
What?!
Her boobs...
will be halved?
It's going to halve the size of President's boobs?
Her boobs...
Her glorious boobs...
My precious...
boobs!
You son of a bitch!
Boost!
You're gonna halve my President's boobs?!
What?
Never!
Boost!
You're never...
getting away from me alive!
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
Look out!
You can't be serious, kid.
A million times stronger over your master's tits...
Boost!
Today's just full of surprises.
This is so incredibly entertaining!
You do anything to Rias Gremory...
and I'll kill you so hard you'll never be reborn again, Vali!
How is he so fast?!
If you keep doing this, you won't just halve my President's boobs.
You're going to halve everyone's boobs!
This is for...
my President's boobs!
Divide!
This is for...
Akeno-san's boobs!
Asia's still developing boobs!
For Xenovia's boobs!
And this is for...
the boobs that'll cease to
exist at all if you halve them...
Koneko-chan's loli tits!
So entertaining...
Most entertaining!
He can still stand?
He deserves to see the Juggernaut Drive.
Don't get carried away, Vali.
It is not wise to do that here.
I, who is about to awaken,
You...
Boost!
envy the "infinite" and pursue the "dream."
I shall become the White Dragon of Domination.
Vali! Do you intend to be consumed by my power?!
Bikou?
What brings you here?
They want you back 'cuz we're
gonna fight the Aesir up north.
I see. It's already time for that?
Who the hell are you?!
Where'd you come from?!
He's a descendant of the Victorious Fighting Buddha.
Who?
Simply put,
he's Son Goku, the famous
monkey from "Journey to the West".
Son Goku?!
I didn't expect you to be part of the Khaos Brigade.
This is real crazy.
Well, the White Dragon and Son Goku...
kind of work as a duo.
I ain't like the first one!
I do whatever I want!
Nice to meet'cha, Emperor of Red Dragon.
Our next battle shall be even fiercer...
and us, even stronger.
You're not getting away!
You used a huge amount of power in very little time.
It's hardly surprising.
Issei!
Are you all right?
President...
I didn't let him... take your boobs.
Oh...
Issei...
Devils, Angels, and Fallen Angels are all working together.
We've finally created peace in this world.
We are responsible for Cattleya's actions.
Sorry about the stuff Vali did.
It's my fault for not stopping
him before he got out of hand.
This is just the beginning.
Excuse me, Michael-san.
May I...
May I ask you to do something for me?
If it is within my abilities.
Could you please allow Asia and Xenovia to pray once again?
Asia, Xenovia...
Yes, sir?
Please tell me this.
God does not exist anymore.
Will you still pray nonetheless?
Yes.
Even with the Lord gone, I would still like to pray.
As would I.
I would like to pray so I may thank you and the Lord.
I, too, would like to ask this of you, Michael-sama.
Irina...
I blindly believed that you were a traitor.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to apologize for.
Asia-san...
I spoke harshly to you, too.
D-Don't worry, it's okay.
I'm really sorry!
No!
I-It's completely fine!
Friendship between Devils and adherents of the church, huh?
Michael-dono, I believe this is a
symbol of the peace between us.
Yes.
It wouldn't hurt to have two Devils who can pray without pain.
What a merciful heart!
Thank you, Lord.
Lord.
I will have to make some changes to the System back at headquarters.
I've decided to stick around here for a while longer.
Huh?
I told you.
I'm going to repay you with something only I can do.
What does that mean?
I'm tired.
Let's go home.
Nobody was hurt were they?
Everybody is fine, don't worry.
I'm glad.
Gasper...
I apologise,
this all happened because of me.
I failed to protect Gya-kun properly.
It's not your fault, Koneko-chan.
Gya-kun...
Koneko, you did a great job.
Gasper...
you also did your best today.
I am so proud of you.
I also...
am proud of you.
President Rias, Koneko-chan...
Sona-chan...
I have come to like this academy.
Is- Is that so?
✩I think I will become a teacher here.✩
Y-You can't.
Huh? No?!
U-Uh, err...
Hey Tsubaki-chan, I can teach in this school, right?
Uh... err... yes.
Tsubaki !
No, I mean...
It is up to the Student Council Chairwoman.
Eh?!
Michael-sama...
Hmm?
About my earlier request,
I wanted to thank you.
You helped save the day,
granting your request is the least I can do.
Ah, well...
I see now. It isn't the power of the Dragon,
but he himself that President and Asia have fallen for.
I will now return to Heaven and spread the word of peace...
and prepare for those who oppose it... Farewell.
Issei-san.
Wha- Oh there you are, Asia?
Issei-san....
I love you.
H-Hey... Asia!
My, my,
Asia-chan is getting bolder.
Hmm... That seems to be an important factor...
Important?
Hyoudou Issei,
for their strength.
Oh, Xenovia...
Xenovia, now you can pray once more.
That...
Huh?
Uh... No...
Thank you...
Well tomorrow we'll continue with club activities.
Yes, President!
So, there you have it.
Starting today,
I will be the Occult Research Club's
official adviser.
What in the world is going on?
I asked Sirzechs about it,
and he told me to talk to Serafall's little sister.
Her?
If I didn't, my sister threatened-
Er, begged to come here.
You basically sold us out, didn't you?
I wish you the best of luck.
Hey, Sona!
Uh...
Where'd that arm come from?
This?
I made it while I was researching Sacred Gears. It's an multi-purpose arm.
I've always wanted to use one of these things.
But in exchange for letting me stay at this academy,
Sirzechs gave me one condition.
A condition?
To properly train your underdeveloped Sacred Gears.
The Boosted Gear, with unfathomable potential,
a Holy Demonic Sword,
Forbidden Balor View...
I'll apply what I've learned in my research to bring each of you to your full potential.
What do you want to do?
churuchuchu doushitai
Hey, girls
churuchu hey girls
chu
Hey, girls
ru
chu
hey
Listen up!
girls
Lovely devils
raburi debiru
ra
girls
bu
ri
You're gonna call me "Azazel-sensei" from now on.
girls
ri
de
bi
ru
You know what we wanna do! Yes!
churuchuchu aa shitai yes
chu
ru
You know what we wanna do! Yes!
chu
ru
aa
shi
"Azazel-sensei?"
ta
i
They've descended upon us again
yes
kyou mo kourin
They've descended upon us again
kyou
mo
kou
yes
rin
That just feels wrong.
yes
rin
Girls are always greedy for more
shoujo wa shinkakei ni yokubari na no desu
Well, that's about it.
ke
i
ni
Best of luck to all of us.
yo
ku
Best of luck?!
I want this, I want that
are mo kore mo
I haven't approved of-
Oh, right.
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
kinou to kuraberun ja manzoku dekinai
ki
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
Sirzechs had a message for you.
He did?!
ki
na
i
Uh-oh
arere
a
Uh-oh
i
a
re
When he stayed at the Emperor of Red Dragon's house,
i
re
Let's have a strategy meeting on how to upgrade
appugureedo sakusen kaigi
a
Let's have a strategy meeting on how to upgrade
he realized how important it was for a master to be close to their family.
gi
Agreed!
sansei
san
sei
I'm sure you have at least one of these
daredemo hitotsu kurai motte iru desho
da
I'm sure you have at least one of these
re
Especially you, Emperor of Red Dragon.
Your power depends on it, after all.
You too, and you too
kimi mo kimi mo
ki
sho
mi
mo
Uh, I'm not following.
Original magic words that protect your heart
orijinaru no jumon kokoro no omamori
o
Original magic words that protect your heart
This is an order from Satan Sirzechs Lucifer!
Uh-huh
aruru
a
ri
ru
Positive thoughts that give you strength
purasu shikou taishitsu kyouka
pu
Positive thoughts that give you strength
ru
pu
ra
su
All the women of the Occult Research Club
are to live with Hyoudou Issei!
Never compromising our love or dream
koi mo yume mo totteoki wo ne te ni ireru tame ni
ko
Never compromising our love or dream
That's it.
te
o
ki
What?!
Huh?!
ki
wo
ne
Issei-kun,
te
ni
i
re
Akeno is here now, by your side!
ru
ta
me
ni
Everyone
minna
mi
Everyone
We want to follow our heart
fiiringu juushi de
A-Akeno-san!
de
na
risaachi
de
Research
ri
saa
de
As we grow up
seichou shitai na
I suppose I should stay in Asia's room.
ta
i
na
You see, girls are lovely devils
onna no ko wa ne raburi debiru
o
You see, girls are lovely devils
Hello.
Issei-senpai.
ra
Yes?
bu
ri
de
If you peek into my room or steal my underwear,
bi
ru
Deep down in their hearts, so treat them with great care
mune no naka kakushiteru no toriatsukai youchuui
mu
Deep down in their hearts, so treat them with great care
ne
no
na
ka
I'll kill you.
P-President...
W-Well, they are my brother's orders. What can we do?
u
i
They're only interested in having fun
tanoshii koto shika kyoumi nai no yo
ta
They're only interested in having fun
All right.
Their whimsical temper makes them cute
wagamama ni kawaiku narun da
wa
ga
ma
ni
We'll ask my brother
to expand this house!
ru
n
What?!
da
Promise!
yakusoku
ya
Promise!
ku
so
White seeks power,
and Red seeks women.
Both simple
and straightforward.
A-Akeno...
Even without God,
the world keeps on spinning.