Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
We aren't needed in
outer space Heero!!
We mustn't fight each other.
Relena...
The Locus of Victory and Defeat
That's right.
I still don't know where
Heero has gone.
Please don't laugh, Father.
Because I can still hear
Heero's voice even now.
Father.
I believe he'll come here
to the Sanc Kingdom.
I wonder how much time
has passed...
...since we met.
It was during my shuttle
flight with you...
...on our way back to Earth.
Father, what is that?
That was when I first came
across the shooting star...
...Heero Yuy, who carried
the colonies' hopes.
One more to go.
This is where everything
started.
My code name: Heero Yuy.
I was given one mission.
To destroy OZ.
He's still just a young boy.
Did you see?
See what?
They're down there!
Hurry!
Hey, who are you?
What?
My name is...
My name is Relena Darlian.
What's yours?
Until then, I enjoyed
a world of happiness.
Ignorant of the world and
giving nothing to society.
But meeting him greatly
changed my destiny.
Hey, that's him!
I'm Heero Yuy.
It's a pleasure.
I'm sure that's him.
Here you go.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
I hope you'll be able to
make it to the party.
Why?
I'll kill you.
I wasn't the only Gundam pilot
that landed on Earth...
...as part of Operation Meteor.
There was also Trowa Barton,
pilot of the Gundam Heavyarms.
Quatre Raberba Winner,
pilot of the Gundam Sandrock.
This isn't right.
No.
You and I shouldn't be fighting!
Put your hands down.
I was the first one to surrender
and come out, remember.
Stop! Stop or I'll shoot!
He's just a young kid!
A kid did all that damage to
the base by himself? :!
Hm? A woman...
Now it makes sense.
Wu Fei Chang, pilot of
the Shenlong Gundam.
Where's this light coming from?!
It's the enemy!
And Duo Maxwell, pilot of
the Gundam Deathscythe.
Heero, what are you doing?
Tell me!
Who are you anyway?
Those are torpedoes, right?
I can tell!
I want to know who you are.
Talk to me, Heero!
Relena...
Heero...
You're in too deep.
It's pretty obvious that
you're the bad guy here.
Are you all right, lady?
Huh?
Heero! Are you okay?!
Don't overdo it; remember,
you're injured.
Stop it!
Why do you wanna
shoot him?!
What in the world is that?
Don't look.
Lady, I'm sure you have your
reasons for being here...
...but you'd better just leave.
Do yourself a favor.
Haven't had enough?!
I don't consider the other
Gundam pilots my comrades.
I never had any comrades
from the start.
Just like Relena, this guy
who calls himself Duo...
...is merely an obstacle
to my mission.
Finally, everything is finished.
Mission complete.
Father, that was when you
strongly wished for peace...
...between Earth and
the colonies.
We've heard everything
you have to say.
I'd like you to leave the room
now, Vice Foreign Minister.
Isn't it about time you
people realized...
...that you're posing the
greatest threat of all!
And Father, you flew with
me to space once more.
That turned out to be
your last gift of kindness.
To show me just how
beautiful the Earth was.
Father!
What're you doing
with my father?!
Relena...
Father...
I'm not your biological
father.
Your real name is
Relena Peacecraft.
You're the daughter of
the Peacecraft family...
...who once advocated
Total Pacifism.
That's not true!
Watch out for the
OZ organization.
Father...
Father!!
NO!!!
Delete files on Heero Yuy
at the Saint Gabriel Institute.
Transfer procedures complete.
Are you off to fight again?!
Where's your next mission?
I'd come across too many
of his secrets.
But the fact that Heero
was a Gundam pilot...
...sent from the colonies...
...might have influenced
my personal situation...
...in regards to how I was
going to live out my life.
Heero, I know too much.
You still gonna kill me?
Yeah.
Before, I didn't want to die
without any answers.
But now it's different.
Now I know how you
feel when you fight.
And I'm now fighting with you.
With me?
What am I thinking?!
I'd be better off if she died!
Why?!
Heero!!
Don't run away.
Please Heero.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Marshal Noventa...
...Chief Commander of the
United Earth Sphere Alliance...
...pushed for peace
with the colonies...
...and planned a significant
reduction in armaments.
But the Commander in Chief
of OZ, Treize Khushrenada...
...shrewdly released some
information...
...to lure the Gundams to
the New Edwards Base.
And tricked them into killing
the Alliance Military leaders.
Don't be rash now, young man!
The second act has just begun.
We'll be getting busy.
Operation Daybreak...
This scrupulously planned
coup d'etat allowed OZ...
...with soldiers assigned at
Alliance Military Bases...
...under the guise of
Specials soldiers...
...to overthrow the Alliance
in just one day.
This is a revolution.
Just see for yourself.
The era of the Alliance
has ended!
Our OZ organization must
give rise to a true alliance!
In addition, Colonel Une
proposed a plan...
...to transfer Taurus space
suits to the Siberia Base.
But this was also a deceptive
operation...
...to annihilate the Gundams.
You think the other
Gundams will come?
We can't win by ourselves.
But I'm positive the others
will come.
What speed!
We'll fight for recognition
of superiority.
I'm sure that'll suit you!
You ARE a Gundam pilot.
Who would've guessed
Gundams had this much power.
Get Space Fortress Barge
on line!
Calling all Gundam pilots.
We're ready to stage an all-out
missile attack on the colonies!
I demand all pilots to
surrender at once...
...and hand over your Gundams!
They've targeted the colonies!
Hand over our Gundams?!
Sounds like OZ's tricks.
You guys can't fight, can you?!
Attention OZ.
I never imagined you people
could be so foolish.
To you, inhumane moves like
colony assaults are justified...
...if that's what it takes for
you to come out victorious.
I have no choice but
to surrender.
But I will not hand over
the Gundams. I repeat.
I surrender, but I will not
hand over the Gundams.
Mission accepted.
Off to fight again, Heero?
Well, I'm headed for
my own battleground.
The Romefeller Foundation
sought to maintain peace...
...by dominating others.
That may be possible as long
as they keep winning battles.
But as Relena Peacecraft,
leader of Sanc Kingdom...
...I can't allow them to reign
at the cost of many lives.
I was defeated.
Because the colonies were
being used as a shield.
But Zechs repaired
my Gundam...
...hoping to end our
unfinished battle in Siberia.
The battle took place
in Antarctica.
I refused to accept charity
from Zechs...
...and challenged him in
Trowa's Gundam Heavyarms.
But this battle was meaningless.
Between a man looking
for something to protect...
...and a man who had lost
all means to protect.
A mistaken past is difficult
for anyone to swallow.
But we're still young.
We should be thinking
of building the future.
Heero.
I wanted to end this
meaningless fight.
Has it begun?!
That's more like it!
This'll finish you off!
Heero!
Stop this battle immediately!
See for yourself how dirty
and foul battles really are!
No...
If you're a true warrior
and a Peacecraft knight...
...you couldn't possibly
use such foul play!
Relena, call from
Lieutenant Noin.
Miss Noin!
I misunderstood you.
I thought you were sincere.
Precisely.
I deserve your contempt,
but I can't help myself.
I believe in Colonel Zechs!
I'm not about to interrupt
any of his plans.
Heero!
Defeat Zechs!
Stop it! Relena!
But Relena, no matter what tricks
of fate you have been through...
...please don't wish for
your brother's death!
Brother...he's my brother?
I learned then for
the first time...
...that Zechs was my brother.
Numerous carriers approaching
from 3 o'clock!
They're here!
Do you read me, Heero
and Zechs?
Thirty suits in flight.
A hundred if they unload
all Aries suits.
I'll attract them away!
Glory to the colonies!!
Heero!
We'll meet again!
Zechs!!
Next time I fight him...
...will he be Zechs Merquise
or Milliardo Peacecraft?
In any case, I'll defeat him
if he's in my way.
If he's an enemy, I'll kill him.
I haven't seen Heero
or my brother since then.
Now, with OZ splitting
into two factions...
...and continuing their
foolish battle...
...the world is headed
even further toward chaos.
But I have confidence.
You'll come back to me, Heero.
To end this war.
Heero!
I'm waiting for you to
hurry and return to me!
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
As long as mankind
exists in this world...
...there will always be battles.
And denouncing battles
will never lead to peace.
Treize Khushrenada has
disappeared...
...from the center stage
of history.
But while destinies slip
past one another...
...Treize begins to proceed
with new plans.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 28,
Passing Destinies
"Passing Destinies".