Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
With high hopes, humans
leave Earth...
...to begin a new life in
the space colonies.
But the United Earth Sphere
Alliance gains military power...
...and in the name of
Justice and Peace...
...seizes control of one
colony after the other.
The year is After Colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
To counter the Alliance's
tyranny, rebel colonists...
...bring new arsenals
to the Earth...
...disguising them as
shooting stars.
But the Alliance headquarters
catches on to this operation.
Relena.
It's pretty obvious that
you're the bad guy here.
Are you all right, lady?
Five Gundams Confirmed
We've been forced
into a stalemate.
There wasn't much
we could do about it...
...considering we don't
know their objectives.
But if we must act, the
Mediterranean Sea's best.
That's where the old Leo
manufacturing base is.
The Alliance appears to be
thinking of added security.
We shouldn't discourage them.
I figured the Aries Middle East
troops would be appropriate.
Their ability to handle mobile
suit combat is quite low.
So they probably shouldn't
join the Alliance Military.
Want to go?
Huh?
It's written all over your face.
Shoot them down for me, Zechs.
So even OZ's latest mobile suit...
...the Cancer, was defeated.
That suit's pretty advanced.
It's a shame.
Is that wounded enemy's new
model that dangerous sir?
We've lost five good men.
Our loss is significant.
So what are our next steps,
Lieutenant?
Confirm where the five
suits are...
...and find out their objectives.
We'll leave this search to
the Alliance's Marina.
Yes, sir!
The enemy's no longer
in the ocean.
They've gone far beyond
what we predicted.
They've succeeded in a mission
we deemed impossible.
Respiration 27, pulse 57,
temperature 34 degrees Celsius.
They're all rising.
What?
Nothing...
Just thought I saw
a fluctuation.
Continue recording his data.
I've been captured.
This is the treatment room
on the 50th floor...
...of the Alliance Military No. 3
medical building...
...in the South J.A.P. Area.
Major Sally, there's a call
in for you.
The disk you gave me...
It has high level encryption.
I can't use any access code.
That kid had the disk on him.
So even the Alliance's mother
computer can't decode it?
Think he's an intelligence
member of the rebels?
It's too early to say.
He's in excellent physical
condition.
He has over 200 bruises
and broken bones...
...but his only visible injuries
are the shot wounds.
It's obvious he's not just
any ordinary kid.
Should we use truth serum?
Absolutely not!
Careless drug use will
poison someone his age.
Yeah, that'll do.
Also both of the pull carts
are broken...
...so have my lunch ready
at the back of the wheat field.
I'll help you thresh
the wheat later.
Now, I should go visit
that patient!
It's traveling as if it knows
we're locked onto its position.
It's the one spotted at
the Yangtze River.
It's slow...
Judging from its speed, flying
probably isn't its specialty.
There are different types
of these fighting units?
Yes.
Maybe we'll see one of them...
...at the Corsica Base
in the Mediterranean.
And even destroy
it then and there.
The one at the Yangtze River...
...won't show up at the
ceremonies at Corsica Base.
It headed for the Alliance
offensive.
It's not as bad as long as
we can see it.
At this rate, the Indus Supply
Base will be attacked.
Pray they fight well.
That's all we can do.
They're just so defenseless.
They're not taking
me seriously enough.
No visitors allowed?
Are his injuries that serious?
Oh, you're the one that
brought him here.
Wait here for one moment.
I'm Major Sally.
Could you tell me about
that cute man you brought in?
Cute man?
No changes.
You've got no choice
but to lie there.
I'm sure a talented guy
like you can read my lips.
Well, can you?
Your acting is just amazing.
You've regained consciousness
without increasing your pulse...
...or your brain waves.
I've got a few questions
I'd like to ask you.
If you're up to it,
I'll help you break out.
I'm very interested in
that young man.
He has a wild look about him
but I sense an inner strength.
He's seems like just your
average young guy to me.
What's your name?
My name's Relena Darlian.
Darlian?
Related to the Vice
Foreign Minister?
I'm his disobedient daughter.
Forgive me if I said
something to upset you.
No, don't worry about it.
Can I go see Heero now?
Heero?
Is that his name?
Yeah!
I'm a close friend
and classmate.
Any changes?
Nothing to report, Major Sally.
Heero!
What do you have him
tied down for?!
Let him go!
We're unsure of him.
He's much too strong for us.
That's why we've got him
tied down in restraints.
We have some questions
we want to ask him...
...then we can unbuckle him.
He's not in the Alliance
Military?
Let's go downstairs.
What?!
Time to liven things up!
Hurry?
Damn!
How do you get these off?
Your knife.
I'll cut the middle.
What happened to your hand?
You've got guts!
- You all right?
- Yes.
This way!
Hey!
Hurry, release your parachute!
Do you wanna kill yourself?!
Crap.
I'll have nightmares over this!
They must've jumped from here!
Heero!
No, Heero!
It's too late!
Heero!
He's alive.
Incredible.
I hope he's not our enemy.
I shouldn't have released
my parachute!
I understand your wanting
to kill yourself...
...but if you can't do it
from that height...
...then think of another way.
I'm not asking you to
trust me or anything...
...but I'm the only
friend you've got.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Next we bring you the latest
news from the military.
Mass production of Leo
mobile suits...
...at the Corsica Mobile
Suits Factory...
...will resume at full capacity
and without further problems.
The factory experienced delays
after a mysterious explosion.
To continue the inquiry
and for safety precautions...
...Specials from the Middle
East will oversee the factory.
Lieutenant Zechs should
be there by now.
I'll be back in two hours.
I managed to make it
on time for the ceremony.
Commander Bonaparte, it'd be
too risky to go in this!
You fool!
It's the best way to make
our intentions known...
...to the enemy and the Specials.
We don't need the Specials
to help us!
They'll use this situation
to show themselves off.
The Special Mobile Suit Troops,
known as the Specials...
...advanced in the United Earth
Sphere Alliance Military...
Young leaders were trying
to start a new trend.
Colonel Treize Khushrenada.
The aristocratic founder
of the Specials and...
...an official in the mysterious
Romefeller Foundation...
...financially backed by
royalty and aristocrats.
With this strong backing...
...Treize focuses on the
development of mobile suits.
The Specials unit supplies
mobile suits to the Alliance...
...and starts instructing
the combat army corps.
Their reputation on the
battlefield is excellent...
...earning them the right to
act independently anytime...
...and at any battle they wish.
But there is no denying
that this special status...
...angers the elder soldiers
even more.
The men confuse the battlefield
for an aristocratic game.
They want to kill so badly
they're stirring things up.
We mustn't be persuaded.
If we proceed cautiously,
we'll avoid unnecessary battle.
I'll teach those bloodthirsty
Specials about smart battle.
So Commander Bonaparte
isn't here?
I'm sorry, Lieutenant!
I heard that he dislikes me...
My apologies!
Don't worry about it.
I can't really blame him.
Lieutenant Zechs!
Officer Walker, it's been a while.
You haven't changed,
Lieutenant.
Got a machine for me?
I wanna show you something
to do with that.
This is huge!
It's one of the original
mobile suit models...
...and it's larger than the Leo.
It's outdated, but when I saw
the data on Gundam...
...I thought of this unit; it's
seen as a historic artifact.
You're from Corsica.
I used to work there.
Only this machine can
compare to the Gundam data.
I wasn't told how this
was made, but we know...
...that it'd have to be this
big to maintain its power.
It was too big...
...so the current mobile suit
size became standardized.
Tallgeese.
I think that's what it's called.
This unit could fight the
Gundam if it were completed?
Take it from this factory.
Counting on dying, Walker?
You taught me this...
..."to fight for the soldiers
of tomorrow."
And I've lived by that advice.
You're a braver soldier, Walker.
How many Gundams?
I expect the maximum,
as you taught me to do.
There are four.
One isn't headed here.
Sorry Walker; that's
all I know.
I'd be grateful if we
eliminated one, Lieutenant.
Please don't, Commander
Bonaparte!
No enemies are coming!
They ARE.
They are coming?
No one would challenge
this security!
They will.
Specials, we'll attack at once.
Assemble!
Only one unit's here, sir!
It doesn't matter!
One's enough!
Descend! Descend at once!
Calm down!
There's only one enemy unit.
Surround and destroy it!
It's not on the radar.
I'll check the monitor...
enemy confirmed!
Can't rely on equipment!
Strategically, when annihilating
a small number of enemies...
...it's best to block retreat
and shower them with bullets.
The commander's decision
to surround and destroy...
...the enemy was correct.
He shouldn't have acted
without knowing my potential.
How could we have made
such a huge miscalculation?!
Assist retreat of the
Commander's vessel!
The rest, attack the enemy.
Sir!
What?!
Given the enemy's strength,
we won't make it out alive.
Give instructions to the Stats
Department of the factory...
For the soldiers of the future!
I'm sorry!
Attack up close and
stay focused!
Roger!
The aircraft's ready;
you can leave any time.
And Commander Bonaparte?
We received word of his safety.
Lieutenant Zechs, I'm going
there too, with the Leo.
Otto, I wish you wouldn't
make this harder for me.
Sir?
I'm about to convince myself
to protect the Tallgeese.
Please, I need your help.
Sir!
He's out of bullets!
We did it!
Stay on guard!
I'll show you what the
Specials are made of!
Fool!
We can't afford a mistake!
That was pretty fast.
Surprise, surprise.
Come get me, monster!
I wanted to find out
this thing's limits.
Sorry...
I'm going.
Master Quatre!
I don't need any help.
Seems he's already used
up all of his bullets.
That pilot isn't relying
on any firearms.
No! There goes an OZ aircraft!
This isn't right.
No.
You and I shouldn't be fighting!
Put your hands down.
I was the first to surrender
and come out, remember.
There! I pulled up yours too!
You could at least show
a little gratitude.
What are you doing now?
I can't take this.
He goes and puts a broken
bone back into place.
That grosses me out,
just thinking about it.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Duo and Heero depart for
another battleground.
Meantime, Wu Fei heads for the
Lake Victoria Base in Africa.
At the base are OZ's advanced
Taurus space mobile suits...
...as well as Ms. Noin, an
instructor of top pilots.
There, Noin experiences
a nightmarish incident.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 4,
The Victoria Nightmare
"The Victoria Nightmare".