Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Heero!
Defeat Zechs!
Go ahead!
Kill him!
Stop it! Relena!
Brother...he's my brother?
Glory to the colonies!!
Betrayed by Home, Far Away
Nothing from the command tower!
We'd better leave!
- Hurry!
- Yes, sir!
Enemy approaching!
Fire!!
The United Earth Sphere
Alliance had posted...
...their own Space Forces to the
colonies and strictly controlled...
...the colony citizens' freedom.
After the collapse of the Alliance,
the Space Forces had remained...
...to control the colonies.
But the Forces were
overpowered...
...by the mobility of Taurus,
OZ's space suits from Siberia...
...and their powers were
diminishing.
Soldiers of the Alliance,
stop this futile resistance!
Our OZ organization has come
to bring peace to outer space.
Now, let us welcome
a new age together.
Taurus Mobile Doll
troops all fine.
Or rather, everything's
in perfect form.
Oh?
Then return the unmanned
Tauruses back to Barge.
What about security?
The colonists consider
mobile suits their enemies.
I'll have a private meeting
with them later on today.
Over.
Cancel orders for mobile dolls.
Return to Barge.
Mobile dolls are unmanned
battle weapons, huh?
So OZ is starting a war
for the sheer fun of it.
Today, in the year
After Colony 195...
...the citizens of outer space
deserve to live freely.
However, to date, the United
Earth Sphere Alliance...
...has oppressed you.
The days of the Alliance
are now over.
A new order is being
created on Earth.
And it shall be the same
here in space.
You people are free.
OZ supports you all.
That concludes the message
from the OZ Military.
Or rather the OZ peace-support
organization.
I'd like to discuss this matter
at our next scheduled meeting.
OZ says they're in no hurry
for our response.
On that note, I hereby adjourn
the Area D Colony Conference.
Thank you.
Oh, not at all.
I'm thanking you on my own.
But in the future, the whole
colony will be thanking OZ.
You're very young for a leader.
Couldn't you interpret youth
as potential?
We third generation
colonists...
...know OZ and the Alliance
differ, unlike our elders.
But OZ was part of the
Alliance at one point.
It'll take some time before
the people can understand.
Troops of the former Alliance
Military are still scattered...
...throughout the colonies.
Excuse me, I must leave
to liberate the next colony.
Pardon me, but I didn't
catch your name...
Oh yes, that's right.
I'm responsible for OZ's
outer space supervision.
Lady Une is my name.
Forces of the former Alliance
Military unjustly stationed...
...in the colonies have been
forced to surrender.
With the new and powerful
OZ mobile suits...
...operations have commenced
for removal of space mines.
This'll mean communication
is re-established...
...between the colonies.
I thought OZ wanted to
take over the colonies...
...no matter what it took
for them to do it.
They do.
And they're using the dirtiest
method.
If OZ used force, the colonies
would prepare to retaliate.
But they'd be accepted if they
used the guise of assistance.
Most people in outer space
are easy going.
I doubt if anyone will
question OZ's plans.
I think it's time for us
to return to space.
With our Gundams.
The Gundams were built for
the people of the colonies.
Only we can save the
people from OZ's evil plot.
You're right.
But how do we get into space?
It's important that we
don't get noticed.
No, we WANT to get noticed!
If OZ is falsely promoting
peace to get at the colonies...
...then they can't threaten
the colonies to get to us.
But what if OZ gives up
their facade?
That'd mean revealing their
identity to the colony people.
The present OZ wouldn't
see that as wise.
So we can still fight them!
Let's return to space!
I'm very impressed with OZ.
All Alliance Military troops in
this area have surrendered.
Are they trying to atone for
Heero Yuy's assassination?
That remark's unfair.
Rumors that OZ was behind
the assassination are unfounded.
That's what OZ would
have us think!
Honorary Advisor!
Why are you here?!
I came because I heard you were
ready to accept OZ's agreement!
These days OZ wants peace.
They're not to be trusted,
neither in the past nor now.
At the very least we know
Colonel Une is trustworthy!
She's executed many aggressive
and bloody plans in the past.
Those are rumors!
She's been overlooking the
situation and taking on...
...the dangerous task of
removing space mines!
It's because they want to
conquer outer space, isn't it?
They're currently working for
the well-being of the colonies!
In any case, OZ is reaching out
to us in the name of Peace!
It's not in our interest
to reject them!
Our policies focus on our
friendship with Earth!
I think we should welcome OZ!
This is truly most annoying.
Entering the space mine area.
I'm sending the mobile dolls
ahead.
Approaching space mines.
This is Nichol.
We're finished with Area P0314.
Cleaning up outer space has
become so much easier.
Colonel Une!
In 13087 of Colony D...
...we've found a Gundam
manufacturing factory...
...and arrested an engineer!
Well done.
I'm returning to the
command tower!
Is this the engineer?
So, I finally get to meet
the commander.
He was trying to destroy...
...an underground military
equipment factory...
...for manufacturing suits.
Destroying evidence?
Yes; unfortunately he'd
destroyed it already.
Were you the one who
built the Gundams?!
What a stupid way to
ask a question!
Just answer my question!
I think you're heavily involved
with those five Gundams!
Nope.
Not with the other four.
What do you mean?
I designed the best Gundam
I possibly could.
Why would I make four
other variations of it?
Are you saying you only
made one of those Gundams?
Yeah!
A masterpiece I called the
"Gundam Deathscythe".
The others are a coincidence.
The Alliance prohibited travel
and communication...
...between the colonies.
I made only one Gundam.
So it was a coincidence?
A coincidence that the others
were made at the same time?
Transmission from Earth,
Colonel Une!
Gundams Zero Two and Zero Four are attacking
the Singapore Space Port Base!
What?!
I figured they'd come home.
This new OZ base isn't
like their others!!
I can't get any closer!
Let's go for the HLV ready
for mobile suit delivery!
Quatre!!
Don't overdo it, Quatre!
It's okay.
We have to fight so the other
pilots will figure it out!
They'll see us battling like
this and realize...
...that they need to go
to outer space.
That outer space is waiting
for us!
To outer space!
All of us, together!
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
So those are the Gundams.
They're attacking OZ's base
on Earth.
The Alliance Military
oppressed the colonies...
...and OZ was once
part of the Alliance.
I can understand a certain
colony's feelings...
...wanting to retaliate against
Earth.
Yes, but even as we speak,
our peaceful ways...
...are changing opinions
within the OZ organization.
We can't continue to run
around with weapons.
Those Gundams are fighting
because they truly believe...
...they protect the colonies.
So?
They're a nuisance to
the colonies.
We must show OZ our
intentions...
...before the Gundams make
them uneasy.
The Gundams love the colonies.
The Gundams have chosen
to fight...
...because they love
the colonies.
Those Gundams are desperate.
They're facing their enemies
with limited power.
So why can't we support
the Gundams?
Let's see...
Good.
We made it into the news
around the world!
What's this?!
We wish to publicly
announce a decision...
...made by Space Colony
Area D.
Mobile suits known as
Gundams are currently...
...destroying OZ's facilities.
These Gundams have nothing
to do with Colony Area D.
We declare that if the Gundams
consider OZ an enemy...
...then we'll consider
the Gundams ours!
OZ has been fair to us.
OZ and we have worked out
our misunderstandings.
We hope that the Gundams
are defeated in this battle.
We further hope that
other colonies will follow...
...our example set with
this declaration.
I expected this.
But even so, it's still
hard to swallow!
It's all right, Duo.
We came down to Earth
all alone.
It's okay if the colonies don't
understand right away.
I'm just happy the others are
fighting for the same cause.
That's enough.
Quatre!!
Come on Sandrock, stand up!
It's too early to be defeated!
Damn it!
At this rate, we're not
gonna make it.
I still think what we're
doing is a good thing.
So why do we have to
die in a place like this?!
Because we're doing
the right thing!
We are right!
It's that guy!
The ones who are right
have to be strong!
If this is your limit,
then so be it.
The rest of us will take
over from here.
The rest of you will
take over?!
That's more like it!
You'd have a hard time
explaining to your comrades...
...if you were defeated now!
They figured out we need help!
They all understood our message.
My mission's to wipe out OZ.
If they're headed for outer
space, then I'll follow.
It's gonna be a difficult battle.
But right now I sense peace
in our 5 hearts.
Is that the colony where the
fifth engineer's holding out?
The other four hardly
put up a fight.
But there's a stubborn one
who's trying to resist.
Colonel.
There's a factory in an outermost
block of the colony...
...but access has been
completely shut off.
You've advised him to surrender?
He's ignored all communication.
Then there's only one answer.
Open fire on him!
Colonel!
Heat detected from the colony!
Spread out front-line troops!!
Two manned suits are down!
The mobile dolls are unharmed
because of their quick response!
Taurus mobile doll unit, prepare
to fire special beam cannons!!
The beam cannons
are too strong!
They'd crush the colony
if they hit it directly!
Nichol, since when has OZ
tiptoed its way through battles?
We're not trying to establish
diplomatic relations.
We're trying to fight a war.
Damage to the colony
wouldn't be our fault.
It'd be the fault of the rebel
holding out against us!
I'm delighted to hear that
OZ is still so mean spirited.
In that case, I'll happily
surrender to you!
Good; I accept your surrender.
Come out at once!
I'm certain that one day the
colonies will recognize...
...the dark side of OZ!
But I won't let the Gundams'
battle go to waste!
Hurry up, Quatre!
A Gundam 's operating the mobile
suit delivery HLV spacecraft!
Surround it!
Those suits will try to shoot us
down when we start to lift off.
Hurry, Quatre!
Don't worry about me.
I'll back you two up
until you lift off!
Have you lost your mind?!
We all have to make it
to outer space!
I know, but that's why I
have to back you up.
To make sure that at least
you two make it!
Quatre!!
I can't take this much longer!
I'm grateful.
The only way to show
my appreciation...
...is to make it safely
into space.
You fool!!
And now, the last remaining
choice is to self-detonate.
What's this?
You're telling me to get off?
Sandrock!
Thank you, my dear Sandrock!
Get in there!
Hi!
What took you?
Why didn't you guys
put up more of a fight?!
There were just too many
other things to do.
Well, anyway...
It's been fifteen years.
I'm amazed that all five of us
completed our Gundams.
Shall we have a public trial?
No, there are other ways
we can use them.
After all, they're the engineers
who built those Gundams.
Excuse me Colonel!
Five shuttles with Gundam pilots
have launched for space!
Prepare to fire low-orbit
satellite missiles!
Problems in the electric
power generator.
We've got a system jam!
Communication's down, and
the radar's malfunctioning!
What in the world could
be causing all this?
Hey OZ.
You're gonna seriously regret
that you kept us alive.
Not to mention the pilots.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The battle between the
Tallgeese and Gundam...
...concluded one chapter
of the war.
However, a cruel destiny
still awaited the pilots.
Mortally wounded, Quatre
calls on the other pilots.
Zechs refuses to fight as
a knight of Romefeller.
But Treize then demands
that Zechs die a hero.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 18,
Tallgeese Destroyed
"Tallgeese Destroyed".