I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Right? I told you so.
Let's go again sometime.
Sure.
- Hey.
- Who the hell are you?!
Sorry, Miss.
This probably isn't a very
amusing place for a woman.
No bother. But I do rather
dislike noisy places.
The Kousa clan is on the move.
Here, in Roppongi, we don't
stand out like a sore thumb.
Our neutralization of enemy targets
is proceeding according to plan.
But the Kousa clan is
a very large outfit.
We need to go further to squeeze them.
We move on to phase two
and institute a shift.
- A shift?
- Yes, we shift gears.
First we clamp down on
their income sources...
...retailers, entertainment venues,
waste management.
Those guys aren't amateurs.
If we keep this up, they're bound
to notice what we're doing.
This is just to rattle their cage,
of course.
Our main target is something else.
What do you mean?
We will resort to a tactic
that works in every nation.
Abduction. An abduction, Mr. Bando.
We'll target the family of the
Kousa clan head, Masami Kousa.
B-Boss!
I hate to dampen the mood,
but that's the one thing you can't do.
- What was that?
- He said, "We can't do that".
What we are looking for is a fight where
the Kousa clan loosens their grip.
After you make a ruckus for a while,
we can then lure them in with talk.
Don't go overboard and make
things difficult for us later on.
Did you hear that, Sergeant?
They don't get it at all.
Rock, translate this carefully, okay?
Mr. Bando.
We will employ any means
necessary to secure profits.
We are taking on most of the risks here.
Therefore, the decision-making
belongs to us, not you.
W-Wait a minute.
Oh, it's you, Rumi.
I told you not to call me at
this time of day. Huh? Prada?
I don't want any. I've got enough
to sell. You talk too much.
Watch it or I'll take two of your teeth
out later. Huh? Then get false teeth.
- I gotta go.
- Chaka! What the hell are you doing?!
Don't you realize what we're
talking about here, you idiot?!
Oh, sorry about that. That stupid bitch.
- Get outta here!
- Yeah, sure. I'll go.
Yoshida, let it go.
I apologize for making a scene.
Martin Heidegger's
"Holzwege"
Oh, Yukio, you're still here.
Hi, Maki. Oh, my. Look at the time.
What are you reading now, Yukio?
This? Martin Heidegger.
It's philosophical,
but very powerful. I like it.
I'll pass on it. I like skincare
guides and modern horror books.
You did say you like Anne Rice.
What do you like for light reading, Yukio?
Let's see. Umm...
Never mind. It's all right.
Forget that I asked.
What you were just thinking about
probably wasn't light reading at all.
You think so? I like any book that
makes me feel like I'm out in the sea.
Swallowing knowledge and
emotion and everything else.
Endlessly expanding,
yet somewhat different from reality.
- I think that's what I like.
- I see.
I can't get into reading the
difficult ones. How about King?
I don't care for scary novels.
Really? That's a bit surprising.
I would've thought you like Poe.
I don't like the ones that
make you imagine the night.
So dark and lonely and sorrowful.
I don't like the night.
I get really scared, thinking
I'll be sucked into this darkness.
It's not romantic. Not at all.
- I hear we've got trouble.
- They're waiting for you.
- Target 012 confirmed.
- 012 confirmed.
Can't I have a little more time
before you go ahead with that?
Of course I'll wait, so long as it
does not interfere with the operation.
So that we can raise a toast
to each other.
Hey, Mr. Taka. What's with that girl?
You idiot! Haven't you
learned your lesson yet?
It's not what you think.
She's that skinny interpreter's
body guard. From Roanapur.
What? She's a woman and
she can fight?! Are you serious?!
Chaka, you idiot!
Cut it out! They're guests!
Yeah.
I know, Mr. Taka. But you'd like to
see what she can do, wouldn't you?
Can't we go home yet?
It's time for socializing now.
- What a waste of time.
- Don't complain, Revy.
It's a way to keep things
moving smoothly.
If it takes care of things without
incident, then it's a small price to pay.
I don't understand it.
It'd be faster to make them drink...
...cresol cocktails.
Oh, there she is.
So, I hear you're a gunman.
I don't speak no stinking Japanese.
Speak English.
Oh, right. How's this, then?
This is my place.
Can't run a place like this
without speaking English.
Hey cutie. You from Roanapur, right?
Rumor says that place
has more bad ass motherfuckers...
...than a supermax prison.
Hey. Have you ever shot anyone?
I've shot about ten guys.
Romeo. Can I tell you one thing?
Your breath stinks, dimwit.
I can smell it over your cologne.
Your insides are rotten.
Revy. Revy, let's go.
Miss Balalaika is waiting. Come on.
Hey, Mr. Interpreter. Can't you tell?
We're talking. Please don't barge in.
Revy. Go on ahead.
Go back and get Mr. Bando or...
Hey! Who do you think you are?!
Don't you ignore me. When I snap,
I have trouble controlling myself.
Hey! You listening?! Hey!
Hey, lady. He's getting beat up
pretty bad. Not very cool, is it?
Why not give me a try? You can't be
satisfied being with a weakling like this.
Well?! Bastard!
Say something!
What the hell are you doing, Chaka?!
What is this?!
This is not the time or place for this!
We were just playing around.
Come on, Mr. Yoshida.
I'm terribly sorry.
I'll have a talk with him later.
An incompetent officer and
a soldier who ignores orders.
I can hardly stand it, Sergeant.
It would have been better
if it were a battlefield.
They'd be killed off
in battle and discarded.
Sorry, Rock.
He had his hand on his gun
the whole time.
He wasn't after me.
He wanted you to draw.
You're beginning to develop a soul of
diamond. You're absolutely right, Rock.
I may need my Cutlass, after all.
- Hey, Revy!
- I don't plan on starting anything.
But at some point,
that guy will turn his gun on us.
He is a pea brain who can't
tell his ass from his head.
Let's accept his challenge.
We'll just wait until then, Rock.
When that time comes,
I'll kill him, for sure.
Boss.
Would you please pass
me the miso?
Sure. We don't have enough power
to shut the Kousa clan up.
It was a good plan, despite the
Peacekeeping Council's decision.
I thought money would take care of
matters instead of reasoning with them.
But because of those Russians...
- Boss, the sweetened sake, please.
- Here you go.
Honestly, this isn't good.
Is there anything else
you need, Benny?
Thanks a lot. You're a great help.
I prefer not to go through
the black market in Bangkok.
Oh yeah, Revy wanted something.
She wants you to send
her Sword Cutlass.
A troubling request, I must say.
- Is a storm brewing?
- I don't know yet.
But I sure hope not.
- So do I. I'll take care of it.
- Thanks.
Due to difficulties
caused by the snow...
...trains in both directions
aren't running.
This isn't good. I guess I'll get a cab.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
- You're from...
- ...the other day...
Yeah, it's been a while
since I experienced the cold.
Well, with you being
from a subtropical zone.
Have you gone home yet, Mr. Okajima?
Home? Well...
To be honest,
I don't really wanna go home.
Mr. Okajima, you're like the old me.
I used to hate my home.
But I realized it's the place to return to.
I have a family that raised me.
You have your head on straight
for someone your age.
My friends say I'm like an old lady.
Ah, no, that's not what I mean!
I'm kidding.
I don't have anything like that.
I feel like I'm just hanging in between.
I feel too attached to just discard it, but
I don't have the resolution to go forward.
A certain Frenchman said
that people are like dice.
You throw yourself in the
direction of your choice.
People are free because they
have the ability to do that.
Everyone's circumstances are different,
but no matter how small the choice...
...at the very least,
you can throw yourself.
It's not chance or fate.
It's the result of the choice you make.
What do you think?
You can be pretty harsh.
Excuse me for a moment.
Yes, this is Yukio.
Oh, it's you, Gin. I know.
You worry too much.
Yes. I'm out of the snow...
...with Mr. Okajima.
You know, the person
we met at the festival.
- Miss.
- Yes? What is it?
Today...
What? Mr. Bando's there?
Then I'd better hurry home.
Yes. I understand.
I'm sorry, Mr. Okajima. I've gotta go.
- Yukio. Um...
- Yes?
Well... I hadn't asked yet
what your last name is.
Right. It's Washimine.
Sounds pretty solemn, doesn't it?
I'm against this.
This has nothing to do with the Miss.
Imagine if the Peacekeeping
Council heard about this.
Not only would they not
allow us to rebuild our clan...
...they'd kick us out of the region.
- Miss!
- You were already home.
I apologize for not noticing.
Mr. Bando. About what you
were just talking about...
Well then, Miss...
As soon as the old man passed on...
...they immediately came to us
about not having a boss.
They said they'd accept
anyone of direct relation.
Idiots, they knew very well
what that would mean.
- Then...
- That's right. A direct relation.
You, Miss, are the only one.
Those dirty bastards.
And they'll slowly come
to strangle us with it.
- Yoshida?
- Boss! Is it you, Boss? I...
I got a tail behind me.
And it's not anyone local.
Boss!
They're from higher up.
When I get the chance...
...I'll lose them and head to a hideout.
Boss! The Russians aren't
holding back!
They blew up a car in front of a
police station when a man from Kousa...
...tried to turn himself in!
Yeah.
What are those
evil bastards thinking? I...
- I hear you. I'll contact you again.
- Boss!
Prepare for some trouble, and clean up.
Anything from the Washimine clan?
- Nothing yet.
- This is a waste of time.
Earlier, at 0600 hours...
... a detective approached the
Washimine office for information.
It's only a matter of time
until we're discovered.
Tell the main unit to move
to the Maria Zeleska.
Yes, ma'am.
What should we tell Laptev?
There's no need to tell him anything.
Um, Miss Balalaika.
What is it?
Well, um... what if the Washimine
clan abandons the agreement?
Rock!
Does it concern you in any way?
No.
That's right. Don't misinterpret
your position in this.
Hey, Sis. You're not being too nice.
It's not really a secret...
so why not tell him?
You're certainly taking his side,
Two-Hands. Silence is golden.
That's true, but Rock's on our side, right?
Trusting each other is important, too.
You've become a much
better talker, I see.
All right, fine. Let's suppose they
did something stupid like that.
Then, we'd have one more name
to add to our target list.
Our job won't change and
the world will continue the same.
It's as simple as that.
Yuki!
I'm sorry. We'll stay late
with you to help next time.
- Goodbye.
- Don't worry about it.
Take it easy at work.
So, Yukio, my last finals
were really bad...
...and Mom made a big fuss about
wanting me to quit my job.
Gin. I am involved in this.
I was raised in this house.
I am the daughter of Ryuzo Washimine.
And she would keep
nagging me to quit my job...
About that guy, Okajima.
He is involved in this matter.
On the Russian's side.
Yukio! Yukio!
Come on.
Are you listening to me at all?
- Oh, sorry.
- Really.
This is a big concern for me.
You know, Maki...
What is it?
No. Never mind. On second thought,
discussing it isn't gonna help.
Come on, don't leave me
hanging like that!
Boss!
Oh, it's you, Yoshida.
I'm just out for a walk.
There's nothing interesting about it.
Bro! You're off to meet
the Russians, aren't you?!
It's been a long time
since you called me Bro.
B-Bro! I'll go too!
Yoshida. Take this.
Ask Gin about what to do next. You may
not like him, but he's a good man.
Bro!
Well then, goodbye.
Or something like that.
- When did this happen?
- This morning.
There was a suitcase sitting in front of
our office. Those god damned Russians!
Yoshida, no matter who did it,
it would've ended this way.
We had to do something about Kousa.
The boss was just too smart
for his own good. That's all.
- What do we do now?!
- Dark and lonely.
The snowy night sky.
Stop right there! You lowlife!
Rock!
I want you to translate
this in strong, blunt Japanese.
B-But...
Tonight I'll tell you about the truth.
What I seek is destruction
and domination.
I don't have any interest in
anything else.
I'm only interested in how much
I can dance in the pit of Hell.
See you eventually.
Hey! Hey, Rock! Are you all right?!
- You're sweating like crazy.
- Was I asleep?
You were breathing like
an old Buick engine.
- It's not good to drink so heavily.
- Yeah.
It's about to get wild.
We're moving.
Moving?
The Visotoniki are splitting
up into two groups...
...the cargo ship and the
Russian Embassy.
So this is really gonna be war.
Sure it is. Hotel Moscow is serious.
A storm is coming, Rock.
A storm of steel and blood.
You're planning on going,
aren't you, Gin?
If only I walk a path in the sun...
...you'll all end up
wandering in darkness.
Miss. You mustn't.
I can't run from this.
Now, I feel the night
inside of you, Gin.
There's body warmth.
Very sorrowful, but therefore not cold.
Miss. I...
I wanted you to walk
the path of a human...
...and get hold of honest happiness.
To this day, I have lived
for that reason only.
Kousa's rats and the Russian villains.
They're all trying to ruin us!
We will do what we can,
even if it's on our own.
If they will accept me on
equal terms, then it shall be me.
Hey, Ginji.
The snowy night is beautiful.
This is the first time I ever thought that.
Ginji.
Will you protect me, Ginji?
Though unworthy, I am Ginji Matsuzaki,
lieutenant of the Washimine Clan.
Allow me to protect you
with all seven of my incarnations!
People are just like dice.
Man is, before all else, something which propels itself
towards a future and is aware that it is doing so.
We throw ourselves into our lives.
Next Episode
Gin. This is your first job.
Please work cautiously.
Let's take care of this quickly.