I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Sorry, Miss.
This probably isn't a very
amusing place for a woman.
The Kousa clan is on the move.
Here, in Roppongi, we don't
stand out like a sore thumb.
A shift?
Those guys aren't amateurs.
If we keep this up, they're bound
to notice what we're doing.
What do you mean?
B-Boss!
I hate to dampen the mood,
but that's the one thing you can't do.
What we are looking for is a fight where
the Kousa clan loosens their grip.
Just make a ruckus for a while.
W-Wait a minute.
I apologize for making a scene.
Martin Heidegger's
"Holzwege"
Can't I have a little more time
before you go ahead with that?
Man is, before all else, something which propels itself
towards a future and is aware that it is doing so.
Next Episode