Your dream is where my heart belongs.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
It's more fragile than a life.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Now, sleep in peace.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
My pulsing urges
myakuutsu shoudou ni
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
trample upon my wishes.
negai wa okasare
As often as I sadly forget,
wasureteshimau hodo
I remember once again.
mata omoidasu yo
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
nani wo mamoru no darou
when a reason ceases to exist.
mou risei nado nai naraba