Every epoch dreams its successor.
Jules Michelet
Producers
Masao Maruyama Iwao Yamaki
Based on the Comic by
Osamu Tezuka
Screenplay by
Katsuhiro Otomo
Character Design/Animation Supervisor
Yasuhiro Nakura
CG/Art Director
Shuichi Hirata
CG Technical Director
Tsuneo Maeda
Music
Toshiyuki Honda
Directed by
Rintaro
At this moment our state extends
its reach to the stars!
I tremble at the honour
of announcing...
...the culmination of humanity's
long history of intellect and science.
Our power spans the earth.
Now it will illuminate the stars!
May it stand forever! Our Ziggurat!
Those robots are getting big ideas.
They don't know their place!
But our economy is unthinkable
without robot labour.
Yes, but they cause friction
with human workers.
The enemy is developing new weapons.
What Metropolis needs is a leader
who will be a powerful symbol!
Duke Red, with the Ziggurat complete,
will you be entering politics?
Don't be silly!
As long as President Boone governs,
our state is secure.
Politics has no need of me.
Mr. President, would you like
to see Duke Red in politics?
Don't encourage him! How could I
compete with anyone so popular?
Is it true there are military
facilities in the Ziggurat?
Would the mayor care to comment?
Ask Minister of State Skunk about that.
Hurray for the Ziggurat!
Long live Metropolis!
Uncle Shunsaku,
what does ''Ziggurat'' mean?
Who knows?
-Hey! Look up there!
-What's that?
Malduk! It's the Malduks!
There he is!
You said she'd be ready tonight,
Dr. Laughton.
Er, well....
What is the meaning of this?
I've given you the best facilities...
...money can buy!
If you could wait a little longer,
I'm almost done.
I'm tired of hearing that.
I'll be at your lab tomorrow night.
But it's not the kind of place
you'd go to!
And the place is a mess!
Get back to work!
-It's me.
-I hear there was trouble, Rock.
Yes. A robot agitator in the plaza.
You were supposed
to have that under control!
Yes, Father.
Fool! I am not your father!
I merely found you during
the last war and took you in.
Yes, sir.
I'm Shunsaku Ban,
a private investigator from Japan.
I have a letter of introduction
to Superintendent Notarlin.
I see.
So you're saying this Dr. Laughton...
...is hiding out...
...here in Metropolis?
Yes. This is a reliable tip from
an organ smuggler he dealt with.
The International Human Rights
Committee and other organizations...
...have warrants for him...
...for vivisection experiments
and dealing in human organs.
To which end
I ask for your cooperation...
...seeing I've never been in this city
and I don't know east from west here.
I'd like to help, but with
the celebrations for the Ziggurat...
...going on all week...
...it's taking every single person
I have to keep things under control.
I don't have anybody.
Well, I could give you a robot
if that's okay with you.
A robot?!
Yes. He's very good.
He's not authorized to
arrest people...
...but he can certainly assist you
in your investigation.
Do I have to return him
with a full tank?
He only needs refueling
every five years.
Soon they won't need us anymore.
I'm Kenichi. How do you do?
I am Model 803-D-RP-DM...
...497-3-C.
Uh, how do you do?
The completion of the Ziggurat...
... establishes our Metropolis
as the world leader...
... in industry, economics and culture.
Thus is born a state that
will last a thousand years!
I tremble at the honour
of announcing...
... the culmination of humanity's
long history of intellect and science.
Our power spans the earth.
Now it will illuminate the stars!
May it stand forever! Our Ziggurat!
Well, where do we start,
uh, 803, uh....
D-RP-DM497-3-C.
Don't you have an easier name?
We are not allowed human names,
as it may infringe...
...upon human rights.
I know! As of now, your name is Pero.
That's a dog's name!
That's right. I used to have a dog
named Pero. He was a great dog.
In my opinion,
a criminal could not hide...
...up here in Metropolis.
I have reliable sources
that say he's here!
Dr. Laughton would not hide up here.
He would go to Zone 1.
-Zone 1 ?
-Underground.
Hey! You are a detective!
It is simply a calculation
of probabilities.
Robots are strictly forbidden...
...to operate outside
their assigned area.
That robot was not authorized
to operate at surface level.
Okay, but who are those guys?
They look like fascists.
The Malduk Party, vigilantes
who started as a political group.
Movement between levels is restricted.
No one who carries the mark
may pass through this gate.
So that robot had the mark?
Yes. Each block has a gate like this.
There are, of course, hidden ways
and people who work as guides to them.
Damn right! The system's wrong!
It takes light
to create shadow, I guess.
This level is not
particularly dangerous...
...but there are places in which
police writ does not run. Avoid them.
We can't do that.
We're not here as tourists.
Duke Red.
Let's see it.
Very good. Isn't she finished?
Her final-stage energy processor
isn't stable yet.
Are you using real organs?
Dear me, no! That's illegal!
Real organs are quicker,
but they don't last very long.
Hers are mechanical. I made them.
She will be my masterpiece!
When will you finish?
Within the week.
If I start her too early...
...she'll build up too much energy,
catch fire and explode.
My Tima....
I'm not giving you to anyone!
I'll put on the finishing touches...
...and together we will flee!
Rock? What are you doing here?
Protecting my father is
my most important task.
Father? But Duke Red has no children.
And the child who died was a girl.
Quiet! I know what you're up to.
No mad scientist is going
to deceive my father.
And no mannequin like this
will steal his heart.
Stop!
It is at Duke Red's request
that I've made Tima.
Tima is the super-being
who is to sit...
...on the Throne of Power
atop the Ziggurat.
You lie! He would never give
the Ziggurat to a robot!
Perhaps you should ask
Duke Red about that.
Will you destroy the super-being for
whom the one you call Father waits?
No robot will steal my father!
No! Don't!
O, ye Gods, give me courage...
...and strength to guard
my father from machines!
Fire! Fire!
A Malduk set that fire!
I saw him!
The ones up there want to kill us!
Atlas is right!
They think we're nothing but garbage!
To arms! Now we have to fight!
Please remain calm. Fire-fighting
operations are commencing.
Everyone please step back.
Robots out!
First you take our jobs,
and now you're trying to kill us!
This is no time to be fighting!
What the--?!
But why did he set fire
to that old factory?
Well, that strange old man was around.
An old man? This one?
-Yes.
-Thanks a lot!
There's someone in there!
Oh, no. Kenichi, go round the back.
Hurry!
-Come on, Laughton!
-Notebook....
That notebook?
Laughton!
Laughton's lab burned down?!
I guess he was doing an experiment.
The fire just ripped right through it.
-What happened to him?
-His body was found.
Whatever he was doing...
...considering there are warrants
for his arrest...
...it must have been
something dangerous.
What's wrong, Father?
What did Dr. Laughton mean to you?
Get out! Leave me alone.
Where am I?
That was sure some fire!
Well, it was just an old factory.
Saves the trouble of tearing it down.
This is strange. She was
the most advanced robot there is.
There should be something left.
-Pero, who's that?
-Rock of the Malduks.
He's young,
but he's one of their main men.
They say he does
Duke Red's dirty work.
Duke Red?
ls he connected with the Malduks?
He's the party founder.
Now there's no official connection,
but he funds their activities.
It's a public secret.
Everyone knows.
Where does this sewer come out?
It merges up ahead
with the sewage from Zone 2...
...and goes to
the processing plant in Zone 3.
If she's down there, she'll have
been chopped up with the garbage.
Anyone else, yes.
The criminal always returns
to the scene.
An old saying, but a good one.
We should continue searching
for Kenichi.
Who are you?
No, no, no. You call yourself "I".
"I" am who?
-"I" am....
-You are I.
No, listen.
You are "I". I am "you" ....
Huh?
I am who.
Yeah, that's right.
And I'm Kenichi. Kenichi.
-Kenichi.
-Yeah.
Anyway, it'll all come to you
after a while.
Your name, your family,
your father, your mother.
Family...father....
Uh, thanks, I guess.
I know this is food,
but it's all rotten.
Food....
Yeah. You put it in your mouth
like this and eat it.
No, don't eat that!
It'll make you sick!
No, don't eat. Make you sick.
Attention Control. Cloud cover 1.1.
Clear to proceed with experiment.
Magnetic bias 3.7.
Continuing line adjustment.
Commencing cooling. Opening dome.
40 seconds to radiation.
39, 38....
Motor, cooling, sensor
and operating systems, all go.
Control authorization. We are go.
Energy condensers confirmed
at Level 3, plus-33.
Roger.
Observation Group to Control.
Transmitting footage from city.
Commencing final preparations.
Magnetic target: bias 0.25.
Optical target: bias 1.06.
Radiation equipment in position.
We'll radiate for three minutes.
Citizens won't be affected,
but aboveground robots will.
I'm having everything recorded.
The data will be valuable.
Begin at Level 3.
Yes, doctor.
Commencing radiation!
Terminate Level-3 radiation
at 180 seconds.
Solar constant deviation at minus 24.
Five seconds to Sector R.
4...3...2...1.
Omotanium fusion!
Omotanium confirmed
in Fraunhofer phase.
35,000...40,000...45,000.
Sunspot field density,
800 and rising.
Ionospheric disturbance.
Communications disrupted.
Level-3 radiation terminated.
Control disengaged.
Success!
This will set
the whole world on its ear!
You now hold the power
of the gods themselves.
If only Dr. Laughton had finished
building our guardian deity....
He's caused anomalies in sunspots...
...and bathed Earth
in harmful magnetic radiation.
It's an outrage that he would
endanger national security...
...by developing such a thing!
The Malduk robot hunters are
using this as an excuse...
...to cry "human rights" and press
for changes in the Robot Law.
The pro-robot citizens' groups...
...say that's reactionary nonsense.
They're organizing protests.
There's fighting breaking out.
This is our chance, Mr. President!
We could make a case for treason here.
Will the military support us?
Some units are under Duke Red's
influence, but I can handle that.
We'll stir up the public
with a few leaks.
Once sentiment is against Duke Red,
we'll arrest him for treason.
Should military action be needed,
you have...
...my approval.
I suspect he was the guy
who did in Laughton.
What I don't understand is
how they were connected.
Just what was Laughton
working on, anyway?
What will you do?
Laughton's already dead.
I want, at least, to know why.
My client deserves that.
-Where's he going now?
-Zone 2, I think.
There's another level below this?
How far down does this place go?
Zone 2 is the Metropolis
power plant area.
Zone 3 below that is
the sewage-handling facility.
The sewage facility.
You know, he was looking
at a drain behind that factory.
I'll report back
and get permission to go below.
I'll file a missing persons report
on Kenichi too.
-Hey! You're old for a petty thief!
-Sorry!
If anyone was wandering
around down there...
...they'd notice him right away.
How often are you down here?
Twice a week,
for maintenance on the robots.
These are Albert ll types.
It's their last check this week.
Is anyone here?
You never get used to
the stink down here, though.
No human could last a day
at this work.
-What is it?
-Someone's there.
Impossible!
Hey! What are you doing there?!
This is a restricted area!
So she survived.
Help!
-What are you doing?!
-It's all right. They're criminals.
How do we get out of here?
Stop that, please!
You'll hit the equipment!
Are you okay?
That guy's trying to kill us!
Move! Move! Out of the way!
You piece of junk!
Move!
Is it safe?
It looks okay.
What's wrong?
Oh, I get it.
Fifi can't go through that gate.
Thanks for everything, Fifi.
We'll see you again.
Move!
It's him!
Fifi!
No weapons through here.
May I see your I.D.?
I'm Rock of the Malduks!
Demonstrations are forbidden
during Celebration Week.
Please disperse immediately.
Kenichi?
-Kenichi!
-Hey!
Pay up!
-They're not here!
-They have to be! Keep looking!
Look over that way!
What's the matter, Atlas?
We're waiting for your signal!
Not today. There are Malduks
all over the place.
-Was there a leak?
-They're the reason.
Rock's after them. Come on!
He was at that factory.
Who are you?
Where did you come from?
I'm Kenichi. I'm from Japan.
My uncle's a private....
-A private what?
-A journalist! I'm his assistant.
Why is Rock after you?
I don't know.
He just started shooting at us.
I don't trust them. Let's kill them.
Cool it! We're not a gang.
He says he's a journalist.
If he can tell the world
about Metropolis, that helps us!
We can't waste time on nice uniforms
and our pictures in the paper.
The uniform I die in...
...will be the uniform
of the revolution!
Look at that!
-She looks like an angel!
-Yeah.
An angel.
Around here there's two
or three families to a room.
There are no schools
and hardly any jobs.
They survive on food handouts,
but with the Ziggurat celebrations...
...that's all been stopped.
What does "Ziggurat" mean?
It's an ancient Babylonian tower.
The Tower of Babel was one.
You know what happened to that.
The king's pride brought down
the wrath of God on him.
History repeats itself.
The same thing will happen to Duke Red.
But it won't be God this time.
It'll be us.
Is that wrong?
No, it's fine.
I was just thinking your hair's grown.
What kind of hair do you like?
Yours is fine right now.
Let's get back to your writing.
Next comes....
-Tima.
-What?
Tima. My name.
So you remember!
That's great! Now you'll start
remembering more and more.
Thank you, Kenichi.
Oh, I forgot.
I borrowed this from Atlas.
Kenichi?
So the army's with us?
That helps a lot.
The underground residents
support us...
...but they're not sure
if we've got the strength to win.
The Malduks are to move
when the Ziggurat celebrations end.
We want you to crush them
and storm the Ziggurat.
The president will announce
the arrest of Duke Red for treason.
He will invoke his powers...
...to take control of
the police and military.
Then Metropolis will be governed
by the rule of law.
And we will participate as
a proper political party.
Of course, Atlas. The president
will welcome you with open arms.
The things I get myself into!
I finally find that kid
and look what happens!
I'm sorry I could not have been
of more assistance.
What are you talking about?
You've been lots of help!
I don't know east from west here.
Don't worry about Kenichi.
He's tougher than he--
Cut that out!
Just look at this, will you?
"Watch out. Hide, robots.
Coup d'état."
What?! A coup d'état?
Oh, man!
Take a good look, Kenichi.
Tell the whole world how angry we are.
I'm all out of breath!
We'd better get out of here, Pero.
We can't do anything.
Ask headquarters for backup.
I'm not leaving you here!
It's robots they're going
to attack first!
-I will be fine.
-What?
It is also my duty to ensure the
safety of all visitors to our city.
All right. Just don't stir
anything up till I get back!
Are you going to hold this gate
all by yourself?
Demonstrations are forbidden during
Celebration Week. Please disperse.
Sorry, we can't do that.
Our time has come.
Why must humanity settle matters
by resorting to violence?
Yes, we all know that.
I agree it is a problem.
It's our emotions.
They vibrate, and all we can do...
...is move forward
within that amplitude.
But without affirming them,
we can't survive.
It's time for the uprising to begin.
When should we release a statement?
Things should be clear
by about 1 p.m...
...so I suggest 3 or 3:30.
What is it, minister?
Hard to relax, eh?
Yes, Mr. President.
I have an unpleasant duty to perform.
What the--?!
You've gone over to Duke Red!
I am merely history's agent.
Wait! We can discuss this!
Why?
Why do humans just go
and destroy robots?
Revolution.
The coup d'état has failed.
Martial law is in effect,
under the command of Duke Red.
Abandon your weapons and surrender.
I repeat,
the coup d'état has failed.
Martial law is in effect,
under the command of Duke Red.
Abandon your weapons and surrender.
Kenichi!
Hey! Kenichi!
Uncle!
You're safe! That's great!
-Are you all right?
-This? It's nothing!
Who's this?
Her name's Tima.
We escaped from that fire together.
Tima, this is my uncle.
Uncle.
Atlas!
It was a trap!
We meet at last.
Don't move!
No trouble.
Give me the girl,
and you might get back home alive.
Don't make promises
you won't keep, Rock!
Don't play games with me!
Tima, pick up the gun!
I'll have that back, please.
Don't give it to him!
You going to shoot?
I'm human, you know.
Rock!
So it's these people
you've neglected your duties...
...to go chasing after--
Tima!
It's you!
Rock! What's going on here?!
You told me no one survived
the fire in Dr. Laughton's lab!
And how did you know about Tima?
Answer me!
I will.
You are the one who must sit
on the Throne of Power.
No robot must ever rule
the Ziggurat and Metropolis!
Fool!
Robot?
Do you think you fool me?
You're out of line, boy!
Get up!
I never want to see you again!
Kenichi!
-So it was you who hired Laughton!
-What if I did?
I've come from Japan
to arrest Laughton.
My name is Shunsaku Ban....
Get in.
-And Kenichi?
-You'll see him later.
I'm here to see
Superintendent Notarlin.
He's been transferred.
His successor hasn't been named.
There's been a mistake.
The Malduks have taken my nephew away.
Handle it through your embassy!
At this moment our state extends
its reach to the stars!
I tremble at the honour
of announcing...
... the culmination of humanity's
long history of intellect and science.
Sake.
Make it hot.
Hot whiskey or gin I can do,
for a Japanese detective.
Hot whiskey, then.
Who gives a damn about the Ziggurat?!
And those Malduks can eat dogshit!
Here.
Hey! That was Rock!
I heard he quit the party.
What's he doing here?
-Thanks.
-Take care.
Whoops!
A man earlier tonight asked me
to give you this. I said no.
He wanted it kept secret
from Duke Red, and of course...
...I said I couldn't possibly,
but his name was Kenichi.
"I can't move at the moment...
...so I can't come to you.
I'm leaving the country soon.
I want to see you again. "
Kenichi!
What's going on here?
You will bring her back soon,
won't you?
I'll be in real trouble
if they ever find out.
Don't worry. This won't take long.
This wasn't my idea.
I have to get back.
You tricked me.
How else could I talk to you?
Where's Kenichi?
If you know, take me to him.
Well, well, well.
To talk to you,
you'd never guess you were a robot.
I guess Father chose
his mad scientist very well.
-What are you talking about?
-You being a robot.
That's not true. I'm not a robot.
So what are you? Human?
So who's your father? Where is he?
My father...
...is Kenichi.
The super-being?
A mannequin like you?!
If you can't take me
to Kenichi, I'm going.
Tima's gone?!
Watch where you're going!
Let's see inside this super-being that
Father wants so much.
Come on, Laughton!
Notebook.
That notebook?
Don't be alarmed. I taught Rock
a lesson he won't forget.
Where's Kenichi?
I'm looking for him too.
I need your help for that.
You do?
I think they've got him
somewhere in the Ziggurat.
I need to look for him
on the Ziggurat's data network.
Can you do that?
Hold out your hand.
Kenichi!
Well?
Kenichi's in that building!
You did it! I knew he was there!
What happened to me?
I see. You don't know
who you are, do you?
What do you mean?
I'll report the instant
we find anything, sir.
-Duke Red?
-Yeah.
-Anything?
-We can track the signal...
...by where it burned out
the splitters.
-Got it!
-Where?
Zone 1 , South Block 17.
The Hotel Coconut.
Tell me, please!
Am I human or am I...?
Well, you're different
from normal robots.
I'm human. Just like Kenichi!
Uh, yes, of course you are!
Anyway, now we've got
to rescue Kenichi.
Tima! I've been looking for you!
Tell me what's going on
or I'll charge you with kidnapping!
I'm not your man.
It's your son you want to talk to.
Rock?
I don't know what the plan is...
...but I suspect Dr. Laughton
was involved in it somehow.
And I suspect you had him killed...
...to keep her a secret.
Take him away.
Come on!
That is a special throne
made especially for you.
One day from here,
you will rule the entire world!
Me? Why?
That is your destiny.
I'll show you.
Kenichi!
Wake up, Kenichi!
It's me! Can you hear me?
Kenichi. Kenichi?
What have you done to him?!
He's in no danger. We just had
to quiet him down a little.
Kenichi? Kenichi?
I'll file a protest with my embassy!
It'll be an international incident!
Oh? I didn't realize
you were so politically important.
My apologies.
But soon every nation in the world
will bow down before Tima.
Make Kenichi the way he was.
What's one or two young kids, Tima?
You have the power to rule the world!
What power is that? Am I human?
Or am I one of those poor robots?
Oh, don't be silly! You're nothing
like those piles of junk!
Then am I human, like Kenichi?
What are you saying?!
You're no mere human being...
...ruled by emotion and feeling,
torn between morality and love!
You are the super-being!
So then I am a....
I've brought you
new clothes, Miss Tima.
Yes, you are a robot...
...but you stand at
the pinnacle of all existence!
No. I have the emotions
and love that you hate.
That's because your full capacities
haven't yet taken form.
As your abilities evolve, they're
taking the form of emotion and love.
In time--
You will become one with that throne,
a computer weapon meant on conquest!
Your memories and emotions
will all be erased!
How did you know that?!
I fancy myself a detective.
Come, Miss Tima. You should change.
Father, open your eyes!
Rock!
What on earth?!
What are you doing?
It is you who must sit on that throne.
You are the leader we must bow to!
No!
Tima!
You're awake?
I am a humanoid, a machine
made to destroy the world.
-Not destroy! Make again!
-Stop!
Kenichi....
Hey! Who threw that switch?
It just started up!
-Cut the power!
-It won't respond!
It's going into the red!
Dr. Ponkotz!
What's that alarm?
The omotanium generator's going wild!
-What's going on?
-I'm not sure.
Stop, Tima!
You'll destroy the Ziggurat!
This comes of trifling with robots.
Her memory's merging with
the data network. She'll go mad!
Thus God destroyed the Tower of Babel.
Tima!
No! She's no longer the Tima you knew!
All right.
The omotanium generator will explode
if we don't shut it down!
The chance of human survival will fall
to 30 percent within one hour.
My entire worldwide
network of forces...
...will be completely activated
within 30 minutes.
Their targets are the world's major
cities and 7 586 other facilities.
Estimated time period...
...for eradication of humanity
by biological warfare:
17 hours, 27 minutes.
Hear that, Duke Red?
Your super-being says
she doesn't need us!
Tima! Come back!
Kenichi!
Tima!
Doctor, we've lost control
of the underground power pl--
What's happening?
Get out! You robots are
not supposed to be here!
Tima! It's me!
Kenichi! It's Kenichi!
Stop!
The likes of you...
...will never kill...
...my father!
Rock!
Tima!
Tima! Grab my hand!
-I'm Kenichi. Who are you?
-Who are you?
No, no, no. You call yourself "I".
Kenichi!
Grab on!
I am who?
Tima!
Where did you find this?
Fifi?
Fifi!
Kenichi!
Uncle!
Uncle...
...I think I'd like
to stay here a bit longer.
I am who?