You want us to exchange Naruse Mio for that man?
You should have seen it for yourself.
The tremendous power this Toujou Basara possesses.
I don't think it's a bad deal.
I don't know if you understand what is going on...
You can not decide while your master is out?
Marquis Zolgia was supposed to leave for the royal castle
on His Majesty Leohart's orders, after all.
Are you the one who recommended His Excellency Zolgia to His Majesty?
Should I have also reported to him
the fact that Naruse Mio was kidnapped to this refuge?
It goes without saying,
but this is a clear act of betrayal against His Majesty and the Council.
Are you threatening us, Lars?
I am merely fulfilling my duties as Naruse Mio's observer.
You should do your duty to protect the marquis you respect.
I suppose it can not be helped.
Wise decision.
I am grateful for your warning.
Zest!
If you kill me...
Do not worry.
By the time your death reaches His Majesty's ears,
His Excellency Zolgia will have obtained both their powers
and seized the highest standing in the demon world.
Pardon me, Your Excellency.
A matter requiring your attention has arisen.
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「Plaintive Betrayal」
I am sorry, Mio-sama. I...
I'm glad you came, succubus girl.
Where is my mother?
Do not worry.
Mother!
Will you follow my orders and betray Naruse Mio and Toujou Basara?
Yes.
I am yours... to command.
Basara-san?!
There's a slight change in plans.
These are orders from His Excellency Zolgia:
Subdue him and dominate his heart.
It shouldn't be that difficult for a succubus like you, right?
Mio!
I can sense her.
There's no mistake.
Mio's in this building.
So this really is...
Yes.
Maria?
This is Zolgia-sama's mansion.
Wh-What are you doing?!
There is nothing you can do anymore, Basara-san.
Let us at least enjoy your end.
I heard from Takigawa.
It might be difficult for you to rescue your mother on your own.
But we're here with you now, right?
Let's save Mio, and-
If he were not such a formidable opponent,
I would not have betrayed you and Mio-sama.
But now that he's captured Mio,
he no longer needs you or his hostage. Eventually-
I know that!
But right now, this is all I can do!
I have to obey their orders and dominate your heart.
Maria...
I will do whatever it takes to dominate your heart!
Even if I have to use my trump card.
A key?
Is that you, Maria?
Yes.
When Mio-sama was first attacked,
it was because of this power that I was able to escape with her.
Now, Basara-san, please savor the real taste of a succubus' baptism.
I'll find some way to pin down the enemy's base.
Then I'll go with you.
No. I don't know if it'll go well yet,
but I have a plan.
A plan?
That's too dangerous, Basara!
It's the only option we have right now.
Basara, stay safe.
Now, Basara-san...
You can have your way with me.
You really are forceful at heart, Basara-san.
Basara-san...
I should have let you have me earlier.
Then this would not have had to be our first and last time doing this together.
But I will grow tainted together with you.
Forgive me.
Maria!
If you really mean that I can have my way with you...
Then I'll save you.
You took my baptism head on, and yet...
No way.
You plan to resort to force?
Fine.
What are you trying to do?
You don't actually think you can beat me without your weapon, do you?
No, I don't believe for a moment that I could beat you bare-handed.
But I came here to save you.
You are still worrying about me now?
However...
If you hold back like that against me now,
then you will die!
It is futile.
I will say it once again.
Basara-san, there is nothing you can do anymore.
Basara?!
That's...
I see, so that's...
What an incredible increase in her combat abilities.
Even if it's only temporary,
I can understand how she repelled Zolgia-sama.
However...
It should be easy for her to seduce and dominate his heart,
so why go that far?
If she goes too far and renders him useless to us,
then it defeats the point.
I will have to do this myself.
How did you get here?!
His Excellency's barrier is gone?!
It can not be!
Using that elimination skill?!
You underestimated Basara.
The moment Mio was kidnapped,
I lost the ability to track her position.
Their barrier is able to interfere with the effects of our Master-Servant pact.
So we'll use that to our advantage.
"Use that to our advantage"?
Once I'm inside the enemy's base,
my presence should disappear.
I'll nullify the barrier from inside.
That is what has led to your defeat.
You are quite skilled,
but you are no threat.
This mansion is in a dimension near the demon realm.
You heroes cannot receive the protection of the human realm's spirits here.
Naruse Mio?!
Mio!
Thanks.
I know you didn't come here on your own, right?
Where's Basara?
Most likely with Maria.
Her family is being held hostage.
I see...
I knew they were forcing her to obey them.
I will not let you escape.
As if I'd run.
I still need to repay you.
On her behalf, as well!
This will finish it!
So that is all you have?
Don't gawk. Do it now!
Please Sakuya, lend me a bit of your power!
Get back!
Did we get her?
No.
Huh?
It didn't feel as though I cut her.
It is over.
Trying not to injure one of them is more trouble than I thought.
Too bad, Naruse Mio.
Right now Toujou Basara is trying to save Maria, not you.
How does it feel?
Knowing that your precious partner favors
your betrayer over you?
You're right. It's not a very pleasant feeling.
But it can't be helped.
He forgave both me and Maria, and protected us both.
Putting his life on the line.
I'm sure he's trying to save Maria
because she was there when he opened his eyes.
That is quite the convenient interpretation.
The fact that I'm here is proof.
Unfortunately for you,
our relationship isn't the same as the one between you and Zolgia.
What do you mean?
You always seem to be forcing yourself a bit when you're before that man.
You're envious, aren't you?
Of the relationship we share with Basara.
You are quite full of yourself.
However,
you seemed awfully shaken up when you saw your friend
rendezvous with Toujou Basara, did you not?
That was-
Was that Maria's attack?!
What?
Wh-Why?
You should not be able to move!
Do you want to die, Basara-san?!
Of course I don't!
But I have to endure it.
Because there are things worse than death.
Maria, I can't imagine that all the time you and I spent together was a lie.
This room is most likely being watched by Zest...
If I do anything strange, my mother will...
Maria...
There were times when having you around
brought smiles to our faces or helped save us.
So...
Now it's our turn to save you.
That's right.
So I don't lose anything precious to me again.
I'm going to save you.
I'm going to save everyone.
So you...
can't give up either!
Sorry for letting you suffer alone up until now.
Leave the rest to your big brother.
Hey, Yuki...
Did you decide on your own to come to get me?
No way.
I had no choice, because Basara ordered me to.
I knew I was right.
It looks like we won't be able to make her cooperate or talk to us.
Then it's dangerous to leave her alive.
Is there anything else we can do?
Now let's hurry to Basara as fast as we can!
M-M-My body...
No way!
It appears you got awfully violent while I was away.
Zolgia!
Oh? You can talk this time?
It would seem having your comrades is reassuring for you.
Hmm, a hero girl?
The real thing is an even more wonderful specimen.
That wave of his aura is fearsome!
I will make you mine, as well.
Along with exquisite pleasure that brat Toujou could never give you.
I would never let you!
Well, soon you will come to desire it yourself, the same as Naruse Mio.
Now...
Are you all right, Zest?
Your Excellency...
My apologies.
I do not mind.
It only means I have earned new toys.
Yes.
Yuki!
Zolgia-sama?
Oh, sorry.
Are you all right?
I will heal you up later.
I will treat every inch of your body perfectly.
If you can not even guard my prey, then you are trash.
But, Your Excellency, I-
You envied those girls, did you not?
Wishing your master were that young man instead.
Your thoughts always reach me.
Have you forgotten who it was that made you?
Subordinates who do not stay loyal must die.
B-But!
Banishing Shift!
My spell was eliminated?!
Basara!
Hmph. Brat, that was good attack.
However...
You are impressive for nullifying my barrier and my curse of instant death.
What happened to Maria?
Nothing that matters to you.
Hmph.
Her current power held one of the few chances of defeating me.
Naive.
Be careful, Basara!
He uses weird magic!
Huh?
It is futile.
No one can escape from my mental bondage.
You!
Now to have a peek at what kind of power you possess,
just as I did with Naruse Mio's.
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
Espionage and What Lies After