Why did you save us?
Oh, thanks. I'll dig in.
You're not afraid to drink it?
I do not think you would go through the trouble of saving us from those demonic beasts
and bringing us home only to poison us.
Besides, when you learned that we deceived you,
you were genuinely angry with us.
Why did you, a member of the hero clan, decide to save us?
I heard from my father.
From Jin-san?
He told me about the situation you're in.
He did?
So Jin-san knew everything...
That man is the worst.
Well, I won't argue that.
I'm the same as my father.
I'll protect what I want to protect,
and I absolutely won't leave someone to die
when I know the circumstances.
She's innocent.
But earlier you said that the hero clan was watching us...
Right now we don't have any relations with the village.
We're just ordinary humans.
What do you-
Oh, is Mio all right?
Mio-sama always takes long baths.
I just hope that is enough for her to calm down.
Maria-chan?
We have to put our belongings back in place...
And "Maria" is fine.
After all, we are your little sisters.
"Little sisters," huh?
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「First Contract Between Servant and Master」
Maria taught me how to use magic for six months, and yet...
If it weren't for him, I'd be dead.
Just remembering it makes me shake uncontrollably.
I'm no good.
Uh, got a moment?
I just wanted to say something.
I'm sorry.
Wh-Why are you apologizing?
I didn't know anything about you, and I got mad...
I'm really sorry.
B-But that...
What's wrong? Hey, Mio?!
Y-You okay? I'm opening the door.
Mio!
Hey!
I-I'm fine.
Don't bathe so long you get dizzy.
Here, can you stand?
Why would you apologize?
We deceived you.
I hid the fact that I belonged to the hero clan from you, too.
We're even, right?
But I tried to drive you out.
With your demon powers,
there were plenty of faster ways to do that.
Instead, you tried to manipulate my memory so I would leave unharmed.
That's... because we didn't want to get you two involved.
I understood that, too.
Huh?
That was a performance to protect me, right?
There's no need to do that sort of thing anymore.
My father and I have both decided to protect you.
Wh-What are you say- Hey! What?
We're family now.
But we told you the remarriage was all a lie!
If you want to live with someone and protect them,
they're family, aren't they?
Oh?
I see the two of you are less reserved when around one another.
Wh-What, Maria?! I'm not really...
That is really reassuring.
Basara-san seemed quite strong, too.
No, don't count on too much from me.
Now, now, you negated my magic, did you not?
Hm?
Yeah... unfortunately,
that was a fluke.
Completely negating magic on a fluke is impossible.
What technique was that?
Sorry, but...
it really was a fluke.
If you want to live with someone and protect them,
they're family, aren't they?
Family, huh?
Oh, yes?
Mio-sama, how do you feel?
I'm fine now.
Would you like some water?
No, I'm really fine.
Does he really intend for us to be a family?
What's this?
Basara-san printed it out for us.
Do you think Jin-san and Basara-san were faking
how they interacted with us?
Then why not accept their kindness?
Right now you need every ally you can get, Mio-sama.
Then it is settled!
Actually...
I have a proposal regarding our future!
Proposal?
Master-Servant pact magic.
I would like you and Mio-sama to weave a Master-Servant pact.
Why do Mio and I have to become Master and Servant?
It is a mere formality.
Those whose souls are bound by a pact are able to sense each other.
I would like to take advantage of that
so you can pinpoint Mio-sama's whereabouts.
Then isn't the GPS on a cell phone good enough?
Who knows when that might malfunction?!
And what do you plan to do if she's caught in an enemy's trap then?!
W-Well...
This magic can be used only on the night of a full moon.
Tonight happens to be one.
We can not afford to miss this chance!
Hey, say something, Mio.
I-I'm fine with it,
but do you... have something against doing it with me?
A-Are you really sure?
Yes. If it just means knowing each other's whereabouts...
Then it is settled!
This will be Mio-sama's first magic casting,
so I will be supporting her.
Okay...
When you kiss the magic circle that forms on the back of Mio-sama's hand,
the pact will be complete.
Kiss her hand?
That's an outright master-servant relationship, isn't it?
Hmm?
Hey, there's something showing up on my hand.
Huh?
Hey, Maria, what's the meaning of this?!
W-What? This is strange.
Where did I err?
What are we going to do now?!
F-For now our goal is to be aware of each other's whereabouts,
so Mio-sama, if you could kiss Basara-san's hand...
You're kidding, right?!
Why do I have to be his slave?!
Hey, you know, "slave" has a different connotation...
U-Um...
Be quiet, Basara!
Uh, well, this looks like it's about to disappear?
Oh, no! Mio-sama, hurry up and kiss it! Kiss it now!
B-But...
It can be released on the next full moon!
The next? B-But...
It disappeared.
Wh-What's this?
No way...
No.
H-Hey, are you all right?
Wh-What is it?
Ahh, the curse is already taking effect!
Curse?
Ah...
Could you explain it to us?
The main purpose of a Master-Servant pact is to maintain the subordinate's loyalty.
So when the subordinate takes rebellious or traitorous actions,
the curse activates.
Most likely, since Mio-sama refused the kiss of loyalty...
This is her curse?
Despite my appearances, I am a succubus.
Succubus?
You mean the lust devils that do lewd things to people in their dreams?! Y-You?
It is slightly different, though.
I used my own magic in the pact,
so Mio-sama is suffering a succubus's curse.
In other words, powerful aphrodisiac effects... how regrettable.
You idiot!
J-Just, hurry... Hurry up and save me.
Can't you do anything?
Rest assured.
The curse is alleviated when the master makes the servant submit.
S-Submit? How?
Simply.
Please touch Mio-sama.
Huh?
Right now the aphrodisiac effects of the curse
are making Mio-sama's senses hypersensitive.
She has never experienced pleasure like this before,
so if you touch her for a while,
she should obediently swear her loyalty to you by choice.
H-Hey, Maria, what are you say-
Please bear with it a little longer, Mio-sama.
Basara-san will relieve you soon.
It is definitely not the case that I want to watch your face
as you fall from pleasure, Mio-sama.
Now, Basara-san!
Please touch Mio-sama's embarrassing places and relieve her.
I-I can touch her anywhere, right?
You can. However, the longer you take, the more her mind and body will suffer...
Mio-sama will ascend to heaven in both senses of the phrase!
Do devils even go to Heaven?
Well, if you personally prefer to tease her bit-by-bit,
then that works, too.
I prefer that, myself.
Fine, already!
No! S-Stay back! Idiot!
If you do anything strange,
I'll kill you a hundred times-
It's unfortunate, but give up.
I'll finish this as quickly as possible.
H-Hey...
Basara-san! This is for Mio-sama's benefit!
It's for Mio-sama's benefit!
I know that!
No!
That seems to be it.
Mio-sama's weak spot...
N-No...
Wh-What do I do?
At this rate, I'll...
N-No... don't, Basara!
I will... N-No, I will burst.
Don't, Mio-sama!
In order to fulfill to the end the master-servant compact...
you must let Basara-san to take care of this problem of yours.
You must come in visual contact with your master and look at him with love.
Master... my master.
He is my master now.
No way! Such a thing...
Could you please rub Mio-sama's breasts, Basara-san?
Would be that... okay?
It's undoubtedly alright to do it if you want to help Mio-sama get rid of this trouble.
I understand.
No way!
No! Don't! Onii-chan! Don't, Onii-chan!
No way! Why?
I see... I'm really bound to Basara after all...
It's so embarrassing...
You have to bear it just a little more there...
That's no good, Mio-sama!
You want to get back well, right?
Then you need to look him straight his eyes.
Here I go!
Don't! No, just don't!
Onii-chan...
It's enough..
Onii-chan! Onii-chan! Onii-chan!
Nine times? That is our Mio-sama.
She held out longer than expected.
By the way, Maria.
Yes?
Why didn't you mention the curse from the start?
As insurance in order to make sure you would not change your mind.
Forgive me.
I see.
Huh? You are not mad?
It's not my role to be.
Maria, we need to talk.
Mio-sama, my head! That hurts my head!
I did not do that on purpose!
That hurts! That hurts, Mio-sama!
You will tear me in half!
Now then, I will be on standby nearby.
Thanks.
You'll be escorted away if you loiter around.
Don't worry. I will be perfectly fine!
A license?
A fake license!
It would be one thing if I were underage,
but now I can wander as much as I want,
even on weekday mornings.
Oh, I see.
Have a good day!
An adult with her appearance?
Won't they notice the fake license?
Summer break just ended,
so you didn't have to go out of your way to transfer to our school.
My father already finished the paperwork.
Apparently he knows someone here at this school.
Jin-san does? Who?
Well, I don't know, either.
The faculty room's that way.
All right.
Listen, don't cling to me at school.
I don't want others finding out we live together, either.
The Master-Servant testament is predicated on mutual trust.
Even if one displays insubordination,
so long as it is motivated out of concern for the Master,
the curse will not activate.
The curse activates
when the Servant takes action with the intent of betraying the Master.
Trust, huh?
Faculty Room
I'm Sakazaki Mamoru, the one in charge of your class.
Nice to meet you, Toujou.
Thanks.
Toujou Basara
Umm, I'm Toujou Basara.
My name's a bit over the top, but I'm an average guy.
I hope we can get along.
That empty seat over there will be yours.
Okay.
Oh, and Nonaka, since you're the class representative,
could you take care of him?
Yes.
Everyone, line up in the hall.
We're moving to the gymnasium.
Line up?
Basara.
You're the class rep, right?
What should I-
Huh?!
U-Umm...
Wh-What are you two doing?!
W-Wait!
Hey, can you back off me a bit?
Basara, have you really forgotten?
Huh?
Are you... Yuuki?
Yes. Basara, it's been a while...
Would you let go of him already?!
H-Hugging him all of a sudden...
Is there something wrong with you?
Not really. This is normal for us.
Huh?
H-Hey, Basara, what does she mean?
It's none of your business, Naruse-san.
I-It is my business!
I'm living with him now!
Is it even possible to be this isolated on my first day after transferring?
Huh? Seriously? With those looks?
Yes, apparently.
That would creep a person out. So? So?
Then...
Oh, Mio.
What?
Well, what should we do about lunch?
Did you hear that?
You can buy something from the store, right?
Why not eat with your rediscovered childhood friend?
Well...
What a disaster, transfer.
I'm Takigawa. Nice to meet you.
Entry is Forbidden
This comes off easily.
Is it all right?
I'm the only one in the academy who knows about this.
I understand how you feel.
I moved into this area last year myself.
The way the guys in class are looking at me isn't normal.
Nah, you made enemies of the entire school, not just our class.
Huh?
Princess Mio and Princess Yuuki-
they're the twin idols of our school,
so you're quite a conqueror, tripping flags for both of them.
"Princess"? That's what they're called?
The envy of a man runs deeper than a woman's, surprisingly.
So, have there been problems before?
Nope. If anyone tried to get a step ahead,
the rest of their fans wouldn't stay quiet.
So they're all keeping their eyes on each other?
Exactly.
I guess the people after Mio couldn't infiltrate the school and make any bold moves.
So isn't it bad for you to be associating with me then?
Don't worry about it.
If it comes down to it, I'll offer you up and run.
Such a dependable classmate.
It's pretty incredible that you've already set flags with two pretty girls.
It seems like fun to hang out with people who have that kind of luck,
or other such unseen powers.
You're overestimating me.
Unfortunately.
Why are you following me?
Well, I'm just trying to go home like normal.
Hey, Mio-sama!
Well done on your hard work.
Isn't that phrasing a bit off?
Basara-san, Basara-san...
She seems as though she is in a really foul mood.
Well, a lot happened...
Oh. That is no good.
You have to use protection.
Hey!
What?
Look, about Yuuki...
Basara.
Y-Yuuki?
I have something important to discuss. In private.
Hey, Yuuki.
We don't need to sit next to each other, do we?
No. I don't want other people hearing us.
I-I see.
Thank you for coming.
It's been five years, huh?
You've changed.
So have you.
Before, you'd squeeze me back when I hugged you.
Did I?
You often used it as a chance to touch my butt.
D-Did I?
Basara.
Hmm?
Don't involve yourself with Naruse Mio any further.
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
Reunion and a Gap in Trust