Don't involve yourself with Naruse Mio any further.
She's a mid-S-rank surveillance target, right?
You knew?
So you're the one, huh?
The one the village assigned to observe her.
I've heard the gist about it from my dad.
Then why? You and Jin-san will get caught up in this!
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「Reunion and a Gap in Trust」
I never imagined one of Mio-sama's classmates was a member of the hero clan.
I've... been a fool.
It was not your fault.
If it were that easy to notice them,
they would not have been chosen to keep watch on you.
That's not what I mean.
I should have known the moment I learned she was one of Basara's childhood friends.
Yet I declared that we were living together in front of the whole class...
Now the two of them are off on some lovers' rendezvous or something...
Well, there is nothing to worry about if they do not come after us.
Also we do not have enough energy to spare on making enemies out of the hero clan.
But that's not what I'm worried about.
I...
Mio-sama?
No! I'm not peeking!
I'm concerned about Basara's safety!
Is something wrong?
Nothing.
I-I can't believe something like this would activate the curse.
Mio's parents were murdered by those plotting against her,
and now they're after her life, as well.
She's innocent.
She was just living her life as a normal girl.
That's why I've decided to protect them.
But...
Yeah, I don't have the power I used to.
But if the hero clan can't protect her...
If they can't fight for her...
Then I believe it's my role to do so.
Basara...
P-Pardon me!
M-Ma'am!
Your change!
Mio-sama!
Please wait!
What do I do, Maria?
What?
He's going so far for me...
How am I supposed to face Basara from now on?
Is this not a good thing?
Now we know that Basara-san is a genuinely good person.
But...
It just means it is all right for you
to open your heart and have faith in him.
A-And that's enough?
Other than that, well,
if you would like to do something for Basara-san,
then I think you should do it.
I understand your concern, Yuki.
I couldn't finish bearing everything five years ago.
That's not it.
That wasn't your fault. You were...
But what I've done won't change.
That's not true at all.
No matter what anyone else may say,
you're the one who saved us.
Thanks.
But Mio...
She's not like me.
She's trying to face her past and live as best she can.
She's trying to fight.
That's why I want to protect her.
Th-The bath?
I hope she at least cheers up...
Hmm? What's wrong?
That's not good enough.
I can't imagine you alone will be able to defeat the demons after Naruse Mio.
They're after the power lurking within her.
I don't need to win.
I just need to avoid losing.
But...
Anyway, I don't intend on involving you or the village in our fight.
That's impossible.
Yuki...
Lesser stray demons.
They're being drawn by Naruse Mio's power as the Demon Lord and growing in number.
If her existence starts causing danger to her surroundings,
the village will mark her for elimination.
Once that happens, I won't be able to show mercy.
Even if that means you end up resenting me, Basara.
There you have it.
U-Umm...
I see. I understand the situation.
Y-You do? Good, then let's fix dinner-
However,
Huh?
if you are out this late on a lovers' rendezvous,
then it is a slight cause for concern.
I just told you, didn't I? It wasn't a rendezvous.
We thought you might be working together with her.
Right, Mio-sama?
Huh?
Yes, we did...
Of course, we have faith in you.
We trust you. We do.
It is just, as those who are going to be fighting together from now on,
we would like to deepen our bond of trust.
That is all.
Right, Mio-sama?
R-Right. Exactly.
Do you not agree, Basara-san?
Well, that's true.
I knew you would say so!
That is our Basara-san!
So?
What do you want me to do?
Wait,
how did this happen?
Spending time naked together is the perfect way to build trust, is it not?
That's between two guys!
No, no,
if you are both sharing in the embarrassment,
then your unity will grow whether you like it or not!
What's that supposed to mean?
Now then,
Mio-sama, shall we wash Basara-san's back?
No, that's fine. I can do it myself-
No!
Allowing yourself to be vulnerable
by exposing your back to us is
how you'll actually be able to build trust!
Now, Mio-sama!
Y-Yeah... I get it.
She must have said the same things in order to convince Mio.
I'm not going to lose to the likes of Nonaka Yuki.
I-I'm starting now.
What's wrong?
Huh?!
N-No,
it's nothing.
Ahem. Ahem.
I-I know!
H-Hey?
D-Don't move!
Please, stay still.
If you move, I'll kill you a hundred times over.
This is so embarrassing.
But why?
Basara...
Th-That's enough.
W-We haven't eaten yet, either.
I even got a cake.
So we should...
I thought this might happen!
So I brought it!
Huh?!
Now, go ahead, Basara-san.
W-Wait! What are we doing eating cake in the bath?
That's too different!
Eating a cake in the bath is going too far.
Let's wash each other off, and then...
You must not!
You bought this cake for us.
I will enjoy it.
E-Enjoy it?
It would be rude to the cake if I did not at least eat the portion that is not on the floor.
This was well made.
Would you like some, too, Mio-sama?
Hey, Mio!
Not you, too?
Huh?
Onii-chan...
You two.
All right.
If that's how you want it,
then I don't care what happens anymore.
No! Basara! Onii-chan! No!
B-Basara-san, c-calm down!
I'll pay you back in full!
So that you can't behave in such a provocative way again,
I'll make you succumb to me completely!
Huh?
That was all a dream?
No, Basara-san,
it was real.
Partway at least.
Huh?
When you suddenly stood up,
you shot out an incredible nosebleed, and fell over.
Oh, yeah. That time...
Umm, by the way, Basara-san.
Hmm?
Would you mind removing your hand from my butt soon?
Huh?
S-Sorry!
No, I am the one who snuck into your bed after all.
However, for you to subconsciously reach your hand
into a woman's underwear while you sleep...
I am surprised to see you're so forward.
But well, while having a dream like that...
Dream?!
You didn't use your succubus magic to make me-?!
I only peeked in on it.
The dream you saw was all your own.
My own?
My, my, I am surprised you would dream of such things...
Perhaps you might have a talent for being a sadistic brute.
That reminds me, where's Mio?
She was taking care of you,
but it's late now, so I had her go rest up.
I see.
Then maybe this is perfect.
Huh?
Maria, there's something I want to discuss with you.
Yes?
Want to go somewhere after club?
Let's start by heading to the station.
What's with him? Sleeping so carelessly...
Hey, Basacchi.
You were exempt from the summer-break assignment, right?
I transferred in between semesters, there's nothing I could do about it, right?
Lately he's been falling asleep in class without thinking about how I feel.
I know that, but it's not fair, is it?
Don't involve yourself with Naruse Mio any further.
Oh, Nonaka!
The teacher asked you to visit the faculty office.
Both of you together.
Huh? Me, too?
They want you to help organize the summer break assignments.
Why me?
Too bad, Basacchi.
If you thought you'd get off easy by yourself,
you were sorely mistaken.
What should we do?
Call Maria on her phone?
No, I'll be waiting.
I'll be fine on my own.
This is my job as class representative.
The teacher asked me, as well. I'll help.
Why me...
At this rate, it's as though I can't trust Basara...
Wait, I'll come, too...
H-Hey, Mio?
Don't tell me-the curse?
No.
I-It's nothing, so...
Hey, Mio?! What's wrong?
Mio!
An anemia.
She has a slight fever, but she should be fine with a bit of rest.
You're the transfer student everyone's talking about?
Huh?
How does it feel to make an enemy out of every man in the school
on the first day you transfer in, playboy?
The faculty heard those rumors, too?
What am I supposed to do when I make enemies without even intending to?
You should build up allies.
It's not that simple.
Right now all the guys in school-
It's not a matter of quantity;
it's the quality of your allies.
"Quality"?
Don't misunderstand me.
Don't separate quantity and quality
when you're weighing the scales.
Hasegawa-sensei, please report to the faculty office immediately.
Is it that time already?
Repeat. Hasegawa-sensei, please report to the faculty office immediately.
Sorry, but I need to step out for a meeting.
Lock it again when you leave, and return the key later.
I'm the school nurse, Hasegawa Chisato.
Toujou Basara.
Consider who your enemies and allies are when you act.
An odd nurse.
Mio, are you all right?
Is the curse still active?
I'll step out for a minute.
Please... don't leave me alone.
B-But...
All right, I'll stay with you.
I'll stay with you, so don't look at me like that.
Oh, Takigawa.
Sorry, but it doesn't look like I'll be able to go back yet.
Yeah, I'll handle it here.
Then give Yuki and the teacher my regards.
Takigawa said he'd handle organizing the assignment for me.
I see.
How are you? Will you be all right?
I think I might have calmed down some.
What happened?
The curse doesn't activate unless you think something bad about me, right?
I-I didn't...
Oh, right.
I'll give Maria a call, so get some more rest.
S-Sure.
Maria's at the arcade again?
Y-Yeah. She said there's a game she's been hooked on lately.
Good grief!
Playing, sleeping in class...   All of you are like that.
Sleeping in class has nothing to do with it.
I'm right here beside you, so don't be so upset.
I-I know.
So it looks like we might be a while longer.
Understood.
I will come to get you a bit later then.
Thanks. And things on your end?
Today I did not sense such a presence for once.
I see. Later, then.
Oh, it's just you, Takigawa.
Don't look like you've seen a monster.
Sorry for asking you to take my place.
Who cares? More importantly, how's Naruse?
Yeah, more or less.
She's settled down.
I was surprised when she suddenly collapsed.
Her face was bright red...
She seemed awfully embarrassed.
A-Anyway, thank you.
I'll definitely pay you back for this someday.
Oh, speaking of which, Basacchi, did you see Nonaka?
Yuki? No...
That's strange.
She left, saying she was going to check up on you two.
Yuki did?
I'm heading back, then.
Whoa, a blackout?!
Don't tell me?!
They've infiltrated the school?!
Mio!
Basara?
Nonaka Yuki?
I need to talk to you.
Wh-What's going on?
Hey, Basacchi!
Let me through!
Mio! Dammit!
What do you mean by "talk"?
You should have heard from Basara.
You know why I'm here at this school.
Yes, I've heard.
I know what you are, and what your relationship with him is.
With you around, Basara will suffer.
So...
Leave Basara.
She shouldn't have gotten far yet.
Dammit!
All because I let my guard down.
Mio!
No.
Even after learning the whole truth,
he said he would protect me.
Because we're family.
I see.
So you're resorting to force in the end?
In that case... I won't show mercy, either.
You're only taking advantage of Basara's kindness.
Then what about you?
You're ignoring his own will,
and pushing your selfish kindness onto him!
I'm not making any excuses.
I don't regret it, either!
If I apologized after getting him this involved,
it would be rude to him!
So I'll fight fair and square.
Together with him!
My magic barrier?!
If you say such things again, I won't forgive you.
If you knew Basara, then you couldn't say such things!
What do you mean?
Basara can't fight like he used to anymore.
It's likely hard for him to even hold a sword in his hand.
Wh-What do you mean?
Five years ago, in order to save us,
Basara eliminated many of his companions from this world.
Mio! Dammit!
Right, this is what that Master-Servant pact was for!
Above, huh?
What do you mean?
The reason Jin-san and Basara left the village...
and lost their right to belong to the clan...
Even now, that past is making Basara suffer.
You have no idea how cruel it is
to make Basara wield his sword!
Basara?
What's the meaning of this, Yuki?
Weren't you supposed to be her observer?
Mio, you, too.
You told me you wouldn't make enemies out of the hero clan, didn't you?
I...
Mio? What's wrong?
They were talking about your past.
Up until just now.
When did he?!
You're exiled from the hero clan!
And you're guarding the descendant of the previous Demon Lord?
What an awfully intriguing tale.
You're behind those demons that showed up before?!
Basara, what demons?!
Don't worry.
But!
Indeed.
It's pointless worrying about it now.
These past few days,
he's wielded his sword in battle several times.
Huh?
Every night. Until dawn.
Basara, what does he mean?!
Quiet!
Now, now.
Basara!
He's strong!
Basara, what does he mean you've been fighting every night?
It was for your sake.
The power you've inherited from the previous Demon Lord
draws stray, lesser demons to you.
If those were to begin harming other humans,
the hero clan would determine your existence to be harmful,
and upgrade you from a target for observation to a target for elimination.
Once you become a target for elimination,
you wouldn't be allowed to live, even though you're a former hero.
That's why that woman told you to leave him.
Well, he and that succubus at your side
have been hunting stray demons every day and night in order to keep that from happening.
Is that true, Basara?
Then the reason Maria stopped coming to get us was...
If I told you, you'd only blame yourself, right? So...
I'm sorry. I didn't know anything...
No. You're not the one at fault.
No. Naruse Mio, your existence is to blame for it all.
Why you!
If that comes as such a shock to you,
then would you mind ceding the previous Demon Lord's power
that's the cause of all this?
Get down, Mio!
Are you planning to eliminate her this time?
Dammit!
Basara!
No...
Hey...
You're kidding me, right?
Basara?
Basara!
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
Even if it means turning the world against me
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
Countdown of Sadness