Sorry for the wait.
Now I would like to begin the ritual for Yuki-san's Master-Servant pact.
Can I ask something first?
What is it, Basara-san?
Yuki, why are you dressed like that?
I said I didn't want to lose to Naruse-san,
so Maria prepared it for me.
All I did was comply with Yuki-san's expectations.
You liar!
Basara, look at me.
No, change your clothes first, Yuki!
Basara.
Wh-What?
If you don't turn to look at me in five seconds,
I'll start stripping layer by layer.
A-All right! I'm sorry!
Now, Yuki-san, let us begin.
Yes.
Understood.
All right.
Yuki, you know what to do after this, right?
You'll need to kiss the magic seal on my hand-
I won't.
Huh? Wh-What are you saying, Yuki?
I will not make a normal pact with you.
Huh?! If you don't hurry,
the magic seal will be gone, and we'll be in trouble!
That's fine.
Do the same with me as you did with Naruse-san.
Please, Basara...
Dominate me.
Ahh, it's disappearing!
Hey!
Now, Basara-san!
It is your turn to respond to Yuki-san's feelings!
All right.
I don't have a choice.
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「Merits and Demerits of Master and Servant」
Then, you're ready?
Wh-What is this?
I knew it would be your butt.
Yuki, raise your butt.
I'll make you submit soon.
No way, this...
What an erotic butt.
It is a good match for Mio-sama's breasts.
Wh-What...?
Today is your first day as a servant, Yuki-san.
How could I go without recording this?
If you do not like it I can stop,
but it appears Mio-sama still has some resistance to being recorded.
Of course I do!
So if you endure it with the knowledge that you are being recorded,
then you will win above Mio-sama, will you not?
Keep going.
Yuki!
I'm fine. I'm fine with this, too!
Basara...
Please...
Not just my butt.
Okay.
If that's what you desire.
Basara...
Let us now play it live.
Please, more... more...
This is...
Incredible...
I was like that, too...?
See, Mio-sama?
Take a good look.
You don't mean...
To achieve a strengthening while forging the Master-Servant pact,
Yuki-san shows promise for the future.
Now, Basara-san, let us put Yuki-san in the bath.
Huh? Me?
When you were with Mio-sama the other day,
you took the time to warm her up afterwards, right?
But back then...
Take me.
Huh?
Take me to the bath, too.
Okay.
Now, Mio-sama, go with them.
Huh? Why should I go with Nonaka?
Tsk, tsk, tsk. It is "Yuki-san," not "Nonaka-san."
Yuki-san, you should start calling Mio-sama by her first name, as well.
Her first name...
You are both Basara-san's servants now, after all.
Hey, I'm not sure about putting it like that.
All right. I'll join Yuki.
Me, too.
I don't mind taking one with Mio.
I never thought I'd be doing this with Basara, as well as a hero on duty.
Until a while ago, I was living in fear of demons,
but now my feelings are...
Maria, is this thanks to you?
What is the matter, Mio-sama?
I'll help you.
Thanks.
Now, let us all enjoy being naked together!
Seriously?
Mio-sama, Yuki-san, please hurry up and bring Basara-san!
Thank you, Maria.
Hey, what's this?
It is good.
For a Master and his Servants to be playing around like that...
If my Master were a young man, then perhaps...
That would never happen.
Mio!
There!
Nice toss, Yuki!
You're pretty good.
Hey, Basacchi!
Ow...
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, I was just a bit distracted.
Those two pretty girls used to get along like oil and water.
I admire your training technique.
Y-You dumbass! Don't say strange things like that.
I'm going to the nurse's office.
Yeah, I'll let the teacher know.
I'll tell them you're resting for a while.
All right, that should do it.
If the pain gets worse, come see me right away.
See you? Not the hospital?
I'm a lot more skilled than most doctors around.
That aside, you seemed quite stressed before,
but have you managed to relax any since then?
Yeah, somehow.
Sounds like not much has changed.
No, that's not true.
You've been a big help in many ways.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Huh?
Instead of fearing the problems that might arise,
think about how you plan to deal with them.
That's how you can protect the things important to you.
"Protect"...
Don't lose sight of that, Toujou.
Thank you very much, Hasegawa-sensei.
Oh, right, Toujou!
About that bandage-don't remove it until I say you can.
No matter what?
Still, she's a mysterious person...
Sakaki?
Sorry. I wanted to talk to you, Toujou-kun.
Hey, class already started, didn't it?
I didn't want others to hear.
Toujou-kun, are you going out with Naruse-san or Nonaka-san?
Huh?
You're living with both of them, right?
I am, but that doesn't mean I'm dating...
Then it's okay to believe there's a still chance for me?
H-Hey?!
N-Naruse-san told me...
She said that you've done incredibly lewd things with her a bunch of times.
M-Mio did?
You've seen her right?
You've seen her naked!
Sakaki?!
Please, Toujou-kun.
Look at me, too.
What are you two doing?
I used the power of our pact.
It was taking too long for you to change...
Mio!
Hold on, Yuki!
Jeez, you're so violent, Nonaka-san.
It's pretty cruel to try to cut me all of the sudden.
She can see Sakuya?
I knew it. She's under someone's control.
You knew it? What if you were wrong?
It wouldn't matter.
She just would've been hurt a little bit.
Doing this with the door open...
If you're sane, then it would mean you were trying to be seen.
On purpose.
Hey, Toujou-kun,
it's mean to shove me away after my confession
and talk to Nonaka-san who got here later...
Yuki, can I leave this to you?
There was a mark on Mio's neck.
If she encounters an enemy in that state...
I'll leave her to you.
But don't be reckless!
I guess Naruse-san is important, huh...
We've been dumped, Nonaka-san.
You're the only one who was dumped.
Oh, class rep, you're carrying a blade at school?
Do you want someone to call the cops?
You got Aikawa-san, too?
Change in plans.
Huh? What, Nonaka-san?
I can't hear you, class rep.
Basara told me not to be reckless,
but that's impossible...
I'll end this in one blow!
Why?
Why is this so painful?
When Yuki and Maria were with Basara...
It wasn't this bad.
So, why?
Mio-sama!
Maria?
Yes, Mio-sama. It is all right now.
Okay...
Relax and sleep, Naruse Mio.
That suffering of yours
will be healed by Zolgia-sama.
Maria? A demon?!
Basara-san...
Mio!
I'm not letting you get away!
I can find Yuki.
But Mio's...
I can't sense Mio's whereabouts.
Jeez, the whole class laughed at me.
Oh, my...
I wish I could've seen that.
Jeez, Dad! It was really embarrassing for me.
It can't be?!
Wh-What's that?
Mom?
Did you think you could run away?
Zolgia!
Dad!
Wilbert pulled an awfully intricate trick.
You!
Dad! Mom!
It's all right now.
You're... my cousin, Maria-chan...
Where are Mom and Dad?
Th-This is a dream, right?
Right. This couldn't...
It is not a dream.
Huh?
Maria-chan?
I am not the relative you thought I was.
What are you saying? Who was that man?
Why are Mom and Dad...
Those people are not your parents, either.
They're not my parents?
Your real father was the previous Demon Lord, Wilbert.
You are the demon princess.
"Demon"?
Anyway, right now, please just worry about running away with me.
That is all we can do.
Maria-chan, you're...
Please call me Maria.
I have been sent here to protect you.
Please, rest assured, Mio-sama.
Maria...
Where am I?
Wh-What is this?
Looks like you have come to.
I see. So you've captured me.
You catch on quick.
I did not think you would fall for it this easily when I sprung it.
Using my friends for that...
You're a servant of the present Demon Lord
who wants the power inside me, aren't you?
No, she is not.
That voice...
Don't tell me?!
I certainly am a servant of His Majesty Leohart, but...
Unlike His Majesty, I am not after Wilbert's power alone.
Zolgia...
Zolgia!
Oh, your face is so beautiful,
even when you lose yourself to anger.
It was worth capturing you.
How dare you!
How dare you kill my father and mother!
That was quite regrettable.
If it meant enjoying this reunion so much,
I would have murdered that trash even more cruelly.
I'll never forgive you!
I'll kill you a hundred times over!
Hmm, it looks like you need to learn how to speak to match the way you look.
M-My voice?
I will replace all your rage and hatred with sweet pleasure.
I will teach you which master you should be serving.
Help me, Basara, Maria...
Zolgia-sama.
Maria.
I believe I ordered you to stand by.
There was an urgent message from the royal castle,
so I came to report it.
Go ahead.
From the royal castle, you say?
Zolgia, can you hear me?
Yes. It is a pleasure, Your Majesty Leohart.
Your Majesty? The current Demon Lord?
Zolgia. Where are you right now?
I can not see you.
In accordance with your imperial decision,
I am confined within my private residence.
Due to fluctuations in the magic waves in the area,
a portion of the barrier is growing unstable.
I received word that we have lost track of where Naruse Mio is.
Ever since you dismissed me from active observation,
that has not been my concern.
I am sure.
More importantly,
I would like you to come to the royal castle right now.
That is a very sudden matter.
We uncovered a ruin we believe dates back
to the old Diavola Era war between demons and gods.
We would like to you to join the inspection.
Why me?
We made progress related to your area of expertise, ancient magic.
Is there any problem?
Understood, Your Majesty.
I will make my way at once.
I will be waiting.
What will you do, Your Excellency?
Young though he is, he is still the Demon Lord.
No matter, it is not a big mission.
Just wait. As soon as I return, I will make you all mine!
I'm busy, too.
You can't just call me whenever you want, Basacchi.
There's no way you don't know anything when you were her observer.
Tell me, Takigawa!
What happened?
Who kidnapped Mio?
You should have seen me meeting with Maria.
You noticed?
Shouldn't you have suspected everything at that point?
Why would Maria?
It's true that she was sent by the moderates to guard Naruse.
But until just a while ago,
she was following Zolgia's orders.
Zolgia tried to obtain Naruse on his own.
On his own?
He plotted to get ahead of the reigning Demon Lord, who was targeting Naruse.
However, Maria ran away with Naruse at the last minute.
Zolgia hasn't given up on Naruse.
Zolgia's after Mio?
Then Maria...
Why would Maria?
Despite how that succubus seems,
she's apparently hiding quite the trump card.
"Trump card"?
He certainly considered Maria's existence to be an interference.
So, as soon as he returned to the demon world, he went after Maria's family.
Apparently her mother has been captured.
So that's why...
Maria...
Zolgia's the one who ordered her
to reverse the Master-Servant pact between you and Naruse.
Why would he...
It's a matter of his tastes.
By adding the succubus' aphrodisiac effect,
if anyone aside from her master steals her chastity,
then the subordinate is assaulted with pleasure until they break.
Wha?!
The curse is intense once activated.
If things go bad, then right now she...
Tell me! I don't know where Mio is!
I have some delicate circumstances.
I can't do anything carelessly.
Takigawa...
I don't know what it is you want.
But I'm Mio and Maria's brother.
I'm going to make you tell me where they are,
even if I have to beat it out of you.
And here I thought I finally grew close to someone.
It was a short friendship.
Maria...
You've been deceiving me this whole time?
This place is surrounded by Zolgia-sama's special barrier,
and it negates the Master-Servant pact's ability to detect your location.
Basara-san can not come here, either.
You can not run anymore,
Mio-sama.
What do you want, Lars?
I came to collect Naruse Mio.
She is here, is she not?
What are you talking about?
I am not asking you to do it for free.
I will give you this one in exchange.
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
Plaintive Betrayal