I am Vali, Emperor of White Dragon...
the Vanishing Dragon.
You're...
My left hand is burning.
Not here...
No way!
You're defenseless.
For instance, right now I could use a magical-
Boosted-
Your joke is getting out of hand.
We can't let you start a fight with the Emperor of Red Dragon here,
Emperor of White Dragon.
Issei-san...
Asia, stay back!
Don't even try it.
You couldn't defeat Kokabiel,
so you're no match for me.
If you don't mind people seeing, then by all means, go ahead.
Hyoudou Issei,
where do you think you rank in power among the people of the world?
What?
Your Balance Breaker,
although incomplete,
is pitifully four digits from the top.
It ranks somewhere between one and one and a half thousand.
Actually, considering the strength of the host, probably lower.
What are you trying to say?
Hyoudou Issei is a rare gem,
very much worth training,
Rias Gremory.
President?!
Emperor of White Dragon.
What might you be after?
If you are affiliated with the Fallen Angels,
we will avoid-
In times past, the Two Heavenly Dragons,
the Welsh Dragon and Vanishing Dragon,
the Red and White, have caused all they meet
to lead miserable lives.
How are things working out for you?
I'm not here to fight today.
I have a lot of things to attend to.
President...
Her hand...
is covered in sweat.
Takaga shireteta terai ga uzumaite
My puny arrogance came back to me
Oisugaru koto mo dekizu ni ita yo
and I couldn't go to you for help
Namida no wake kimi ni ienai mama de
I couldn't tell you why I was crying
Kuchibiru wa itsumo sora wo nirande ita
and always frowned up to the sky
Uzumoreteta yami yori kimi ga koete kita kyoukaisen
You dug through the darkness to cross this line
Sekai system wa kakumeigire
The world's out of changes to make
Kaikan itami hakai souzou
Pleasure, pain, destruction, creation
Kaete yuku watashi no yowasa wo
I'm going to change my own weaknesses
Ima oshiyoseru kanjouron
All I can make are appeals to emotion
Inochi gake no ai wa amakunaiwa
Love's not easy with my life on the line
Tsuyoku motto tsuyoku
Stronger, even stronger
Donna uso ga matteita to shitemo
No matter what lies I face
Eranda michibiki shinjite
I've already chosen which signs to follow
Furumau koto wa nai to yasashii akuma no hohoemi wa
The devil smiles at me, telling me to be myself
Hakanaku subete wo terasu no
and shines a faint light on the world
Infirmary
Episode 8
Open House Begins!
It's calmed down.
I can't have Akeno-san suck the power out during class.
Vali, the Emperor of White Dragon...
So that's how he fights, huh?
I looked like that when I fought Riser.
He's complete.
Ddraig?
You were nothing compared to him.
Hey, what's the deal with the Red and White Dragons?
When the three factions -God, the Fallen
Angels, and the Devils- were at war,
the monsters and humans all took sides.
We Dragons were the exception.
The exception?
We didn't care much for the war,
and did whatever we wanted.
But in the middle of the war,
two stupid Dragons decided to start a petty fight.
Two?! You mean...
They didn't give a damn about the war that would decide the next rulers of the world
and took their fight over the battlefield.
Why the hell were they fighting so much?
Who knows?
I'm sure they don't remember, either.
Talk about selfish!
The factions couldn't keep the war going with the Dragons around.
They formed a truce and set out to eliminate the Dragons.
There was a truce just to stop your fight?!
Just how crazy were you guys?
Those two went crazy when their fight was interrupted.
They set their sights on God, the Satans, and the leaders of the Fallen Angels.
"How dare the petty God and Satans interfere with the noble Dragons," they said.
They pretty much lost their minds with all the rage.
You guys were the worst, meanest, scariest dragons around.
The Dragons were eventually chopped to pieces
and had their souls sealed in the form of Sacred Gears.
Through their human mediums,
they have met many a time.
And many a time they have fought.
And those Dragons were Ddraig and Albion, huh?
This wasn't exactly the best time to meet.
It's all right.
We're destined to face each other someday.
Coincidences do happen.
That's what he meant by that?
Once in a while, the hosts never meet,
and die without fighting.
I see.
And it's my turn this time around.
Hold on, I just met the other one!
You're telling me all about destiny and stuff,
but there's no way a piece-of-trash, Low Class Devil like me can...
No...
Screw destiny.
I'm going to become a High Class Devil,
and become a Harem King!
Issei, you bastard!
We've heard the rumors!
The new student, Xenovia-chan, was invited into the Occult Research Club too!
You lucky, lucky, lucky bastard!
How does that give you an excuse to punch me?
Oh, sorry.
You've got too many hot chicks around you already.
We just need someone to vent this anger on!
Asshole!
Cool it.
Anyway...
you haven't done anything to Xenovia-chan, have you?
O-Of course not.
Issei,
Xenovia.
I apologize for what I said to you the other day.
Huh?
O-Okay.
It's fine. Let's have this conversation later.
That is why...
we should use these and practice first.
You idiot!
What?!
Xenovia-san, what are those things?
You should use them, too.
Okay?
Thank you?
What's this?
Is Hyoudou being perverted again?
None of your business!
Kiryuu-san, what is this?
This is...
Hey, Kiryuu!
The hell are you telling Asia-
But Hyoudou,
are you sure about this?
If you sleep with Xenovia, Asia would be real sad-
Don't say it, Kiryuu-san!
You shithead!
Matsuda-san! Motohama-san!
Asia-chan?
Issei-san isn't a bad person.
Please don't hurt him.
You're my only ally, Asia-chan.
I'll always believe in you, Issei-san.
Y-Yeah...
Issei.
Huh?
So, about our first practice session...
Cut that out already!
Xenovia may be a little lacking in common sense, but this is crazy!
Oh, Issei.
Oh, President, Chairwoman.
Is your arm doing any better?
Oh, yes. Now that I've rested it,
it's gone back to normal.
I heard you met the Emperor of White Dragon.
Yes, but it seems like he just came for a chat.
A chat?
We don't know why,
but he seems to be under the Fallen
Angels' control and can't act up.
Let's hope he doesn't do anything on the academy grounds.
Yes...
We've got enough of our own problems already.
Yes, truly.
Goodbye.
All right.
Farewell.
They both seem a little bothered.
What's going on?
They're both worried about Parents' Day.
Parents' Day?
I can understand why the President is worried, but the Student Council Chairwoman, too?
I guess your arm...
is completely fine now.
Y-Yes.
Looks like it was just a short-term thing.
That's too bad.
If you had any Dragon power left,
I would've used my mouth to suck you dry.
Akeno!
My, my!
Good grief. I can't take my eyes off you.
Oh, no. I was just worried about Issei-kun.
Were you really?
Now it's Azazel and the White
Dragon...
I really don't want to deal with foes all the time.
Forgive me...
Issei-san?
Ah, Issei.
P-P-President...
Issei, going to have a bath?
Er... No!
Oh? Asia?
Yes.
Rather than waiting out here,
lets all have one together.
Huh?
Asia, your skin is so silky.
N-Not so...
I think your skin is much softer, President.
That's not true.
Now what do I do?
I want to look...
Damn, a nosebleed right now would be bad.
But I want to see everything they are doing to each other, and burn it into my memory!
President!
You know Issei, I've always wanted to bathe with you.
R-R-Really?
This is too much for my senses to take in.
Hey, Issei, don't you want to bathe... with me?
O-Of course I do, this is awesome.
I see...
It makes me happy to hear you say that.
I wouldn't mind if we did this every day...
But maybe you can't handle touching me everyday?
Perhaps every few days?
If it was only once a week I would be sad.
D-D-Damn!
Crap, Asia is watching us right now.
If I was more depraved, I would go all the way with the President.
You know...
If Asia weren't watching us right now,
I would be getting intimate with you-
Don't say such things.
I also want to be intimate with Issei.
Hold on, Asia!
Let me make this clear, so listen closely,
he is mine, he is my subordinate, he is my Issei,
understand?
That might be true, but he was my Issei first.
Asia, you are always at Issei's side.
Why can't I be alone with him?
No.
I am waiting for the time when Issei and I become closer.
Asia, but can you do this yet?
Of course I can...
Asia, don't...
Issei-san,
between the President and me, who do you like more?
She might have bigger breasts,
but I am better in every other way.
Oh? But Issei is only interested in big breasts,
that is what he always says.
Issei...
Thats's not true is it, Issei-san?
Issei?
Issei-san?
Hey Issei!
Issei-san, come back to us!
For English class today,
I'll have you make anything you like with the papier-mâché on your desks.
You can make animals, people, houses,
anything you like.
You're going to shape exactly what is in your mind.
That's one way to communicate in English.
"Exactly what is in my mind", huh?
Go, Asia-chan!
Asia-chan, you're really cute!
What're they doing?!
There are people watching!
Jeez...
Shit, I'm the only one who hasn't done anything!
What the hell am I going to make, though?
What's in my mind?
Whatever I like...
I like...
Issei...
The President's boobs,
her curvy waist,
her hips,
her thighs...
Every part of her has been saved in my brain's hard drive!
I've already tagged them and sorted them into folders!
President!
Hyo-Hyoudou-kun?
Huh?
Wha-
Isn't that Rias-onee-sama?!
It sure is!
It looks just like her!
Wonderful!
I didn't know you had such talent, Hyoudou-kun!
W-Well, I was just pinching and poking away.
Your hands know every inch of her body, huh?
Hey, Kiryuu!
Would you just...
Dammit, Issei!
You really did...
No way!
Rias-onee-sama with this monster?!
Hey, Issei, wanna trade that for my masterpiece?
Screw that trash! I'll give you five thousand yen!
Make that seven!
I won't let you have Rias-onee-sama's body!
Honey, look at our son!
I thought perversion was all he's got,
but he might become a famous artist someday!
I never knew, Asia.
Parents' Day is a day for us to get rowdy and entertain the parents.
I think you've got the wrong idea.
It's very well-made.
My, my.
Touching and looking at our President's body every day has really paid off, hasn't it?
E-Every day, you say, Akeno-san?
I try to memorise it whenever I have the chance!
I would love to also have a figurine of myself.
I-In the nude?
Of course I'll be nude...
and I'll be yours to touch.
Mine to touch?!
Yours to touch...
"Mine to touch..."
Nothing could ever spark my artistic interests more!
No! You can't!
No!
So I can't?
A photo shoot of a magical girl?!
As an ex-photography club member,
I must record every detail through my lenses!
A magical girl?
It can't be...
My, my.
One more, please!
C-C-Could you look over here, please?
That's...
Magical Girl Milky Spiral Seven Alternative cosplay!
You're very knowledgeable, Issei-san.
A regular customer once had me
marathon the entire anime series.
A regular customer?
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?! You're at school!
Shoo! Party's over!
Shut up, you tyrant!
Why can't we have a photo shoot?!
Yeah!
It's Parents' Day. Quit making a racket!
Go away!
God dammit.
See ya, Milky-chan.
Are you family of a student?
Yeah.
We can't have you walking around school in those clothes.
What?
✩Milky✩Milky✩Spiral✩
Please be serious-
Hey, Saji.
Good to see you finally hard at work.
Shut up, Hyoudou.
Saji!
What's going on in here?
Oh, Chairwoman, I was just-
Found you, Sona-chan!
Could she be...
an acquaintance of the Student Council Chairwoman?
Sona-chan!
Sona-chan, what's wrong?
You're blushing like crazy.
You've finally been reunited with your big sister,
why aren't you joyfully greeting me?
"Onee-sama!", "So-tan!", we should cry to each other,
while having a girl-to-girl embrace.
That's what I think.
"Onee-sama?"
Serafall Leviathan-sama.
Huh?
One of the Four Great Satans,
and my Chairwoman's older sister.
It's the first time I've ever seen her, though.
What?!
You're actually super duper happy to see your sister again, aren't you?
Serafall-sama, it's been a while.
Oh, Rias-chan!
It's been ages!
How ya been?
I've been well, thank you.
Are you here for Parents' Day?
Yeah!
Sona-chan's so mean.
She didn't say a word to me about Parents' Day!
I was devastated!
I was so angry I was about to attack Heaven!
I can't tell whether or not she's kidding.
Rias-chan, is that the kid with Ddraig I've heard about?
Yes.
Issei, come and introduce yourself.
Y-Yes!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
I'm Hyoudou Issei,
Rias Gremory-sama's Pawn!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Serafall Leviathan, a Satan!
Call me Levia✩tan! Okay?
Y-Yes.
Onee-sama,
I am the Chair of the Student Council here.
Even if you are my family,
such behavior and attire is completely unacceptable!
Say it ain't so, Sona-chan!
If that's what you think, your sister...
will be so very sad!
You know how much your sister's into Magical Girls, don't you?!
I've heard that line before.
✩I'm gonna use my sparkling stick and
slaughter all the Angels and Fallen Angels!✩
Onee-sama, please behave yourself.
Your little sparkles could level a small country in seconds.
Hey, Saji.
When Kokabiel came by,
your Chairwoman didn't call her sister,
but it's not because they don't like each other, is it?
It's the opposite.
Because Serafall-sama loves her sister, Chairwoman Sona, so much,
calling her would only cause trouble.
Y-You're right.
She may have screamed, "My sister's been assaulted by the Fallen Angels!", and caused a war.
I...
I can't stand this any more!
Hold on, Sona-chan!
Stay away from me!
No Sona-chan, don't go!
Okay, I better go assist my Chairwoman.
Get out of those clothes!
S-Sure.
Good luck!
Saji-san has his hands full.
I hate to say this,
but the four current Satans are all like this.
Like what?
They're sort of eccentric in private.
Regretfully.
Hey, Issei!
Dad?
Rias, there you are.
Father!
What?!
President's dad?!
H-He looks so young!
Are you Hyoudou Issei-kun?
I'm Rias' father.
Thank you for looking after my daughter.
H-Hello.
Dad, what's going on?
I bumped into him in the hallway.
It's difficult to talk here.
We don't have much room, but would you like come talk at our home?
Ah, that would be excellent.
What?!
We're going to head back home, then.
Do you like to drink, Mr. Gremory?
Well...
Dad...
You know who that is you're talking to, right?
I-Ignorance is bliss.
What a show.
Onii-sama.
Looks like we'll be eating with Father today.
This is splendid.
It looks delicious.
I made the finest food I could!
Why don't we start with a toast?
Cheers!
There you are, Asia-chan!
It's a little embarrassing.
You're always so feisty, Issei.
Let's see the video of Rias next.
Ah, you filmed her?
P-President!
It's a parent's duty to watch his daughter at work!
This must be a new kind of torture.
Look!
Our Ria-tan is answering the teacher's question!
I can't stand this!
Onii-sama, you meanie!
President!
Right?
Look at that!
Have another!
Uh, President?
Would you like to come in to my room?
W-Well, I think it's nice that my parents and your parents
could meet and get along so well.
I know.
Hey, Issei...
Yes?
Are you glad that you met me?
I am.
I'm honored!
I'm glad as anything that I met you!
But...
But?
No, it's nothing.
Just the thought of President getting a boyfriend...
That's unfair, President!
If Akeno's taught me anything,
it's that you've got to be quick.
Then, I'll just take him by force!
What's that supposed to mean?
There, there. Don't fight.
Onii-sama?
Sirzechs-sama?
Rias, I had a thought.
What would that be?
Why don't you release your other Bishop?
Huh?
Her other Bishop?
She has another one?
His ability was too dangerous for me to control and was sealed away.
Dangerous?
I thought you were the one who decided that.
That's right, but after your battle with Phoenix and Kokabiel,
I have begun to change my mind.
Go on...
You've expanded your family and strengthened your forces.
I think you can now handle him.
Release him, Rias.
If my brother...
If the Great Satan, Lucifer-sama, commands it...
What do you want to do?
churuchuchu doushitai
Hey, girls
churuchu hey girls
chu
ru
hey
girls
Lovely devils
raburi debiru
ra
girls
bu
ri
girls
de
bi
ru
You know what we wanna do! Yes!
churuchuchu aa shitai yes
They've descended upon us again
yes
kyou mo kourin
kyou
mo
kou
yes
rin
Girls are always greedy for more
shoujo wa shinkakei ni yokubari na no desu
I want this, I want that
are mo kore mo
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
kinou to kuraberun ja manzoku dekinai
Uh-oh
arere
a
i
re
Let's have a strategy meeting on how to upgrade
appugureedo sakusen kaigi
Agreed!
sansei
san
sei
I'm sure you have at least one of these
daredemo hitotsu kurai motte iru desho
You too, and you too
kimi mo kimi mo
Original magic words that protect your heart
orijinaru no jumon kokoro no omamori
Uh-huh
aruru
a
ri
ru
Positive thoughts that give you strength
purasu shikou taishitsu kyouka
Never compromising our love or dream
koi mo yume mo totteoki wo ne te ni ireru tame ni
Everyone
minna
mi
ni
n
na
We want to follow our heart
fiiringu juushi de
risaachi
de
Research
ri
saa
de
As we grow up
seichou shitai na
You see, girls are lovely devils
onna no ko wa ne raburi debiru
Deep down in their hearts, so treat them with great care
mune no naka kakushiteru no toriatsukai youchuui
They're only interested in having fun
tanoshii koto shika kyoumi nai no yo
Their whimsical temper makes them cute
wagamama ni kawaiku narun da
Promise!
yakusoku
ya
ku
so
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
And she's a cute little girl who's a shut-in!
Wha--? Girl? Huh? Wa--? Seriously?!
Next Episode: "I Have a Junior!"
I Have a Junior!
Episode 9
No boobs?!