Boobs!
Issei.
Issei-kun.
Issei-san.
Issei-senpai.
Issei.
Now that's what I call a birthday suit!
Come on, don't be shy.
Go ahead and touch them.
My, my. Feel free to play with my breasts as much as you like.
I-I'll close my eyes and grit my teeth until it's over!
P-Please!
Maybe a little.
Come! Let's make babies like there's no tomorrow!
Gosh, what's a guy to do?
P-Please go out with me.
Aw, I—
Whose voice was that?
You're so cruel. Have you forgotten me?
We went on that date together.
It can't be.
Yuuma-chan?
Yuuma?
That's right.
I was going to kill you at sunset.
That was the name I used.
So would you die for me?
Damn it, why am I remembering that?
There we go.
Akeno-san?
Hey, Issei-kun.
Does my body feel good?
Y-Yes. It feels awesome.
That's wonderful. I want to explore you more, too.
Explore me more?
Has ever a more sweet and beautiful phrase existed?
Akeno.
When did you get in here?
President!
This is but a little morning skinship with my cute little Issei-kun.
Your?
When did you become Issei's master?
I may not be his master, but I am his senior.
It's my job to treat him right.
Senior?
I see. So that's what it's come to.
U-um...
Is it morning already?
Asia!
Asia, go back to sleep, okay?
You're so kind! Let me to use you as a pillow, then.
You already try to get your hands on what's mine.
Why can't you share him a little?
You're so selfish, Rias.
We only just remodeled the place.
You're not getting your way!
My, my.
You guys, calm down!
Wait, remodeled?
Wha—
What the hell?!
so
no
mu
If you listen to the voice of your heart
You'll be born anew again and again
born
born
new
mo
u
ko
I can't hide it anymore
The purported salvation is but a mirror paradox
Trying to come to terms with myself
I realized my soul must lie with my wishes
The moment we met, the warmth of the tears
de
ta
shun
shun
ta
kan
shun
Falling off your palm ignited my heart
And we understood the DxD each other felt
I've been waiting
What's there to be gained amid all the despair?
It's not bliss but rather a good feeling
feel
feel
ing
so
no
mu
Until I reach deep inside your heart
I'll call out your name again and again
your
name
your
name
Episode
Summer in the Underworld
Boy, was I surprised!
Our house just suddenly turned into a six-story tower, with three basement levels!
Rias-san's father said he worked with people who did remodeling,
so he redid the place as a model house for his business.
And imagine our shock when the construction finished while we were sleeping!
The kitchen's so big. I could really expand my repertoire in there.
Aw, your cooking's the best no matter what, honey!
Oh, you smooth talker, you!
Save it for the bedroom!
Let 'em hear.
I'm more afraid of my parents'
attitudes than any devil's power.
Dear!
See you later!
The house has gotten so lively!
Lively, huh?
Well, I'm not gonna complain about a bunch of babes living under my roof.
Why am I remembering that?
Issei-san?
It's nothing.
Asia!
Asia, I...
I swear I'll protect you, no matter what.
Yes, thank you very much, Issei-san.
My, my. Issei-kun, you sure are energetic this morning.
Akeno-san!
N-No, I just remembered
something nasty, and, well...
Nasty?
Baby-making?
Uh, Xenovia, that seems kinda wrong.
Issei-senpai, your creep engine is on full throttle today.
K-Koneko-chan...
We're blocking the way here.
Issei, if you want to proclaim your love to Asia, pick a better spot.
Oh, but I don't stop at Asia!
For you, President, I'd give up my life!
Thank you. That's nice to hear, Issei.
President?
My, my. We should hurry or we'll be late.
Oh. Right, Akeno-san.
Let's go, Asia.
President!
That's right.
He calls them Akeno and Asia.
But he calls me "President".
Hey, what're you guys gonna do tomorrow? Summer break is starting!
I've never had such a long break before.
Yes, I haven't a clue what to do.
Oh? So this is your first summer break?
Summer break finally starts tomorrow!
Yeah!
A Japanese summer is a summer for gentlemen!
And summer means hitting on chicks at the beach and pool!
My Scouter's ready for battle!
Planning a sad and lonely summer, Pervert Trio?
What?
Who're you calling Pervert Trio?!
Begone, Kiryuu Aika!
Motohama's got the glasses moe covered!
Hmph. Don't lump me in with that four-eyed pervert.
You debase the holy glasses moe.
What?!
Motohama's glasses can analyze a girl's size in an instant!
You're 80.5 cm, I see.
You think you're the only one with that power?
I-Impossible!
You have a Scouter, too?
Oh, I see, I see.
Stop it!
Hyoudou.
What?!
You're about... long... round...
And at full mast...
She's even more detailed than Motohama!
It can't be!
D-Damn you!
Then I'll just announce all your measurements, too!
Go ahead and try, if you can.
It's a battle of gods!
You're a lucky girl, Asia.
S-Sorry?
Hyoudou Issei's packing.
Right.
Packing?
Packing? Where's he packing for?
Not where, but what?
Eek!
Dummy, don't tell them that!
Just you watch, Kiryuu!
By the end of summer I'll have a girl all over me!
You're gonna eat those words!
A girlfriend, huh?
I acted tough, but the fact is my first girlfriend killed me.
I wish I could forget.
Maybe it's that dream that's making me remember.
What's the matter, Issei-senpai?
Oh, nothing.
Hey, Kiba.
You got anything going on this summer?
Oh, right. This is your first time, isn't it?
What do you usually do, Koneko-chan?
Everyone here?
You're going to the underworld?
It's summer break, so I'm going home.
I go every year.
Wh-What's the matter, Issei?
You just dropped this bomb on me about leaving!
Am I gonna be all alone?
Of course not.
We'll be together all of eternity. Don't worry.
I wouldn't leave you all alone.
Thank you, President.
So we're all going to the underworld tomorrow.
Pack for a long trip.
Huh?
We're going too?
You're my servants. Of course you're coming with me.
It's so exciting to be able to go the underworld while I'm alive!
I'll pretend that I've died to set the mood.
A former servant of God setting foot in the realm of devils?
I suppose it's fitting now that I am a devil.
I'm going to the underworld, too.
Azazel-sensei?
When did you get here?
If you still can't sense when I'm around, you need to start training some more.
Guess I'll tell Matsuda and Motohama
I'll be on a club trip with the President.
So we're going to the underworld by train?
Last time, Grayfia-san used magic to take us there, and we flew back to Earth on griffons.
It's tradition for new servants to travel via the formal route.
Koneko-chan, are you not hungry?
Koneko-chan?
Don't worry.
It's nothing.
We will be arriving in Sitri shortly.
What's "Sitri"?
Heya, Hyoudou.
Saji!
And the student council president and vice president!
Hello, Sona.
We'll be sharing your train, Gremory.
I thought it prudent to say hello before getting off.
I'm kinda dreading this.
This year's return home is
quite different from most years, after all.
You're gonna be training in the underworld too, right?
Huh?
Actually, we weren't told anything
except to accompany the president.
Anyway, you better be ready, 'cuz the next time you see me, I'm gonna be way stronger than you!
Saji, we must leave.
Roger!
See ya!
See you soon.
Yes. Soon indeed.
It's been a while since the
student council president left.
The underworld must be really big.
We will soon be arriving at the Gremory estate.
Finally here, huh?
Look out of the window.
That massive expanse of land is all...
Yes, the Gremory estate.
A-All of this?
It's about the size of Honshu, Japan's largest island.
Wha—
We stopped?
This is an emergency stop.
My, my. What could have happened?
I dunno, but I think I landed in Heaven.
U-Um, was there an accident?
Some major players will be assembling soon.
They could be taking extra precautions.
Major players?
Doesn't seem like the engine's running.
I'll go check on it.
See ya.
A representative from Asgard will be joining us for the conference.
Asgard?
It's from the Norse legend.
Other than devils, angels, and fallen angels, various other factions such as Olympus of Greek mythology
and Mt. Meru of Hindu Mythology.
There're even more factions than those I've mentioned.
I see. That guy who took Vali
away called himself Son Goku.
So President, is this "conference" about the Khaos Brigade?
Yes. It's an anti-terror conference.
Asgard is involved, too.
Vali...
Next time, you're mine.
Outside!
Ow!
Wh-Where are we?
A forced teleportation?
Where's the president?
I don't see her.
I don't see Sensei either!
Quiet!
Something's coming.
A dragon?
It's not friendly, that's for sure!
Indeed!
Koneko-chan, no!
Hiya!
K-Koneko-chan!
Koneko-chan!
With the president missing, I am in command!
Yuuto-kun, Xenovia-chan, draw the dragon's attention!
Issei-kun, use that time to charge your Sacred Gear!
Asia-chan, heal Koneko-chan!
I will provide support!
Roger, Vice President!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Don't look at me!
You need to be punished.
You face bigger problems...
...with us!
Durandal was repelled?
Koneko-chan, you have to stay still!
Yuuto-kun!
Roger!
Sword Birth!
Boost!
Whoa!
Issei-san!
Are you not done yet?
This ain't enough to take that thing down yet!
Boost!
Issei-kun's Sacred Gear is resonating?
I-I've gotta help!
I'm...
I'm a man, too!
Nice one, Gasper!
It's moving again!
I can't! I'm too scared to concentrate!
Explosion!
Yes!
Issei-kun, with me!
Right!
Dragon Shot!
Seriously?
No way!
Oh no!
Issei-san!
Issei-senpai!
Issei!
Issei-kun!
All right. That's enough.
President and Sensei?
That dragon's a devil?
It has been a while, Ddraig.
Indeed. What a sight for sore eyes, Tannin.
It talked?
Wait, you know this guy?
The Blaze Meteor Dragon—in other words the devil dragon saint—Tannin.
He used to be one of the Dragon Kings,
but circumstances arose that turned him into a devil.
A dragon turned devil?
That's like awesome times two!
We asked him to help train you guys.
Train? You mean sharpen our skills?
I came here at Sirzechs-dono's request.
Don't forget that this is a favor, Governor.
Are any of you hurt?
I'm sorry for tricking you.
I was against this, but my brother insisted.
Rias, your constant babying and hesitation is what's keeping them from growing truly strong.
I've never hesitated!
I wanted to see for myself just how well they could handle a surprise attack.
Now I know exactly how to train you all.
Only a fallen angel would come up with such a plan.
I'd do anything to make you guys stronger.
I am your sensei, after all.
Ddraig, why didn't you tell me you knew this guy?
There was little point in me revealing the farce.
Farce?
Tannin didn't even use a thousandth of his power.
Anyway, it wouldn't do to show up at home dirty.
I'm okay!
I'll take a bath later!
What're you embarrassed for? You're a guy!
If you're really a guy, don't hide your chest with a bath towel!
You're confusing me!
No way!
Issei-senpai, you were looking at me like that?
Of course not!
Issei-kun, don't sexually harrass Gasper-kun.
A-Akeno-san?
The top bath's for women?
Which means up there is boob heaven!
The underworld's hot springs are awesome!
If I had booze, it'd be even more awesome.
Oh, and Issei.
Yes?
Have you ever fondled Rias's tits?
Yes!
My right hand has plied that flesh!
Then have you poked a girl's nipple like this?
N-No, not yet.
What, you've never had the pleasure?
When it happens you must shove, not tap.
The sweetest part is when your finger sinks into her breast.
Say what?
My finger, sinking into a breast?
A nipple isn't a doorbell!
Oh, but it is.
Press it, and a sound comes out.
"Ahhh!" she'll say.
Ahhh!
I-I don't believe it.
I'd always thought boobs were for fondling, sucking, and squishing!
Boobs...
Nipples...
They can do that, too?
You have much to learn.
A woman's breasts are infinity incarnate!
Sensei!
You've set my heart aflame!
Sensei! I gotta poke some boobs!
Keep that dream alive, kiddo.
I know you can do it!
If you do, the boob training is over!
Yes!
Yes, sir!
Issei-senpai gets fired up about everything.
Hey, Gasper-kun. During our training...
Yes?
Koneko-chan attacked before Akeno-san even gave the word, didn't she?
Hey, yeah.
She's been acting kind of strange.
You think so too?
What about it?
Nothing.
I was just wondering.
Xenovia-san, you sure love training.
Your constant babying and hesitation is what's keeping them from growing truly strong.
What exactly do you think I'm hesitating about?
Did you say something?
No.
I'm sorry you had to take command for me today.
It's my job as vice president.
Then why don't you have Issei call you by your title?
Like he does me.
I prefer Akeno. It's much more intimate.
Of course.
You're right.
Rias?
We should get out.
Sorry I took so long.
Honestly. I've been waiting forever, Bikou.
I was going over the first stages of the plan with Vali.
I should go get him.
He's a real pain when I'm late.
I don't care about Loki, though.
Don't say that, Kuroka.
This is work, remember?
I just want my little sister back, meow.
Just wait for me, Shirone.
sou daitai no koto nante
Well, yeah, I do think that
mou wakatte wa iru na tte
I've got this stuff mostly figured out
omou yo dakedo ne
But still, you know
kokoro wa bannou ja nai
Feelings on their own can only get you so far
daiji na kotoba ga ishin fudenshin
We're not using the right words
saishuuteki ni wa analog tsuushin
So we have to rely on analog communication
dakara ima sugu
That's why, right now
motto chanto katachi ni shite yo
I want you to be more concrete
kimi ga
Do it
ijiwaru na
Stop teasing me
give me kikasete yo
Give me, just tell me
chotto dake de ii no
Just a little hint is fine
aimai na no wa yada na
Don't leave me hanging
no secret sansei
No secrets, yeah?
answer todokete ne
Give me your answer
kowaku nante nai shi
I'm not afraid to hear it
iwanai kedo nee wakaru desho
I don't have to actually tell you, right?
wakatte yo
Take the hint
tell me how tell me how
Tell me how, tell me how
subete wo kaeru no wa
If you want to take it to the next step
give me one give me one
Give me one, give me one
itsu de mo kimi dakara
The power is in your hands
Next Episode:
Xenovia, why do you have to be in the crazy-sleepers club too?
I'm here to lay down an ultimatum.
Are you all right?
Red Dragon Emperor?
You're just a low-class devil.
Episode
Gathering of Young Devils
You should accept it gratefully, like a gentleman.
Brace yourselves!