I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
So that's it? It looks smaller
than I imagined.
It has the proper air to it
for an inheritance of the Empire.
And such a fantastic array of color.
It's simply splendid.
Commander?
What is it?
Still, although it may be
a valuable inheritance...
...the fact that so many of our resources
are being used for its retrieval...
It was Lord Alfred's passion and iron will
to make this painting...
...the ideological basis for
an unstoppable...
...National Socialist movement.
Try to understand that.
Yes, sir!
Upon our success, he has promised
our party financial assistance...
...as well as an introduction
to the Anti-communist Union.
Although our party's numbers
are small in America...
...this will be the opportunity we've
needed to make a breakthrough.
What's with that painting?
It can't be helped that their peculiar
political principle is different from ours...
...but coming with that much
weaponry and equipment...
...is not something some poor
Caucasians can pull off.
Their investment is obscenely out
of proportion to their objectives.
But... wait a minute.
Talk about too much money for the job...
the money we've been offered.
Hmm... I see.
You're pretty sharp, Rock.
It reminds me.
We've also been hired with a lot
of money to get that painting.
It suggests great value. But it doesn't
match the artist's lack of fame.
Hopefully that mystery will be
solved tonight.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Rock. Go fetch Revy some
dinner too, will you?
Sure.
Tell her they don't deliver
pizza out here.
So she'll have to give in and eat
something from a can.
Revy.
Yeah.
Here's dinner. Dutch says to have
something to eat.
I'll leave it here.
Um... If this is about what happened
in the U-boat...
Rock. We're done talking about that.
There's no reason to go
over it again. Right?
Yeah.
It's a good night.
The moon is about to sink and the only
light will be from the stars.
As soon as that happens,
we'll raid their ship.
I've been keeping an eye on their ship
at the outer range of our radar.
That's good. Revy and
I will raid the ship.
Now that they have what they wanted,
they're probably sitting back, relaxing.
You idiots can keep casually
toasting each other.
We're gonna come banging on our
tom-toms and raid you like Navajos.
Wagner won't even compare to that.
Sorry, but I'm gonna need you to take on
one more job, partner.
All right.
Now's your chance to go wild,
discharging those lead bullets.
You distract, I search. Make some noise.
All right. I have no complaints if I can kill
who I can kill and steal what I can steal.
I'm going, Rock.
You seem glum, Revy.
Something happen with Rock?
Nothing happened.
O-Oh no! Someone!
The first little piggy came to its end.
Oink, oink, oink.
It's started.
I'll make my way to the upper deck
from the bow.
Liven up the place with
a big ruckus. Okay?
Yeah. I'm gonna eat until I get my fill.
Where did that gunshot come from?
I don't know.
They can go on a wild spree if they want,
but tell them to stop shooting.
Yes, sir.
Oh, boy.
Commander! The enemy!
The enemy's made their way on board!
They're still going at it.
Hey.
At times like these, what kinda face
do we put on while we wait?
Do we sit here looking bored,
smoking and drinking beer?
When you two were being shot at
earlier today, Dutch looked very calm.
I envied him. In any case, we're not
the type who can sink bullets into people.
That's why we hold down the fort.
All squad leaders gather your men
in front of the dining room!
Assemble there and...
Yo.
Bastard. Take aim!
Oh, boy. They're only dressed
like real soldiers.
So, is this where the boss is?
Y-You won't find the commander here!
He's on the upper level!
That's very kind of you.
Revy, can you hear me?
Revy? Revy? Where are you?
Damn it, that bitch!
Wait. Please wait. The crew here are
hired outsiders. S-So please...
So? So what?
Whether or not you're unaffiliated or
non-resistant has nothing to do with it.
If you're all insured,
there's no problem, right?
Oink, oink, oink.
Revy. What the hell are you thinking?
Blitz! Punish the lawless hoodlums
with a decisive shot!
Roger!
What? I was just going
about my job, Dicky.
Creating a bloodbath is what
we always do.
A gunman is an occupation.
Someone who shoots based on their
mood is just a reckless shooter.
I don't remember hiring Charles Whitman.
Going wild and letting loose
is your decision.
But if you screw up, I die too.
You've gotta be cool
as a cucumber, Revy.
If you can't handle that,
climb a church and shoot all you want.
So you're gonna lecture me too?
Don't make me laugh, Dutch.
What do you expect, Two Hands?
I'm your employer!
I thought you were gonna kill me.
I thought the same, partner.
No trust here.
You couldn't even take a joke.
So what's next, big boss?
The commander. We'll find him.
Your Excellency. The enemy is likely
those grave-robbers.
Our comrades are boldly
countering and dealing with them.
We'll be sure to get them!
So please do not worry, Your Excellency.
Rachmann. Not once has
a military unit been victorious...
...when entering a battle with
nothing but desired observations.
"Please do not worry"
shows a lack of sincerity.
Do you not think so?
Tell me what you base your
confidence in your victory on.
Otherwise, you should refrain
from such casual consolations.
I'm terribly sorry!
Did I sound like I wanted an apology?
Frankly, I'm surprised.
Do you think I place greater importance
on your apology than the painting?
I want the painting, and you are in
need of connections into our world.
It is clear and simple.
You better understand that.
Revy. Have you cooled down a bit?
What do you mean?
You get Whitman fever whenever
we get a newcomer.
It happened when we took in Benny.
Our style's not to dig too deep
into each other's past, right?
I'll finish this job. Perfectly.
Of course you will. Or we wouldn't
be able to support our way of life.
I'll check this area.
We'll finish talking later.
So, you're still alive, little girl.
I compliment your audaciousness.
M y name is Blitz Stanford.
I am the acting captain of the glorious
White Aryan Socialist Union.
This is a fated confrontation.
For the sake of those
who died for the Union...
...you shall atone with your blood!
Behold!
This gun I proudly wield!
I call it the Eiserne Reich Luger Special!
The base is the Luger artillery long
and the frame is hardened carbon!
With a thick grip and
a double re-enforced chamber!
A 454 Casull is used, making it way too
destructive to just be referred to as...
...specialized in man-stopping!
I am the only one on Earth who
can wield this terrible gun!
Are you afraid?
There's no way you're not afraid!
I'll show you the power of this gun...
Shut up!
I'm not even listening. How long are you
gonna talk? Are you a televangelist?
Y-You coward!
I'll teach you something worthwhile.
All these things need to do
is fire and hit their target.
Now that's a useful lesson.
Say "hi" to the Fuhrer for me.
That's the sound of the finale.
It appears that you've lost. I've heard
that tune many times in my past.
It's just a distant memory to me now.
Hey, Nazi. I've come to get you.
Were you on the phone?
Well, given what we've been through,
I don't think I'll apologize for being rude.
Don't mind me. I'll wait until you're
done with the phone.
He certainly is a brave man.
I want to talk to him. Put him on.
- It's for you.
- Oh?
You the boss? Your subordinates
were a real waste.
Indeed. Forgive me for
the shameful display.
I've got two questions for you.
Oh?
About what the painting really is?
Then start with that.
There's another candidate for who
painted this piece...
...other than the commonly
believed artist.
I commend you on your research.
A former Bohemian artist...
...Adolf Hitler himself.
Or that's how rumor has it.
The Fuhrer's?!
Don't rush to conclusions, old man.
The Fuhrer as an artist could, at best,
only do mediocre scenic pieces.
It reminds me that the SS officer also
believed in that false information...
...when he left for Batavia.
I see.
So what you want isn't the painting,
but something else inside it.
And, this is just a guess...
...but you know the phone number
to our office, don't you?
The antique trade company from Madrid
that asked for this salvage job.
Indeed...
...that was me.
I was also the one who wanted you
and Rachmann to collide.
What?
It was a most amusing method...
...which also acted as their rite
of passage and insurance for me.
And, this is a fleeting
and dear memory.
The day Heydrich decided
on the "Final Solution"...
...we made a vow at the Wannsee
lakeside to become realistic guardians...
...rather than idealists
believing in victory.
We gathered all of our capital
and created a file...
...with all of our signatures
and account numbers.
When signs of the end approached...
...we placed our files into four paintings
and escaped Berlin.
That painting there is the last piece.
You have quite the insight,
Mr. Jungle Bunny.
Watch what you say, white man.
I might get upset and return it
to the ocean.
That's fine. I simply wanted to get it
back because it was discovered.
We are a financial success...
...at this time.
But what about the trust you might lose?
I don't like it, but you're right.
You're very wise.
It's a shame you are black.
Thank you. Now, please continue
with your conversation.
No. There's no need for that.
He has already fulfilled his role.
Alfred! You bastard!
First you set me up in this fixed race,
and now you betray me?!
Watch your mouth, youngster.
You and the black man were...
...given equal terms.
You should have known better than
to try and enter our society...
...with that level of ability.
Now, black man. That was a splendid job.
If you were an Aryan,
I would send you an Iron Cross.
I don't want one. All I want
is the money, you Gestapo.
Honesty is wonderful.
Hypocrisy rots this world.
I hope that all people like you will be
wiped off the face of this planet.
Thank you kindly.
And I hope that you'll go to hell.
Come on. You're not done cleaning up?
Is that man the commander?
Yeah.
Wanna make a bet, Dutch?
You know, the usual.
It's not much of a bet, Revy.
Let's do it anyway. Here you go old man.
Use it as you wish.
I say black.
I told you. I say black too.
It's not much of a bet.
See?
Told you. Not much of a bet.
You know, I thought he might
just surprise us.
They're all the same. Rotten by nature.
Damn right. Let's finish this job.
Yeah.
Sure got the shivers today.
Too much trouble.
Shut up. I won't cause any more trouble.
I think I know what you're hung up on.
It has more to do with
what's deep down inside you.
I n other words, you won't feel any better
no matter what you do.
Dutch.
What is it?
Rock's a guy that's on the other side.
He's completely different from
people on our side.
I just can't stand that feeling.
It's not that I don't like him.
But Dutch, it's just not possible. I...
I can't partner with him.
Next Episode
Shut up! Shut up, damn it!
I'm serious! I'm gonna kill you!
Sure, then do it.