Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
I'm terribly sorry,
Your Excellency.
It's a country road for
quite a while.
That's fine.
I'm perfectly satisfied...
...with this beautiful
display of nature.
And there's no need
to worry about me.
I'm a defeated man,
and no longer your leader.
Sir.
Does this area all belong
to the Romefeller Foundation?
Yes.
Initially, the Romefeller
Foundation...
...used its financial power
to protect this beautiful area.
My support for that attitude...
...is precisely why I built
the "Specials" unit...
...within the United Earth
Sphere Alliance.
Then those young warriors
with rebellious wings...
...placed themselves before us.
Passing Destinies
Gundams: the mobile suits made from
Gundanium alloy...
...and sent from the colonies.
The high-level pilots of
these Gundams...
...soon challenged me.
My name is Wu Fei!
I'm Treize Khushrenada.
The duel is mine.
Kill me!
That strength and bravery
was exceptional.
I was moved by every
action they took...
...and could not remain still.
I'm sure it was the same
for you, Zechs Merquise.
However, you should fight
with a pure heart...
...to achieve your goals.
Set the Sanc Kingdom
free from the Alliance's grasp.
All mobile suits have
left the carriers.
Then I'll leave too.
I'll be backing you up.
Concentrate only on achieving
your mission, Lieutenant Zechs.
I'm totally focused.
The new type of mobile suit
is approaching fast!
Direct all laser beams
at that suit!
It took me 13 years to
return to these grounds.
Please forgive me, Father.
There's been much bloodshed
along the way...
...and I've only been able
to live a lifestyle...
...that counters your
pacifist teachings.
My hands are too stained
with blood.
I'm completely unfit to head
the Peacecraft monarchy.
But I'm sure she would
be able to head the country...
...as you'd intended.
I'll fight to make that happen.
I've failed you.
Please forgive me.
By appearing on the
center stage of history...
...we directed the times
in the right direction.
The remaining frontier
is outer space.
Lady Une, I'm leaving outer
space in your hands.
Explain our love to the
people of the colonies.
I'm sure they'll be able
to understand us...
...if you greet them with
your affection.
In the year After Colony 195...
...the United Earth Sphere
Alliance collapsed.
However, the Alliance's forces
remained in space.
In charge of outer space...
...my mission was to
subjugate these forces...
...free the colonies, and allow
them to become independent.
Once this was accomplished...
...we should have achieved
Treize's and our ideals for OZ.
If only Treize and Duke
Dermail hadn't disagreed.
The Gundam pilots witnessed
the changes in history.
Transmission from Earth,
Colonel Une!
Gundams Zero Two and Zero Four are attacking
the Singapore Space Port Base!
I'm returning to the
command tower!
Hurry up, Quatre!
Don't worry about me.
I'll back you two up
until you lift off!
Have you lost your mind?!
We all have to make it
up to outer space!
I know, but that's why I
have to back you up.
To make sure that at least
you two make it!
Quatre!!
You fool!!
And now, the last remaining
choice is to self-detonate.
What's this?
You're telling me to get off?
Sandrock!
Thank you, my dear Sandrock!
But there was neither glory
nor praise to greet them...
...when they returned to
outer space.
All they got was isolation...
...and a cruel destiny fitting
for such rebels.
We'll have to considerably
restrict your activities.
For defeated men like myself...
...restrictions become the
foundation for new strength.
But in my case I feel
much freer, not restricted.
Perhaps until now I didn't
experience freedom.
Maybe my latest move
has allowed me...
...a chance to step back
and re-evaluate myself.
Just like you overcame
the ordeal I put you through...
...and earned your
freedom, Zechs.
Treize, stop following me
around!
I can no longer be your friend!
Farewell, Treize!!
After you left...
...with Chief Engineer
Tubarov at the helm...
...Romefeller completed
those mobile dolls...
...that are incapable of feeling
a battle's beauty or sorrow.
Romefeller used them...
...to try ruling the Earth
from outer space.
As one who looks for
meaning in human battles...
...I couldn't accept the
Foundation's way of thinking.
Zechs, without you OZ
ends up allowing...
...worthless actions by
worthless people.
Very nicely done,
Treize Khushrenada!
The people in space are
close to accepting OZ.
So it seems.
And Colonel Une's achievements
have been impressive.
She's forming friendly relations
with one colony after another.
The sense of independence
built by forming a nation...
...will trigger a desire for
productivity and defense.
This leads to the nation
becoming militaristic.
Which means that every
country on the Earth...
...will jump into OZ's arms
and beg to be governed by us.
It's beautiful Treize.
You've made space a member
of the Romefeller Foundation.
The living environment
of the colonies is bogus.
As is their pacifism.
They may only be a hotbed
leading to countless battles.
Zechs...or rather Milliardo...
Had you already realized that?
The new system since OZ and
the colonies became united...
...has had a considerable
influence on Earth.
On behalf of my nation...
...I've come to find out
about this situation.
Your nation?
That's correct.
I've come here from the
Sanc Kingdom.
I'm Milliardo Peacecraft.
Oh, His Excellency has had
ties with the Sanc Kingdom...
...since his youth.
I heard your nation was
recovering from the wars.
I think I understand
the implications of war.
So I thought I could
give advice...
...to the colonies desiring
military power.
There are many ways
to obtain peace for oneself.
Between us, we'll find
the best direction to take.
You might be on the
right track to peace...
...Representative Lady Une.
My beloved Lady.
You were right all along...
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
As long as mankind
exists in this world...
...there will always be battles.
And denouncing battles
will never lead to peace.
It's natural for this world
to continue fighting.
Treize...
Zechs and the Gundam pilots
are making an effort...
...to construct a new future.
Those that fight have
a sense of fulfillment.
And those in actual combat
are not seen as being tainted.
A human life is more precious
than anything else.
It is because one faces
an enemy...
...and risks his own
precious life...
...that amid all the sorrow,
a warrior's soul shines nobly.
Tag along, on my
journey into hell!!
Pure and genuine
Gundam pilots.
As I've repeatedly seen
the way you fought...
...I couldn't help but
feel inspired.
You changed something
inside me.
Even altered my destiny.
Nataku.
We have to become
a lot stronger.
When the foolish Romefeller
Foundation...
...removed the human aspect
from battles.
I might have suddenly
found myself in a position...
...where I must personally
bury OZ.
But the times have entrusted
the pilots with destiny itself.
Young warriors.
What do you see beyond this
dark mass of confusion?
They continue to fight.
These youngsters who'll
change the times.
Treize is hoping we'll
put up a fight.
There's no choice left
but to battle.
Without fighting, nothing
can be created.
What?
Treize!
Zechs Merquise...
Or rather, my eternal friend,
Milliardo Peacecraft.
OZ is changing, and I'm
sorely lacking in power.
Romefeller's way, or rather...
...the path that mankind is
taking, is too selfish.
I'm shocked to see...
...that their increased power made
them abandon their compassion.
Milliardo, there's one other
person who understands me.
Her feelings toward me have
given her split personalities.
I implore you, Milliardo.
Please save her.
I'm going to fight for Treize...
...to help realize his ideal!
Treize...
I've got no power.
In the confusion of
all these battles...
...I can only walk the
path of a soldier.
Take me to Fortress Barge.
That's when I realized
the purpose of battles...
...isn't limited to making
ideals into reality.
I know this was what
Treize wanted me to understand.
Botched your mission?
You couldn't destroy the base...
...and you didn't kill
Dr. J and the others.
Don't rub it in.
I'm still glad I decided
to come here.
Good news.
Your Gundam and mine
are being rebuilt.
I can hardly wait!
Just watch.
I'll be the God of Death again!
I will.
Well...
...good night...
Even if the Space Colonies
have no reason to retaliate...
...and the pilots are captured
and stripped of their suits...
...those Gundam pilots
will continue to fight.
Quatre.
What's going on?
Trowa.
Outer space has gone mad
so I'll destroy it all.
Tell the others for me.
Tell them to stay away.
I'm telling you not
to get any closer!!
What strong will.
And what purity.
We must fight against
each other.
But our desire to fight
is the same.
Good-bye, Heero.
Trowa, escape!
The Vayeate's gonna explode!
Trowa!
Trowa!!
We have to acknowledge
the facts.
The five of us have become
redundant soldiers.
Trowa!!
Duke Dermail.
I can't support the Romefeller
Foundation's current path.
What?!
I believe that what mankind
needs is not absolute victory...
...but his attitude toward
fighting; his demeanor.
An era constructed by the
soulless weapons...
...known as mobile dolls...
...will become an embarrassment
to future generations.
The traditions you value
so highly...
...would be blurred alongside
those five genuine warriors.
Heero!!
You're saying that you want
Romefeller headquarters...
...to take OZ out of
your control?
I hereby confine you to
Romefeller headquarters!
I have come to a decision.
I'll look over those young
men who shine in battle.
And I'll love them.
I fail to understand
what you're getting at.
That's exactly why you
and I are enemies!
Wanna escape?!
After we pay them back.
Lady Une, my love.
Rest in peace.
Beyond those distant
shining stars...
...I see many destinies pass
by each other.
Time goes by so fast
and fleetingly...
...from my memories of those
olden days.
Operation Nova.
I can't imagine the
Romefeller Foundation...
...allowing the rebellions of
the soldiers that support me.
And now they have sent
mass-produced Virgo dolls...
...to Earth in their quest for
its complete control.
But right now, I have no
right to express these opinions.
Am I right?
Heero.
Let's go to the Earth.
There it is!
Discarding his Gundam
like that...
What was he thinking?
Heero.
The foundation of our future
will be built by these suits.
And now, casting for the
actors is almost complete...
...as we begin the third act.
All that's left is to wait
for the curtain to rise.
Yes.
Everything is proceeding
just as you planned, Treize.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Outer space rushes aimlessly
into a period of battles.
Heero and Quatre arrive
on Earth and are targeted...
...by Romefeller's plan to
execute the Gundam pilots.
Without any time to rest...
...Heero heads to gather data
for his next battle...
...when he hears of Sanc
Kingdom, Relena's home country.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 29,
The Heroine of the Battlefield
"The Heroine of the Battlefield".