I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
At the entrance to the
gulf, the statue of Buddha...
...who brightens the world with the light
of virtue, sits in a sad state.
Beyond it lies the port
of immorality, Roanapur.
From the overland entrance to the city...
...there's always a noose,
hanging for some unknown person.
Past it lies the
city of pleasure, Roanapur.
Until recently a businessman
living in Tokyo...
...I am now a member of a pirate ship.
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Hey, bastard! I'll kill you!
You're not getting away!
You're not getting away! Die, you
bastard! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Revy. I'm stepping out for a bit.
Gotcha. Be careful.
Going out?
Yeah, for a bit.
What the hell is this?
Revy.
Where's Dutch going?
Who knows. It's no concern of ours
what Dutch does in his free time.
I only asked because I was curious.
Nosy types aren't too popular, you know.
What the hell is this?! I don't
know what you paid for this...
...but it's worth less than
nothing. You got burned.
I guess so. In this city, the
situation doesn't...
...improve in the
downtown core either.
You've gotta realize, international
villains run around here ramming horns.
They all trick one another,
from top to bottom.
You're not given the right to live
if you trust everything you see.
Though you're lucky if that's
the biggest of your concerns.
I'll take that to heart.
She's right. I may still be too soft.
After all, I don't even know
the histories of my peers.
Their pasts remain heavily masked
by their sense of independence.
But I don't care. That's how I feel.
Hello, it's me. How are you doing?
Yeah, please.
International number 10013. Right.
Send me 120 thousand dollars.
To the name, Flyers Company.
Yeah.
Hey, Dutch.
I'll talk to you some other time. Oh, boy.
Great weather. Don't you agree?
How's business for you guys?
Not bad, Mr. Chin. We're
pulling through somehow.
That's great. By the way.
How long do you plan to work
with that Fry Face bitch?
I don't know, Mr. Chin. I have no
idea what you're talking about.
I'm talking about that crazy Russian.
Ever since that Ruskie got
here, the market's been down.
Those Ivans took all the prostitutes,
hotel rights, and heroin routes.
Not a shred of honor. And if they
get the sea routes on top of that...
...we're dried out from head to ass.
Get it, don't you? What I
mean is pull out, and quickly.
Let me give you some advice, Mr. Chin.
Even villains have sense. Got that?
When you sold that junk
to the New People's Army...
...we were the ones hired to deliver it.
It wasn't even close to a "no problem"
situation, but who pulled out then?
Let that go, Dutch. Don't bring
up the past like some old bitch.
I'll say what I want.
At the very least, Balalaika
has more honor than you do.
We'll ship your goods at our rate.
We're done talking.
You won't get any
second chances, Dutch.
And you won't get any second
chances with us, Mr. Chin.
Use your head to survive. Later.
Hi, Dutch. Why don't you drop some
money onto us from time to time?
I know what's inside your bottles.
I shipped them here, after all.
That bastard.
Is it true that the torpedo boat bastard...
...works for some Russian
from the countryside?
Yes, sir. But it seems that they'll
take on jobs from pretty much anyone.
This sure is an unhealthy city.
Dutch, I got it. The new board's arrived.
This is the pure,
unadulterated, real deal.
"Pure" is a word you don't
hear much of in this city.
Then hurry and get it on
the boat, Benny.
Yeah, sure thing.
Our crew can really be
so damn simple minded.
Hey, Dutch.
Wake up, sailor! We have a job!
O-Okay. A job?
Where's Rock?
I told him to wash his face, but
he's taking an awfully long time.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
What is it, today?
It just came in, passed
on from Donnie Yen.
Donnie Yen?
He gives us jobs from time to time.
Today, we're receiving
a package from...
...the Vietnamese military
at Phu Quoc island.
And since our schedule is open...
In any case, work is to be respected.
What are we going to do with
all these pathetic jobs, Dutch?
No wonder we can't get him out of
these shitty white collar suits.
Stop that. I like wearing these.
Which reminds me, Rock.
What did you do with that aloha
shirt I got you at the market?
That ugly aloha?! Wearing that
would be pure punishment!
What do you mean, Rock?! You
saying I don't have taste?!
Stop that!
Got it.
Looks like they fell for the trap.
Whether you want to go ahead
or not is up to you now, Luak.
I know you've been down
on your luck lately.
I hear you messed up on the last hunt
and got chased around by a battleship.
What's that? You take care of this...
...and you get all the tolls
between here and Kalimantan.
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
Give that lots of thought.
I told you, Dutch. You're not
gonna get any second chances.
Like this... like this... this... and then...
Like this. Hey...
That's funny.
Come on.
You're desperately clumsy. Or
are you just not trying hard?
Sorry.
You're just not cut out for this.
Like this. Look. Even
a monkey can do this.
I guess. But don't be so hard
on me. I never did this at work.
Rock. What did you do at work?
I was with the materials
procurement department...
...so I went on business
trips, wrote reports...
...made phone calls, but
I think lowering my head...
...to my superiors was my real job.
Come night, I'd accompany my superiors
when he'd go out for drinks.
I even got my ass kicked once
when he was drunk.
That's great, Rock.
That was a disgusting story.
Putting up with all that crap.
Are you some masochist?
Putting up with it is part of the job.
No one wants to end up on the streets.
Everyone survives like that.
Pathetic.
Revy. What did you do
before coming here?
What I do hasn't really
changed from then to now.
Really. Then let me guess.
As a kid, you ran around by the river,
swinging around your Sword Cutlass.
It's true. I stole, I killed...
...I did everything that's considered bad.
Nothing fascinating about it.
Dutch, we've got several boats.
You better pray, Dutch, 'cause you'll
need directions on how to get to heaven.
There shouldn't be...
...any merchants around.
It's a pirate's bay. Can
you find out what they are?
They're small and fast.
They could be police boats...
...looking to arrest pirates...
Dutch! A red alert!
What the hell is this. They blew right
by the yellow and gave us the red lamp.
Their speed, 28 knots.
Dutch!
Hold on.
Benny will explain the
situation to you.
Wait a second.
There are three more!
A total of six boats!
The first three started accelerating from
the side of the island we just passed.
The other three on port side came
from behind a different island.
Changing course to
port side is dangerous.
The ships on the left will
catch up to us.
But to starboard, the guys
on the right will get us.
A basic hunting pattern.
Those guys are fast, too.
Hey Dutch.
Yeah?
I smell it.
You know who they are?
It stinks all the way up here.
These guys aren't marine cops.
These guys stink too much
of blood and smoke for that.
Pirates?! We're being
targeted by pirates?!
Dutch! What's the
background on our client?
Rock. That observation hurts.
I've been conducting checks on
Donnie Yen's economic situation.
Hello!
Hello! Can you hear
me, Lagoon?! It's me!
It's been a while, Dutch.
Oh I see. It's Luak.
There's no prey here. Go
home before you get lost.
There's prey right here, Beans.
An old torpedo boat with
a nice wingspan.
Our counterpart has six boats. If it is
Luak, he's brought everything he's got.
Damn it, all these bastards.
Chin got you involved in
this, didn't he, Luak?
God must pity you for your stupidity.
Once we get a pint of lead in you, maybe
it'll put an end to your sleep talk.
The enemy's got us on both sides.
But these positions, Dutch...
I know, Rock. Get inside.
Stop! Don't shoot!
Nice job.
If you're gonna surround the enemy, it's
common sense to position yourselves...
...out of each other's
line of fire. Amateurs.
Bastard. Don't get too confident.
I'll send you straight to hell.
There are still four vessels. Dutch...
...they're coming.
Revy...
...It's your turn. Give
them a taste of "Two-Hands".
Leave it to me.
It's show time. Can
you make them dance?
Of course.
Revy! What are you planning to do?
Rock. We're taking a break from
the casual talk about your world.
I need to concentrate on this world.
Benny-boy.
There are two on the left, and two more
to the right, behind us. Am I right?
And one more...
...right behind us.
Do that one last, Revy.
All right. I'll start with the
shit on the left.
Let's dance the jitterbug!
She jumped!
She's jumped onto another boat.
Do something about that bitch!
Damn, I can't see with the smoke!
Make sure you don't hit
one of our guys!
Damn it!
Kill her! Kill her! Finish her off!
Rock. Which boat is she on now?
She's working on her
fifth boat. Wait...
...the third's still alive.
There she is! Shoot her! Kill her!
Damn it. My... My ships...
It's a dead end. It seems
like you're the one destined...
...to dance the cha-cha
with some hot lead, Luak.
Damn it! How dare...
That bitch isn't human.
I'm not dealing with
these demons any more!
She defeated the whole group
all on her own. Amazing.
While saying that out loud, I
was having different thoughts.
I don't know what got shattered
to make her like this...
...but I must be pretty broken
myself for praising this woman...
...for her destructiveness.
Damn it! That stingy Luak.
He's failed me.
That idiot. I'd like to see the mother who
would bring up a child to be like that.
He shoved a burner up my ass,
and then conveniently croaked.
Things couldn't be worse! I'd like to
kill that Luak myself, all over again.
Well, well, well...
Moving out so suddenly?
That's such hard work.
Shall we help, Mr. Chin?
N-N-Never mind. You must have
misunderstood something.
It's a pathetic rumor going around.
If we sort it out over lunch, you'll
see that any fool...
...can understand what happened.
Listen carefully, you piece of horse shit.
We've got nothing to ask you.
We already know everything
we need to know.
Pray. That's about the only thing
you can still do while you're alive.
We busted our asses for
nothing. So damn stupid.
It's not so bad. Kinda
like being bitten by a dog.
It's terrible, moron. Bullets
aren't free, you know.
Yes. Lagoon Company.
Oh, Japonski! It's been a while.
Is Dutch around?
Who is it?
Ms. Balalaika.
Hi Dutch.
I heard you went on a wild goose chase.
And you got stuck playing with Chin.
Who told you?
He told me himself.
He's a bit too loud to
conspire about anything.
He was blabbing away about it to
practically every group in town...
...so even the dead would've
known what was happening.
Anyway, we'll make sure nothing
like this happens again.
It was a pain for you, wasn't it?
Not really. It wasn't even
enough to give me a headache.
Thanks, Dutch. I realize it's nothing
compared to what you went through...
...but I'll let you hear
something amusing.
So-called "pleasure and pain".
Oh?
Cooler than J.B.?
Of course.
Yeah, that's cool.
We'll have a job for you
soon. I'll call you then.
Was that a call about a job?
Something like that.
She filled me in on some
gossip to lift my spirits.
Revy. Rock. Do you guys
have any plans?
Not really.
How about you, Benny?
Maintenance on the electronics,
but nothing that can't wait.
Well, then.
Considering the mental anguish
incurred due to external interference...
...as your employer, it is my duty to
provide entertainment as compensation.
And therefore...
I propose a trip to the Yellow Flag...
...to drink away our pain.
Of course, it's on me.
So, who's coming?
Can we stay there till dawn?!
I'm going!
Ah, me too!
Then it's decided, Benny! Get the car!
Rock, it's not a job. Wear
that aloha shirt!
I don't wanna.
Next Episode
Despite that, there are fights
that you must still take on.
Let's go. Prepare the torpedoes
for surface attack!