Come on, Issei.
Hurry up!
It's delicious!
Okay!
U-Um, should I help him carry the bags?
It's okay.
He has to be able to handle it.
I'm going on ahead.
Damn you for showing off how easy you have it!
Pardon me.
I give up!
You got it?
The game will be held in ten days.
Ten days?
Given the differences in experience and resources between Raiser and you,
I believe this is necessary to level the playing field.
I hate to admit it, but I have to agree.
I'm going to take you up on your offer and use the time for training.
Issei, I'll use this training camp to make you a lot stronger.
A lot stronger.
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
I Began Training!
Episode 9
Wow! This place looks lovely!
Let's get inside and start training right away.
Training?!
Just as I thought, you're a monster, President!
No, I'm a devil.
Hey, Kiba.
Back when we fought at that church,
you said something about hating fallen angels and priests.
And personally, I'm not overly fond of fallen angels and priests.
I despise them.
Just like how she saved you and Asia,
the President also helped us.
That's why we have to win this game for her.
Right?
Yeah, of course!
Lesson one.
Let's see if I can do this!
It's not simply about swinging your sword.
Watch your opponent and surroundings.
Just as expected of a knight.
Come on!
Don't let your guard down!
Lesson two.
Direct your entire body's aura flow to
one area to concentrate your magic.
Focus your mind and feel the flow of magic.
I did it!
Oh my,
it seems Asia-chan has a talent for magic.
W-Well, Asia getting stronger is actually great too.
Woah, awesome!
Once you get used to magic, you can
manipulate things like water, fire, or lightning.
Asia-chan, this is what you're going to practice next.
Sure!
Issei-kun, you should continue
practicing to focus your magic.
O-Okay.
The source of magic is your imagination.
Forming a clear image in your head is essential.
An image in my head, eh?
Yes.
There, that's it. Concentrate.
Concentrate!
What am I thinking?
What's wrong, Issei-kun?
No, nothing!
I-I'll do my best!
Lesson three.
Weak.
I'm just getting started!
Aim for your opponent's body's line of symmetry,
and try to deliver a deep, precise blow.
Damn it! I don't stand a chance
against Kiba or Koneko-chan at all.
As for magic, Asia is way better.
I suck!
Everyone has their specialty.
Specialty?
What do you think is my specialty?
You're a pervert.
Also, one other thing:
You're a hard worker.
I-Is that so?
I'm going to try hard, Koneko-chan!
Okay.
Lesson four.
This time we're using magic...
...to cook?
Just do what you can.
Good luck!
Water, please boil!
During Akeno-san's lessons,
I could only conjure a mere speck of magic.
But just thinking about her breasts makes me so...
Wow, potatoes are easy as well!
This is amazing, Issei-san!
I just wasn't in form earlier.
This is my true power.
You're amazing!
I think this happened before.
Oh, yeah,
it was when my Sacred Gear activated the very first time.
I see!
With this...
I might...
become invincible!
Issei-san,
what should we do about this?
The source of magic is your imagination.
Forming a clear image in your head is essential.
Everyone has their specialty.
You're a pervert.
You're making a lewd face.
Not at all!
Issei?
Yes!
How are you feeling after your first day of training?
Well, I was the weakest.
Yes, without a doubt.
But, Asia's healing ability and your Boosted Gear
are both valuable resources to us.
Our opponents are aware of this too,
so make sure you can at least protect
yourselves and don't drag the others down.
R-Roger.
Yes.
True, I'm the one who got Asia into this.
At the very least, I have to be able to protect her.
Okay, since we've finished eating, let's take a bath.
A bath?!
Oh, Issei, are you planning to peek on us bathing?
Want to go in together with us? I won't mind.
How about you, Akeno?
I want to try washing a guy's back.
Asia, you won't object to bathing with your beloved, will you?
Koneko?
Don't wanna.
Never mind, then.
Too bad.
If you peek, I'll hate you.
Like I thought, hot springs are great.
I hope this'll alleviate the fatigue from training,
even if it's just a bit.
It will, without a doubt.
Don't be greedy.
W-Well...
Issei-kun, that's a pointless—
Shut up! This is also training!
Are you trying to become clairvoyant?
What do you think is my specialty?
You're a pervert.
Yes, that's my power!
My power!
Just as expected.
Yes.
How typical of her.
Her chances of winning are...
Yes, pretty much nonexistent.
You knew that, but you still...
I merely gave her a choice.
Rias made the decision herself
as heiress apparent of the Gremory household.
Yes.
Asia. Asia.
Issei-san!
Sorry to wake you,
but you're the only one I can ask for this.
Sorry?
I can do it!
I'm sure I can do it!
Issei-san!
Asia, I want to borrow your clothes.
He looked so serious.
What is he trying to do?
Well,
we devils, the fallen angels, and God with his heavenly host,
waged a huge war a long time ago
that seemed to last an eternity.
No one really won when all was said and done.
The war ended with all sides suffering heavy casualties.
To make up for our near eternal lifespan,
we devils reproduce very slowly.
Due to the war, the species itself is at the brink of extinction.
After the hostilities, the families of noble and pure-blooded devils,
known as the 72 Pillars, mostly died out.
My family - the Gremory house,
Sona's family - the Sitri house,
and Raiser's Phoenix
are all that remains of the 72 Pillars.
This is why we devils use
resurrected humans as our servants.
Subsequently, the Rating Game was created.
It allows our servants to gain real battle experience
and gives us masters a chance to demonstrate our abilities.
Currently, one's performance in these games has a huge influence on rank and position.
We should take a break now.
I guess all of you are tired.
I'll go make some tea.
Ah, I'll help you!
Asia!
Sorry about last night.
Oh no! You were really amazing back th—
Let's keep it our secret for now.
Our?
It's still not done and far from usable.
I get it.
I'll help you until your ultimate move is complete!
Ultimate move?
It's a secret!
Oh yeah, Asia.
Because you were a nun,
please tell us what you know.
O-Okay.
Well, there are two key tools that the exorcists possess.
The first one is holy water.
Devils like you should not touch it.
What happens if we do?
Something very bad.
Bad?
Being ambiguous only makes it scarier.
Asia, you're a devil too.
Oh, I forgot.
I don't know whether it'll be useful,
but I can show you how it's made.
There's also this,
the Bible.
I've been reading it since childhood.
But now, even reading a single line
gives me a splitting headache!
I'm at wits' end!
You're a devil, after all.
It's expected of a devil.
A devil.
It damages devils a lot!
But, but, this passage is absolutely enlightening!
Ah, it hurts!
O Lord, please forgive me for no
longer being able to read the Bible!
Ah, I can't take it!
I can't decide whether she's serious or trying to be funny.
But I'm even less talented than Asia.
One more time!
Issei?
Oh, President.
What're you doing at this hour?
Perfect timing.
Let's have a talk.
Is that about war strategy?
Yes, but to be honest, playing it by the book
only offers a bit of consolation.
That can't be true!
You're working hard this late at night...
But this time we're up against Phoenix.
I'm sure you heard of it.
A sacred beast said to be an immortal bird.
Although they're devils,
his family shares the name with this sacred beast.
On top of that, they're a Great Marquis family, considered elite even among the 72 pillars.
He also shares the sacred beast's power:
immortality.
Immortality? Is that even possible?
Well, he's pretty much invincible.
Even if you hurt him, he'll regenerate instantly.
His game record shows eight wins and two losses.
However, these two losses
were against an allied family.
He lost on purpose.
After the Rating Game became prevalent
the Phoenix house rose to prominence extremely fast.
It's natural, right?
Being immortal, he simply can't lose.
I'm sorry.
What for?
I spoke up against Raiser back then,
forcing you into this fight.
Actually, that was rather helpful.
We could cut to the chase afterward.
My father has set up this game in advance, knowing I will probably lose.
It's a trap. In chess terms,
a swindle.
Um, why are you so opposed to the engagement?
I'm the daughter of the Gremory house.
I'm never treated as an individual.
I'm always Rias Gremory.
The name Gremory follows me everywhere.
Although I am proud of my house,
when it comes to finding a life partner,
I want someone who loves me.
Not as daughter of the Gremory family, but as Rias.
They may be conflicting ideals,
but I still hold on to this small dream.
I'd love you regardless of rank and name.
I don't know anything about your family or the social hierarchy of devils.
But I can see you right here, right now,
and Rias-senpai, you're my number one.
D-Did I say something strange?
Not at all.
Anyway, let's try to win this battle.
A while back, Kiba told me
people call you the Ruin Princess
because you're a genius of that magnitude.
And now your first battle is against that guy...
You're wrong.
My powers are not a natural boon,
but something cultivated by the
Gremory house for many generations.
They belong to both me and the Gremory household.
That's why I won't lose.
If I'm fighting, I will win.
I must win.
You're amazing, just as I thought.
Compared to that,
I suck.
Issei?
Being here makes me constantly realize
I'm the most useless.
Even if I possess a great Sacred Gear,
it's wasted on me.
Despite that, I always foolishly rush forward.
In the end, I'm always causing you problems.
I'm... I'm...
completely useless!
You want confidence, don't you, Issei?
Okay, I'll give you more confidence.
Confidence?
That's right.
So, you should try to calm your mind and body for now.
I'll stay next to you until you fall asleep.
Don't worry, Issei.
I will definitely instill you with confidence.
Use your Boosted Gear, Issei!
But you said I shouldn't use it during this camp.
Without my permission, I meant.
Can you be his opponent, Yuuto?
Of course, President.
I won't go easy on you!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Try again.
Once more.
Boost!
Still not enough.
One more time!
Boost!
Try harder!
He powered up twelve times.
Stop.
Issei, do you see now?
You wouldn't have been able to handle so many boosts before this camp.
That's the result of your training.
I see!
Begin.
Let's go. Boosted Gear!
Explosion!
What is that?
It allows Issei to fight with the
accumulated power for some time.
Yuuto!
Issei, unleash your magic!
Damn, I still fail!
Shoot!
You...!
My, my.
The mountain...
...was leveled to the ground!
This is my power...
Issei-san!
I guess he used up all his energy.
Yuuto, how was he?
Well, I was really surprised.
That single burst was equivalent to a high-class devil's attack!
Issei, you will be a decisive factor in the game.
Your attack power will greatly influence the flow of it.
Believe in us and more than anything else, in yourself.
Believe in everyone
and myself.
Issei!
I'd love you regardless of rank and name.
Rias-senpai, you're my number one.
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
But we're in the middle of an important game!
This is unbelievable!
Come on, why are you crying?
Episode 10
The Decisive Battle Is Starting!
Sorry, Asia.
It's time! Are you ready?