Chu-ru-chu-chu doushitai?
What do you want to do?
Chu-ru-chu Hey girls?
Hey, girls
raburii debiru
lovely devils
Chu-ruchuchu aa shitai♪ YES!!
You know what we wanna do! Yes!
kyou mo kourin
They've descended upon us again
shoujo wa shinkakei ni yokubari na no desu
Girls are always greedy for more
are mo kore mo
I want this, I want that
kinou to kuraberu n ja manzoku dekinai
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
arere
Uh-oh
appugureedo sakusen kaigi
Let's have a strategy meeting on how to upgrade
sansei
Agreed!
daredemo hitotsu kurai motte iru desho
I'm sure you have at least one of these
kimi mo kimi mo
You too, and you too
orijinaru no jumon kokoro no omamori
Original magic words that protect your heart
aruru
Uh-huh
purasu shikou taishitsu kyouka
Positive thoughts that give you strength
koi mo yume mo totte oki wo ne, te ni ireru tame ni
Never compromising our love or dream
minna
Everyone
fiiringu juushi de
We want to follow our heart
risaachi
Research
seichou shitai na
As we grow up
onna no ko wa ne raburii debiru
You see, girls are lovely devils
mune no naka kakushiteru no toriatsukai youchuui
Deep down in their hearts, so treat them with great care
tanoshii koto shika kyoumi nai no yo
They're only interested in having fun
wagamama ni kawaiku naru n da
Their whimsical temper makes them cute
yakusoku
Promise!