Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
In the year After Colony 175...
...the leader of the colonies
was assassinated.
Five Gundams were sent
to Earth to take revenge.
However, since OZ's activities
in space...
...took the form of cooperation
rather than control...
...the colonies decided
to accept OZ.
The year After Colony 195.
As OZ moves to take over
both Earth and outer space...
...Gundams are labeled rebels
and are isolated from society.
With no place to return...
...the Gundams and
their pilots...
...must fight for a reason to
exist in the changing world.
Hurry up and return, Zechs.
If you're not around to help...
...OZ will allow worthless
actions by worthless people.
Treize...
I can no longer be your friend.
Assault on Barge
I'm alive...
Hey!
Howard, look at him!
Give me a minute!
You don't look bad.
Can you get up?
You were piloting that
interesting machine.
I picked it up, as well.
I never would have guessed...
...that anyone other than those
kids could pilot the Tallgeese.
Who are you?
I'm one of the people who
was involved in its design.
But that was long ago.
You mean you made the Tallgeese?
I was sailing through this area...
...and I saw an intense battle.
I stuck around to watch.
You in pain?
Why did you bother
to save me?
You've become OZ's enemy.
Zechs Merquise.
OZ's very own hero has
broken away from them.
There's no harm in
taking care of you.
Zechs Merquise is dead.
That's what they say.
The times are changing.
I'd love to see the new era
while I'm still alive.
It's a fabulous piece
of machinery.
No wonder it's the prototype
for the Gundams.
Are those vernier rockets
for atmospheric clearance?
To tell the truth, they were
originally manufactured...
...to get the Gundams
back into outer space.
Oh, by the way...
Think you can make it
to outer space?
Outer space?
It's about to undergo
a drastic transformation.
There's a growing need for
skilled people like you.
OZ started cracking down...
...on the former United Earth
Sphere Alliance Space Force...
...stationed at La Grange Points.
OZ was steadily increasing its
strength within the colonies.
The Space Fortress Barge was
symbolic of this strength.
But OZ didn't reveal its
aggressive side...
...to the colony citizens.
Instead, it showed a completely
different aspect of itself.
OZ's Colonel Une replaced
the former Alliance...
...as the Commander
of the Space Force.
She formed relations with
representatives of the colonies.
With a sense of liberation...
...from the militaristic
pressure of the Alliance...
...the colonies were welcoming
OZ in its new establishment.
In order to attain peace
and to coexist...
...in the colonies and within
the whole Earth Sphere...
...we must have your
cooperation.
Unfortunately though, some
people within the colonies...
...are doubtful of OZ.
They point out mistakes
that were made in the past.
However, I believe that
the day will come...
...when these people will
understand OZ's efforts.
We feel they'll change
their minds as well.
We're trying hard to
convince each of the colonies.
On the other hand, we have
no means to counter violence.
That's what OZ is here for.
As long as OZ is present...
...I have no doubt that
justice will be served.
If Colonel Une says so,
then there's no need to worry.
Once peace spreads into space...
...even those who still
harbor doubts toward OZ...
...will awaken to the truth.
Yes.
Colonel Une!
We have the item in question.
Huh?
Colonel, please return to Barge.
To Barge?
Orders from His Excellency
Treize.
His Excellency Treize...
I'll return to Barge.
Are you certain?
No question.
It's the HLV carrier that left
Earth carrying a Gundam.
The Gundams are evil and
will harm the colonies.
They'd be valuable as
our evil scapegoats.
Bring out the Tauruses!
Capture it!
What about the pilot?
Depends on his looks.
Huh?
If he's ugly, let him live.
If people could sympathize
with him, then kill him.
We can't have anything
interfere with...
...changing public opinion.
Let him live if he's ugly?
Just kidding.
We have confirmation.
It's an HLV from Singapore
used to transport a Gundam.
No energy detected.
It's a miracle it flew
this far without refueling.
It might be unmanned.
Regardless, orders are
to capture it.
We'll tow it along to
Colony C 102.
Roger!
What?!
What an honor, being
greeted by the latest model.
But anyone carelessly
approaching me will die!
Taurus mobile dolls, attack!
They're fast!
Damn!!
That didn't work either!
Zero output.
My Deathscythe's bought it
and I don't have long myself.
But still, I'll die fighting!
Gundam, you're just lucky
that I wasn't a mobile doll!
I don't want to copy
Heero, but...
Tag along, on my
journey into hell!!
Not my lucky day.
Can't even self-detonate.
Or maybe...I am lucky...
One of the Gundam
mobile suits...
...known for their destruction
and threat to peace...
...was shot down by
OZ's Taurus unit.
The Gundam pilot has
been arrested.
The background of this pilot
has not been confirmed.
But OZ has said that
the arrest will assist them...
...as they attempt to eradicate
rebels and their organizations.
The colony governments have
announced their cooperation.
Hopefully with the cooperation
of OZ and the colonies...
...we will soon be able
to return to total peace.
Are the people of the colonies
so used to being controlled...
...that nobody can figure out
the Gundams are the only ally?
Still, I have no choice left
but to fight.
It's too far away from here.
But it's near the colony
Heero went to.
He'll do something, for sure.
After Colony 175.
No major incidents within
the colonies?
The assassination of the leader
Heero Yuy has been deleted.
OZ's methods haven't
changed one bit.
OZ has said that
this will assist them...
...as they attempt to
eradicate rebels...
This wouldn't be the
right time for battle.
All negative factors
must be eliminated.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Flight 0904, proceed to R28.
Proceed to R28...
What's this?
Following the capture
of the mad scientists...
...who were foes to the colonies
and the people of Earth...
...one of the Gundams and
its pilot have now been caught.
Colony C 102 authorities are
calling OZ's actions a success.
They say they'll continue to
promote cooperative efforts.
Hooray for OZ!
I wasn't expecting the Gundam
pilot to be just a kid.
Well, excuse me!
Have I wounded your pride?!
Not compared to how
your pride has suffered.
You'll be executed.
The people's feelings toward the
execution will unite the colonies.
I never expected to use
the Gundam pilots this way.
Why you!
Damn all of you!
Shit, they did me over.
This sucks.
What a surprise, Heero.
You really are superhuman.
Just in time.
They were about to use me and
my Gundam for their plans.
If I'm gonna die, then this
seems like the way to go.
Go ahead and shoot me.
Hey, you're seriously gonna
shoot me, aren't you?
If that's what you want.
Your right hand's still okay?
So, where's your Gundam?
I left it on Earth.
It'd stick out, here in space.
Then I'd get caught like you.
Yeah, well pardon me.
How will you get
us out of here?
I came to kill you.
I hadn't thought up
an escape plan yet.
And if we don't make it?
It's as simple as silencing
the two of us.
What's going on?!
What happened?!
It's always the quiet guys
who're the flashiest.
Several small bombs have been
set in the supplies block!
What about the Gundam?
Increase security around
the Gundam pilot!
Surveillance here!
The Gundam pilot has escaped
with an outsider's help!
Damn it!
What about the Gundam?!
There were explosions
in the area.
But no sign of intruders.
Show me the explosion points.
Explosions are centered around
the supplies storage and gate.
The mobile suit gate and area
is untouched!
The enemy will escape
from there!
Send out the dolls!
Wouldn't target settings be
difficult within the colony?!
The dolls aren't a
cheap system!
They're annihilation machines!
Deploy them at once!
Enemy attack in Colony C 102!
Backup troops, head
there at once!
What?!
I finally found you.
Now you can show me
what you're made of!!
We're sending Tauruses
to attack!
Colonel!!
Colonel Une!
Look out!
A Gundam is right by the base!
She's going to a colony
meeting in a new district.
Colonel!!
This couldn't be all you've got.
You people are strong enough
to control the colony citizens.
You're underhanded and
much stronger!
Lieutenant Nichol!
Gundam Zero Five and the Leos
in pursuit...
...are in the firing range
of Barge's Beam Cannon!
Okay, fire!!
But we'd fire on our Leos!
No matter!
Do it before the Colonel leaves!
Gundam Zero Five is within
firing range!
Fire!!
Yes, sir!!
Sacrificing your own men?!
I've never seen the enemy
as foul as they are now.
When deceitful guys like you
are strong, I can fight you!
Please, stop this futile battle.
Let us greet a new age together.
Who's that?!
Let's do away with any
desires to battle...
...which were left over
from the passing era.
Such destructive desires
aren't needed in the future.
Who are you?!
Taurus troops, we're moving
in on the Gundam!
Please end this futile battle.
Colonel Une, please give us
orders to attack!
I can't do that.
Peace should prevail
in outer space.
Colonel!
Never mind, attack Zero Five!
Just you wait OZ;
I'll come back to get you!
- We're going after Zero Five!
- Sir!
No, wait!
Forget it!
Which Colonel am I
supposed to follow?
So those new models
are the mobile dolls.
No wonder their reaction
time is quick!
Once they're locked onto
a target, there's no escaping.
Then how will we get away?
I'm not thinking about escaping.
What?!
Duo!
We could use this.
Hey!
What's going on?!
Why are the mobile dolls
attacking the Leos?!
I got it.
A Leo was scrambling
to get off the premises.
So the mobile dolls
set it as a target!
And it seems another
target has been set.
It's an astro suit!
The astro suit has also
been set as a target!
Cancel the auto command!
Cancel it! Hurry!!
I left my Gundam behind.
I've gotta destroy it!
The Gundams are worthless.
What?!
Dr. J and the other scientists
who designed the Gundams...
...have all been caught by OZ.
I'll kill them all.
Heero...
I'll eliminate all obstacles.
This is going overboard,
to get one person into space.
Outer space is rejecting humans.
And perhaps the Earth is
telling us we're wrong...
...by pulling us back down
toward it.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The five scientists start
developing OZ's new suits...
...Mercurius and Vayeate.
In an attempt to stop them...
...Heero sneaks on the Lunar
Base to assassinate them.
But he's stopped in his tracks
by none other than Trowa.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 20,
The Lunar Base Infiltration
"The Lunar Base Infiltration".