Maximum Titillation OVA Vol. 3
Koneko's Healing Sage Arts, Meow
How is that?
Feels great.
The Juggernaut Drive took
a lot of your life energy.
I don't want you to die.
I'll spend my whole life
healing you if I have to.
Just never let that happen to you again.
I won't. I won't worry you guys ever again.
That's great. Thank you.
Issei...
There's a much quicker method, actually.
Oh? What is it?
Th-The Carnal Arts.
A lady who's an expert
told me yesterday that using it
to share a man's energy
can significantly revitalize him.
Wow. There's that handy of a technique?
Maybe I'll have you use it next time.
A-All right.
But... it would be my first time too...
Huh?
By the way, how do you do these Carnal Arts?
Th-The woman becomes one with the man
and her body sends energy
directly to the man's body.
W-Wait, do you... doing it?!
Me and you... doing it?!
I can't!
Are you not satisfied with me?
N-No, no, no! It's not like that!
You're my junior, and, well, err...
I may have a tiny body
and chest, but I ca n do "it."
I can have children, too.
I-I'm ready to, if need be.
K-Koneko! No! Don't be a naughty girl!
But I can't help but feel
I should when I'm in this house.
Listen, Koneko! Don't try to
compete with the other girls erotically!
You need to be yourself, always!
No matter how difficult it is!
But...
Koneko! You shouldn't
try to mimic the other girls!
They're nothing but a bad influence! Got it?!
Bad influence? Whatever do you mean?
P-P-President!
Well, Issei?
Err, uhh, well...!
- Issei! Is that how you see us?!
- Yes?! No?!
Fine! No more fondling for you!
Tonight didn't work out...
but someday, for sure!
Let's see how yo u like getting poked!
Sure! Be my guest!