I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Have you finished getting changed,
big sister?
Yes. We won't be coming back here.
Let's gather what we need and go.
I know, big sister.
Here, big brother.
Please become big sister.
Yes, big brother.
Shall we go, big sister?
Don't forget our tickets
and passports.
Of course not. Without them,
we can't go anywhere...
...and they won't let us
through anywhere.
Then let us be
on our way, big brother.
Big sister.
Yes. Yes. That's precisely it.
That's what reminded me. Yes.
Thank you, Rock.
I'll be sure to return the favor sometime.
Rock was able to give me the answer.
The kids are from
Count Dracula's home country.
They're Romanian.
That was Romanian!
Romanian troops at Kabul
were speaking similar words.
I should've known.
Really, as people get older, remembering
things becomes quite the task.
Don't worry about it, Sergeant.
It's the same with me.
Sergeant. Rowan, the owner of
the pink shop on Rachiada Street...
...secretly sells illegal videos,
doesn't he?
Yes, he does.
What about Rowan?
You got rid of unwanted company,
have you, Chang?
Yeah.
This is a delicate meeting. It would
be so much nicer if this were a date.
You can't enjoy a matinée with the
smell of blood lingering, now can you?
Chang, we now know who they are.
I see.
That's an intriguing subject.
How'd you find out?
In the end, we found out what we
needed from an item Rowan sells.
Rowan, the porn shop guy?
You called him to your office?
He must've been scared as hell.
Enough to create a masterpiece
in his pants.
What an unfortunate man.
What I demanded from him
was kiddie porn...
...or a snuff film starring
Romanian twins.
He came up with 250 titles.
Again, very unfortunate.
I tackled those 250 made-for-pervert
videos all night and half the next day...
...then finally, bingo.
Hansel and Gretel.
That's what they were
called in the video.
Following the change of government
in Romania...
...many children were sold
to the black market...
...by facilities that could no longer
take care of them.
Illegitimate children of the dead dictator.
Treated like toys by sick perverts, they
eventually ended up as food for the pigs.
So how were these kids, destined for
the same fate, able to get away?
For entertainment, the sick fools decided
to let them take part in some killings.
Killings of sacrificed children
much like themselves.
In order to survive
from one night to the next...
...these kids desperately learned
how to kill in ways...
...that would please the perverts.
And over time, the kids
would come to accept all of it.
They left the world of blue skies
and fell into the pitch-black shadows.
Stunt dogs for video entertainment.
What a brutal story.
It suits our world perfectly.
You know, I sometimes feel
I'm walking on this huge piece of shit.
Stuff like morality and justice
just don't suit me.
Words like that are surprisingly similar
to the stuff that comes outta your ass.
I have about the same amount
of sympathy for those kids...
...as I have for the idiots selling missiles
while preaching about peace.
I'm merely telling you what I know.
We have no need for justice.
All we need is profit and trust.
Once we got to Rowan,
the rest was simple.
I see. So this is where it came from.
Having their own killed does work
as a perfect alibi, doesn't it?
They were intended for show.
It's not as if they ever learned manners.
They scatter trouble and create shit.
Your men just happened to
get caught in the blast.
Whatever the reason,
they're gonna have to pay for it.
What's going on?! Damn it!
They only have to get rid of
that lady fox...
...yet they keep adding
unwanted dead bodies!
- Boss.
- Yeah?
Why don't we just call it quits?
If we stop now, we could still get away...
...by saying we got rid of the nut job
that wreaked havoc in town.
If we're gonna get rid of those kids
without causing a commotion...
...now would be the time.
How dare a petty underling like you
talk back to your boss!
But Boss! They're too much to handle!
Why do you think...
...we called those damn kids
over here in the first place?!
Don't you agree it's about time
to change the color of this city, Chang?
There'd no longer be a purpose
for the information sessions.
You gonna start another war?
I'd rather you refer to it as a controlled
conflict. We have reason and motive.
So it's a war with a just cause. I never
thought of you as the type for pretty talk.
It's simply a matter of whether or not
it works as an excuse.
Have the dogs chew on
whether or not it's just.
Join us or forget about it.
It's your call.
You got a point.
It's not something I should need to
consult my country about.
The one and only thing that can
be trusted in this world is power.
Does this mean we'll be seeing
the gunman within you again?
I'm counting on you, Babe.
I don't dislike standing in
the gaming room...
...but right now I have a position
to protect. Such a drag.
Oh, and one other thing.
Don't call me "Babe".
I hate that nickname.
Captain?
Sergeant. Chang has agreed
to our suggestion.
As of this moment, we will form a
common front with the Hong Kong Triad.
Roger.
Send a message
to our fellow comrades.
Standby for assumed battle,
from nineteen-o-five hours.
Recite "Regulation 217, Case Five".
Standby for assumed battle,
from nineteen-o-five hours.
A snatch mission within the city's
controlled battlegrounds.
Correct.
Chaos is to be expected.
The city is like a festival with everyone
trying to get their hands on the reward.
The festive spirit
is a good thing, Captain.
All the better if it comes from
the sound of bullets being fired.
You're right about that, Sergeant.
This is the only type of war we can
be involved in right now.
We'll deal with it with respect.
You know, the Bosses of Palermo...
...have expressed an interest
in this damn, boring city!
They're fed up with me because
I haven't been able to take control!
Listen very carefully,
you damn bastards!
Unless I do something about it now...
...you know what will happen to me
at the next meeting of the top brass?!
- Damn it!
- Um... Um, Boss?
- Shut up!
- But... Um... the twins...
Th-Those kids...
I-I thought I told you not to come here!
What are you doing here?!
The two of us talked it over,
and made a decision.
What the hell?!
Yes.
We'll have borscht for our main dish.
We'll start with macaroni.
D-Don't mess with me
y-you damn brats!
Looks like the macaroni
is thoroughly boiled.
You damn kids!
You wanna die now, do you?!
Boss Chang. We've completely
surrounded the building.
We'll move in as soon as
you give the order.
Cho.
Yes?
You'd be wise to keep your head low.
Our job has just been
changed to hunting.
Contact Hotel Moscow.
I want to do them a favor
they'll feel obliged to pay back.
Revy. The police are on the move.
They're about to close off
the main street.
There appears to have been some
movement around the Verrocchio family.
Revy! We'll never reach the prize
from the bleachers!
I know. Stop shouting, Eda.
So, where do we meet?
Joey got a room at the Palcana Square.
Get here quickly!
Oh boy. The blasting fuse has been lit.
There's no stopping the bomb
from exploding now.
All units, attention!
Fellow comrades. Earlier tonight,
the Verrocchio Family was assaulted.
However, there are no changes
to our plan. We expected this to happen.
We commence our plan now!
My brave fellow comrades.
Private Sakharov and Corporal Menshov
were very special comrades.
We will light the sacred light of repose!
The souls of our passed comrades will
turn our guns into a goddess of revenge!
With the judgment of our Kalashnikovs,
tear apart their gills...
...with your 5.45-millimeter AK-47s!
Yeah!
Boss Chang.
A message from Hotel Moscow.
"We have a dangerous situation.
Retreat at once."
Pretty clever.
In any case, it's too late now. Cho.
Duck!
Duck!!
Not bad!
You're pretty good!
Thanks, young lady!
Unfortunately we don't have the time
to be dealing with you.
Maybe some other time.
What a relief.
The source of the fire is
the Verrocchio Family.
Watsap is questioning the Triad.
This route is now much
closer to the gold.
It's the opening
of a Carnival Night Party.
Hallelujah!
Listen. It's a Japanese-make
black sedan.
But if they get rid of the car,
we'll have no way of knowing.
Doesn't matter.
Shoot anyone who passes by.
Hey, don't push!
Revy.
Come here.
What is it, Eda?
I just realized a moment ago.
There's something odd about this, Revy.
What do you mean?
Stop beating around the bush.
It's Balalaika.
There's no one in this world that
wants revenge more than that lady...
...yet she hasn't appeared on this street.
Yeah, come to think of it.
Right?
If this were really where it's going down,
we'd be shut out of here by now.
So, where would those twins go?
They're two kids with no logic...
...but if they were after anyone,
it'd be Balalaika herself.
Anything else would be a feint...
...or rather a stopover
to get to their destination.
Balalaika got the Visotonikis moving so
that she could fuck those twins herself.
The soldiers are all pragmatists.
They won't act on speculation.
The twins will try to outwit them.
Everyone's treating this like...
...they're hunting deer
in the mountains of Montana.
But these are no deer. The twins
are coyotes. They won't be easy prey.
Yeah.
If they were the type to get their asses
stuck in this kinda trap...
...they'd have been
resting below a tombstone long ago.
You catch on quickly for someone
with no education, Revy.
So, which alley will get us
to Hotel Moscow quickest from here?
Through the Chalquam Market and
straight along Saatanam Street.
But more importantly...
...you have no education either,
you lust demon!
I'm sorry for your loss, Chang.
If I'd have known those kids were there,
I would've brought some of my top guys.
Imagine, I've gotta walk home now.
This is too much.
Oh, right. I took care of Watsap for you.
I figured you could do without him
in your way...
...so I sent him off to nowhere
on a hunting spree.
You can pay me back later somehow.
You certainly have all the angles covered.
I owe you one.
Everything's going according to plan
on our end, Chang.
The first march will commence
any time now.
There it is! It's that car!
There's no mistake about it.
It's a Japanese-make black sedan!
- Are the twins in it?
- I can't see through the tinted windows!
Why wait to check? Blast 'em!
Ow! You idiot!
Go to hell!
Did we get 'em?
That kid isn't white!
It's one of the local kids!
Damn it!
- We missed! Shit!
- Shit!
Watsap's headed south
for the fishing port.
- That's where the catch is!
- Bring the car around!
We'll smoke those kids out!
As we expected, right big sister?
Having someone take over your identity
for 5,000 baht? Now that's pretty cheap.
But I kinda feel sorry for him.
He said he was an orphan.
It couldn't be helped, big sister.
You either kill or get killed in this world.
You're right, big brother.
It couldn't be helped.
That's right, big sister. So let's kill.
Let's kill more.
Enemy located.
The squad behind Chalquam Street
has located the enemy.
A diversionary attack
was executed.
Good.
- Which direction are they headed now?
- East, as planned.
They should come to
Ladoga Point any time now.
Target has turned left.
They're proceeding
along the course properly.
After Squad Three
opened fire on them...
...they left Ladoga Point and are now
headed to Livinsk. We'll be standing by.
- Send a squad over to Hamipon Street.
- Right.
Make certain there's only
one floodgate.
Have the squads retreat as soon as
they've done their part.
Their main objective
is to guide the enemy.
Which squad was that?
We're not fully set up
in that direction yet.
It could be a hunter.
All units, report back!
Get rid of anyone who gets in our way.
Hold on. Don't move, damn brats.
You'll find yourself in trouble
roaming the streets this late at night.
Especially tonight when
the whole town is out on a manhunt.
You really should think about
worshiping God more often.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Can I ask you a question?
What's the bounty being offered
on our heads?
Eighty grand. Don't move!
Wow. That's pretty good.
Then I'd like to
discuss something with you.
I have with me money I brought
from Verrocchio's office.
We could go at it here, but there are
things we wanna take care of.
Will you accept 100,000
and pretend you never saw us?
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'm not gonna be used by some kid.
Then what about 150,000?!
Well?
Ah... Um, well, let's see...
What should we do, Revy?!
What are you hesitating for, Eda?
80 grand, 150 grand, and their lives!
We'll take it all!
We've relocated the target.
The Chinese woman
from Lagoon Company...
...and the sister from
the Ripoff Church are also there.
They have nothing to do with
our operation.
If you have to, crush them.
Next Episode
The smell of blood and rotten sewers.
You and I are the same thing!