What a strong and passionate will.
I see.
So this is the little sister of Sirzechs, one of the Satans.
You mustn't, Rias!
Issei, I wanted you to...
Rias!
There is no point in going down together, Rias!
Episode
The Last Day of Summer Break!
That bastard, Odin.
How astute of him to summon Thor's war hammer.
Fenrir, destroy that detestable hammer with your jaws!
What a monster!
No!
What is the meaning of this?
The Magic Chains of Gleipnir?! Why are they here?
We brought them.
Nee-sama!
Shirone, that form...
Have you finally accepted your own power?
I will not become like you, Nee-sama.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
We are a hostile species that cannot find peace, even in the very depths of our hearts.
Someday, you too will...
How dare a mere demon of the Far East go against me!
Who's there?
I am Arthur of the Vali team.
Loki-sama, we will be taking Fenrir with us.
What did you say?!
Vali wants the fangs that can devour even gods.
The Holy Royal Sword Collbrande.
Even a god like you cannot scratch it.
You tricked me, Vali Lucifer!
It's your fault for being fooled.
Well, everyone. Have a good day.
Shirone.
I'm in a hurry today, so I'll come pick you up sometime later!
Damn you, White Dragon Emperor!
Your goal was Fenrir from the beginning!
Boost!
How did you—
A gift from the young lady of the Phenex family!
I thought it was some kind of gem, so I didn't even bother opening it!
Issei!
Yes, President!
Let's do this, giant hammer!
Boost!
It's heavy!
But I can do this!
Boost!
I won't let you!
Shit! Damn weaklings!
I won't let you escape!
Vritra!
Transfer!
You should never underestimate...
young devils like us!
Damn you, Red Dragon Emperor!
Damn you, Odin!
Instead of an evil god like you,
I want to meet up with the god of breasts!
I won't go down without a fight.
I curse you.
Suffer greatly until the end.
What was that just now?
Was it my imagination?
It's over.
Good work, Saji.
Thank you.
Huh?
Wh-What are you saying?!
To think you'd thank me!
I'm actually scared to see you smile.
Watch out!
Kiba!
Don't let your guard down at the end of a fight.
Sairaorg-san!
One punch, huh?
Though, it seems you no longer needed any reinforcements.
Hyoudou Issei!
Y-Yes!
I'd like to fight you and Rias in a Rating Game for the
title of number one amongst the young devils some time.
We won't lose when that happens.
That's right!
I like the look in your eyes.
I'd like to have an all-out battle with you sometime.
Though, I have to wonder where Fenrir was taken to.
Just what in the world is Vali thinking?
Just what I would expect from the last Excalibur fragment, the Holy Sword of Control.
Sorry, Loki.
I only wanted Fenrir by my side.
Enjoy your sweet dreams for now,
but, Shirone, you will definitely...
Thank goodness the Red Dragon Emperor was there.
A lot of power is needed to control Mjolnir.
That was a lot of work off my hands.
But Loki-dono is an important god in your mythology.
Was that really okay?
The times must change.
All right, Father, Mother, Millicas. We shall take our leave.
Rias-neesama, are you going home already?
I'm sorry, Millicas.
Rias-sama is quite busy.
You mustn't be unreasonable.
Yes, Mother.
Huh?!
M-Mother?!
Then...
Sirzechs-sama's wife is—
Um, Koneko-chan?
We are a hostile species that cannot find peace, even in the very depths of our hearts.
This is the place I find the most peace.
To think that even Koneko-chan's opened her heart to Issei-kun.
That would have been unthinkable not too long ago, right Rias?
Yes, that's true.
Hey, Rias.
Can I borrow Issei-kun from you for just one day?
Hey, Akeno! He's not something to lend!
I see. You're going to tell him.
Yes, since I've come to terms with it.
Somewhat.
In the end, everyone is saved by Issei.
Indeed.
Yes. Me, as well.
Mother, can I become strong?
I forgot about our final enemy!
Why do they have to give
homework over vacation in Japan?
It seems like everyone else is
already done with their homework.
No, there's still one more person.
Dammit! There's still so much!
Unfinished homework because of our training camp
reflects badly on me as your President.
Make sure you finish all of it.
Dad and Mom are both gone for vacation
so I thought I could get away with not doing it!
But I have something far more important than homework to do!
During my training,
I pushed away all my earthly desires in order to get stronger.
But as a result, my unrelenting desire to see and talk to girls
made me realize my overwhelming lust for boobs.
I ended up hallucinating about having conversations with boobs!
But thanks to that,
I have come one step closer to the truth of erotica!
I'm going to create a new skill just like how I came up with Dress Break!
Y-Yes!
Issei-kun, I brought you some tea.
Akeno-san.
Here, look. This is wrong.
Um, um, uh...
My, my. Are there parts you still don't understand?
N-No.
Don't hold back, I will teach you everything you need to know.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing. S-Sorry.
I feel bad making you help me with my homework, too.
This is just another one of my duties as your senior.
I actually feel bad asking you to return the favor, but...
I must request something of you.
Wh-What?!
We live together.
Why are we meeting outside?
Sorry.
Did I make you wait?
A-Akeno-san?
I-It's embarrassing if you stare at me so intently.
Is something wrong with the way I look today?
No! You look really cute! It's the best!
You'll be my boyfriend for the day, Issei-kun.
Can I call you "Issei"?
S-Sure.
Great! Thank you, Issei!
Th-This side of Akeno-san is cute, too.
Boyfriend for the day?
What kind of things do you do on a date?
S-So this is a date, then?
It's...
my first time, so...
This memory is going to be filed away as an important event in my life!
I-I gave her permission,
but I can't believe she linked arms!
If anything else happens...
Gya-kun, if something happens, stop both of them in time.
I-If something happens?
B-But isn't this stalking?
Th-They're so obvious.
Were they following us the whole time?
Let's run, Issei!
She noticed us!
Gya-kun, let's go!
President's definitely going to murder me later.
Looks like we lost them!
Well, I guess it'll be okay as long as Akeno-san enjoys her day today.
I didn't realize it because we were running so fast,
but we ended up here!
A-Akeno-san! It'd be bad if
someone got the wrong idea!
Quick! Let's go somewhere else!
A-Akeno-san?
It's fine.
Huh?
Issei, if you want to go in, I'll go with you.
I'm okay with it.
S-Seriously?!
Akeno-san!
Why do you have to like an innocent girl instead of the sexy lady you usually are?!
I need to calm down!
First, I should give thanks to Satan for my luck!
Goodness, in the middle of the day.
Not bad, Red Dragon Emperor brat.
Odin-sama?!
I didn't have time to really talk to you.
I just wanted to thank you for what you did.
This old man is the Great Father of the Norse?
Odin-sama, so this is where you went!
Even Rossweisse-san is here!
Please don't wander off on your own.
At least think of me, your guide!
Akeno.
After what happened with Loki, I realized I need to
strengthen our relationships with other forces as soon as possible.
In particular, we don't have any connections with the gods of this country.
And that's why we had Baraqiel guard him again.
He's very familiar with the human world.
True.
Akeno, I want to talk with you.
Don't address me so casually.
I knew that Baraqiel-san was Akeno-san's father, but...
Why were you meeting with the
Red Dragon Emperor in secret?
I can do what I want!
What right do you have to say anything about it?!
I am your father—
Then why didn't you come at that time?!
You were the one who left Mother to die!
I need him right now.
So get out of my sight!
You are not my father!
Akeno-san, um...
Please, don't say anything.
Just let me stay like this for a bit.
Please, Issei.
You can derive the theorem by doing this.
Rossweisse-san, you're amazing!
You can even do homework in the human world!
Beautiful, smart, and strong in battle.
You are the perfect woman.
I have much to learn from you.
No, I'm nothing much.
Even with all these compliments, why can't I find a single lover?!
Even though Akeno-san said that...
I am the daughter of Himejima Shuri and Baraqiel.
Yes?
Akeno-san?
You wanted to tell me something?
I want to tell you about me and that man, Baraqiel.
My mother, Himejima Shuri,
was a priestess born and raised at a Shinto shrine.
One day, she met a fallen angel official who was severely injured from battle
and fell in love.
And so, I was born.
My mother and I were disowned by the Himejima family because of it,
but we started a quiet life
together with that fallen angel.
But those days didn't continue for long.
My black wings were detested,
and they alienated me from others.
Eventually, they tried to eliminate my existence.
To protect me, her young child, my mother...
And she passed away?
After that, I spent every day running from the hunters.
But in the end, I was just a child.
There was a limit.
When my body and spirit were completely exhausted...
Live for me.
...I met Rias.
So that's how you met.
I wanted to tell you my past and put it all behind me.
But I can't!
There's no way I can call the man who tossed us aside my father!
Um, I don't think Baraqiel-san is a terrible person like that.
I bet something hap—
I don't care about the reason!
My mother died because of that man!
But...
I don't know! I don't know, myself!
What I said in front of the hotel.
Those were my true feelings.
Please. Make me...
A-Akeno-san?!
No. Akeno-san won't be saved by something like this.
Make me forget everything.
You're the only one I can ask.
Wh-What's this?
What's going on?!
I was lonely.
Father, I kinda like your wings.
They're black, but they're shiny like my hair!
I see. Thank you, Akeno.
Hey, Mother. Do you think Father loves me?
Yes, of course.
It would be better if Father were always with us.
This is my treasured daughter! And his, as well!
Shuri, your heart has also been tainted by the dark and evil angel.
You leave me no choice.
Mother!
No! Mother!
Akeno.
Don't touch me!
Why weren't you with Mother?!
If you were here, Mother wouldn't have died!
Those people told me!
It's all because you're a black angel!
Black angels are bad people!
I hate it! I hate it!
I hate black wings! I hate you!
I hate everyone! I hate it all!
I knew it wasn't Father's fault.
But blaming him was the only way I could cope with what happened.
I'm weak.
That's why I'm always lonely.
I wanted to see Father more!
I wanted Father to pat me on the head more!
I wanted to have fun with Father more! I wanted...
I wanted to live with Father and Mother more!
Akeno-san.
A dream?
I-I dunno.
It's fine even if it were a dream.
I know this is all thanks to you.
No, I didn't do anything.
That feeling just now, I've felt it before.
That's right. It was during my training.
Issei-kun, I'm sorry.
It seems I wasn't myself just now.
I have to go prepare dinner.
It's hard filling in for your mother, Issei-kun.
Are you going home already?
Yes, I spoke with the various gods in Japan.
I even went to the titty bar I always dreamed about.
I bet that was your main reason for coming!
Odin-sama.
It's almost time.
Akeno?
What's this?
A lunch box for your long trip.
I'm in charge of the household chores right now.
I see. I will accept this gratefully.
Oh! Tonight we have simmered meat and potatoes!
Yes.
I haven't made it in quite a while.
Please have a taste.
Oh, can I?
Here, say, "Ah".
Huh? A-Ah.
Huh?
Thank you, Issei.
This is...
Delicious!
Just like Shuri's.
sou daitai no koto nante
Well, yeah, I do think that
mou wakatte wa iru na tte
I've got this stuff mostly figured out
omou yo dakedo ne
But still, you know
kokoro wa bannou ja nai
Feelings on their own can only get you so far
daiji na koto bakka ishin fudenshin
The stuff that matter isn't getting across
saishuuteki ni wa analog tsuushin
So we have to rely on analog communication
dakara ima sugu
That's why, right now
motto chanto katachi ni shite yo
I want you to be more concrete
kimi ga
Do it
ijiwaru na voice
With your flirty voice
give me kikasete yo
Give me, just tell me
chotto dake de ii no
Just a little hint is fine
aimai na no wa yada na
Don't leave me hanging
no secret sansei
No secrets, yeah?
do you do you know
Do you know?
answer todokete ne
Give me your answer
kowaku nante nai shi
I'm not afraid to hear it
ienai kedo nee wakaru desho
I don't have to actually tell you, right?
wakatte yo
Take the hint
tell me heart tell me heart
Tell me your heart
subete wo kaeru no wa
If you want to take it to the next step
give me word give me word
Give me your word
itsu de mo kimi dakara
The power is in your hands
Next Episode:
It seems girls usually start having secret affairs around our age.
It's decided.
Asia, I've come to see you.
Issei's always like that.
Episode
Second Trimester has Started!
And here I was, worried because you guys didn't come back!
Such indecency!