Maximum Titillation OVA Vol. 1
Rias and Akeno's Womanly Battle!?
I could win Issei's heart easily,
anytime I wanted.
P-President!
Oh, how so?
Huh? How so?
W-Well...
Playing his "private tutor," for example.
P-Private tutor!
All men dream of getting sexy lessons from one!
Issei. Try hard on your next test, okay?
If you manage to be one
of the top three students...
I-If I manage to...?
...I'll let you fondle my breasts all you want!
Private tutors are the best!
Oh, in that case...
I'll play a wife having an affair!
A wife having an affair!
The forbidden, secret act of
consorting with another's spouse!
My husband's on a business trip,
but I needed someone.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
Oh, no, this is nothing at all!
I'd like to repay you in some way.
Do you have any suggestions?
I-In that case... your boobs.
Oh, my!
Don't tell my husband, though!
Cheating wives are the best!
Say, how can we celebrate
if you get into your chosen school?
I'll do anything you want as a reward.
A-Anything?!
I'll give you every bit of me you want...
Private tutors are the best!
Oops. I made dinner for two,
even though my husband is away.
Won't you eat with me?
Or would you rather have me instead of food?
Cheating wives are the best!
See? He's more into my role-playing than yours.
Th-That's not true!
Issei. You like my private
tutor role-playing, right?
You enjoy my lessons more, right?
No, you prefer being naughty
with a married woman, don't you?
Issei!
Issei...
You're both the best!
Wh-Whoa, Issei! Are you okay?!
Issei?!
The best...