Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
With high hopes, humans
leave Earth...
...to begin a new life in
the space colonies.
But the United Earth Sphere
Alliance gains military power...
...and in the name of
Justice and Peace...
...seizes control of one
colony after the other.
The year is After Colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
To counter the Alliance's
tyranny, rebel colonists...
...bring new arsenals
to the Earth...
...disguising them as
shooting stars.
But the Alliance headquarters
catches on to this operation.
But... But why?
I'll kill you.
The Gundam Deathscythe
Hey, Heero.
I hear you ripped up Relena's
invitation yesterday.
Why did you do that?
I'm her classmate so I'm
choked you'd treat her that way.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself,
as a gentleman?!
Tell me sooner next time.
I'll give it to you instead.
Was that Heero?
That's him all right.
Then he's pretty strong.
Sure doesn't look it.
What's taking you?!
We can't deploy the suits.
The carrier isn't
equipped for them.
Don't stop until all underwater
mobile suits are deployed.
Captain, I have Lieutenant Zechs
from Specials on the line.
What does Treize's little
pawn want now?
Having some problems?
None of your business!
I know I may be out
of line for saying so.
But don't you think the
time spent on this search...
...will affect your evaluation
by the Alliance headquarters?
Damn you!
Actually, we're having engine
problems with our new submarine.
You're wasting the
military's money.
We'd like you to let us make
some repairs to our submarine.
You mean on MY ship?!
Yes.
And to return the favor...
...we'll lend you our latest
underwater mobile suits.
The Pisces and Cancer.
I read you.
You'll give us a hand if we keep
quiet about the engine problems.
Do we have a deal?
You're on.
Get over here!
Right!
Lieutenant Zechs, there's
nothing wrong with this sub.
It's the only way he'd
agree to help us out.
We need to find
what we're after.
Huh?
Wow!
I see that everybody's here.
Let's begin our
horsemanship class.
Today we'll practice
some new maneuvers...
...and I'll explain
the main points.
Hey, Heero's not here.
Huh? I'm sure he's
around somewhere.
That guy doesn't need to
be taking any lessons.
This'll destroy it.
Deep water torpedoes.
Guiding functions installed.
In the Marina weapons
warehouse; that's not far!
And now for the minor revisions.
Heero Yuy, entrance fees unpaid...
Cleared.
Boarding unpaid... cleared.
Bursary funds... cleared.
Financial check on
Heero Yuy...
...no problem.
See you, Relena.
We'll come over right away.
Relena?
Yes?
What's the matter Relena?
You'd never guess it was
your birthday...
...from that gloomy expression.
Come on Relena; show us
your pretty smile!
Thanks you guys.
He's so secretive...
He has many secrets;
that's why...
I know his secret;
That's why he said
he's gonna kill me!
Reading some kind of suspense
thriller are you, Miss Relena?
Yes.
Three torpedoes should
trigger...
...the self-detonation device.
I'll destroy this thing
before OZ gets to it.
I'll get rid of it.
Lieutenant Zechs.
The detector has picked up
a trace of metal at point 5500.
Good.
Send the Cancer and Pisces.
Lieutenant, let me handle
this one.
Are you sure?
This isn't like being in
outer space.
I know.
Please leave this to me.
Right. Move out.
Sir!
Pisces will be in the lead and
Cancer will follow.
I'll be giving orders.
Roger.
Lieutenant Zechs, I've got
mobile suits from the Marina.
Looks like that Captain's
caught on to us.
An explosion!
Numerous mobile suits are being
destroyed at this same depth.
Stop engines!
I don't understand!
How about the Pisces
and Cancer?
Let them be.
What in the world's going on?
We're under attack!
But I can't see the enemy!!
We've lost contact with
all of our mobile suits!
Launch torpedoes to
those coordinates!
But Zechs' submarine
is still in the area.
Never mind that!
HE could even be the enemy!
Launch!!
The Captain's ship has
launched torpedoes!
That fool!
What's with all the commotion?!
Careful!
Our enemy's close by.
You don't suppose that
Gundam pilot survived?
I doubt it, but be
cautious anyway.
Sir!
Try and survive THAT
kind of torpedo shower!
What is it?!
You'll all die!
Anyone who sees me has
got a date with his maker!!
Oh, my! How beautiful!!
Thank you all for coming
to my birthday party.
I've never been so delighted.
Miss Relena.
I'd like to wish you
a happy birthday.
Happy birthday!
Thank you all.
Do you really have to
leave so soon, darling?
Couldn't you stay a bit
longer for Relena?
Father...
Relena. I'm terribly sorry.
No need to apologize Father.
I'm old enough to understand
how important your business is.
Take care.
Those pictures...
And now for the news.
According to a military
announcement...
...the meteorites that entered
the atmosphere in five locations...
...disintegrated before
reaching the ground.
They weren't manned spacecrafts
as previously rumored.
That's a lie.
Heero was in one of them.
Then, what does that make Heero?
Is he a "Star Prince"?
Darn.
I'm gonna be late for
Relena's party.
Whoa!
Huh?
That looked just like Heero.
Couldn't be.
OZ is moving ahead
with its plans.
Will I make it in time?
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
What's that?
You wanna join?
Any experience?
This doesn't tell me
a bloody thing.
Hi.
Hey! What's going on?
Beasts only bare their
fangs at enemies.
They're true to their feelings.
Mysterious kid...
Master Quatre, I've brought
you some refreshments.
Thanks a lot.
Leave it there.
How do you like Earth?
It's beautiful.
Very, very beautiful!
The Earth...
Do they know how
beautiful Earth is?
This should help.
Where should I leave these?
Right here.
What? A place like this?
Why're you handing a huge
amount of explosives to a kid?!
Mind your own business.
He's paid in full
for the truck, too.
Take care.
Thanks for your help.
Blow them out, Miss Relena.
Yeah, Relena.
Huh?
The candles.
Oh, that's right.
Good.
I didn't miss the main event.
Happy birthday, Relena.
Thank you.
So it looks like Heero's
not here after all.
Then maybe that WAS
Heero I saw.
Did you see Heero?
Yeah, along the coastal road.
But the funny thing is,
he was driving an ambulance.
Must've been someone else.
An ambulance?
That's him all right!
Which direction was that
ambulance headed for?
Hm?
For the military port.
Where are you going, Relena?
Please continue the party
without me.
I'll be right back.
If you're going to the port then
at least let me give you a ride.
Let us go with you.
No!
You stay here!
Excuse me, everyone.
Wait a minute, Relena.
What's gotten into her?
I've never seen such
a severe expression.
Heero.
What are you planning to do?
Who are you going to kill?
I've found the Leo.
But where's the Gundam?
Doesn't make sense.
There's no other metal
being detected.
Got it!
I can see it!
Right.
Let's inform Lieutenant Zechs.
Good job.
You've found it.
Yeah but it's amazing.
There's not even a scratch!
I must say our enemies have
built an impressive beast.
However, now that we
have it in our grasp...
...we'll be fierce beasts
ourselves.
Watch out for the current.
We'll wait at this depth.
Okay, get the cables
and floats ready.
Yes, sir!
Hey, what's with the noise?
Is it self-detonating?
What is this?!
Where's this light coming from?!
It's the enemy!
Impossible.
How can he use a thermal
energy weapon underwater?!
I'll get you!
I defeated it, Lieutenant Zechs!
OZ's new armor
is pretty tough!
So that's what they were
searching for.
It's on self-detonate mode.
It's identical to mine!
Even the location of the
self-detonation device.
No sense destroying it.
I'll use it for parts.
Retreat!
Load the injured!
Hey meds! Move your butts!
Hurry up!
Huh? Where'd they go?!
Heero!
So it IS you, Heero.
No, Heero.
Heero, what are you doing?
Tell me!
Who are you anyway?
Those are torpedoes, right?
I can tell!
I want to know who you are.
Talk to me, Heero!
Relena...
Heero...
You're in too deep.
Good-bye, Relena.
Heero!!
Who're you?!
It's pretty obvious that
you're the bad guy here.
Are you all right, lady?
Heero! Are you okay?!
Don't overdo it; remember,
you're injured.
Stop it!
Why do you wanna
shoot him?!
Wait a minute.
Great!
How did I end up
the bad guy here?
It's already risen this high.
Must've miscalculated the tide.
What in the world is that?
Don't look.
Lady, I'm sure you have your
reasons for being here...
...but you'd better just leave.
Do yourself a favor.
Haven't had enough?!
So it IS my mobile suit!
What are you doing, fool?!
Finally, everything is finished.
Mission, complete.
Damn it.
He knows Gundanium's
impact tolerance.
Which means he's the
pilot of the mobile suit.
Who are these guys?
Lieutenant Zechs.
I've lost all communication
with the Cancer and Pisces.
I see...
They say you won't live
once you see a Gundam.
I hope that's not true.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Heero is restrained in the
medical treatment room...
...of the Alliance Military.
Duo, in the meantime,
plans Heero's escape.
Zechs predicts that a Gundam
will be attacking the Aries...
...at the Alliance Military Base
of the Mediterranean Sea.
It's there that Zechs is
introduced to a new weapon.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 3,
Five Gundams Confirmed
"Five Gundams Confirmed".