Basara!
No!
Hang in there! Hey!
Though he was a member of the hero clan,
he was but a ruined one in the end.
He was more fragile than I expected.
Hey!
I'll never forgive you!
How dare you!
Oh? You're not bad.
You need to treat him soon,
or it might be too late for him.
Do you understand?
This is the result of your decision.
My...
Will you involve others, get them hurt,
and still continue fighting your futile battle to carry out your own revenge?
However, depending upon your decision,
I could end all of this in an instant.
Basara...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「Countdown of Sadness」
How is he?
His wound has closed, and his pulse is normal.
Thank goodness.
Think it over well.
If he just gets some rest and recovers his stamina...
Mio-sama?
Oh, I just felt a little feverish.
That is not good. We should get medicine...
Don't worry.
I'll be resting in my room for a bit.
Take care of the rest here, okay?
Oh, yes.
Basara-san!
I'm sorry. If only I would have arrived a bit sooner.
No, you helped enough.
But you are incredible.
You are conscious already?
Our clan undergoes special training for our bodies.
Since childhood.
Good! Basara, that's enough.
Incredible, Basara!
That's Jin's son for you.
It's more than just his swordsmanship.
The power he was born with, too...
That child is the hope of our next generation.
Bad news!
What happened?
The sacred demon sword!
The seal on Brynhildr has been undone!
"Sacred demon sword"? You mean...
The sword that sealed the evil spirits long ago.
But who?!
Seito!
Him?
He has always shown discontent with our ceasefire with the demons.
Don't tell me he tried to go to the demon realm on his own?
Worse than that!
His body's been possessed by the evil spirits that were sealed,
and he's heading for the village!
What?!
The children!
Get the children to safety!
Dammit!
It had to happen while Jin was away!
Yuki!
Basara-san?
Right, where's Mio?
She said she was feeling feverish and went to her room.
Feverish? Was it the curse again?
When the curse activates, she is more...
squirmy and embarrassed.
Oh, I will go call her.
What? Something's nagging at me...
There is trouble! Mio-sama is-!
That idiot!
This is my fault.
If you could just tell me where she is...
You are the only one who can sense Mio-sama!
Let's go, Maria.
Absolutely not! You have not fully recovered!
I will go alone...
Maria.
The spell to keep people away is complete.
This is for the best.
Maria, Basara... I'm sorry.
It would seem...
you've reached your decision.
If you're willing to be the sole sacrifice, then...
all of this will end.
That's right. I'm the only one...
who should get hurt fighting!
Not yet!
Now...
Are you satisfied now?
Your flames are quite pretty.
Shall I order my subordinates to find out?
Your fire spell or the home where that former hero sleeps-
Which do you think will make the prettier flame?
You coward!
You're the one who got him involved.
If you want to blame anyone, blame yourself.
You're after me, aren't you?
Please, don't lay a hand on Basara or the others.
That's a wise decision.
You have a deal.
Give me your hands.
Shall we go, then?
Where do you plan on taking me?
The demon realm.
Our master is expecting your vis-
Nonaka?!
Why?!
I'm surprised you would ally with her.
I...
I simply can't forgive you after you hurt Basara.
Naruse Mio, you apologized to Basara over and over as you cried on that roof.
And now, you're even trying to offer yourself up.
I think I can understand why Basara is trying to protect you.
You can't defeat me.
You should already know that.
Then take this!
How did you break the barrier?!
If you can't cut it down in one stroke,
then keep cutting until it breaks.
That's all.
You mean.
You focused all your attacks on the exact same spot without erring?
Don't underestimate the hero clan!
Fine.
Then allow me to toy with you a bit more.
Look out!
Oh? You managed to evade that?
In that case!
Nonaka!
I can...
I can still fight. After all, he...
I'm alive only because Basara saved me.
That's why I withstood harsh training and became strong!
This is the end.
Stop!
Nonaka isn't involved!
I don't care what happens to me! So!
That's not possible.
Anyone who interferes with my mission will be eliminated.
No!
Leave it to me, Mio!
Let's go!
Banishing Shift.
It renders all forms of attack meaningless.
Because it eliminates the phenomenon-the power's very existence-
and sends it to the zero dimension.
Don't be afraid.
It eliminates everything, even the remains of its victims?
It's dangerous!
It's frightening!
It's too dangerous!
We should confine Basara and the demon sword Brynhildr
in order to prevent a repeat of this tragedy!
Give up.
To never run away!
That's what I've learned from Mio!
Protect what you want to protect!
B-Basara, that power!
It's incomplete, but I can handle doing this much.
I don't think I'll be able to fight for long.
I see.
Then I'll readjust my evaluation.
The biggest hindrance to my mission...
is you, Toujou Basara!
Now!
Not a scratch?!
You're mine!
The power to eliminate my attacks...
What on earth is that?
It looks as though it activates only as a counterattack...
but if it were to activate without limits,
it would have the potential to destroy this entire ci-
Shut up!
However, a counterattack is meaningless in this situation.
Unfortunately, this is as far as you go.
Yeah, it is unfortunate. For you.
Maria!
A succubus?!
Too slow!
Toujou!
Basara!
Basara.
It's over.
Mio-sama!
I was so worried!
I was so, so worried!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Looks like you're safe.
Yes. Th-Thank-
What's wrong?
Basara!
No!
Wh-What happened?
Mio!
Is this the Demon Lord Wilbert's power?
B-Basara!
Calm down. See? I'm fine.
It's all over now.
No!
What?
You can't!
Holding this power back is all I can do,
and I can barely do that!
Gravity waves?
If it keeps going out of control...
Please, Basara...
I can't keep this power under control any longer. So...
Wait! Don't give up!
There's no time!
Please, before I end up destroying this world!
Kill me!
I refuse!
Y-You idiot!
It should be clear what you're supposed to protect!
I'm not a hero anymore.
But I am your family!
Your brother!
And brothers protect their little sisters,
even if it means turning against the entire world!
I'm bringing you home.
Huh?
I'm definitely bringing you home.
You and I are going home together!
If you're my little sister,
then shut up and let your brother protect you!
Yes... Yes...
Please,
Save me, Onii-chan!
I should be able to save Mio with a complete Banishing Shift.
I need to discern the root of the power going out of control...
Then eliminate only that.
Just hold on, and I'll get rid of it.
I'll reduce all your sadness and suffering to nothing.
Banishing Shift.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
Yes?
Oh, hello.
About earlier...
Umm, where's Basara?
He's sleeping.
He pushed himself so hard when his wounds had not finished healing, so...
What's this?
A medicine passed down in our village.
Since Basara bears the blood of us heroes,
it should be especially effective.
Thank you for going so far.
Come in, come in.
I just wanted to bring this by.
Take care.
Banishing Shift.
That...
Was that the same as before?
No.
He controlled its power.
So he's finally...
he's finally facing it.
Welcome back,
Basara.
It's been a week since we were at school.
You didn't have to take off, too, Mio.
Wh-Who cares?
I told them we both came down with a summer cold.
That is right.
Thanks to the medicine we received from Nonaka Yuuki-san
and Mio-sama's warm-oh so warm-and tender care,
he did not need to be hospitalized.
M-Maria!
When you analyze this passage from the beginning,
the subject of the first line-
Hey, Basacchi.
Is it okay for someone who just recovered to be skipping out?
Weren't you the only one who could open this lock?
Well, this is a big school.
I'm sure there's someone.
Were you all right?
Hmm? Oh, you mean that night?
What happened there?
You suddenly elbowed me in the sternum and then ditched me.
Not that part.
I cut you up quite a bit there at the park, didn't I?
What are you talking about?
If you plan on acting innocent, you'll regret it.
When did you notice?
That night at school you were talking about how Mio collapsed, right?
I was surprised when she suddenly collapsed.
Her face was bright red... She seemed awfully embarrassed.
Wouldn't one normally think she had a fever,
if she was wobbling and had a flushed face?
No, seeing Naruse's unusual reaction,
I knew her succubus attendant must have been involved right away.
I had trouble holding in my laughter, so...
Ahh, I really did it now.
So?
What are you going to do, Basacchi?
Nothing.
Right now I'm not sure I can beat you for certain, and in fact...
I want to negotiate with you.
Negotiate?
Yeah. You're the one the acting
Demon Lord sent to observe Mio, right?
So, your goal is to help her awaken
while you were observing her.
That's your mission, right?
Things nearly went well back there at the park, though.
But you failed.
If he finds out you failed in your mission,
the acting Demon Lord will probably send someone even more powerful.
And I'm not ready to deal with them yet.
I see.
So either pretend nothing happened
and continue observing her,
or you and that succubus can tell the acting demon lord I screwed up.
It's not a bad deal, is it?
You and I are enemies.
There's no telling when I might betray you.
I believe in you.
What makes you say that?
The fact that I'm still alive right now.
The shadow that attacked me didn't kill me.
The dagger it used was clearly avoiding my vitals.
That could simply have been luck.
Then there's Maria.
She's out hunting demons by herself,
so there should've been plenty of chances to kill her.
Those are the reasons I believe in you.
You've got quite an imagination.
But well, things have gotten difficult
for me after what happened.
For now, I'll play along with that idea of yours, Basacchi.
That's a relief.
Now, I need to be heading back.
Hey, Takigawa,
do you know who killed Mio's foster parents?
Hold on now.
It's not fair to expect information from me without anything in return.
It was Zolgia.
"Zolgia"?
He was Naruse's observer before me, but...
He's not the type who'd lay low forever.
He will make a move.
Mio!
See ya!
I'm shocked.
Skipping classes here together...
The weather was so nice, we didn't realize the time.
What were you talking about with Takigawa?
Nothing really, just how nice the weather is.
U-Umm, you see...
I haven't thanked you yet for saving me.
What are you on about again?
So... So...
Stop!
Y-Yuki?!
N-Nonaka? Why?
I can't let my guard down.
Stop throwing yourself at Basara.
No one's throwing herself at Basara!
Basara, I would like you to eat this.
A bento?
Oh, I remember your food being delicious ever since we were little.
Hold on!
I was also planning on having lunch with Basara...
Empty-handed?
Leave it to me, Mio-sama!
M-Maria?
The bento is prepared!
Now Mio-sama, you can't lose to his
expressionless childhood friend!
Do that with Basara-san! It's "Aah", "Aah"!
You must be joking!
Why should I do that for a guy like him?
Again?
There's no choice.
Since it's come to this, Basara-san, you'll have to do "Aah"...
...or rather, make Mio-sama "Aah"!
Now Basara-san, use this thick Frankfurter...
to violate Mio-sama's cute mouth a bit-
As if I could do that!
You're saying that now?
Haven't the three of us done even more amazing things together?
Just the other night, we even had a naked cake-play in the bath.
My...
What's she talking about?
You didn't know?
Basara-san recently became Mio-sama's master.
I won't allow that! Ever!
Mio-sama's body and soul have been enslaved to Basara-san.
It happened right in front of me.
Hey, why are you running your mouth, Maria?
I'll kill you a hundred times!
Will you two cut it out?!
Basara is mine!
Huh?! Since when is he yours?!
Stop talking nonsense!
You lot...
Yeah, I got a message from him.
I told you so, didn't I?
So long as the chance was there, he'd rise to the occasion.
After all, Basara's their son and mine.
Yeah, that's right.
Please keep an eye on Basara and the others while I'm away.
Don't let yourself get complacent with this, Basara.
Mio's not the only one.
No one can run away from their past or their destiny.
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
Hell Hath No Fury Like a
Demon Lord Sister in the Morning