This is incredible.
Are you looking for something?
Huh?
Welcome!
See? This will definitely look amazing on you.
Now, there's also...
Was that just my imagination?
Sorry, Nonaka!
Didn't mean to keep you waiting.
Huh?
Mio?
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
Just so you know,
「Bearing Growing Feelings」
I just happened to see you two while I was out shopping.
I mean it!
I didn't follow after you or anything like that at all!
Mio-sama, if you get too agitated, it will backfire on you.
I'm not agitated!
But thank you.
We would've been forced to buy it if you hadn't come.
Right?
Yuki?
Naruse-san.
Wh-What?
If you don't mind,
could you help me choose some clothes?
Huh?
What does she mean, trying to prepare for her next date?!
Now, now.
Next customer, this way please.
No more being friendly, Onee.
Kurumi?
She's not here either.
Shall we have the store make an announcement?
I can't imagine Nonaka leaving on her own.
Not when Basara's here.
I still can't get through.
If Yuki and I had the same Master-Servant pact I have with Mio, this would be easy...
Idiot! What am I thinking?!
If anything happens to her, I...
The space...
Dodge! Maria!
Oh? You react faster than I expected.
A demon?
Has the current Demon Lord changed his policies?!
A fool who inherited that power but couldn't even survive that attack
wouldn't be very useful anyways.
That was your doing?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Was Yuki's disappearance your doing?
Ahh, you mean that woman from the hero clan?
Hmph. You've got a quick fuse.
What's the matter, huh?
Is that all you've got?
I'll break every bone in your body!
Basara!
Was that supposed to be an attack?
It doesn't even make me sweat!
That hurt, hey!
Are you all right?
Basara-san!
All your moving around is such a pain.
I'll finish you all off at once!
You!
Oh, you can do it if you try, huh?
Huh?
What's this?
That's...
Takashi...
Huh?
Why are you here?
That's Byakko.
Shiba-san, why are you here?
Isn't it obvious?
Orders from the village.
Don't try to play me.
The village would never send you out.
Who's playing whom?
Are you trying to say it's normal to be with the girl
who inherited the last Demon Lord's power?
Are you saying they decided Yuki wasn't enough to keep an eye on Mio?
Where's Yuki?!
Did you all do something to Yuki?!
Mio-sama!
Kurumi! You, too?!
Don't utter my name so freely, you traitor!
You're protecting the Demon Lord's daughter?
How dare you do something so ridiculous?
You have no idea what my sister has gone through these past five years!
Yuki.
The village has upgraded Naruse Mio to a mid-S class target for elimination.
Elimination?!
Yuki... You...
You're not one of us anymore.
If you interfere,
we'll consider you an enemy.
Yeah. I was already prepared for that!
You truly are Jin-san's son.
You broke the barrier that easily?!
I believe I told you not to get emotional.
Could you try not to make me work too much while I'm here to keep an eye on you?
I know!
If you accidentally destroy the city,
the elders will be furious again.
Right, Basara?
We'll prepare a barrier space that's capable of withstanding our battle,
since we'd prefer to settle matters there, so how about it?
Saying "no" would be pointless, right?
It's three against three.
We'll send the location later.
Our fight...
will take place one week from now.
I knew it was going to come, sooner or later,
but that was fast for the elders.
I didn't think they'd let that Kyouichi out of prison, either.
Shiba-san's an observer,
and won't be involved in the fighting this time.
If they let him out,
they must have some kind of collar on him,
but don't let your guard down.
I know.
Not against Yuki, either.
She isn't the type who likes fighting!
There's no way she wants to fight against Mio because she wants to.
But she's still a girl from the village.
She's charged with protecting the peace of this world.
And you have something you have to protect yourself, don't you?
Are you sure?
If I go against the village,
it'll mean making enemies out of all the heroes in this world.
I don't care.
They're the kind of people who exiled you from the village,
and then charged me to keep an eye on you.
Like I have any obligations left to them.
It doesn't matter if they're planning on unleashing Byakko or not.
I've got your back.
Go crush them.
Yeah.
All right, Dad.
Yuki...
Takashi focuses on speed the way I do,
but right now Takashi seems to have more power.
However, that still doesn't come close to reaching Maria's strength.
Mio, for now you should focus on keeping your distance
and attacking from outside their range.
All right.
Okay, let's take a break.
Our biggest problem...
is that spear.
The sacred spear Byakko...
As the name suggests,
it's a divine weapon housing the might of the guardian beast Byakko.
I've heard it can create powerful gusts that mow down everything.
Can we actually beat such a thing ourselves?
"Can we" is not in question. We will.
Our direction will determine our outcome against that one.
"Direction"?
Byakko represents west.
In other words, he always defends with the west behind him.
Because of that,
it's impossible to wield his power toward the west.
So we need to fight with the west at our backs, then?
That girl-Kurumi was her name?
She used magic, though.
Kurumi is an elemental master who opens channels between herself and spirits
in order to avoid expending her own magic power.
That sounds dauntingly troublesome for us.
However, this time she's going to be restricted by Byakko's wind attribute,
so she should only be able to channel wind spirits.
It doesn't change the fact she's a powerful enemy, though.
If we control our direction and distance,
we'll still have a chance against Takashi's spear, too.
All right. Understood.
They've settled on the location of our duel.
I see.
Happily hanging out and shopping with a target for observation...
Have you grown fond of her?
That's not the case.
The village's decision is absolute.
I know.
Why?!
Onee, you worked really, really, really hard
to become strong enough to serve on observation missions, didn't you?!
And yet you're seeking someone who's forgotten what've they done
and living a carefree life in the city?!
Why?!
I'm sure Basara and the others are trying
desperately to come up with counter strategies right now.
Sorry. Are you all right, Takashi?
Man, you sure are strong, Basara.
Basara's power eliminated even the remains of the dead.
I can't believe we can't even send off the children who died.
Basara!
Never forget, Toujou Basara.
Even if you leave the village,
your past will never disappear.
Training day after day sure takes its toll.
You are tired, are you not, Basara-san?
I have brought you some hot milk.
Thank you.
What's with that outfit?!
This?
I think this is pretty natural for someone who just finished her bath.
That's not what I mean!
Listen, Basara-san, I would like to discuss something with you.
"Discuss"?
Yes. Something very important.
Would you please subdue Mio-sama some more?
Huh?
These past few days you've been continuing your training,
but unfortunately you're still a step-no, two steps-behind me and Mio-sama.
That's...
As you are aware,
as the trust between those bound by a Master-Servant pact grows,
both individuals grow stronger. So...
Let me take this chance to say it.
I do those kinds of things only to help Mio.
But that's all the more reason I don't want to build our trust that way.
I want to take the time to develop our trust.
Even if it happened by accident, I'm her master now,
and before that I'm her brother.
I understand.
In that case, there are other methods,
so let us use those.
There are?
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Please do not move.
Wh-What are you trying to do?!
Succubi are able to absorb lust and arousal
and turn it into our own strength.
So if you can not do that with Mio-sama,
then you can help make me stronger instead.
This isn't "helping" you?!
I am sorry.
But it is your fault, Basara-san.
When you say something like that with that look...
Hey?!
Worry not. Leave it to me.
Hmm?
Ah, no, this isn't...
My, Mio-sama...
What are you doing, standing over there like that?
M-Maria?!
It is all right.
Please watch.
Hey, wait!
Hmm?
Mio?
Mio-sama, I am sorry,
but Basara-san and I and have important battle preparations to take care of...
and if you keep standing there, then to put it bluntly, you will be in the way.
Maria!
Please, wait!
I'll do it.
No, let me do it.
Huh?
I'm the one who needs to grow stronger the most. Not Maria.
I heard what you said.
It made me really happy to hear you say
you wanted to take the time to build trust with me.
Thank you, Basara.
Mio...
A-Are you all right?
N-No way...
Why am... I?
It is only natural.
The frequent activation of the curse
has made your body much more sensitive than ever before.
That's... that's...
Basara...
Are you really looking at my breasts?
Basara, you pervert.
Oh yeah, Basara-san...
W-What is it?
In order to achieve strengthening the
connection between you and Mio-sama,
I happen to know of a good way to do this.
D-Don't say "strengthen"!
Seeing how I randomly have this
with me, how about we try using it?
M-Maple syrup?
Yes... Let's use this as lotion.
W-Wait!
It's the most appropriate way to arouse the opposite sex, you know.
I-Is that so?
Well then, here you go, Basara-san.
Oh yeah, Mio-sama...
W-What?
Earlier, during the conversation we held, you eavesdropped on us, right?
Huh? T-That's...
Eavesdropping on your master's conversation -
how impolite for a servant...
Basara...
I'm...
embarrassed.
Onii-chan, please...
My chest feels hot...
This is tough...
Onii-chan... Onii-chan...
This light is proof of your master-servant contract and that your connection has improved.
When that light settles down,
the two of you should be even stronger than you were before.
You did well.
Let's win.
What should we eat today?
Curry?
Naruse-san, we're going ahead.
Ah, wait!
Basacchi.
Shall we grab something, too?
Yeah.
Nonaka's been absent this whole time.
Seems so.
It's tonight, right?
You're good.
Valga was done in.
Of course I'd look into it.
So, where's it going down?
Who knows?
Hey, don't give me tha-
No, I'm waiting for them to tell us.
Well, I'll trust you on that.
I'll also give you a bit of warning.
The people who defeated my comrade are after Naruse Mio.
So sorry, but I'll have to interfere, if it comes down to it.
Interfere?
If it looks like they're about to kill Naruse,
I'll get rid of them by force.
Even if it happens to be Nonaka.
You?!
Don't forget.
You and I are only joining forces for mutual benefit.
If you don't want us to act,
then make sure you win.
Let me tell you this, then.
If you lay a hand on Yuki or the others from the village,
then I will stop you.
Even if it means turning you against me.
Still no word...
I'll meet up with Mio and Maria for now...
Yuki!
Come.
Where have you been?
Please, Basara.
I want you to withdraw from tonight's battle.
I can't do that.
I told you before, didn't I? I'm-
I know.
But if you ally yourself with a target for elimination,
you'll be facing more than just exile!
Even so, I want to protect Mio.
I'm her brother.
Even if it means fighting me, Kurumi, and the others?
Yeah.
I see.
I'll tell you the location for today.
I'm sure I'll be the biggest hindrance once we start fighting,
but I won't lose.
All right.
That concludes my business.
Let go of me.
I have nothing more to say.
Toujou
A key?
It's a spare key.
Toujou
To our home.
Why?!
You often visited our home a long time ago, right?
With your own spare.
But tonight, we're...
It's not over yet.
I don't want this to be the end. At all.
Only ten minutes are left until the promised time.
But is it really here?
Hey, you're here.
Well, then. Shall we get this started now?
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
The Depths of Love and Hatred