It is morning. Please wake up, Basara-san!
Maria?
Hmm?
Wait, what on earth are you doing?!
You're naked?!
You know you are actually happy about it.
Now, just be honest.
Fine, I lose!
So get away from me!
I refuse.
Huh?
If you must insist,
could you say, "Maria... I want to be inside you."
Whisper it sweetly with a single breath.
Maria.
Yes, Basara-san?
Y-You raised your hand against a woman?!
Yeah.
It's the lowest thing for a man to do.
However, I had no choice because your actions were even lower!
Good grief, you are simply not being honest.
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「Hell Hath No Fury Like a Demon
Lord Sister in the Morning」
Jeez, that lewd devil.
S-Sorry!
I just accidentally...
Ow!
Hey!
Not there!
Huh? Wha?
Wh-What are you coming in here for, pervert!
I'll kill you a hundred times!
Wait! The door didn't have the "bathing" sign hung on it, so I assumed...
Come up with a better lie if you're making excuses!
I'm not lying!
Besides, if I did something like that this would all be over!
Huh?!
Our life together here!
Oh...
That's why, to protect our privacy, we've only used
the Master-Servant pact when necessary, right?
So it's only natural for accidents like this to happen, right?
I guess you're right.
I'm sorry. But I know I hung the sign.
I didn't remove it.
There's only one other person, right?
Oh.
Well, I'm sorry I ended up panicking.
That reminds me,
you were like that when we first met, too.
I'll let you off with 500,000 volts!
Damn, I'm still numb.
Allow me.
Sure. Thanks.
Huh?
Y-Yuki?
I came to pick you up.
I thought we could go to school together.
I-I see.
Wait, hold on.
How'd you get inside our house?
Through the entrance like normal.
That succubus let me in.
Maria again?!
But you...
I tried completely concealing my presence.
That's a bad way to show humility.
You could give someone a heart attack like that!
Basara, let me wash you.
N-No, that's a bad idea.
Why not?
Before, we used to bathe together often.
Basara, don't you like bathing with me anymore?
The issue isn't about whether I like it.
Uh, Yuki-san?
You bathed with Naruse and that succubus,
yet you don't want to with me?
H-Hey!
Basara, let me wash you.
If you don't let me wash you,
then I'll do something even better.
It's been five years already.
It has.
Basara...
Hmm?
Will you and Jin-san ever return to the village?
Basara?
S-Sorry. I'm coming out.
Come on.
Hey, Basara.
You were at fault earlier, too, you know.
My bath towel came undone because you were so rough,
and you seized the chance to do those things...
It really was embarrassing for me.
I-I'm sorry. But that was...
Hey! What are you doing?
What's wrong, Basara?
N-No, it's nothing.
H-Hey!
Basara, what did you seize the chance to do?
N-No, it was a bit of an accident.
Hey, Basara.
Y-Yeah?
Why is there a girl's uniform here?
Huh? O-Oh, s-sorry.
That's mine.
I actually have an interest in cross-dressing.
I'm kidding.
That's impossible, right?
W-Wait!
No, no way...
Right now? Like this?
Don't tell me?!
I knew it.
What's wrong?
Just a wrap a towel around yourself!
Excuse me!
Where is Mio-sama trembling with pleasure?
Oh!
I thought this might happen, so I bought this!
It's the world's smallest and most lightweight!
Never let your memories fade,
so the memorial to your youth remains with you always!
Huh?
What are you doing, Basara-san!
I do not care about me, just take the camera!
Please take the camera at least!
My pride as a succubus demands that I must film Mio-sama right now!
Shut up!
Show some restraint, you loli pervert succubus!
Are you all right, Mio?
It's your fault, and yet I...
Onii-chan, you jerk!
I'll kill you a hundred times!
I get it. Let's go to your room, then.
Basara-san! Can you hear me?
Sorry, Yuki.
Please give me back my camera!
Could you wait in our living room?
Please! Give it back!
All right.
We really have to undo this Master-Servant pact on the next night of the full moon.
Incredible! There's no way this is beef!
It's perfectly good beef.
Watch out. It'll burn if you cook it took long.
I won't let something this good burn!
So good!
But are you sure, Basacchi?
This is expensive, right?
I always repay my debts.
I see!
Uh-huh.
Are you sure it's all right to be spending money on this
when your dad's out of town?
It's pocket change from my savings.
I couldn't use Dad's money to treat you.
You're so earnest.
Are you really Jin Toujou's kid?
Is my dad famous in the demon realm, too?
Huh?
Well, yeah.
Apparently, one of the reasons the previous Demon Lord, Wilbert,
decided to withdraw his troops
was that he feared Jin Toujou's monstrous strength in combat.
He was the demons' greatest enemy,
and they treated him like a war god.
My father's my father, and I'm me.
Regarding our last incident at the park...
Word from the top is they're sending reinforcements for observation.
Reinforcements?!
Apparently they've decided there's a chance
that Naruse Mio has awoken to the previous Demon Lord's power.
It'll be difficult for me to cooperate in the future.
And they might not necessarily send someone who's weaker than I am.
Plus, you and Naruse formed a Master-Servant pact, right?
Y-Yeah.
Judging from that, I guess you haven't heard.
That magic doesn't just allow you to detect each others' locations
or activate a curse when betrayed.
It raises your combat strength the stronger your faith and loyalty grow.
You mean it makes us stronger?
That's why the higher up a demon is,
the more that demon will try to amass others to command through Master-Servant pacts.
The curse does more than just prevent betrayal, too.
If captured by the enemy,
the subordinate becomes a liability to the master.
That is the greatest act of betrayal towards their master.
So the curse activates to its fullest,
and well, most don't live through it.
You mean if the enemy captures Mio, she'll die?!
Plus, if I remember right...
You formed your pact using that succubus's nature, right?
Y-Yeah. She said using Mio's nature would be dangerous.
What about it?
No, I'll stop there.
It's not a very pleasant topic.
We're here enjoying some barbecue.
Let's end that talk here.
Yeah.
It's all-you-can-eat,
so we'll be missing out if we don't keep placing more orders.
You're right.
All right, let's eat!
Wait... uh...
Ahh...
What? It's you two?
Hasegawa-sensei?!
Mind if I join you two?
Huh?
No, please do, please do.
The men from other tables came up in turns
to ask me if I'd eat with them.
Does a woman eating barbecue by herself seem that lonely to others?
No, they probably...
Yeah, I think it's something else, Sensei.
Did you choose this restaurant, Toujou?
Huh? Oh, yes.
This place is run by a friend of my father's.
But why do you ask?
This picture is your father's, right?
You know my dad?
Yeah, I love the photos he takes.
Thanks. I'll let him know.
Sorry for the wait.
Now then, shall we eat?
Yeah! We're just getting started!
Cheers!
Later, I've got business to take care of
You two were having an awfully strange conversation,
talking about demons and loyalty.
Huh? Oh, we were discussing a game.
A game, huh?
You seem awfully into it.
Huh?
Your tone was serious when you were talking about it with Takigawa.
I guess so.
Even if it is a game...
There are some things I just can't lose.
Huh?
S-Sensei?
You have to protect your little sisters in your father's stead?
I see.
But it's hard, you know?
Right now it seems impossible with my power.
You're taking too much on yourself.
Listen.
If you draw a line you absolutely refuse to surrender,
then that's the only thing you need to protect, no matter what.
A line I absolutely refuse to surrender...
Toujou, you should give some more thought to
what it is you truly want to protect.
All right.
Good!
Huh?
For the future of the heavens up high,
may the protection and guidance of the spirits of light be with you.
S-Sensei?
Oh, sorry.
It's an old charm from my village.
Don't worry about it.
I didn't expect it would be you, Valga.
Well, shall we see how our target's doing?
The hero clan is moving already, too.
Oh?
If we stir things up too much,
they might make some serious move,
and if anything happens to Naruse Mio...
Those above will kill you.
I want to get to know the situation myself as well.
Jeez.
We both know you won't stop at just observing.
Please wait.
Zest?!
I heard they were sending one person as reinforcements.
I'm not here as your reinforcements.
Then why would Marquis Zolgia's right-hand woman make an appearance herself?
I am not acting on His Excellency's command alone.
I have orders from His Majesty, as well.
Do you have any complaints?
No.
If that's the case, then I'll gladly work with you.
Basara-san, what you say is true.
If Mio-sama were to fall into the enemy's hands,
the curse is likely to activate its greatest effect.
Don't tell me...
You said this was so we could sense each other's whereabouts,
but you actually had us form this pact so Wilbert's power wouldn't fall into enemy hands?!
I did not!
If Mio-sama is kidnapped,
then you would be able to pinpoint her location.
As you are now, you should be able to rescue her!
I gave it serious thought.
And you chose to let me protect her
over the risk of her falling into enemy hands?
That is all I can do right now.
If Mio-sama knew about this,
she would probably feel responsible and worry about it.
She might run off on her own again like last time.
Which is why I did not tell you about this,
and tried to cultivate your trust in each other,
hoping that it would grow stronger.
But I never thought you would go looking into the Master-Servant pact.
Well, I am a former member of the hero clan.
I have a connection or two...
Which means it's probably best to leave our Master-Servant pact tied as is.
Please leave it to me, Basara-san.
It might be presumptuous of me,
but I have thought of the most effective solution for this situation.
SKIP
AUTO
SAVE
Mai
We're all alone together now, huh?
D-Don't stay silent. Say something.
It is good, is it not?
The smell of a woman fresh out of the bath.
So, how is this supposed to be an effective solution?
Right now, building the trust between you and Mio-sama is our top priority.
This software can be used as a reference for training her.
This is a good opportunity to say what I've been thinking for a while.
Hmm?
You're an idiot, aren't you?
My, my...
I think it is far more foolish trying to fight with conventional means
when we need to combat the current Demon Lord's faction and our forces are limited.
1) Approach her normally and put her at ease.
Basara
SKIP
AUTO
SAVE
2) Act very kindly and gentlemanly
3) Knowing Mai's determination, I can't hesitate.
In order to respond to her feelings,
I'll be forceful with my love.
3) Knowing Mai's determination, I can't hesitate.
In order to respond to her feelings,
I'll be forceful with my love.
I won't regret it.
That's my responsibility as her step-brother, her family.
That's something I believe.
I won't regret it.
That's my responsibility as her step-brother, her family.
That's something I believe.
so please select the choice you think is appropriate.
Basara
1) Approach her normally and put her at ease.
2) Act very kindly and gentlemanly
3) Don't hesitate and be forceful
SKIP
AUTO
SAVE
Hey, isn't there something wrong with that third option?
Ah, I knew it.
What? Do you have a problem with it?
No. Please continue.
The next morning I woke, feeling a chill on my skin.
Our home was the same...
See? You got the bad ending, did you not?
but the girl who should have been there was gone.
She had disappeared. Leaving only a single letter...
"I'm glad I got to feel your kindness in the end."
...It read in her familiar, trembling handwriting.
How'd things end up like this?
Basara-san, you do not understand a woman's feelings at all.
Oh well.
Hey?!
Now, let us help her out!
Basara
1) Approach her normally and put her at ease.
2) Act very kindly and gentlemanly
3) Don't hesitate and be forceful
SKIP
AUTO
SAVE
Mai
"What are you saying all of a sudden?
Is there something wrong with your brain?!"
See, look? That third option's out.
What are you saying? You should be looking closely.
SKIP
AUTO
SAVE
Mai
"No! Onii-chan!!! Don't stop!
More... More!! I love you!!"
What's this?!
Listen, Basara-san.
Strong-willed women tend to be masochistic, once you peel away their shell.
What kind of twisted reasoning makes you say that?
So, for Mio-sama, you need to forcefully strip away her shell!
Are you really her subordinate?
It is because I am her subordinate that
I want Mio-sama to be true to herself.
Now, Basara-san, there is no time to waste.
In order to help you forge an unshakable bond with Mio-sama,
you are going to pick up the proper know-how to train your little stepsister!
I knocked several times, and you weren't answering,
but you seem to be having an awfully fun chat.
Mio-sama!
What?
I-If you let me...
if you let me explain, you will understand.
Perhaps.
But before that, can we have a moment, Maria?
Don't worry, I won't take too much of your time.
Basara-san, quit watching and help me, please!
I taught you, did I not? What it means to be strong?
Now is the time!
I knew it. There's an awful lot being drawn here.
Having a victim on hand would give us a reason to eliminate the target.
There's no call for unnecessary victims.
You sure are earnest.
Good grief, it's hard work being a hero of justice.
Don't you agree, Kurumi-chan?
No, that's our duty.
Shiba-san, the village has already given its decision.
The target...
Naruse Mio has been upgraded from a target for observation to a target for elimination.
Umm, did you need me for something, senpai?
I hear you're living with Princess Mio, but...
you haven't done any weird things to her, have you?
I've heard Princess Yuki was giving you a hug,
but are you two really just childhood friends?
Hey, say something!
What are you all doing over there?
Tsk.
We weren't doing anything.
Let's go.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Thank you very much, Sensei.
Sure.
Yuki! I see. You called the teacher.
Yeah.
I thought it would be better for Sakazaki-sensei to show up than for me to.
Thanks.
I didn't want to make a move, either.
Not against normal people.
Actually, there's something I want to ask you.
Why so formal?
Do you have any plans next weekend?
No, not particularly.
Then, go on a date with me, Basara.
Huh?!
Well, shall we get going then?
To be heroes who protect this world
by defeating this future Demon Lord.
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
Bearing Growing Feelings