Let's begin.
Shiba-san?!
I don't want him acting on a whim and interfering with our battle.
It appears you all have some issues of your own.
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「The Depths of Love and Hatred」
Is that where she's aiming?!
Take this, too!
I can't believe you'd go after Onee!
Just how much do intend to make her suffer?!
Hmm, so you weren't after Onee,
you were actually angling to bring me into a one-on-one duel?
You're underestimating me an awful lot.
Takashi worries about every little thing.
Well, I guess I'll enjoy the show.
So they're luring Takashi away
and buying time until Basara returns, huh?
Are you trying to secure the western side?
Now, let us keep this going!
Don't toy with me!
Too bad for you.
Thanks to Basara-san and Mio-sama,
my tanks are all filled to the maximum.
Very well.
Then I'll simply revise my assessment of you.
Howl, Byakko!
Even if it can't attack the west,
I can still use Byakko's power to attack a close range.
Unfortunately for you.
"A close range," huh?
Then how about this?!
What?
Basara never learns, does he?
It's fine to be kind.
But if he's too greedy,
he'll end up losing everything again.
Just like five years ago.
Striking me with the back?
How long will you treat me like a kid?
You think the village will reconsider its decision
if you show your strength and win without hurting us?
Sorry.
I made my decision.
I can't abandon a girl when people are after her life just
because she's the previous Demon Lord's daughter.
I'm going to protect her!
But...
Am I allowed to have only one thing precious to me?
Must I limit myself to one?
Do as you please.
You're using Banishing Shif-
Here I go!
He even eliminated my channel to the spirits?!
Onee...
I'm sorry.
He's the one person I didn't want to let Onee fight.
Y-You!
My, this is an odd turn of events.
No!
H-Hey!
Y-You idiot.
That's what I mean by underestimating me!
Looks like you're fine, then.
Look, look!
Wow!
You did it, Kurumi.
Basara... onii-chan.
Yuki...
Huh?!
No! Run!
Please, hurry!
Onee!
Basara!
Onee, why?
I couldn't think of any other way.
This should put him out for half a day.
Take care of Basara for me.
What are you going to do?
Don't tell me?!
Maria, thanks to you, I got one off on him.
That should buy us some ti-
Mio-sama! That is reckless!
You can not manipulate all the water in this building!
Hurry and disengage the magic!
This is...
You got careless.
Seiryuu, who is guardian of the east and opposes Byakko,
flies in the sky to protect the earth from the heavens!
So, what do you think Byakko does?
No way!
It can activate its power against the skies as well!
Rip them apart, Byakko!
It's over.
I think it's a bit too early to celebrate.
How on earth did you?
However!
That's all?
Yuki, have you gone mad?!
I will show no mercy and cut down any who side with the demons!
Even if that happens to be you.
Do as you please.
What?!
Are you saying you've forgotten
the tragedy from five years ago?
How could I forget?
I never want to experience that again!
Then why...
At this rate, we'll be repeating what happened five years ago.
What?!
So this time I'll protect him.
That's why I became stronger!
I will protect those Basara's trying to protect!
If I don't, there's no meaning in being a hero.
You idiot!
Withdraw your hand!
Cease this!
That idiot!
Mio-sama!
I can't just leave Nonaka alone like this.
I will take care of this. You go to Basara-san!
If Nonaka's here, then...
I do not believe he lost.
After all, she just said she would protect Basara-san.
So Mio-sama, please go fetch him.
It is a little sister's job to help her precious older brother!
Jeez, why am I doing this...
Five years, huh?
He has grown manly.
Everyone...
I-I'm sorry.
Huh?
It's my fault...
It's all...
No way...
You mean we weren't the only ones suffering?
Basara... onii-chan...
Basara...
Basara?!
What are you doing here?
This is no time for me to be fighting against you, little girl.
Wha?!
If I wanted to fight you,
I would've blasted you with magic by now.
Basara, get up!
Basara!
Nonaka and Maria are fighting that Hayase guy!
You're the one who said
the only way to stop this battle was for you to defeat Byakko!
That's impossible.
Onee used sleeping incense on him.
Sleeping incense?
Basara! Wake up!
Hey, wake up!
Basara! Basara!
Basara...
Sorry...
I'm sorry...
I... all of it...
Basara! Basara!
Basara, I'm sorry for putting you through such hardship.
But please...
Please hang in there a while longer...
You've been protecting me all this time.
So please... this time...
Mi... o?
This time, protect Maria and Nonaka!
Protect...
Basara!
Right. I...
I...
Basara!
No way?!
It's futile!
Basara was a victim of that tragedy, too.
And he was exiled from the village.
He didn't betray us.
It's us who betrayed him.
You!
Basara-san!
You're here.
You hurt Yuki.
She sided with the demons.
Naturally, that made her an enemy.
She's your childhood friend!
We're members of the hero clan.
We put our duty to protect this world above all else!
I understand.
What are you trying?
Did you change your combat style?
Doing that now won't help!
Not yet.
Is he going to be okay, raising his speed like that while wounded?
He may seem to have the advantage now,
but how long will he last?
More...
What's wrong, Byakko?
The spear?!
It's about time.
When Byakko faces danger, it activates its auto-defense.
Stop it, Byakko! We don't need to defend!
A sacred guardian beast whose role is to protect its wielder
won't listen to an order like that.
Takashi, it looks like it was too early for you to wield Byakko.
Takashi!
Byakko!
Onee, are you all right?!
What about you, Kurumi?
What's that?
The spear's out of control,
and its sealed power is revealing its true form.
Byakko's a guardian beast!
So long as we don't attack, it shouldn't do anything.
But half of this barrier is built with Byakko's power.
If we leave it be, the barrier might start to crack.
If this started to happen in the middle of the street...
There is one way.
Huh?
But for that, I'll need to draw out his attack
and break through his wind barrier at the same time.
I'll handle that.
Onee!
I can do it.
With my Sakuya.
You can't in your condition.
Trust me.
I can finally fight for Basara's sake.
Those harsh, painful five years were all for this moment.
Please, Sakuya!
Banishing Shift!
It's over now.
Now, kill me!
We're childhood friends.
Don't fool with me!
Five years ago,
how many of our childhood friends were among those you vaporized?
Now, vaporize me, too!
With that cursed skill!
It should be easy for you if you've stooped to siding with the Demon Lord's daughter.
Do you really think you're the only ones going through hard times?!
Don't be stupid!
Do you think Basara could ever forget something that you all can't?!
M-Mio-sama, please calm down.
This idiot deserves to get punched a few more times!
Let me go! Let me go!
If you continue to go after Mio,
I'll stop you every time.
I'll continue to bear my past and your hatred with me for the rest of my life.
It would appear everything's settled.
No way! How did you get inside the barrier?
Since Byakko was controlling half of it, once he lost it, well...
Now, let's go home.
What are you saying?
We're not finished here.
Our mission was temporarily withdrawn.
What?!
Are you serious, Shiba-san?
I made you all clean up
after Takashi let Byakko go out of control.
If we eliminated her with as little justification as we have now,
then we're sure to become tainted.
Badly enough that it would affect our pacts with gods and spirits.
I figure that's probably a bad thing.
No way!
Did you not hear me, Takashi?
I said this is over.
You two come, as well.
We're going home.
Hold on, Shiba-san! Yuki's...
I'd like to remain an observer until the end this time.
So please don't move any farther.
If you do...
You're threatening us?
Basara, don't!
If Yuki-chan and the others don't return now,
the situation will only get worse.
Everyone will meet misfortune.
Thank you, Basara.
I'm glad we could meet again.
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
Erotic Succubus Out of Control