Maria, you wait here.
But-
I promise.
You, your mother, Mio...
I promise I'll save you all!
Basara-san!
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「Espionage and What Lies After」
Basara...
Did Jin Toujou throw away his title as the greatest Hero
for a son of this mere caliber?
Hmph. The man once heralded as a war god
has fallen into a pathetic state.
I will claim the power of Wilbert, sleeping inside of Naruse Mio,
as well as your power for my own.
Stop...
Oh? You forced yourself free of mental bondage?
Was it that difficult for you to bear becoming a burden on your father?
I might not be anything special,
but I won't forgive you speaking ill of my father!
You certainly are fast for a human.
However...
The people she thought of as her parents were murdered.
Apparently her mother has been captured.
I know you can do it. After all, you're my son and making me proud.
Did not your father ever teach you?
This...
is how you use a sword!
You are the epitome of pathetic.
Look out!
Taste the flames of Hell.
Banishing Shift!
Basara!
You dispersed my flames?
Good.
With that skill and Wilbert's power in hand,
I will become the new ruler of the whole demon realm.
Like hell!
Hmph, your final desperate struggles?
I can do this!
Though you made only a scratch,
I praise you for wounding my body.
Basara!
However,
this is the end.
Basara! Basara!
Basara!
Oh? You still stand?
Good eyes.
Show me how those eyes look when tainted with despair.
This is probably the last time
I'll be able to swing my sword well.
If there's a moment when I can catch him,
it will be the second he attacks.
That is it. That's the look I wanted to see.
Basara!
Here is your parting gift for the afterlife...
Meet your final end enraptured in dreams of bliss.
Maria seems to have failed, but rest assured...
That just means your mind will fall under my dominion.
Basara...
Mio?!
Onii-chan.
Basara-san...
Maria...
Look at me, too... Basara.
Basara-niichan... Does this feel good?
No! Don't give in, Basara!
Basara! Basara!
Oh? You still have the will to resist?
I knew you'd come.
The brat was bait, and my real opponent is you, Maria?
No. I made this decision on my own.
Maria... is that you?
Mio-sama and I are the ones who have bones to pick with you, after all!
That form of yours is beautiful, as I thought it would be.
Though you insisted that it could be used only once,
and hid it from me.
Because I would rather die than tend to you in bed.
An impressive sense of virtue.
Did you want to at least become a woman when you conquered that brat?
I do not have any right to long for that anymore.
I am doing this to stop Basara-san from being reckless...
and to kill you!
Impressive confidence,
but you can maintain that state only a few minutes longer.
And you have not forgotten, have you?
Mother!
I will let you choose.
Become mine alongside Naruse Mio and that girl there,
or let your mother die after she betrayed her comrades in the moderate faction to save you.
I refuse both!
I expected that would be your answer.
Huh?
The footage I just showed you was from earlier.
My finger snap just now was the activation key
to the super electromagnetic device in her cell.
M-Mother... why?!
Unfortunately for you,
I'm not soft enough to forgive betrayal.
But do not worry.
Though her death looks horrid,
she did not have time to suffer.
Her body ruptured from inside in a moment.
How much must you toy with the hearts of others?!
Father... Mother...
No! Calm down, Mio!
Is that Wilbert's-
You must not! Mio-sama!
Wonderful.
An anti-magic field?!
I am surprised it went as perfectly as planned.
You showed that footage to Mio-sama on purpose!
The trigger for activating the power sleeping inside Naruse Mio
is her trauma...
In other words, I only need remind her of her foster parents' deaths.
Hmph. Do not make me waste any more magic power.
As expected from Demon Lord Wilbert's power.
I used most of my magic power just containing it,
but now I have the chance to seize it.
Good grief, you gave me a hard time.
Now, let me see a bit more of yourself.
H-How?!
This isn't Wilbert's power!
I see! This is this girl's own, natural-
Listen well, if you kill me...
I don't care what happens.
I've lived my life for this moment.
S-Stop!
No! Mio!
Stop it.
You shouldn't kill him.
He killed them! My father and my mother!
Before my very eyes!
Yes.
I lived to get revenge! I lived to kill this man!
I know.
If you know, then how can you tell me not to kill him?
Because I don't want your future to be bound.
Basara...
Mio, what comes after revenge is a moment's release,
and an eternity of despair.
There's no need for you to suffer bearing his life for the rest of yours.
Then order me!
As the Master in our pact,
order your subordinate not to kill him! To give up!
Order me to!
Then I'll obey you...
I'll listen to you, my older brother.
If I do that, then we'll never be siblings again.
We'll never be family again.
I promised my father.
That as family, as your older brother, and as a man,
I would protect you!
I'll protect you from your hatred at having your parents stolen from you,
and your regret at letting him go...
Please. Mio.
Zolgia is-
You won't escape!
There's no need for that, Yuki.
But...
It's all right.
Maria!
M-Mother?!
"Mother"?
You are safe, Maria! I'm so glad!
How?
Thanks to our accomplice.
Accomplice?
Curse you!
How dare you take my arm!
My, my, it has been a long time, Marquis Zolgia.
Lars! You... Why are you?
Oh? Did you forget that I am a puppeteer?
So Zest only killed one of your dummies?
What a useless woman.
You are not in a position to talk either, Your Excellency.
What?
I mean, Zest was not the only one to fall for one of my dummies.
What? You mean-
A super electromagnetic device, huh?
What bad taste.
Lars? Why are you here?
There are several traps placed together, but...
This is all?
He must have been quite confident that this place would not be discovered.
Please hurry and get out of here.
Unless you want to be fried in a microwave.
So you're saying the Shella I killed was another dummy you made?
It was one of the conditions in the deal
that I made with Toujou Basara.
What?!
Takigawa, tell me what reward you'd expect for your help.
Reward?
I'll see to it, no matter what.
I see. I guess that's an option, too.
But can you honestly do it?
Can you grant my desire?
I had intended to be a bit more cautious in my plans, though.
What are you plotting?!
With your magic power run dry, and one arm missing,
you are just an old man who can not do anything right now.
Will you come quietly with me?
Are you planning to sell me out to Leohart?
You make me laugh.
Lars... what are you after?
I am sure you do not even know the names of those you killed, but...
When His Majesty Wilbert selected the foster parents
to entrust raising his daughter in the human realm,
he chose two especially kind people in his service.
What are you talking about?
They took in many children who lost their homes in the great war,
and they were loved by many of their comrades.
Especially those like me,
who grew up in their orphanage and loved them like an older brother and sister.
You?! Y-You mean...
That's right, Zolgia.
I gave Toujou Basara only one condition-
To kill you, Zolgia, with my own hands.
Then that was a puppet dummy...
Yes. I'm all right.
Thank you, Maria.
I am sorry for making you suffer all this time.
Mother!
I can't believe Maria's mother is this little, er uh, young...
My, my, well, pardon me for the late introduction.
I'm Maria's mother, Shella.
Thank you for taking care of my daughter.
S-Sure... How kind of you. Thanks.
Zolgia-sama's zero-particle reaction surrounding this mansion has disappeared.
It means Zolgia's barrier is gone, right?
All right, let's go home, everyone.
It's futile.
I knew that man would abandon me.
What's going on?
This is...
It is like a living creature. It can not be...
Even for His Excellency,
it is practically impossible to maintain a constant barrier powerful
enough to deceive His Majesty Leohart.
That is why he made the demon realm's most dangerous creature into his base,
and took advantage of its ability to cut off dimensions.
His Excellency merely transformed it physically and put it to sleep.
So with Zolgia's magic undone, that creature is now awake?
Yuki!
I'm fine.
In other words, we're inside that monster's stomach?
Is there any way out?
It is impossible to escape from this space when it is dimensionally cut off. Besides...
You brought a dangerous beast from the demon realm into this world?
If you do that, who knows what will happen?!
That's why it is my insurance.
This world is filled with the aura of life that it favors.
Once free from my yoke, it will multiply infinitely,
and eventually swallow up this whole world.
What?!
I can not afford to let someone else have the fish that got away, can I?
You!
Perish! Perish along with everything!
Multiply infinitely?!
So even if you manage to escape from here, eventually...
This isn't funny.
Mother, please do not leave my side!
Yes, I will not.
Zest, does this creature have any vital organs?
Its core is in the center of the mansion,
but that is the nucleus of the dimensional separation.
Neither magic nor physical attacks work against it.
Take care of Maria's mother.
Basara, where are you going?
With Banishing Shift's complete erasure,
I might be able to eliminate the dimensional separation.
No, it's too dangerous!
There's no time.
We can't let this creature expand into the city.
Wait, Basara!
I swore that I would protect our family at all costs!
Even if it costs me my life.
I'm going, too.
What are you saying?
It's impossible for you to break through to the center on your own.
Older brothers aren't the only ones who want to protect their family.
Little sisters do, too.
Especially their precious older brothers.
Mio...
I'm going, as well
Yuki!
You'll need time to use Banishing Shift's complete elimination.
Mio and I will protect you.
Normally, I should be volunteering, but...
No, you need to protect your mother.
Otherwise, all our hard work will have been for naught.
Mio-sama, I, I...
Don't say it. I've always been grateful to you.
Mio-sama...
Shella-san, when we return, please tell us stories about Maria's childhood.
Yes, as many as you'd like.
M-Mother!
This is no time to dawdle. Let's go!
Wait, I haven't agreed to let you-
You're the one who said there's no time.
I will lead you to the central core.
You...
It is up to you to decide whether or not to trust me.
Please.
Understood.
Let's go!
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
For This Night, This Moment