Are you all right, Naruse-san?
Huh?
Toujou-kun's been acting that way, and our class rep's been out this whole time.
If there's something troubling you, you can always tell us.
Yeah, thanks...
Sure thing.
We're friends after all.
It's still been only ten days since then...
Basara?
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「Erotic Succubus Out of Control」
We're home.
Oh?
That smells good.
What are you cooking?
My special beef stew.
Yuki?!
I came to take responsibility.
But you and Shiba-san both...
The village reverted Naruse Mio's level to its original state.
In other words, they're pretending recent events never happened.
Does that mean the elders have forgiven us?
Kurumi mentioned that the elders received a phone call from Jin-san.
From Dad?
I've got your back.
It doesn't matter if they're planning on unleashing Byakko or not.
Go crush them.
What kind of deal did he strike with the village?
Basara?
Thank goodness. I mean it.
Ahem!
Kissing right away upon your reunion?
N-No, we're not-
Naruse-san.
Basara and I are busy right now, so I'm sorry,
but if you need something, could you wait until later?
Huh?!
How can you say such brazen things in someone else's home?!
Welcome home.
Maria!
Are you the one who let her in here?
Huh? Was that a bad thing?
You were worried about her the whole time too,
were you not, Mio-sama?
I-I...
Don't worry.
I've received permission from the elders to reside with you.
Huh?!
For observation, it's more convenient this way.
I wasn't asking about your convenience!
Was this my Dad's...
No, no way.
Now, now, I have just finished preparing our entertainment for Yuki-san.
Entertainment?
As thanks for saving Mio-sama,
I am going to show her this secret footage!
Wha?!
What do you think, Yuki-san?
Please look at this.
Mio-sama's horny expression and her lewd breasts!
Viva HD! Hooray for 4K!
Maria! Y-You...
Wh-When did you?!
Your first time training her was an event worthy of recording
as much as any sports or academic festival, is it not?
Only for you succubi!
What?! Then what about your first time pleasuring yourself?!
I would never let anyone record that!
M-Mio-sama!
H-Hey...
Hey?! What are you doing, Nonaka?!
I'm going to have Basara do the same with me.
Then I must prepare the camera quickly!
Maria! Cut it out, or I'll kill you a hundred times over!
Hold on, Basara. I'll strip right now.
Don't start stripping!
Basara, where do you keep the maple syrup?
No, Yuki-san, your skin is pale,
so chocolate sauce would contrast better!
M-Mio-sama! I am really- I am really going to suffocate!
Master-Servant pact?
Yes. Mio-sama being in such an unladylike state is the result
of the magic of the Master-Servant pact.
"U-Unladylike"?!
It allows you to ascertain each other's positions...
and makes you stronger...
Yes, it does!
So Mio-sama was not gasping lewdly for no reason!
"L-Lewdly"?!
So with that in mind,
if you do not mind,
would you forge a Master-Servant pact with Basara-san, as well, Yuki-san?
Huh?!
Tomorrow just happens to be a full moon.
All right.
Yuki?!
Nonaka?!
It's true that leaving the village aside,
forging a Master-Servant pact with Yuki would lead to increasing our forces...
But...
What are you getting closer for?!
Hey.
I want to do this.
We need to talk.
Come behind the school after class.
Mio-sama is using her breasts to seduce Basara-san
and close the distance between them quickly.
However, there is no need to be discouraged.
Women's breasts all grow bigger when they are fondled by a man they love.
What are you smiling about?
I can't wait for tonight.
Why are the guys and girls separated for swimming?
Right? Such a waste.
Still, no matter how many times I see them,
those are some awful scars.
What's this all about?
Your village...
No, your old home should be able to get rid of those, right?
There are some scars that never fade.
You've got it rough, too.
Huh?!
What is she doing?
What's wrong, Basacchi?
I got a headache and feel dizzy all of a sudden,
so I'm skipping gym today.
Come up with some good excuse for me, okay?
This is their classroom.
I wonder what kind of naughty things they imagine during class?
Now, in order to help that hopeless Basara-san...
Wh-Why are you here, Basara-san?!
That's my question.
Jeez, Basara-san, are you so worried about me that you would skip class?
Yeah. I'm deathly afraid of what stunts you're trying to pull.
Well?
What?
What are you planning to do with my desk?
Place a spell that makes women want to
rub their sensitive spots against its corners.
What kind of harassment is that?
You do not like the idea?
No, I don't!
The real reason is to check up on Mio-san's safety.
A lot of things have happened recently, after all.
Well, it would be a relief if we could have you check on things, but...
Since you are already here, would you mind accompanying me?
Me, too?
Yes.
We can mask our presence with magic,
and above all, it is for Mio-sama's sake!
All right. I'll go with you.
Hey, Maria...
What are you hesitating for, Basara-san?
That's not the issue here.
Not only is this a semi-private space,
it's a place, where people tend to let their guard down.
In other words, it is easiest to target her in this location.
All right.
How is it?
Now that you have actually seen it, is it different from what you expected?
Yeah. Though it feels like I've lost something in exchange.
Wh-What's wrong?
This presence!
H-Hey, Maria?!
Is it an enemy?
Bingo! I knew there would be some.
You're so dirty...
So are you...
No!
Hey, Maria...
Shh! They will notice us, you know!
Wow, they're both incredible!
It's like a serious race!
You intend to compete to the end?
I will not lose to Naruse-san.
I will win this in order to have Basara fondle me a lot.
Okay, time. Climb out.
Ahh, no. That is completely wrong!
That is way too half-hearted!
I worry about the future of this nation.
Anyone can get onto the roof, can't they?
That Takigawa just made things up.
Hmm? What's wrong?
Now then, on to the next spot!
If I were going after Mio-sama,
I would certainly do it here or in the girl's restroom.
Well yeah, you would...
Since you have already conquered all the girl's restrooms,
a mere girl's changing room or two should barely even faze you.
Don't say things that sound so bad!
We're getting out of here before the girls come back, okay?
H-Hey!
What are you doing, Maria?
Ooh! This is the locker Mio-sama uses.
Basara-san, this is terrible!
What's wrong?!
There!
Hey, Maria?!
No! Basara-san, how perverted!
Why you!
What?! Basara-san, I am just joking! I am joking!
Shut up, you perverted succubus!
This time I'm going to-
Ahh, it's finally over.
Having class in the pool during first period is really just the worst.
Basara-san, hide!
Huh? Wait, hey!
What do we do?
If Mio-sama finds out, she will spank me again!
I think I am in a really tight spot right now.
Don't worry.
I'm in an ever tighter spot.
If I am going to end up making Mio-sama angry anyways, then...
Hey! What are you?!
Since I have the opportunity,
I am going to enjoy sexually harassing you, Basara-san.
Now, Basara-san...
Give up, and join me in lust.
Hey!
I can't wait for tonight.
Are you serious about forging a Master-Servant pact with Basara?
I-I can try harder, too, you know...
There you go, Basara-san.
Is it here?
Does it feel good here?
Or maybe here?
Naruse-san, are you still changing?
You look kind of pale.
I'm feeling a little, uh, unwell.
Are you all right?
Should we take you to the nurse's office?
I'm fine. I can go on my own.
Don't push yourself, okay?
Yeah, thanks. And sorry.
Don't worry about it.
After all, we're friends.
We'll be heading out, then.
Yeah...
To the pervert wearing someone's panties on their head,
and the idiot shedding her clothes:
make yourselves decent again and come out.
Right now.
If you don't,
then this locker is going to get hotter than the latest oven.
In other words, you were doing this in order to ensure my safety?
Yes.
And you?
Do you have anything to say for yourself?
I'm truly sorry.
I need to give Yuki a proper apology, as well.
Why are you bringing Nonaka up?
Huh?
Oh, no! The curse!
No!
H-Hey!
Mio-sama?!
Why are you...
I understood all along.
I knew you were doing this for my sake.
But if doing that made you a bad guy, then I...
I couldn't say anything.
Seriously, you...
Whose fault is this? You jerk!
Basara-san, wait.
If you are going to do that, please be rougher and make Mio-sama submit.
Submit?
You're going on about that at a time like this?
Considering the way you are right now,
it might raise your combat capabilities one step higher.
Please do not let this chance slip by you!
Please, Basara-san!
But...
Please... Onii-chan...
All right.
Just as you used maple syrup the other day,
you need submission that
overwhelms the imagination in order to strengthen your combat capabilities.
What's going to happen to me this time?
Here I go, then.
What...
are you doing with that?
First, we are going to cool your body down since it's heated up, Mio-sama.
Let me know if it gets to be too much.
What's this?
It's just an ordinary shower, but...
No!
Huh?
Mio-sama, that spot is going to get wet
while you are turned on, so it is fine.
N-No!
You'll get wet, too, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan... wait..
Onii-chan...
No!
B-Basara-san?
Onii-chan...
I'm going for it now...
You held out until the very end.
Good girl.
Onii-chan...
Now you have strengthened both of your combat capabilities.
Thank you very much, Basara-san.
What? Usually you're more ecstatic over it.
Well, seeing you shove the shower head into her swimsuit,
I felt your sadistic side has been strengthened a degree, too.
Give me a break...
Maria did?
Yeah. I think she was wandering around that area until a while ago.
Did something happen?
We can't find Maria.
She's here at school?
A few things came up.
Remember? I didn't feel good and had to go the nurse's office, right?
She was worried...
Hey, Yuki? Can you go home with Mio?
I'll go look for Maria and bring her back with me.
All right.
I can't wait for tonight.
Huh? Y-Yeah...
Why you!
Hey, Nonaka, hold up!
Are you listening to me?!
Tonight it's Yuki after Mio, huh?
What a day.
Maria!
She's over there?
Takigawa?
Why are those two...
Oh, Basara-san.
Yoo-hoo.
I was hoping to find another rendezvous-on-the-roof type of event,
and I completely forgot the time.
Like that would happen that often.
Hey, Maria...
Yes?
Just now you were with Takigawa from my class, weren't you?
Huh? You were watching?
While I searched around here and there,
I ended up getting lost,
so I undid my magic for a while and asked him for directions.
Huh?
At worst, I was worried he would treat me like a suspicious little girl,
but fortunately he turned out to be one of your friends.
It was a close call.
That so?
As for me, I would like to try to
regularly familiarize myself with the school's layout from now on.
"Regularly"?
Together let us get Mio-sama to discover us
so that we can force her to get trained again!
Learn your lesson a bit, you perverted loli succubus!
Jeez.
You will not hit me?
I was worried about you.
Oh.
I am sorry.
Ow!
We're going home. Mio and Yuki are worried.
Umm, Basara-san?
Hmm?
Can we... hold hands?
Yeah, of course.
What's with that look?
I feel guilty for getting a lead on the other two.
Don't worry about it.
I'll display it.
She's grown even more beautiful.
I can see omens of her awakening.
The Master-Servant pact magic...
I see, so that brat's...
That's Toujou Basara.
The only son of Jin Toujou.
Hmph.
Wha?! Did he erase the magic?!
Yes. Every last shred and trace of magic power.
We surmise Naruse Mio was saved from the verge of rampage the other day by this power.
The girl bearing the power of the former Demon Lord
and sought by everyone in the demon world,
along with a young boy capable of erasing a power that strong, huh?
Intriguing. This is quite intriguing!
Who else knows about this brat's power?
Lars.
Hmph. There's no need to pay someone like him any heed.
The plan you laid is ready as you commanded, Your Excellency.
Then we should start moving things forward,
so we can seize everything.
I'll show you all
a despair and pleasure
you can never fight.
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama
Next Time
Ups and Downs of Master and Servant