I thought I felt an unfamiliar presence and it turned out to just be a different mailman.
Even if this is supposed to be hard to cook, this is just confusing.
Th-- This is!?
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
「The Hard, Sweet Daily
Life of Toujou Basara」
No!
Onii-chan...
This is...
This is a once in a lifetime chance!
This is a special succubus camera that can capture the target's dream.
I call it, the Half-Demon Type Sensor Filming Dream Camera-kun #1!
The time to use it is finally here!
Maria? Good Morning.
Eh? What are you doing?
Now that it's come to this...
Come on Mio-sama, let's watch the rest of your dream!
I'm sorry, Mio-sama!
However, whether or not the dreams she sees are products of her desires or her deep psyche...
I need to confirm this otherwise I'll go crazy!
Now then, show me Mio-sama's embarrassing desires hidden deep within her heart.
Could she be waiting for a night visit from Basara?
Oh, so you are a real masochist aren't you, Mio-sama?
Wait! What are you doing making her wait, Basara in Mio-sama's dream?
Could it be...
Basara.
Oh so that's what's happening.
To think that I mixed up the "participate" dream with the regular dream.
I was careless.
Well I guess that's that.
This'll be the first time I'm playing a guy, but I guess I'll awaken that part within me.
Oh man, I actually don't want to do this at all,
But as a succubus, it'd be rude to not do anything erotic to you.
Oh, looks like I have no choice!
Yeah, I really have no choice!
I kept you waiting, huh, Mio. Your beloved husband, Basara's here.
You look like you really want something. Don't worry.
I'll melt both your body and your heart just like you wanted.
Heh, it's perfect!
Well then!
This-- This is so much better than I thought!
I'm going to feel good for all the wrong reasons.
You can't!
Of course I can, Mio.
Move your hand.
Show all of yourself to me.
You can't...but...
If you want me to...
That was just meant as a little joke, but...
This is your fault for giving that kind of reaction even though I'm not a guy!
O-Onii-chan!
Doing all of this... you're really dirty, aren't you?
No I'm not! You're the one who made it like this.
I did?
Please...don't tease me.
Mio-sama, you're too cute!
Huh? Why do I have this...
Crap! I was getting so into it, I almost fed this banana to her mouth down there!
But it should be fine if I just move it around on her panties, right?
With this, I'm in the clear!
Onii-chan?
Mio-sama, here's where the fun really starts!
And now, I'll say Basara-san's catchphrase!
I made you wait, huh, Mio?
I'll make you feel goo--
You idiot!!
That hurt!!
Basara-san? When did you get here
Around the time when you took off your clothes.
You're horrible! You didn't even knock before entering a girl's room!
I did! Over and over.
Seriously...What are you doing first thing in the morning?
You can't tell just by looking?
Yeah, I can't.
Is that so?
Seriously, what are you doing?!
I just wanted to show her, her dream...for just a bit longer.
And record her precious dirty self.
If I did, I'd be able to expand my secret collection, and it'd make me so happ--
Ow...
I thought I could take advantage of the good atmosphere I had going...
You can rest a bit longer, okay?
Thanks to that ruckus, I'm completely awake.
Want me to help?
No, it's fine.
Oh. Actually, could you give me a taste test?
Taste test?
This is something I've wanted to make for a while now.
Really? What kind of food is it?
That'll be a surprise for after it's done!
Okay, it's done!
Oh? It's ready?
Here you go, Basara-san. Eat it while it's hot!
Huh? Is this Hanpen?
Try eating it and then guess what it is.
Okay then...Thanks for the food.
Hm? Can't really bite it...
Hey, Maria. What is this, seriously.
You really don't know? It's your favorite food!
My favorite?
It doesn't taste bad, but I don't remember liking something this hard to...
How could you say that Mio-sama's panties hard to eat?
Don't do this at home!
You're joking....right?
How's the taste of your sister's freshly taken panties in the morning?
Look here!
What's the matter Basara-san? Was the fabric bad?
Maybe you're mad because I cooked the and made them into rolled panties...
Making me eat my sister's panties...You always make me do these outrageous things!!
Well, don't worry.
I put a spell on them to turn into protein when they enter your stomach.
This way, Mio-sama's panties will become your muscles and you can contin--
Don't worry. I'll let you off with the back of the blade.
W-Wait! Let's calm down!
Hm?
Yuki?
That was close. If you were Mio...
Um...Yuki-san?
Hey!!
Basara.
Say "ah."
Who would've thought that your favorite food was panties.
In the 5 years that you two have been apart, he's grown a lot!
He's reached that age that he prefers a girl's panties to having 3 meals a day.
What kind of age is that??
Are you saying that even after eating Mio's panties, you can't eat mine?
Wait, it's not like I ate Mio's panties 'cuz I wanted to.
Okay, okay. You're just going to blame it on me as always, right?
Forging a Master-Servant contract with Mio-sama,
And covering her in cake in the bath was all my fault, right?
Yeah, that's exactly it.
I see. I can't let that pass.
If they've done that, then it should be okay.
Wai--
Yuki? What are you doing?
Back when I asked you to wash my back,
You listened to what I asked when I got naked!
So with that in mind...
What's with that logic?!
You ate Mio's panties so readily but you won't even touch mine!
I won't accept such insults.
That's not even an insult!
And I never even did that!
Come on, stop it!
You're right, Yuki-san!
You're half naked with a skirt, no panties, but wearing knee socks!
In a sense, you're better equipped than usual!
What are you saying with your eyes all lit up in a situation like this?
You perverted loli succubus!
Basara, please.
H-Hey!
Looks like you guys are having a lot of fun first thing in the morning.
No, this isn't what it looks like. I can explain!
I'll have you eat mine next time.
Excuse me.
Huh? Hasegawa-sensei?
Is that you, Toujou?
Yes. I slipped during gym...
You came at a good time. Could you come over here?
Y-Yes...
Excuse me...
W-What are you doing, Sensei?
I was asked to help oversee the swimming class.
None of the standard provided swimsuits fit me, so I had one specially made, but the zipper's stuck for some reason.
I-Is that so?
Sorry to ask, but could you help me unzip?
Huh?
O-Okay then. Here I go.
Yeah. Thanks.
Wow, it's really stuck there. If I pull too hard, it might break.
Toujou?
Sensei, do you mind if I use this?
Yeah, I'll leave it to you.
Oh? Sorry, my voice just slipped out.
But like this, won't your hand slip as well?
No problem.
Okay, here I go.
1, 2...
That was a pretty rough way to do it.
S-Sorry!
I wasn't criticizing you, I was just surprised with the way you handled this.
Thanks to you, this swimsuit I just bought didn't have to be ripped in half.
Right. Well, as long as I was able to be help.
Toujou, do you have time after school today?
Yeah. I don't really have any plans or anything.
Then how about we go out to eat?
Huh?
This is harder to sit in than I thought it'd be.
My apartment's over there.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just thought that we'd be going to a restaurant or something.
Are you unsatisfied with my cooking?
No, no! I didn't mean that.
Well I guess there's a first for everything. Making food for another person, inviting a guy over...
Huh?
I tried making food that a guy your age would like.
Well, dig in.
O-Oh. Okay, thank for the food.
How is it?
It's really good!
Really? That's good.
Eat as much as you like.
Yes!
It's so good!
At least let me wash the dishes.
It's fine. Washing the dishes after the meal is done, is a privilege of the cook.
But...
In return, could you do me a favor?
Sure, ask away.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah, do it.
Okay, here I go.
Like this?
This is nice. Hearing your voice a different height than usual is refreshing as well.
As a reference, how do you do it with Naruse and Nonaka?
How?
What do you mean by that?
I mean this.
W-We don't do this kind of thing!
I'll believe you. A good teacher believes her students.
A good teacher wouldn't tease her students like this!
You're going to get in trouble one day.
I'll look forward to it.
By the way, Toujou...
What is it?
How was my cooking?
Um, you might get mad by the way I say this, but...
Hm?
This is the first time I've eaten your cooking but I felt very nostalgic eating it.
Well, I grew up in a house with no mother so I didn't even know the taste of her food or even what she looked like.
I see.
So I was being rude by saying that?
But the food was really good--
Toujou.
Yes?
Even if it's just a little, could you hold me tighter?
We're a student and teacher, you know?
I'll stop if you don't like this.
That's unfair.
I can't let you go home smelling like my perfume.
Women are pretty perceptive.
T-Thank you.
That helps a lot.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
Sensei!? Why are you coming in?
At the start of summer break, there are a lot of students who come to me for romantic advice.
What does that have to do with this situation?
I'm pretty good when it comes to romantic experience.
I was thinking that maybe I could help you understand even a little bit of their feelings.
So that's what you're doing.
You've experienced holding a woman strongly and having your clothes washed,
I doubt you mind having someone come into the bath with you, right?
I do! I really do!
You and I are student and teacher!
You don't want to? Toujou?
F-Fine.
Okay then, Toujou, let me wash your back.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Okay then, let's begin.
Eh? Huh?
W-Wait, Sensei? What are you doing?
Can't you tell? I'm washing your back.
If you're going to wash my back, you can just use a towel!
What are you saying? By experiencing this erotic back wash with my breasts,
You'll be better off in your future endeavors, won't you?
That might be true, but...
Falling into her pace is bad...
I have to do something!
So, Toujou. How are my breasts compared to Naruse and Nonaka?
T-They still have a way to go.
They do this so much better.
Really?
Then give me some advice on how I can improve.
Eh?
First, don't just go up and down, go left and right as well as if you're drawing a circle.
Just like that. Control your power and movements.
Wow. My body is getting hotter and hotter!
Sensei?
I wasn't initially planning on going in for the first kiss...
Sensei!
Toujou!
If you suck so hard--
What is this?
No way. I couldn't have...
W-Wait!
Toujou! No...
Sensei, what are you...
Toujou, how about I let you experience the pleasure of an older woman more?
Se-Sensei!
Huh? What happened?
Are you okay, Toujou?
Sensei...
I-I'm sorry!!
I apologize. My mind went blank and I didn't even notice what happened to you.
No, I'm sorry too.
It looks like you let me sleep on your lap the entire time.
I'm sorry.
Um, Sensei?
Hm?
We took a bath and did some other things together, right?
What, Toujou. Did you forget because of the heat?
Eh?
Yeah, as if.
Your shirt's dry now. Sorry it took so long.
Want me to drive you home?
Uh, no it's okay.
I have something I want to think about alone.
A lot of things.
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
kono mune no oku ni zutto
The words came out so naturally in my dream
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
I practiced many times
nando mo renshuu
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I want you to see you again, my dearest one
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to live with you
tomo ni ikite ikitai
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
Stay smiling forever
itsu made mo egao no mama