Summer Only!!
.Satsuma Chicken
「The Day I Got a Little Sister」
Why Oyako-don?
It's limited-time only!
Now's your only chance!
If you don't eat it you'll regret it later.
You're too old to fall for that crap.
Basara, you said you wanted a little sister, right?
I did not.
What are you talking about?
Sure you did.
It was around ten years ago.
Do you think I'd remember something like that?
I've got good news.
You've got a cute little sister.
She should be here any minute.
Wait, you're serious?
You don't know when to give up, do you?
I told you she wants to meet you and say hello right away.
Right away?
Listen, I just found out about this.
Just now!
Why are you so nervous?
Calm down a little.
I'm going to go wash my face.
How can I be calm?
The old man just suddenly says he's remarrying.
The family's always been just us two guys.
How can he just...
A little sister?
The lock is broken.
The lock is currently
broken. So please
knock first.
Manager
Make sure you knock...
Please knock?
Oh, crap!
Wait a second!
Please, don't panic and listen to me.
I didn't mean for this to happen!
It's a misunderstanding. An unfortunate accident!
It says the lock is broken,
but I didn't see it...
We're both victims here!
So please calm down!
Please, I'm begging you!
Okay, So you understand?
Why?
Why, you ask?
You peeked on me in the bathroom,
and then you came inside, put your hand over my mouth,
and started making excuses!
Think carefully about what you just did!
What are you doing?
Jin-san?
Dad!
Huh?
Pleased to meet you.
I am Naruse Maria.
Toujou...
Basara.
Naruse Mio.
Nice to meet you.
I'm told he really likes cute little sisters.
What are you talking about?
You're blushing.
No I'm not!
Anyway, where's your mother?
Is she coming later?
Oh, Chihaya-san.
So, Chihaya-san's her name?
Yup.
She'll be out of the country on business for a while.
For a while?
Huh?
Toujou Naruse
You're finally awake.
Good morning.
Um... what are you doing?
What? I'm waking you up.
I thought guys liked being woken up like this.
What are you talking about?
Service.
Service?
What are you thinking?
Just get up already, okay?
Um...
Hey, I think I feel something hard.
No, I'm not...
N-Not that!
Hey!
What is this?
Hey, are you okay?
Plowing My Real Stepsister's
Unclaimed Field ~ecstasy~
What the hell is this doing in my room?
Plowing My Real Stepsister's
Unclaimed Field ~ecstasy~
You're living with us now and you've got games like that?
I knew it!
You knew what?
I don't even play-
You pervert!
Next time you do something like that
I'm going to kill you a hundred times.
Wait! You've got it all wrong!
Wait!
I'm glad we found a nice place to live.
Toujou Naruse
What's wrong?
You don't look happy.
Toujou Naruse
This house was dirt cheap.
You're not even remarried yet and you're buying a new house.
And I had to move and switch schools all of a sudden.
This is no funny matter.
We can't just ignore those two.
They were attacked by these weirdos...
And they're actually pretty hurt.
Because of that, Maria-chan won't even go to school.
And now their mom's out of the country for a long time.
I understand that, but...
This must be some kind of fate.
Why not protect them when we can?
This was your decision, Dad.
I'm sure you've got some reason.
If they start hating me before I can
protect them then there's no point!
Basara-san! Good morning!
Morning.
It will be done soon,
Thanks.
Is something wrong?
W-Weird?
Why are you dressed like that?
Oh, is that it?
Too bad!
I am actually wearing clothes under my apron!
Oh, did that excite you?
You are a teenage boy, after all.
Right?
No, um...
Oh, right.
Did you like my housewarming present?
Housewarming present?
"Me and My Real Stepsister's Youth in an Unmarked Lot."
That was you?
What were you thinking?
I thought you could use it as a reference from now on.
A reference for what?
Is there anything you can do with a stepsister except train her to your liking?
W-What is with this girl?
Basara-san?
Is a game maybe not good enough,
so you want to do it with me in real life?
Where did that come from?
Why are you guys so loud? It's too early.
Oh, well.
The truth is that Basara-san is
about to train me for the first time.
Hey!
I see.
First you knocked me to the ground,
and now you're going to enjoy a
"youth in an unmarked lot" with Maria.
That's not it!
Oh, you got your hands on Mio-chan first, huh?
Oh boy.
Dad, say something!
I know you're happy to have
two cute little sisters,
but try not to commit any crimes.
You don't understand at all.
What's with that expression, Basara?
Smile!
What is it?
So you can smile, too?
I was just thinking this was kind of nice.
Is it?
This is our first family portrait,
so try to enjoy it a little.
Okay, I'm taking it.
Family, huh?
Stay here. I'll get the bike.
Hey, are you alone?
Want to have some fun with us?
Don't touch me!
If you touch me, I'll kill you a hundred times over.
She says she's going to kill us!
Then let's see it.
Got a problem with my friend?
Basara.
Basara?
What kind of lame name is that?
It's not as lame as your face.
What?
Why, you-
You bastard!
Mio!
Get on!
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
We can just go buy more pepper.
I'm sorry.
Really.
This place isn't half bad, huh?
It's pretty.
I found this place when my dad brought me to take a look at the new house.
I'm sure it's even prettier at night.
Let's all come together next time.
Yeah.
You're right.
Next time...
Are you still thinking about what happened back there?
Well, our parents haven't remarried yet,
but we're living together.
We have to help each other.
Just like how you came to wake me up.
We need to rely on each other and help each other,
even with the little things.
And become a family little by little.
Um... so...
Cocky.
You're too cocky.
But...
you felt a little bit like a big brother back there.
Really?
Yeah.
Just a little.
Then can you forget about the bathroom at the restaurant and this morning-
No!
But you understand now that
"Youth in an Unmarked Lot" was Maria's!
And the fact that you knocked me to the ground?
It was an accident!
W-Wait, you're going overseas? Now?
A freelancer has to be reliable and fast.
I'm off to Dubai.
This is too sudden.
What are you going to do with those two?
It's the oldest son's job to protect the family when the father isn't around.
Okay, take care of the place while I'm gone.
Looks like he's finally gone.
My dad's gone.
Hey, are you in here?
What?
You're right here.
What's wrong?
Why are the lights off?
What do you want for dinner?
Hey, now.
The minute Dad leaves they put their guard up?
Listen, should we just get delivery?
Listen, Basara.
I have a request.
Sure, we can get sushi or
eel if that's what you want.
Leave this house.
Sorry.
Can you say that again?
Did you not hear Mio-sama's words?
What was that?
A human usually panics when
witnessing magic for the first time.
Magic?
I am sure just hearing the word "magic" is not enough for you to really understand, is it not?
Magic exists.
No, not just magic.
Races other than humans exist, as well.
Then is Mio also...
Would you keep your mouth shut?
You are being very disrespectful...
Towards the future Demon Lord.
Your light pours faith into hope,
hikari wo shinjita kibou no saki e
but the road through tomorrow never ends.
ashita e no michi wa owaranai never ends
Fragments of our oath fill my eyes with light
hitomi ni utsushita chikai no kakera
as your testament sunders the vortex of darkness.
ankoku no uzu wo kirisaku testament
When my shout shakes
kami sae mo koete sakendara
even the gods,
sagashidashite
you will be called to action.
mamorubeki mono
Hold what's worth protecting in your right hand
nigirishimeta migite de
and run far away, for no destination is too far.
far away donna tooku de mo todoku yo
If it means not losing what you hold dear,
daiji na mono nakusanai omoi nara
then we'll rise above this dead world
every way kareta sekai kara susumeru hazusa
and run to the future.
mirai e hashire
So you're demons, and Mio is the Demon Lord?
The clan of gods, our enemies,
and what you call "heroes," exist as well.
Mio-sama and I are taking this house,
to serve as our base in the human world.
Then my dad's remarriage...
It is just a made-up story.
We altered his memories.
Now it is your turn.
You could not get along with the two girls in your house,
so you are going to live with some relatives in the country.
Will that suffice?
Yeah.
That'll do.
You were lying to me this whole time? Ever since we met?
Sorry, but we're taking this house.
Bye-bye, Brother.
It wasn't for very long, but it was fun.
Now leave.
Does it seem not strange?
I will try again.
When did he-
A-Are you trying to resist?
You are going to get hurt!
My magic...
Impossible!
Why are you so surprised?
Didn't you just say it?
Demons exist... and so do gods...
And...
So do heroes!
No way!
The hero clan should be in their hidden village!
What are you doing here?
I'm not obligated to tell you.
It doesn't matter to me if you're demons,
or the Demon Lord!
Mio-sama!
Leave.
I don't have the money or energy to
help someone who tricked my father.
I'll send your stuff
wherever you end up going.
So get out.
Give him back!
Give my child back!
I have to do something.
I...
It's okay.
It's just a coincidence.
I don't have that technique anymore...
Yes, of course I realized.
You were pretending to be tricked?
I guess so.
I'd actually had my eyes on them for a while.
I realized the guys in the
village were watching them.
The village?
She's the only daughter of the
Demon Lord Wilbert, after all.
Wilbert was a peaceful Demon Lord,
who brought the warlike demons to heel
and put an end to the long battle with
the hero clan with his immense power.
But at the same time,
the warlike demons who disliked
this truce came after his throne.
To keep this threat from coming
after his newborn child,
Wilbert had some of his servants in the
human world raise her as her parents.
That child is Mio.
But why did they do this?
Around a year ago, Wilbert died.
I'm sorry, Maria.
I wanted to see this before we left town.
I knew we couldn't live together.
I had not expect him to be a part of the hero clan.
We will find another base right away.
No, Maria.
Let's stop lying to people.
I don't want anyone to suffer because of us.
If you say so, Mio-sama.
I'm sorry for being so selfish.
Warding magic?
An enemy!
The present Demon Lord, who took the throne shortly after,
came after the great power that Mio inherited from Wilbert.
Mio was rescued by the demons who
used to belong to Wilbert's faction.
Think about it.
A middle school girl who doesn't know anything
is suddenly told she's the daughter of the Demon Lord.
Mio's power hasn't awakened totally yet.
Without help, sooner or later she's going to die.
So I decided to take her in.
It's been five years since we left the village.
If they were going to come after us they'd have done it by now.
You need to tell me this stuff!
Oh, right.
I'm sending it to you.
"It"?
Hey, wai-
You have one new message
Where did they go?
I'm sorry.
Really...
Take this!
Is that everything you have got?
Keep struggling uselessly, and make me wet!
This is the end!
Die a hundred times, and come back then!
Are you hurt, Mio-sama?
They've finally taken action.
Fine.
If you want a fight, I'll give you one.
Mio-sama!
No...
I can't die here...
Dad...
Mom...
Damn it!
Watch out!
Mio-sama!
Let's go home.
Why?
I just came to get...
...my family.
mou ichido aitai nante omoi wa zenbu tojikomete shimaou
As much as I want to see you again, I must lock that feeling away
kono mune no oku ni zutto
And keep it buried deep inside my heart
yume no naka de wa sunao ni ieta kotoba
The words came out so naturally in my dream
nando mo renshuu
I practiced many times
kizukeba itsumo soba de waratteru kimi ga atarimae ni natteta
Before I knew it, I was taking you and your smile for granted
aa hitomi tojitemo kienai kage ni nando mo iu kara
I keep telling the silhouette that remains even when I close my eyes
mou ichido aitai taisetsu na hito
I want to see you again, my dearest one
tomo ni ikite ikitai
I want to live with you
tatoe sekai kara yaiba wo mukeraretemo
At the edge of my dreams, I told myself
mou nidoto kono te hanasanai to yume no soto de ieta kotoba
That even if it meant turning the world against me, I'd never let you go
itsu made mo egao no mama
Stay smiling forever
Next Time
First Contract Between Servant And Master