Over The Testament
Presented by Harunatsu Fansubs
sabireta kono sekai ni habikoru
I will bravely sacrifice myself to become stronger
gizen to jiko gisei
in this desolate world
sore ga bigaku ka
Is it aesthetic?
honne o kakushita kodoku na PIERO
A lonely joker reveals no feelings
kyou mo kimi wa POKER FACE
Today you wear your poker face again
kamen hazushite sa kocchi ni kite
Take off your mask and come closer
ari no mama no kimi shiritai kara
I want to know the real you
kagayaki ni tsutsumare yasashii kaze ga fuku
Engulfed in brilliant light, a gentle wind blows by
sonna sekai o misetakute chikai o koeta
I want to show you that world and go beyond the vow
arata ni kizamareru kibou e no ayumi o
A path to hope, newly etched
tsugi no PEEJI ni kakishirushi
I'll write it down on the next page
ugokidashita jikan wa nyu eiji
Time resumes now, it's a new age.
"The Very Peaceful Daily Life of Basara Toujou"
Basara-san!
How much more are you gonna sleep?
It's morning already.
Good morning, Basara-san!
Good morning, Maria....
The morning air is so fresh, isn't it?
Say, what the hell are you doing in my room?
What do you mean "what"? Of course drying myself.
To encourage Mio-sama and Basara-san,
I always have to be cheerful, right?
Here, look at every curve of my body.
How is it, Basara-san?
Just looking at it,
makes you feel better, right?
My recipes to encourage the spirit in the morning is too excessive.
I'm sorry!
At least don't punish me like this!
Stay that way for a while.
I can't!
I still have to wake up Mio-sama!
Hey, Mio, it's morning already. Come on wake up!
Now that you think of it, Mio is hard to wake up.
Excuse me, I'm coming in.
That Maria...
She did all this, so that i would be blamed.
So what? Mio is still sleeping, on top of that she is hard to wake up, anyway.
If I just close her clothes quietly, it won't create any problem.
Good grief!
At least stay still.
What are you doing, Basara ?
Yu-Yuki?
This isn't what it looks like.
T-This is....
Basara, if you want to see,
it's okay if you look at mine.
That's why i'm saying, you are wrong!
Or is it something you would like to see at night? or may be in the morning ?
No!
That's not what i meant!
Geez. Shut up already.
Early in the morning ....
You don't need to see those big fatty boobs.
I'll show you mine each and everyday.
What the hell are you even saying?
Mio, don't misapprehend me too.
It wasn't me who undressed you, it was Maria-
Oh, that's right I didn't even saw anything, so rest assured.
Cut the crap already!!
My....My...
Everyone's so cheerful this morning, aren't they?
Oh no...
You perverted demon!!
Good grief! It's not like I like it every time.
I'll show you mine each and everyday.
Rest assured, I didn't even saw anything.
What does he mean by "he didn't saw anything"?
Is it even possible not to see?
Mio-sama, I've prepared your dress.
Ah, thanks a lot.
It really suits you, Mio-sama.
Now, Basara-san will be really contented.
Why the heck did you cut my shirt for?
Me too.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Today we're going to play basketball.
Class rep.
Pick someone to accompany you carrying the ball.
Then, Basara will you help?
Okay.
Y-Yeah.
You're late, Mio.
What were you doing?
Nothing special actually.
That Maria!
She even transparent my gym clothes.
Eh?
Where's Basara and Yuki?
We just have to bring the ball, right ?
Yeah.
So, where is the ball?
No....
What are you doing?
Thanks.
Y-Yeah.
There it is, right?
It should be an easy job.
Also that one.
Just hold the ladder, i'll bring that ball.
That one too?
Hold it tight, okay.
I-I got it, but.....
Be careful!
Are you alright?
Y-Yeah.
Basara, i'm.....i'm......
What the hell are you doing?!!
Took my eyes away for a bit.
Hurry up and let go off her already.
Wait a sec, Mio!
Good grief!
B-B-B-Be careful!
Looks like you've finally woken up, Toujou.
Hasegawa-sensei?
You slept so soundly,
and here I was worrying myself to death.
I'm sorry.
Where's Mio and Yuuki?
Nothing to worry about.
They're sleeping quietly.
Oh, I see. Thank heavens.
Looks like you got stuck up underneath them.
It's not like that, I guess.
I think it's probably because my body moved by itself.
Moving on it's own, huh?
I see.
By the way, Toujou, please let me know so that I can get it. ...
You said your body was moving by itself,
meaning in what circumstances ?
Something like this?
Wa-Wait a sec.
Like this?
Or like this?
What's wrong?
You can move as you please, Toujou.
This is bad, Basara-san, Basara-san!
How could I forgot this.
Why did I forgot saying something so important?
What's that important thing?
Actually....
Tomorrow's Mio-sama's birthday!
Mio's birthday?
Yep, we have to make a big surprise for Mio-sama's birthday,
while saying happy birthday!
Birthday huh.
But, today she wasn't excited at all though.
You don't understand woman's feelings, do you Basara-san?
"Actually tomorrow is my birthday" For a girl
to say something like this, is absolutely impossible.
A woman's heart always wait for a surprise.
Mio-sama's a woman after all.
Is that how it is?
But, if it's a birthday, we have to give her a present.
What should we present her?
Yeah, you're right though.
Oh yeah!
How about we give her a cut pantie.
It would be really comfortable to wear.
Not happening.
Then, what about one of my creation,
" Breast Massage machine"?
Think more seriously!
In that case, how about " Maria's special juice "?
One sip is enough for the whole night.
How is it, Basara-san?
You just forget about it!
For me, if it's something given by Basara. I'll accept anything.
Yuki-san?
Were you listening?
By the way, I'ill always accept your presents at any time of the year.
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
Birthday present, huh?
I think it's for the best if I ask her directly, what she wants.
Mio, got a sec?
Look, I heard tomorrow's your birthday-
Mio?
What?
You came. Thanks, Basara.
Tonight I want to stay with you, that's fine, right?
Hypnotic magic? That means...
It's all Maria's doing!
Bingo, you're on target.
I thought the biggest present for Mio-sama would be Basara-san.
By the way, she is still a virgin.
Something sweet and charming of Basara-san,
Basara ....
would be the best birthday present for Mio-sama.
Hey..
Don't you think, Basara-san?
Don't give me that crap.
That's why, I told you not to use Hypnotic magic -
Mio-sama is an honest person, you know.
If you break her heart the real party won't begin.
Basara, am I not good enough?
Ehh...No. That's not what I meant.
I'm telling you, this is wrong, Maria!
No one celebrates birthday in this fashion.
Eh? And here I've made ​​an exciting situation for a young couple ..
You're so selfish, Basara-san.
Okay I got it, then we shall pursue plan B!
Now this will be more exciting.
Here I click.
Come on, please! Please!
Festival?
Well, I thought festival would be the best scenario.
Leaving that aside....
Yo, Bro!
Wanna buy something?
You're....
Whatever, but this could lead to causing problems in the neighborhood.
Don't worry about that.
Since I've created a barrier, there will be no problem of any sort.
Oh, I see. But why in this place?
Basara, sorry for the wait.
Do I look good?
Y-Yeah.
Good, good. You're looking really good, Mio-sama!
You always look charming, but this time you're much more erotic.
It's really good!
Seems like you're the one getting more fun.
Basara.
Do I look good too?
Yuki?
Just because it's Mio's birthday, that doesn't mean i'll just stay put.
If Yuki-san is silent, it's won't be that exciting, right?
So better three of you together do all sorts of things.
Now, Basara!
Let's go.
Hey, hey, where are we going?
Adorable!
Seems like this time something weird isn't gonna happen.
Of course, it's not.
Hey, I got that one first though.
So what? First come, first serve?
A-Are you alright?
No way, we got wet.
Soaking wet.
It's seriously bad!
Now, now, both of you come here, Basara-san you too.
Y-Yeah.
Mask
Shelter, huh?
Maria could even make something like this as well?
Basara.
Are you all fine now?
Please, would you like to hear my request?
Basara, hug me very tightly.
Mio.
Me too, Basara.
Yuki?
Finally, this is the climax!
It'll be a private collection of Mio-sama.
Today is fine, right?
Big brother.
Don't tell me, her magic lost all controls!
This is bad!
Mio, i got it. If this is your wish.
This isn't fair, Basara.
I also want to.
Yeah.
At this rate, adult conversation with Mio-sama won't pursue at all.
But, I want a peek.
Ah, no, no, absolutely not!
However, since I've the instinct of the succubus.
But, If it's turns out that it's just....
Come, big brother.
It's okay, Basara.
Mio, Yuki...
Big brother....
Big brother!
What the heck am I doing?
It seems that somehow the magic disappeared.
Oh! I almost forgot about it.
It turn's out that hypnotic magic use safety magic , so it got disabled on it's own.
Well, I did great though.
It all went accordingly to the plan.
Yeah. I'm really sorry.
You deserve it! Why did you do such a thing in the first place?
That could've been dangerous .
Good grief. Fortunately your birthday didn't turned out to be a huge massacre, Mio.
Birthday?
Eh? I mean Maria said, today's your birthday.
What are you talking about?
If it's about my birthday, it's still has a long time to go.
Sorry, it looks like there is a time difference
between the human world and with the nature of the Devil.
Well, who would've thought, isn't it?
But, don't worry about that, Mio-sama.
Let's make your real birthday more remarkable than this one!
More sweet, more exciting, more erotic and...and....
I told you to....
Cut the crap already!!
I hid my trembling heart
Furueru kokoro o kakushita mama de
In order to live in the present that I saved
sukuiageta ima ni ikiru tame
This cold blade pierces even loneliness
kodoku sae tsuranuku tsumetai yaiba
Believe in the flower that blossoms here
koko ni saita hana o shinjite
Even if swirling doubt looms and unwinds
uzumaita utagai ga bokutachi ga
on the road we should be walking
susumubeki michi no ue tachihodokeru kedo
No matter how painful it is, even in darkness
Donna ni kurushii kurayami mo
If it's not the melting point
Tokenai ondo naraba
Our prayers for grabbing hold of the future will come true
Idaku mirai no inori o kanaeteyukeru
When we exchange the symbols of our vows
chikai no shirushi o kawasu toki
They become limitless power
hatenai chikara ni kawaru
Let's be brave as we head for the world that keeps on spinning
Bureibu ikou megurimeguru sekai no saki de