Over The Testament
Presented by Harunatsu Fansubs
sabireta kono sekai ni habikoru
I will bravely sacrifice myself to become stronger
gizen to jiko gisei
in this desolate world
sore ga bigaku ka
Is it aesthetic?
honne o kakushita kodoku na PIERO
A lonely joker reveals no feelings
kyou mo kimi wa POKER FACE
Today you wear your poker face again
kamen hazushite sa kocchi ni kite
Take off your mask and come closer
ari no mama no kimi shiritai kara
I want to know the real you
kagayaki ni tsutsumare yasashii kaze ga fuku
Engulfed in brilliant light, a gentle wind blows by
sonna sekai o misetakute chikai o koeta
I want to show you that world and go beyond the vow
arata ni kizamareru kibou e no ayumi o
A path to hope, newly etched
tsugi no PEEJI ni kakishirushi
I'll write it down on the next page
ugokidashita jikan wa nyu eiji
Time resumes now, it's a new age.
"The Very Peaceful Daily Life of Basara Toujou"
Mask
I hid my trembling heart
Furueru kokoro o kakushita mama de
In order to live in the present that I saved
sukuiageta ima ni ikiru tame
This cold blade pierces even loneliness
kodoku sae tsuranuku tsumetai yaiba
Believe in the flower that blossoms here
koko ni saita hana o shinjite
Even if swirling doubt looms and unwinds
uzumaita utagai ga bokutachi ga
on the road we should be walking
susumubeki michi no ue tachihodokeru kedo
No matter how painful it is, even in darkness
Donna ni kurushii kurayami mo
If it's not the melting point
Tokenai ondo naraba
Our prayers for grabbing hold of the future will come true
Idaku mirai no inori o kanaeteyukeru
When we exchange the symbols of our vows
chikai no shirushi o kawasu toki
They become limitless power
hatenai chikara ni kawaru
Let's be brave as we head for the world that keeps on spinning
Bureibu ikou megurimeguru sekai no saki de