Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
The attacks by the Gundams
sent by the Space Colonies...
...reflected the colonies'
retaliatory intentions.
OZ has masked its identity
in the Alliance Military...
...and the Gundams' mission
is to attack them.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite soldiers
at his command...
...Treize Khushrenada plans to
destroy the Alliance Military.
The battle between OZ and the
mobile suits sent to Earth...
...causes serious repercussions
on the Earth.
This is where it starts.
He goes to every family member,
seeking their verdict.
Everything he does is thorough
and well thought out.
You're such a coward!
You obviously just wanna
take the easy way out of this!
It's the only way I can live.
To the Battleground, Antarctica
Last stop.
Satisfied?
It's not that simple.
You can't forgive yourself for
accidentally killing a pacifist.
And it happened because
you were tricked by OZ.
I can sympathize.
But to put your life in the
hands of your victim's family...
That's what I want.
Going from place to place...
...I knew it'd only be a matter
of time before someone found us.
I'll take care of it.
Wait.
Shouldn't overdo it
in your state.
I'll stop them.
Trowa...
H-hey!
Thanks; I owe you.
No problem.
So...
If we're gonna transport this,
we can't do it by land.
- Then by sea...
- I've got my eye on a ship.
But now we know that
we're being watched.
So it might be difficult.
You can use my carrier.
I didn't expect you to be alive.
It's the first time we've met
face to face.
My name is Lucrezia Noin.
I serve under Colonel Zechs.
Zechs?
The pilot you fought
against in Siberia.
Don't think we won't
put up a fight.
Colonel Zechs wants to meet you.
He does?
To try pumping us for
information or something?
Don't misunderstand me.
He's not speaking
as an OZ soldier.
He wants to see you as
a fellow mobile suit pilot.
He hopes for another chance
to fight you boys.
He wants a final match?
Sounds like an admirable guy,
this Zechs fellow.
It's up to you guys,
whether or not you believe me.
Where is he?
You're gonna trust her?
He's not the kind of guy
to plant a trap.
No?
Then my mobile suit will
come in handy.
Trowa!
I haven't confirmed if the pilot
of the self-detonated Gundam...
...at the Siberia Base is
dead or alive.
I see.
I've been trying to reach
Colonel Zechs...
...the OZ pilot that fought
the Gundam.
But it seems he's already moved
from the Lake Victoria base...
...and I can't reach him.
So we still don't know anything?
Actually, I've been able to
find out one thing.
What's that?
Colonel Zechs did something
highly peculiar.
Peculiar?
After the battle in Siberia...
...Colonel Zechs ordered a large
amount of Gundanium...
...shipped from outer space.
To reconstruct the Gundam
from the remains they collected.
Even I know he was ordered
to destroy the Gundam...
...because OZ found out.
Actually, there are signs...
...that the Gundam which was
destroyed might've been a fake.
A fake?
So much Gundanium alloy
was shipped...
...they'd easily be able to make
two mobile suits out of it.
So they used a portion
to build the fake.
Now they're using the rest
to reconstruct the Gundam.
I believe so.
What makes that Gundam
so special, anyway?
He wants one final match
to decide things.
He's that kind of man.
Thirteen years ago,
when he was about six...
...I faced him in
a fencing match.
He hates his opponent
having a handicap.
You know Colonel Zechs?
He was a hero in the eyes
of the Peacecrafts.
There are many stories
of his bravery.
Really?
If I could get in touch
with Colonel Zechs...
...then I might find out
what happened to Heero.
Looks like someone else
is looking for Heero Yuy.
Who it is?
Mrs. Noventa.
Noventa?
Yes.
Wife of Marshal Noventa, the
Alliance's Chief Commander...
...who was killed by your
Gundam friend at New Edwards.
She's trying to keep her
search a secret from OZ.
I'd like you to contact
Mrs. Noventa right away.
Of course, right away.
I told you he'd be alive,
didn't I Noin?
Yes.
He's got a strong will to live.
Thanks for your assistance.
And sorry to drag you
into this.
Don't forget that I'm
a mobile suit pilot too.
I understand your feelings
to a certain extent.
Thank you Noin.
Watch your step around
that search party.
Given this situation I won't
be able to help you out.
You'll have to somehow
deceive them on your own.
I'll take care of it.
Over and out.
We must make the final
modifications to Zero One...
...before they get here.
There are numerous rumors...
...that the Gundam destroyed
by Colonel Zechs was a fake.
Should we allow Colonel Zechs
to continue acting on his own?
This Zechs issue is becoming
quite a topic within Romefeller.
Son?
Now...
A search party from Lake
Victoria is in pursuit.
But Zechs would never do
anything to cause me trouble.
Everyone's worrying about
this too much.
So it was one of OZ's carriers.
Oh?
Then there's a good chance
they're aboard the plane.
Think we should just leave them?
Be patient.
They're bound to show
their true colors.
Just don't lose sight of them.
Sir.
I won't let them have
their way this time.
Will the left arm be
automatically balanced...
...for the extra weight?
No, I purposely avoided that.
Instead I've had it
at my fingertips...
...so I'll have a speed
advantage during battle.
Makes sense.
Seeing them working hard...
They're not different from
any other young pilots.
We could keep Colonel Zechs
from getting into any danger...
...by getting rid of them
right now.
You still don't understand him.
Zechs would never forgive us
if we did such a thing.
Has the shield been attached
to the Gatling arm too?
Yeah, but it's heavy.
Sorry.
Normally we wouldn't let others
touch our own mobile suits.
Then you'd better hurry up
and get to know this thing.
Yeah.
But this time I'll defeat Zechs.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
I contacted Mrs. Noventa,
and she's forwarded this letter.
She said she'd like you
to deliver the letter for her.
Mrs. Noventa?
Yes, it's made out to
Mr. Heero Yuy.
To Heero?!
"Your sudden visit caught
me off guard..."
...and I didn't feel that
I was able...
...to express the true feelings
in my heart.
That's why I decided to
write this letter.
You made a mistake when
your plan went awry in battle.
But stop suffering over it.
My husband and Ventei died
trying to build a world...
...where genuine young men
like yourselves...
...could live happily.
I have no regrets.
That's what happens in war.
A wrong turn in the past
can be painful for anyone.
But you people are still young!
I hope you'll think about
building a new future!
Our family is honored
to have met with you!
"I pray the day will arrive
when all battles cease."
"To my dear friend,
Mr. Heero Yuy."
So Heero's still alive.
I knew he'd be alive!
I'm leaving for Sicily.
I'll meet Mrs. Noventa
and ask where Heero is!
Right.
I'll make flight arrangements.
See?
Heero was alive after all!
I can't have our special
guests catch a cold.
Put these on.
Where are we headed?
The South Pole.
A mobile suit battle on
a continent covered in ice?
It's the only place to have
a battle and go unnoticed.
Colonel Zechs.
All areas needed to determine
ability have been restored.
Measuring abilities isn't
enough.
I want this Gundam
completely restored!
Why should we take it that far?
I wanna know more.
More about this mobile suit,
and more about its pilot.
It's impossible to completely
restore the right arm.
It needs power to handle
the giant beam cannon...
...and a system to precisely
control the beam saber.
We'd need enough time to
build a whole new mobile suit.
Then at least complete the
beam saber system...
...using parts from the left
arm of Tallgeese.
Colonel Zechs, what are you
trying to prove?
Please, just try to indulge me.
As you wish.
Everyone listen up!
New instructions for the
restoration of Zero One's right arm!
Problem, Lieutenant!
Our craft is being followed
by a number of carriers.
They've found us.
We spotted them when
we reached the continent.
They've calculated our
flying range.
They must've realized we'd be
headed for Colonel Zechs' base.
We'll throw them off
by changing directions.
No.
If we sacrifice two Aries,
we could break free of them.
Then even if they know the
base location we can attack.
Right!
Stop lying.
You wouldn't do anything
to burden Zechs.
You're going on the Aries?
You'll be overpowered
by their numbers.
My mission is to get you
to the destination safely.
The method is up to me!
Two Aries suits have been
dropped and are free-falling.
They haven't righted
themselves yet!
Don't be tricked by
their pranks!
We'll release our suits too!
Let's go!
Roger!
Carrier One's going down!
- Spread out!
- Roger!
One more shot and Carrier
Two's down.
Get back in the clouds
and be patient!
No, I'm going for it!
Gotcha!
No!
You all right?!
I'm sorry!
That was careless.
Lieutenant!!
Backup troops?!
This time take me directly
to Zechs and the Gundam.
Fire!
I'll cover for you,
Lieutenant Noin!
Get outta here while
you can!
Don't be ridiculous!
Damn it!
Right!
We have to rescue
Lieutenant Noin!
- That's against orders.
- What?!
I won't take that crap from you!
Turn us around!
You're too weak.
That's enough!
We surrender!
Why?!
There's no point continuing!
We've thrown down our weapons!
We surrender!
Stop attacking us!
Do you think the normal
rules apply...
...to someone who's betrayed
Romefeller?
I might consider it, if you
hand over the Gundam...
...as proof of Zechs' betrayal.
What?!
Unfortunately that won't
change Zechs destiny.
We'll finish him off here.
As my reward for
defeating him...
...my superior skills
will be recognized.
I won't let you get near Zechs!
So Zechs is here after all!!
Damn you!!
Okay, we've got our info.
Get rid of them!
You came back?!
Emergency landing!
Let me off first!
I'll correct the mistakes
your weakness caused.
A Gundam!
That's Gundam Zero Three!
That Gundam's strong!
It's too much!
The Gundam will be used as
an excuse to get the colonies.
So I can't let anyone report
that it was seen here.
Fighting Zechs' soldiers
off at Point 103...
...of the South Pole.
We've located...
...a Gundam!
"Those who've laid eyes on
a Gundam shall not live."
Those are my orders.
That's enough! Stop!
THERE'S A GUNDAM DOWN HERE!!
Damn it.
Why do I have to keep
on fighting like this?
These young pilots are too pure.
Are you all right?
The name is Trowa.
I need you to reload
the explosives for Heero.
Forget that...
Stop worrying about that
right now!
Start thinking about
your own welfare!
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Zechs waits at the South Pole
with the completed Wing Gundam.
Heero challenges Zechs to a duel
with Trowa's Gundam Heavyarms.
Heero and Zechs commence their
battle amidst the snowy winds.
Zechs tries to find something
beyond the desperate battle.
As does Noin.
But then Relena arrives.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 16,
The Sorrowful Battle
"The Sorrowful Battle".