I am Azazel,
leader of the Fallen Angels.
A-Azazel?!
The Governor of the Fallen Angels?!
Why did you...
I realized that Kokabiel was plotting something...
so I came here to keep an eye on him.
I wanted to see your Boosted Gear, too.
I see Albion did his job.
Albion?!
The White Dragon...
My direct intervention would've caused some problems,
so I asked him to sort things out.
I'm surprised he accepted the job so willingly.
So it was you!
It was your fault...
The reason I didn't get to suck on the President's tits-
was because of you!
Was it?
Sorry about that.
If you hadn't sent Albion,
I would've got to-
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but you aren't strong enough to beat anyone at Kokabiel's level...
no matter how much you power up.
Anyway,
the leaders of the Angels, Fallen Angels, and Devils
are having a conference about this incident.
A conference?
This is unbelievable!
The leader of the Fallen
Angels was trespassing on my territory,
and interfering with my business?!
Moreover, he even tried to take my precious Pawn from me.
He deserves to die!
President...
President, is it true that the leaders of the factions are meeting here?
Yes, I've just received word to that effect.
The leaders are going to meet to discuss the future of their relations.
That must mean that Kokabiel's actions
have disrupted the relations between the Angels, Fallen Angels, and Devils.
Had the leaders of the Devils and Fallen Angels faced each other here, however...
things would have been much worse.
Still, I wonder what he was up to.
Huh?
Azazel.
Was he after my Boosted Gear?
Don't worry, Issei.
I won't let him lay a finger on you.
My puny arrogance came back to me
Takaga shireteta terai ga uzumaite
and I couldn't go to you for help
Oisugaru koto mo dekizu ni ita yo
I couldn't tell you why I was crying
Namida no wake kimi ni ienai mama de
and always frowned up to the sky
Kuchibiru wa itsumo sora wo nirande ita
You dug through the darkness to cross this line
Uzumoreteta yami yori kimi ga koete kita kyoukaisen
The world's out of changes to make
Sekai system wa kakumeigire
Pleasure, pain, destruction, creation
Kaikan itami hakai souzou
I'm going to change my own weaknesses
Kaete yuku watashi no yowasa wo
All I can make are appeals to emotion
Ima oshiyoseru kanjouron
Love's not easy with my life on the line
Inochi gake no ai wa amakunaiwa
Stronger, even stronger
Tsuyoku motto tsuyoku
No matter what lies I face
Donna uso ga matteita to shitemo
I've already chosen which signs to follow
Eranda michibiki shinjite
The devil smiles at me, telling me to be myself
Furumau koto wa nai to yasashii akuma no hohoemi wa
and shines a faint light on the world
Hakanaku subete wo terasu no
Episode 7
Summer! Bathing Suits! I'm in Trouble!
Morning.
Good morning, Xenovia-san.
Morning, Xenovia.
Morning.
Looks like you've gotten used to living here.
Yeah.
The room the President got for me is very nice.
This is Devil territory,
so you should have little to fear.
What a mess...
It hasn't been cleaned since last year.
And we're supposed to clean this?
Why does the Occult
Research
Club have to clean the pool?
It would usually be the job of the Student Council,
but since they helped us fight Kokabiel,
I volunteered us to do it.
In exchange, once the pool is clean,
we get to take a dip before anyone else!
Take a dip?!
That's right!
Today I get to feast my eyes on the girls in their swimsuits!
Pool cleaning rules!
Bring it on, dirty pool!
Your expression is dirty, Issei-senpai.
In the name of the Occult
Research
Club,
let's make this pool cleaner than it has ever been before!
Yes!
Swimsuits, swimsuits...
Issei-kun.
I promise...
if someone were to come after you,
I would do all I could to protect you.
Wh-Why are you telling me now?!
It's hard to talk about this when there are others around.
O-Okay, thanks.
Pretty sure you're supposed to use that line on the heroine,
not some guy, like me.
I am indebted to you for saving me.
One who didn't return such a favor,
wouldn't be fit to be a Gremory Knight.
You picked one hell of a place.
I-I'll see you outside!
Issei-kun?
Akeno-san only just sucked the power out!
Didn't I tell you to watch out for a strong force?
What?
This should come as no surprise after making contact with people as strong as Azazel so many times.
Power attracts power.
So the source of the strong force was him?
Did you finish that homework, Asia?
I did!
Did you Xenovia-san?
I'm having a hard time with the Japanese.
I'm not too good with kanji myself.
I must say, Japan's writing system is too difficult.
Perhaps I should spend the night studying kanji.
Good luck!
The Lord will watch over your studies!
Yes, you're right.
Amen.
Finish changing.
O-Okay...
We've got trouble, President!
Issei-kun is...
What happened to him?
All right.
Let's have Akeno suck the Dragon's power out.
You're okay with that?!
Of course.
Anything for my precious junior.
Th-Thank you!
What is taking them so long?
Teasing you like this makes me feel like a bully.
A bully?!
Want to have an affair with me?
An affair?!
I won't tell the President or Asia-chan about what we're going to do.
Makes your heart race, doesn't it?
It'll be our little secret.
I'm dying to know how it feels to be devoured by a young boy, fueled purely by lust.
Lust?
I don't mind you controlling me, you know?
Can I?!
Can I really?!
Of course...
I can't call myself a man if I turn her down!
Can't call...
myself...
What exactly's going on here?
P-President?!
I was just distracting the Dragon.
That's not what it looked like to me.
Well, Issei?
L-Let me explain!
Were you getting to know your beloved Akeno?
N-No, I...
See if I care.
President!
My, my. Is she jealous? How adorable.
Issei-kun...
Yeah?
I see that your relationship is steadily progressing.
A-Awesome!
Now, let's swim to our hearts content!
Issei,
Yes?!
How do you like my swimsuit?
I-It's the best!
Hands down!
My, my.
Stepping up the game, aren't you, President?
You must have been dying to let Issei-kun see you in that.
Are you in any position to say that to me, Akeno?
Who knows?
Look at those sexy bodies!
Issei-san!
I-I'm done changing.
Asia
Wow, Asia, you look amazing!
Your big brother approves!
I'm so happy to hear that!
You're doing a grand job as our mascot, Koneko-chan.
You're as cute as a button!
Why do I feel uncomfortable being the only one to not receive your lustful gaze?
Asia
Oh, where's Xenovia?
Sh-She was having trouble with her swimsuit,
so she told me to go on ahead.
Asia
Oh.
Issei...
I have a favour to ask of you.
Okay...
Okay.
One Two
Keep it up Koneko-chan!
Who would have thought...
Koneko-chan didn't know how to swim.
If only it was President or Akeno-san instead.
One Two
That would be so awesome!
Issei-senpai...
W-What is it?
I'm sorry you have to teach me to swim.
I-It's fine, helping a girl learn to swim is fun.
Crap, I'm done for.
Issei-senpai, sometimes you can be surprisingly gentle.
Uh-
Despite being a pervert.
Gah-
I suppose that is my reputation.
But I do want to do things to help my comrades.
Koneko-chan, I like being of use to you.
I suppose you think you can rival me.
I'm up against a girl powered by love.
We might be comrades, but don't think I will let you win, Akeno.
Let's just have a fair race, Rias.
My two onee-sama's are racing.
Alright! Boosted gear!
Transfer.
I can increase my vision by using my power-up ability.
This is what my Boosted
Gear should be used for.
I'm going to burn these images into my internal memory-
Damn you Kiba.
Remember, Asia-senpai needs to learn to swim also.
One Two
Okay.
We're almost at the end.
You can do it Asia-senpai!
One Two
Asia
Maybe we had a bit too much fun.
Issei...
Could you rub some oil on me?
Y-Yes, with pleasure!
This is the best day of my life.
Hey, Issei...
Yes?
Would you like to oil my chest?
...oil my chest?
"Oil my chest?!"
That's the most beautiful thing anyone's ever said!
Well?
A-Are you sure?
Sure.
You love girl's chests, don't you?
Yeah, more than anything in the world!
I'll have you rub it all over them later.
I-It feels like the President's
become a lot more aggressive.
Oh my!
Why is she getting special treatment?
A-Akeno-san?!
Hey, Akeno!
He hasn't finished oiling me yet!
President, your b-b-boobs!
Hey, President,
would you mind if I have Issei-kun?
You can't have him.
He is mine!
You'll never take him from me!
Hey, Issei-kun...
Y-Yes?!
Did you get to suck the president's breasts?
N-No, I didn't.
My, my. You poor child.
Then, I'll let you suck mine instead.
What?
P-President?
Akeno, don't you think you're
getting a little full of yourself?
My, my.
If that's the way you would like to settle this, I won't hold back.
I won't give him to you!
Why can't I just love him?
Besides, don't you hate men?
Says the woman who wasn't interested in them,
because they "are all the same."
Damn, that was scary.
I just can't figure out what goes through their minds at times.
What are you doing back here?
Xenovia?
What took you so long?
I've never worn a swimsuit before.
It took me a while to put it on.
Do I look weird?
You've never worn one?!
Is it because you're from the Church?
I was never interested in
recreational activities like these.
You still took way too long, though.
While I was changing,
I was thinking about a few things.
Like what?
Hyoudou Issei,
I want to ask a favour of you.
You can just call me "Issei".
So how can I help?
Then Issei, I would like to ask you:
Will you make babies with me?
Didn't you hear me, Issei?
Let us procreate.
What?!
My purpose in life was to serve God,
but now that's all been lost.
When I asked President Rias about it...
Devils possess desires, grant desires,
give desire, and seek desire.
Follow your desires.
...she said.
Huh?!
I then decided to have a more womanly goal,
a dream:
To bear a child.
Hey, hold up.
After seeing you fight Kokabiel,
I realized that you possess noteworthy courage.
You even have a Dragon's aura.
Such strong and special genes make you a suitable mate.
Y-You're not convincing me at all!
We're all alone now. This is our chance.
I'm sure we were guided by the Lord-
Anyway, let's give it a try.
Regrettably, I am inexperienced with men.
I will let you, the expert in sex, take the lead.
H-Hey...
Sleep with me!
As long you give me a child,
I won't question anything you do.
Issei, what's going on in here?
My, my. You're so sneaky, Xenovia-chan.
I'm the one who's going to take Issei-kun's purity.
How could you, Issei-san?!
Had you asked me, I would've...
Sneaky bastard.
What's wrong, Issei?
Let's make babies.
Wh-What?!
Look at all those people!
You aren't supposed to...
Let's... make... babies?!
Good grief.
Why are you so indecent?
Oh, no.
He was just trying to get me pregnant.
Can you just keep quiet?!
Seems like you're having fun.
Is something special going on?
O-Onii-sama?!
S-Satan-sama?!
This man is Satan Sirzechs Lucifer-sama,
the President's brother?
Are you Asia Argento?
Y-Yes.
Thank you for helping my sister.
You have become a very talented Bishop.
N-Not so...
No need to be so tense.
I'm here on personal business.
Yes, sir.
Personal business?
Are you a Satan?
Pleased to meet you.
I am Xenovia.
It's a pleasure, Xenovia.
When I heard the wielder of Durandal had joined my sister's family,
I could scarcely believe my ears.
I still believe that I was quite bold to choose to become a Devil.
Sometimes, I still regret it.
Really, why did I become a Devil?
Was I desperate?
But I didn't...
Uh...
My sister's family always makes me smile.
Xenovia, I hope that you do your best to
support the Gremorys as one of my sister's kin.
I can't possibly betray such words
from Lucifer, the legendary Satan.
I will do the best I can.
Thank you.
That aside, Onii-sama, why have you come?
Don't tell me you don't know.
Parents' Day is coming up.
Y-You can't mean...
I would love to see my sister busy in her studies.
Grayfia told you, didn't she?!
Don't worry.
Father will be coming with me.
You're a Satan.
You shouldn't be leaving your work for such a thing.
I'm not.
I'm visiting for work, too.
I would like to host the conference for the three factions here, in this academy.
I-In Kuou Academy?!
I'm glad to hear that my sister isn't causing you any trouble.
You must be kidding!
Rias-san has been a very good girl!
Yes, she's too good a girl for our Issei!
Here, have another.
Ah, thank you.
Dad, that guy's a Satan.
Wow, you drink like a fish!
I like you!
Well, he doesn't know that.
Issei, why did you ask him to stay here?
It's all right.
He said he's going to find a hotel tomorrow.
Jeez...
This is so awkward.
I didn't know the president ever acted like that.
No- No way!
Issei and I always sleep in the same bed.
I promise it will only be for tonight.
It's a chance for Hyoudou Issei and I to talk.
I'm surprised he didn't react when he learnt we sleep in the same bed.
President...
Can you sleep alone?
Can you sleep without me by your side?
I can't do it. I need you by my side!
Let's go, Miss
It's bedtime.
Alright, Grayfia.
Goodnight, everyone.
G-Goodnight.
Goodnight, Issei...
G-Goodnight, President.
Issei-san.
I'm disappointed, but I too will sleep in my own room.
U-Uh... Goodnight, Asia.
G-Goodnight.
N-Now I feel awful.
Uh... I'm sorry.
For what?
For making a Satan sleep on the floor.
I should probably thank you.
Huh?
After all, nobody in my world treats me like a normal guest.
Things don't work like that over there.
I find more comfort here than any lavish pampering could give me.
Does he really feel that way?
And when she was in the Underworld, Rias was never as cheerful as she is now.
It's all thanks to you.
Y-You should thank the others, not me.
Hyoudou Issei-kun,
Yes?
Please take good care of Rias.
Of course I will!
I'm...
I mean, I am Rias Gremory-sama's faithful Pawn!
Thank you.
Would you mind if I called you "Issei-kun"?
O-Of course not!
I'd be honored!
Well then, Issei-kun,
could you call me by my given name as well?
Or you could call me "Onii-san" if you like.
Th-That's a little...
W-Would it be acceptable for me to call you "Sirzechs-sama," then?
That's fine.
By the way, I heard that you met Azazel.
I did.
He may have been after my Boosted Gear.
Azazel certainly is curious about Sacred Gears,
but unlike Kokabiel, he's not a warmonger.
The Fallen Angels were the first to pull out of the Great War, after all.
Azazel has sentenced Kokabiel to eternal imprisonment in ice.
Then why did he...
Does he want me as his servant?!
What am I supposed to do if he brainwashes me?!
Don't worry.
I can assure your safety.
Th-Thank you very much!
I can't afford to lose a legendary Dragon, after all.
On a separate note...
Yes?
I've heard that you like large breasts.
Huh?
Y-Yes, I adore them!
Even as her brother, I believe Rias' breasts are quite voluptuous.
Yes, I believe that my President's,
my Master's, breasts-
are the best breasts in the world!
Speaking purely hypothetically...
Yes?
If you were to charge your Boosted Gear's power-
and transfer it directly to Rias' breasts,
what do you think would happen?
It's just another one of my odd ideas.
Don't let it bother you too much.
Good night.
Use the Boosted Gear on the President's boobs...
Why didn't I think of that?
What would happen if I did that?!
Would they get bigger?
Would her beautiful bust become even fuller...
or would they become firmer and smoother?!
I haven't got a clue!
This can't be!
I've been called "The King of Desire"
and "The Embodiment of Lust," and yet...
I can't even... fantasize.
Hyoudou
BBBBBBBBBBBBBBBB
I was so busy thinking that I couldn't sleep.
Gifting power to her boobs...
What an ingenious idea.
It shows how fit he is to be a Satan.
His creativity is amazing.
I'll be showing Onii-sama around, so I'll be back late.
I'll see you at Parents' Day, Issei-kun and Asia Argento.
Take care!
Grayfia, let's go sightseein-
Official business comes first.
Why do I have to do this?
Xenovia's awfully late.
She said she was going to stay up all night to study kanji.
I'll go get her from her room.
You go on ahead, Issei-san.
Okay.
I'm glad Asia and Xenovia are getting along.
I haven't walked to school alone in a while.
I used to be in the unpopular alliance,
but now I'm coming to school surrounded by pretty girls.
I've come a long way!
Ow!
The hell?
Who's that?
This is the second time we've met here.
What?
Welsh Dragon, Emperor of Red Dragon, Hyoudou Issei...
I am Vali,
Emperor of White Dragon...
the Vanishing Dragon.
What do you want to do?
churucchucchu doushitai
Hey, girl
churucchu hei gaaru
chu
Hey, girl
lovely devil
raburi debiru
Say yes to tomorrow
churucchucchu ashita ni Yes
chu
Say yes to tomorrow
googoogoorii
Girls are always greedy for something more
shoujo wa shikakei ni yokubari na no desu
this and that
are mo kore mo
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
kinou to kuraberun ja manzoku dekinai
ki
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
Oh yeah yeah
Oh
i
yeah
Strategy meeting on how to upgrade
uppugureido sakusen kaigi
u
Strategy meeting on how to upgrade
Agreed!
sansei
sa
n
se
i
Everyone has at least one of these
daredemo hitotsu kurai motte iru desho
da
Everyone has at least one of these
you too, and you too
kimi mo kimi mo
Original magic words that protect your heart
originaru no jumon kokoro no omamoru
o
Original magic words that protect your heart
parunrun
pa
ru
n
Positive thoughts that give you strength
purasu shikou taishitsu kyouka
pu
Positive thoughts that give you strength
So they can realize their special dreams and loves
koi mo yume mo totte oki wo ne te ni ireru tame ni
ko
So they can realize their special dreams and loves
Everyone
minna
mi
Everyone
n
na
seriously
rirurirun juushi de
quickly
saa
sa
de
wants to grow up
seichou shitai na
You see, girls are all hiding deep inside
onna no ko wa ne raburi debiru
o
You see, girls are all hiding deep inside
Lovely devils, so treat them with great care
mune no naka kakushiteru no toriatsukai youchuui
mu
Lovely devils, so treat them with great care
They're only interested in fun things
tanoshii koto shika kyoumi nai no yo
ta
They're only interested in fun things
Their whimsical temper makes them cute
wagamama ni kawaiku narun da
wa
Their whimsical temper makes them cute
Promise me
yakusoku
ya
Promise me
ku
so
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
And even the student council
president's older sister is coming,
and there's a huge commotion at the school!
Is this all right?
Open House Begins!
Episode 8
Next episode:
"Open House Begins!"
Love those boobs!