We've created a protective
barrier around the academy.
If all goes well, it should contain the damage.
Thank you.
This will really help, Sona.
However, I can't guarantee it will hold if the situation changes.
True.
Vice-Chairwoman!
How's Irina doing?
Her life is not in danger...
thanks to you, Argento-san.
What a relief!
What happened to Xenovia?
No sign of Kiba, either?
Yeah.
I've already tried calling him.
But I just know that he's okay.
I'm sure.
We'll do our best to keep the barrier up,
but the school buildings may not remain intact.
A most regrettable loss.
I won't let that happen.
Rias, we still have time.
Call your brother.
In that case, shouldn't you also call your sister?
My family does not...
I'm sure your brother loves you dearly.
Sirzechs-sama will surely act.
So please...
I've already contacted Sirzechs-sama.
Akeno?! I didn't ask you to do that!
Rias, although I fully understand that you do
not wish to cause trouble for your brother,
our enemy is one of the leaders of the Fallen Angels.
This enemy is out of our league.
Let's take the Satan's helping hand.
I appreciate your approval, President.
Sirzechs-sama's reinforcements should arrive in about an hour.
Good grief!
Always one step ahead of me, aren't you?
One hour, you say?
Stand up once again
Tomo ni mou ichido tachiagare
To protect a single life
Mamore hitotsu no inochi tayasanu yo ni
Waking up to another dawn
Futatabi otozureta yoake ni me ga samete
I was dreaming about you
Kimi wo omoi dasu yume no tochuu
I still see your afterimage and can't move on
Me no mae no zanzo susumanai ashidori
I still see your afterimage and can't move on
Me no mae no zanzo susumanai ashidori
Powerless, I drift away
Toozakatte yuku hiriki na boku
What is most precious to me?
Taisetsu na mono wa doko ni aru?
If you believe in the future, never forget
Ashita wo shinjiru nara wasurenaide
Now is the time to risk your life and move on
Ima koso saa inochi wo kakete susumi dasu toki
The stronger your will, the stronger you will be
Omoi ga tsuyoi hodo tsuyokunaru
A faint, fragile dream will never last long
Hengen suru tsugihagi darake no risou dewa
A faint, fragile dream will never last long
sugu ni kiete shimau kara
Let's make an eternal promise
Towa e tsuzuku kawasu chikai
From the bottom of our shivering bodies
Furue dashita karada no soko kara
Decisive Battle at Kuoh Academy!
Episode 5
Issei,
I need you to act as our support.
Your support?
I want you to share your heightened power,
the power of your Gift, with everyone.
I see.
I can do that!
Until Issei can share his power,
I'll need you to buy us some time.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, President.
Issei.
Y-Yes?
I'm counting on you.
Of course!
We're on the offensive this time.
We're going to storm the academy to prevent
Kokabiel from releasing his power.
Unlike our battle with Raiser,
our lives will be on the line.
However, I won't allow any of you to die.
My precious servants,
come back alive so you can study here once again!
Right!
Promotion: Queen!
What is that?
I heard that this man's been dying to fuse four Excaliburs into one.
Kokabiel!
Is Sirzechs coming?
Or will it be Serafall?
In place of my brother and Leviathan-sama,
we have come.
President!
The gym!
How dull.
Oh, well.
We'll have some laughs.
N-No way!
Scared, partner?
That's the biggest spear of light I've ever seen!
He's way out of our league!
Yeah, you bet he is.
He fought God and the Satans and survived, after all.
Do we even stand a chance against him?
If worse comes to worst, I'll turn most of you into a dragon to beat him.
Most of me, huh?
He's that strong, huh?!
Since you've come all the way out here,
why don't you play with my pets?!
Cerberus?!
The dog that guards the gates of hell.
The gates...
of hell.
He summoned it to the human world?!
Let's go, Akeno, Koneko!
Yes, President.
Issei, use your Sacred Gear to give us power!
Yes, President!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Stand back, Asia!
Okay!
Don't worry.
The three of them will tame that mutt in no time!
Boost!
Have another!
They aren't taking any damage!
Boost!
Not yet!
I need more power to give them!
Dammit!
If only I were stronger...
Then I'd be able to help them instantly!
Another one?!
Boost!
Attacking and being attacked will both reset my power back to zero.
I'll act as decoy.
Asia, you run for it!
Issei-san!
Koneko-chan!
I've got this one.
But, Koneko-chan it's-
I can at least buy you time.
Koneko-chan...
Boost!
Alright then, be careful Koneko-chan
Koneko-chan!
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Now it's my turn.
Asia, look after Koneko-chan.
Come and get me, you ugly mongrels.
Follow me, come on.
I'll have to lead it around until i've powered up.
Boost!
Will they be okay?
We have to have faith in the
Occult Research Club...
In Rias Gremory's peerage.
Issei-san, look out!
That was a close one.
I'm here to help.
Xenovia!
Naturally, these demons are no match for the power of a Holy Sword.
I hate to admit it, but I'm glad she came.
W-Wow!
What the...
It's saying that your power has boosted enough to be useful in combat.
I didn't know you could do something like that!
You and your Sacred Gear grow every day.
It just gave you what you wanted.
President, Akeno-san, I'm coming!
Issei!
Issei-kun!
Boosted Gear...
Gift!
Transfer!
Impressive ability, Hyoudou Issei.
We can do this.
Indeed!
Akeno.
Right away.
Thunder, shake the earth!
Asia!
Yuuto!
Kiba-san!
Akeno!
Yes, President!
You did it!
Nice job, Kiba!
That was quite a show.
Take this!
It's huge!
I see.
The Emperor of Red Dragon's power
can make you this much stronger.
Intriguing...
So very intriguing!
It's complete!
Oh no!
Now, at long last!
Upon the fusion of the Holy Swords,
I will use the energy that is released.
That was our deal.
You put that power into an earth-breaker spell?!
No!
Are you telling me that this town
-our hometown- is going to disappear?!
Get out before it's too late.
This city will be razed to the
ground within twenty minutes.
If you want to stop it...
you'll have to defeat me.
What now...
Rias Gremory?!
Need I answer?!
Fools!
President!
Akeno!
Akeno-san!
Issei-kun?!
Are you all right, Akeno-san?
I'm so sorry.
You gave me your power, yet...
That doesn't matter!
How dare you hurt Akeno-san?!
I won't let you get away with this!
He really is quite a man.
We won't be able to last until Sirzechs-sama's arrival.
We have to do something.
Yuuto?!
Kiba!
Valper Galilei...
I am a survivor of the Holy Sword Experiments.
In truth, though, you killed me.
I was only able to live by being reborn as a Devil.
I could not die...
before I avenged my deceased comrades!
Look out, Yuuto!
No!
Kiba!
He avoided a direct hit.
Nimble little rat.
Freed.
Yes, Boss?
You again!
This is the last act.
Use the power of the four Holy Swords,
and destroy these Devils!
Gotcha!
O Gloriously Upgraded Excalibabe-chan
you surely doth rest well in my hands.
Now, then,
who's going first?
Well, which shitty devil wants to taste the powers of my new sword?
Xenovia!
Missed me.
Did you forget that I am super fast?
I can do anything with my brand new Excalibur sword.
Including this-
Huh?
You shitty bitch.
How dare you kick my beautiful face.
I will hack you into pieces,
lots of little pieces.
Now to use the power of Mimic.
Yahoo...
Nightmare.
Witness both the terror of Excalibur Nightmare...
Whats going on?
and Transparency.
So you have merged all the swords powers into one.
Right you are, now get ready.
Xenovia is in trouble, we have to help her.
I'm done for, but I will keep fighting.
Don't forget about us.
I did hear about a subject on the loose...
but who would have thought he had become a Devil?!
I am grateful for your contributions.
Thanks to you, the experiments finally succeeded.
Succeeded?!
The power of each of you subjects had was
not enough to wield a Holy Sword on its own,
which brought me to a solution.
I simply had to take the power out of them!
Then, I found a way to crystallize it.
This is a crystal made from the subjects' power!
The last one, that is!
Everyone else died 'cuz their bodies couldn't handle da powah!
Makes ya think, I gotta be made of super awesomesauce, huh?!
Damn you!
That's...
At the time we were blessed with the power to wield the Holy Swords, she put one of those into her body.
It was to give us the power we lacked?
Those hypocrites...
They shunned me as a heretic,
yet they kept using the results of my research!
If it were Michael,
he probably took power from people without killing them!
T-There wasn't any need to kill us, then.
So why?!
You were simply materials for those experiments.
What was I supposed to do with you if I didn't dispose of you?
We believed that we were serving the Lord...
and bore excruciating pain.
Yet you...
You...
"Materials"?
"Dispose"?
Unbelievable!
Take it if you want.
We have the technology to mass-produce
even more refined crystals.
Run!
Leave us and run!
My friends...
You bastard.
You're going to hell for this!
Valper Galilei...
How many lives did you put to waste
for your experiments and your greed?
Those are...
People?
Yeah.
Looks like it.
In all likelihood,
they are the result of the many forces in this area,
and...
the souls that Yuuto-kun's heart
released from the crystal.
I've...
always...
always wondered...
if I...
if I deserved to be the only survivor.
Many of them had grander dreams than I ever did.
Many of them wanted to survive more than I did.
Did I deserve to live in peace?
Don't worry.
If we all come together...
Open your heart...
to all of us.
I'm not scared, even if God isn't here.
Even if God isn't watching...
Our hearts will always be...
...one.
It's so warm.
Why...
I can't hold back my tears!
That Knight has reached his peak.
When a Sacred Gear owner's hopes and dreams
change to such a degree that they move
against the flow of the rest of the world,
the Sacred Gear will exceed its limits, creating...
a Balance Breaker.
Oh?
My comrades didn't want me to exact vengeance for them.
They never did.
However, I must slay this evil that stands before me.
I must prevent...
any from following in our path!
Freed!
Coming!
You fool.
You should've died when you had the chance.
Kiba!
Wreck Freed and his Excalibur!
Don't let your friends' souls go to waste!
Issei-kun...
Do it, Yuuto.
You are Rias Gremory's family.
An Excalibur should be nothing for my Knight.
Yuuto-kun, you can do it!
Go for it.
Kiba-san!
Everyone...
What's with the Hallmark moment?
You're making me crawl in my skin here!
Ohmigawd!
I wanna slice 'n' dice ya'll
and get me some satisfaction!
I will become a sword.
My comrades, now one with my soul,
let us fulfill our regrets and our dreams of those days.
I will become the sword of the President and my allies.
Sword Birth!
Behold, the Sword of Betrayal...
a blade that is both holy and demonic!
A holy and demonic sword?!
That's it!
The dragon within me said...
that Kiba has reached his peak.
That's Kiba's forbidden technique,
a Balance Breaker!
A Holy Demonic Sword?
Impossible!
Two opposing forces coming together?
That could never happen!
Knight of Rias Gremory,
do we still stand as allies?
I hope so.
Then, let us work together to destroy that Excalibur.
Are you sure?
It is a Holy Sword, but is not a sword that is holy.
An anomalous sword.
All right.
Petra, Basilius, Dionysus,
and Mary, the Holy Mother...
hear my voice.
In the name of the saint which rests within this blade,
I will unleash...
the Holy Sword, Durandal!
The Holy Sword...
...Durandal?!
It's an Excalibur-tier Holy Sword
said to be able to split anything in this world.
It can't be!
My research hasn't produced anyone who can wield the Durandal!
Unlike him or Irina, I'm all-natural.
Flawless aptitude?!
You're a genuine Holy Sword wielder?!
This thing cuts through anything it touches.
I can hardly control it myself,
so we must keep it sealed in another dimension.
Your talk is cheap!
Didn't foresee that happening!
That isn't a complete Holy Sword.
It's no match for the Durandal!
You bitch!
I don't wanna hear about your stupid power balance!
Your scrap of a sword...
cannot part our bonds!
It broke?!
Are you serious?!
These little shits are beating me?
Did you see that, my comrades?
My power has surpassed that of Excalibur!
I can't believe my eyes!
In theory, the Holy and the Demonic can never-
Valper Galilei, prepare to die!
I see!
I understand!
Everything makes sense if the balance
between the Holy and the Demonic is skewed!
Therefore, both the Satans and God-
Valper, you were very capable.
The fact that you reached that conclusion proves it.
Kokabiel, what's going on?
I don't need these men to complete my plan.
Now, I'm done with watching.
Boy.
What?!
Maximize the Emperor of Red Dragon's power
and give it to someone.
What?!
You're going to give us a chance?!
You must be joking!
You are the one joking.
You think you can defeat me?
President...
We don't have any time.
I'll do it.
Issei-san...
Boost!
Hmm?
Even for fated couples
unmeiteki ni mo hakarishirenai
The equation of love is complicated
koi no houteishiki
Love isn't always justifiable
ai ni riyuu wa iranai
The answer lies inside your heart
kotae wa kimi no kokoro ni aru kara
After worrying and hesitating
nayande mayotte
My brain stops functioning
shikou teishi
I keep writing then erasing stuff
kaite wa keshite wo kurikaeshi
I'm running a simulation of you in my head
atama no naka de anata simulation
a
I'm running a simulation of you in my head
It's unpredictable
yosoku fukanou
Will this work? How about this?
kou kana kou kana
But you never follow my calculations
keisan de ugokeba ii no ni
ke
But you never follow my calculations
"Look, it's the beach!" "It sure is."
umi ne sou ne
I can't tell if you love me because you're so innocent
junsui na hodo futoumei
Don't be so kind to every girl
yasashisa wo furimaku na
You'll end up breaking many hearts
tsumitsukuri da wa
Why can't you just be normal?
futsuu ni misete
It's so unfair
zurui hito
zu
It's so unfair
ru
i
hi
to
Then you leave!
jaa kaeri na
ja
Then you leave!
I shouldn't let my rivals take you away from me
raibaru ni ukkari ki mi toraretara
I need a hint!
hinto ga hoshii
Quick, I need one!
hayaku hoshii
ha
Quick, I need one!
As I imagine a lovey-dovey future
love hidai na mirai
love
As I imagine a lovey-dovey future
My expectations only go up
takamatta kitai
ta
My expectations only go up
What should I try as the coefficient?
keisuu wa nan ni shiyou
There are too many variables
michisuu sugiru
mi
There are too many variables
To your feelings
kimi no kimochi
Rather than just work on the left-hand side
hidari yori mo daisuki
Look ahead to the other side of the equal sign
ikooru no saki wa
Although I'm not sure what it does
wakaranai kedo michibiku
It leads to the correct answer every time
kotae wa itsumo seikai deshou
I'll get over my worries and prove my love for you
nayande mo kono ai wo shoumei suru yo
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
Kokabiel's power isn't lessening at all!
But don't underestimate Kiba, or the rest of us!
Next Episode: Go, Occult Research Club!
Go, Occult Research Club!
Episode 6
Boobs are tough,
but I like them soft!