Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Father, please escape!
Quatre, I am escaping.
I'm not putting up a fight.
This fight will never end,
so I've opted to run away.
If I should die, then so be it.
I'm not so attached to space
that I'll compromise myself!
FATHER!!!
Father?!
FATHER!!
The Fight for Independence
It's huge...
I wonder what kind of person
this goodwill ambassador is.
Gentlemen!
That mobile suit was used
against OZ on Earth.
We'll check it, for security.
The new system since OZ and
the colonies became united...
...has had a considerable
influence on Earth.
On behalf of my nation...
...I've come to find out
about this situation.
Your nation?
That's correct.
I've come here from the
Sanc Kingdom.
I'm Milliardo Peacecraft.
Oh, His Excellency has had
ties with the Sanc Kingdom...
...since his youth.
I heard your nation was
recovering from the wars.
I think I understand
the implications of war.
So I thought I could
give advice...
...to the colonies desiring
military power.
There are many ways
to obtain peace for oneself.
Between us, we'll find
the best direction to take.
Then will you allow me
to act on my own accord...
...while I'm here in space?
Of course.
You might be on the
right track to peace...
...Representative Lady Une.
Peacecraft, huh?!
He's none other than that
OZ traitor, Zechs Merquise!!
Space Colony D 120.
Where the United Earth Sphere
Alliance command station...
...is located.
OZ wasn't controlling
the colonies by force...
...but recommending they join
a nation of the colonies.
D 120 continued in its function
as Earth's voice in outer space...
...not forgoing its position as
a military institute from Earth.
Son of the Alliance Space Force
Commander General Septem...
...Gwinter was the colony's
representative.
The former Alliance members
associated with him...
...had been troubled by the
colonial independence policy...
...backed by OZ.
What are you hesitating for?
OZ is trying to secure even
more power for themselves.
We must stop them.
Technological strength will just
become a threat to the Earth.
OZ thinks of space as merely
a factory for military supplies!
Only we can stop them!
It's our mission!!
A battle will result in
many casualties.
With our military strength,
dialog is still an option.
They're planning to use
outer space...
...to develop and manufacture
mobile dolls.
These murder weapons
will allow OZ...
...to take over and
dictate the colonies.
Does everybody feel the same?
Zechs Merquise has arrived
in space.
The Lightning Count is alive?
It's Earth that fears increased
arms in space the most.
Zechs knows OZ well and
he wishes for peace on Earth.
We should take some time
to hear what he has to say.
Zechs has nothing to do
with OZ anymore.
What's he doing in space?
That man holds a great
affection for his homeland.
He knew someone had
to take action.
Even though it was risky.
This visit holds significance.
Very nicely done,
Treize Khushrenada!
The people in space are
close to accepting OZ.
So it seems.
And Colonel Une's achievements
have been impressive.
She's forming friendly relations
with one colony after another.
The sense of independence
built by forming a nation...
...will trigger a desire for
productivity and defense.
This leads to the nation
becoming militaristic.
Which means that every
country on the Earth...
...will jump into OZ's arms
and beg to be governed by us.
It's beautiful, Treize.
You've made space a member
of the Romefeller Foundation.
Excuse me, sir.
Oh, Mr. Tubarov; have you
finished packing?
Yes.
Tubarov is heading for
outer space to oversee...
...mobile doll production and
strengthen our military force.
Lady Une has readily accepted
the new addition.
Lady Une did?
Colonel Une seems to be very
pleased with the mobile dolls!
Your Excellency, it's been
a long time.
It's Lady Une.
Lady Une?
I was sure you'd be coming
with Chief Engineer Tubarov.
I want to talk about that.
How do you plan to utilize
the mobile dolls?
I'll use them as your soldiers
so you won't need to suffer.
My soldiers?
You're not being fair.
You're the one who must
lead the world.
But you've simply left the
world in a state of confusion.
I came here to be of some
assistance to you.
And I've also laid out
a new future for you.
Wars will never disappear
from the world.
Therefore the strongest
should rule the world.
People even take pleasure in
being controlled by the strong.
It's merely natural for the
world to continue fighting.
But that encourages
meaningless bloodshed.
You're capable of loving
all people.
You have a heart that
can make you a god.
From outer space, you can
create peace on Earth.
Lady.
These are your ideals
for the future.
It's what you wanted,
Your Excellency.
My ideal is merely the
fantasy of one individual.
History is an accumulation
of daily events.
I have no interest in
an individual's future.
Your future's already
been determined.
Your future's destined to be
in outer space.
Lady...
I'm not that strong.
Zechs and the Gundam pilots
are making an effort...
...to construct a new future.
There's no need to hurry.
History will repeat itself.
Lady...
Please come back to me.
The Lady Une that I was
so fond of.
Yes!
It's Zechs Merquise, for sure.
So Zechs is in space?
He's establishing relations...
...with the Alliance's
Military Colony.
Lieutenant Nichol.
Destroy the Alliance's
Space Force.
There's no reason to leave
them roaming about...
...now that the mobile dolls
have been completed.
Yes, sir!
I've also sent Colonel Une
orders for the near future.
Tell her I want her comments.
Sir.
Welcome.
We were enemies at one point.
But changes in wartime bring
changes in relationships.
I care about the Earth,
just as the Alliance does.
I heard you came from Earth...
...to discuss the current arms
issue of the Space Colonies.
If this simply involved a new
military nation being formed...
...then I wouldn't be worried.
However, if they're being
tricked by OZ...
...then I can't ignore it.
OZ is planning to use space
as its military factory.
That would result in even more
severe disputes on Earth...
...and serious casualties.
How do you feel about the
people in space, Mr. Peacecraft?
Teachings of the great leader,
the late Heero Yuy, still exist.
Outer space once thrived
as a world...
...neither tainted by Earth's
history nor in need of arms.
The colonies set an example for
all Earth's peaceful nations.
They set an example.
If only the people in space
had heard that sooner.
Perhaps they wouldn't
have changed their minds.
Why not tell Mr. Peacecraft
about the colonies' people?
And the reason we decided
to remain in space!
The reason you stayed here?
Right.
When the Alliance was
defeated by OZ...
...our first thought was to
immediately surrender.
We thought...
...surrendering would
leave space in great turmoil.
The Space Colonies is
a realm of precise calculations.
For instance, this management
center always supported...
...this colony's life zone.
The colony's rotation
operations...
...checking atmospheric
conditions...
...and weather management.
Natural phenomena that are
taken for granted on Earth...
...are generated by machinery
controlled by people.
To live in this atmosphere...
...people needed a new
awareness.
There's insecurity...
Unless you can completely
ignore insecurity...
...you'll have difficulties
living here.
And insecure people feel
the need for weapons.
Because weapons give
people a sense of security.
At what point can one
lose that sense of insecurity?
Men in space will attack Earth,
in their search for stable land.
It's an OZ mobile suit
transport vessel.
Looks like they're finally
going to attack us!
I'd like to be part of
your counterattack.
A goodwill ambassador mustn't
be involved in a battle!
I switch between two identities.
My experience in battle has
taught me to be cunning.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Colonel!
I beg your pardon.
That's fine.
This is the Romefeller
Foundation's plan...
...to send space-manufactured
mobile dolls to Earth.
To resolve all disputes
on Earth at once?
Everybody comes to
that conclusion.
I don't intend to send
mobile dolls to Earth.
The Foundation's plan...
...will mean more
bloodshed on Earth.
The strong shall rule the Earth.
That's all we need
to attain peace.
But now His Excellency
has refused his mission...
...to rule the world.
His Excellency?
True public order will
never be possible...
...unless His Excellency
comes to outer space.
There's no point in
my staying here.
Not true, Colonel.
You still have your duty
to serve as an OZ soldier.
As an OZ soldier?
You'd be doing him
a favor by staying.
A soldier only needs to
follow orders.
Colonel, you're a leader who
stands above the soldiers.
But your superior abilities can
be heightened as an OZ soldier.
I implore you to serve as
an OZ soldier.
Not to guide His Excellency,
but to support him.
As an OZ soldier to support
Master Treize...
That's what His Excellency
desires.
Master Treize desires that?
The mobile dolls have started
a battle in the A Area...
...of the Alliance Military Base.
They'll be in range of Barge's
beam cannon in 600 seconds.
What damage can we do
to the Alliance Colony?
If we can destroy their
electrical power control...
...and management facilities,
one shot should wipe it out.
Okay!
Many civilians live there,
as well as military officers.
They're employees.
They'd know it's risky
living in a military fortress.
Does Colonel Une know
about this?
I'm acting on direct orders
from Duke Dermail!
We're to crush them and that
OZ traitor, Zechs Merquise.
I'll get the Mercurius and
Vayeate ready.
Stop, Trowa Barton!
Don't go near the
mobile suit gate.
I don't trust traitors, whether
they're enemies or allies!
Lady Une isn't aware
of this either?
The Colonel has left for
the battle against the Alliance!
She left me in charge of
operations!
Restrain this man at once!
I won't overstep my boundaries
as an OZ soldier.
But I have doubts
about your plan...
...not to use the Vayeate
and the Mercurius...
...to support the Colonel's
troops.
A soldier doesn't need to
think so much!
Ideals about peace are for
people in the top ranks.
All we need to do is
pursue victory.
Get closer!
Make up for reaction time
in close-range combat!
I did it!
All right!
What?!
We've lost 50% of our
Leo troops!
We believe all the enemy
Tauruses are mobile dolls!
20% of our defense line
has been destroyed!
Have the remaining civilians
in the colony been evacuated?
Yes.
They left on our large shuttle
and are headed for safety.
In any case, mobile dolls alone
can't destroy this colony.
I expect that Barge will be
making the final blow.
This colony is finished.
What do you mean, Grandfather?
This is the first time a colony
has been destroyed in war...
...since the colonies
were built.
Mankind needs to be shown
how tragic the destruction is.
Those of us who brought
military power to space...
...and the colonies who are
considering it for themselves...
...must remember this, so
the wrong path won't be taken.
It hardly compensates for
what we've done...
...but I hope our deaths
send the message.
I'm sorry to have dragged
you into this, Grandfather.
My thoughts exactly.
I'm sorry, Gwinter.
Barge's beam cannon?!
Are they seriously going to
wipe out the colony?
Treize is hoping we'll
put up a fight.
Can't you create a new future,
Treize?
There's no choice left
but to battle.
It's the only way that remains.
Without fighting, nothing
can be created.
What?
Treize!
Zechs Merquise...
Or rather, my eternal friend,
Milliardo Peacecraft.
I'm delighted to hear you've
shown up in outer space.
OZ is changing, and I'm
sorely lacking in power.
Romefeller's way, or rather...
...the path that mankind is
taking, is too selfish.
I never expected their
increased power...
...would lead them to
abandon their compassion.
I used to believe that OZ's
duty wasn't to take part in war.
But to educate soldiers
who had the heart to fight.
Soon battles will be
fought without people.
I'm merely one soldier.
I chose of my own free will
to resist that outcome.
Milliardo.
I don't have the power to alter
the path chosen by Romefeller.
I'm glad to speak with
someone who understands me.
Milliardo, there's one other
person who understands me.
Her feelings toward me have
given her split personalities.
Lady Une...
I'm making the person closest
to me feel insecure.
I've got no right to
talk about the future.
I implore you, Milliardo.
Please save her.
I'm going to fight for Treize...
...to help realize his ideal!
The Alliance Colony is
entering firing range.
Fire the beam cannon!!
But Colonel Une is still
on the battlegrounds!
That doesn't matter;
just follow your orders!
The Colonel knows the dangers!
What?!
Lady Une would cancel any
orders to attack the colony.
She's learned just how
fragile the colonies are.
They missed it!
Was that intentional?
Take me there...
Take me to Fortress Barge.
Colonel, you're safe!
Colonel?
Nichol.
I was able to learn a great
deal as a soldier today.
Very informative.
And as your superior, I can't
overlook what you've done.
Colonel...
The actions you took
were justified.
And what I'm about
to do is also justified!!
Treize...
I've got no power.
In the confusion of
all these battles...
...I can only walk the
path of a soldier.
The Romefeller Foundation
decides to build...
...mobile doll manufacturing
facilities on the moon.
The mass-produced mobile dolls
will be used against Earth.
The strategy is to send
them to Earth...
...and quickly resolve the
many disputes on Earth...
...by wiping out the opponents.
With these ultimate weapons...
...the world heads for an age
where soldiers are redundant.
Unidentified object headed
this way!
What?!
It's a Gundam!!
A Gundam has found us!!
Assassinate the mobile dolls'
Chief Engineer?
That's an easy mission.
Troops from the Lunar Base
are headed for the Gundam!
I have no bullets, no fuel and
hardly any propulsive energy.
Okay, Chief Engineer.
My life's in your hands!!
Full retreat!
Wait!
Take a look!
The Gundam doesn't have
the power to retaliate.
Interesting machine.
I'd like to take it to the
Lunar Base and check it out.
Calling Lunar Base.
Stop your attack and
capture the Gundam.
Yes, sir!
Thanks.
That's very kind of you,
Chief Engineer.
Nataku.
We have to become
a lot stronger.
I hear they have a factory.
Maybe they'll help us
get stronger.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
People in outer space acquire
weapons to defend the colonies.
They do so under the pretext
of fearing an attack from Earth.
But it's OZ that manipulates
their fears.
To prevent mass-production
of mobile dolls...
...Duo heads to the moon
to destroy the Lunar Base.
During the battle with Hilde,
the colony volunteer soldier...
...Duo sees the chaotic
future of the colonies.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 23,
Duo, the God of Death Once Again
"Duo, the God of Death Once Again".