I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Hey! Who the hell slashed my tires?
What a cheap thing to do.
It'd better not be scratched...
No, nothing.
I can't find any trace of them.
Who told you that this
place was suspicious anyway?
A fax?
Damn it! Ogami's being attacked!
Check to see if we
can get backup! Hurry!
What the hell? Leave the
deliveries for later!
Deputy, I can't get a hold
of the Sagamihara office.
And I haven't had any word
from Taguchi since last night.
Mr. Taguchi and his team...
...are dead.
What?
The police contacted me.
They found their bodies
at our bokuto lumber yard.
I will be heading to the station
tomorrow for questioning.
I will do my best to avoid charges
regarding an employer's duties...
...under the Anti-Organized
Crime Law. I understand now.
Their style of fighting isn't that of
the Mafia. It's like that of an army.
Of course. That's why they call
her Captain. I miscalculated.
We're moving into the final
stages of crushing...
...the Washimine Clan's locations.
Sites 371 and 372
have been wiped out.
Daniel's team is currently
headed for site 221.
They will commence at 1505 hours.
Has Corporal Razal
met his objective?
They're tied up in traffic
on the highway.
But they should still
meet the activation time.
Okchabri-skiajin This
is Corporal Jodorowsky.
Report.
We've completed our objectives
within the planned time.
We will now be withdrawing
from our operation zone.
Roger. Return to base.
Site 215 is under our control.
Things are looking good.
The death of officer Shigeru Ito
has been confirmed at site 317.
All right. Good work, men.
In three more moves the Princess
will be completely stripped.
I got a hold of the Sis.
We're done for the day.
She says we've got
another job tomorrow.
Yeah.
What is it? You look gloomy.
I guess.
You seem like you're having
a good time.
We've been together for so long,
I guess you can tell these things.
Meeting a guy like that
surely makes a gunman happy.
Can you believe it, baby?
He sliced a bullet right in front of me.
It blew my mind all the way to heaven.
I can't wait to have a duel
with that big guy.
What benefit is there in
rushing yourself to your death?
Rushing myself to my death?
You're missing the point, Rock.
We're already the walking dead.
Dutch, the Sis, Chang,
and the others...
All of us running around in Roanapur.
If there's one difference
between us and the real dead...
Difference?
Yeah, difference.
Whether we live or die
isn't a big issue.
If you focus on being alive, you
develop fear. Your eyes get clouded
But if you have no such feelings...
...you're capable of fighting
right to the end of the world.
So you prefer to
die in the gutter like that?
Somehow Roanapur
feels so far away.
Hey, Rock. What's going on here?
You're sure snapping
back at me a lot today.
Yeah, sorry. Drinking's bringing out
the worst in me today.
All right. Don't worry about it.
Young lady, you mustn't go
around teasing adults like this.
You're the one who
brought up the point...
...that it's conditional that the
successor be a direct blood relative.
This has been acknowledged
by the Peacekeeping Council...
- Don't fool with me, you little brat!
- Shut up, Morozumi.
I don't plan on allowing
you to succeed.
Besides, what are
you gonna do about...
...those crazy Russians
you brought in?
Like you say,
that's an error on our part.
The entire Washimine Clan is
doing everything we can...
...to expel those Russians.
You're missing the point,
Washimine girl.
What I'm asking is how are you gonna
repay us for all that's happened.
Excuse me, but you haven't
forgotten the reason...
...why our last boss, Bando...
...took this desperate measure,
have you?
Well, that was some grudge
you had against us.
We even sent you
a replacement head...
to try and protect
our brother organization.
And who turned that down?
Very well. We shall eventually settle
this with the Peacekeeping Council.
You little brat! You're in over your head,
taking a position like that!
The Peacekeeping Council has the
authority to direct mediation...
...and we have gathered enough
material to justify our actions.
Little brat!
Is that all you have to say?
Given Boss Kousa's attitude...
...it may be useless to get
the Peacekeeping Council involved.
That's...
The people in this world
are all controlled by greed.
It's clear which side would be
more beneficial for them to support.
Justice has fallen.
I'm sorry for the painful reminder...
...but the current
Washimine Clan is only...
...one-third the force we had
at the start of the fighting.
The Russians' attacks
are too severe.
They started by targeting
and eliminating...
...the guys heading our forces.
But we're still here. You and I.
- Mr. Inoue.
- Yes?
Please stop the car.
Yes, miss.
Miss! But then...
I know. Please send a message
to everyone who is still alive.
But, Miss!
I cannot allow those who have
been protecting Washimine...
...to be eliminated at this point.
And that includes you, Mr. Inoue.
We will create
an opportunity on our own.
So please stay alive and wait.
Now, Miss...
Of course I will not
let things end this way.
Today, every group's
office entrance...
...is protected with
a surveillance camera.
I'm sure they're well aware of that.
Although heavily damaged, this is
a video tape that survived the scene.
I succeeded in taking it...
...before the police closed
off the place for investigation.
Did you see that?
Quite clearly.
They're moving around in
electric repair shop vans.
If only we knew where these
cars were coming from.
I envy the police for
that N-system they use.
Indeed.
It's such a thrill to be a villain!
We're Bonnie and Clyde!
I like that.
Next up, we're gonna
rob a bank in Bolivia!
A robbery has occurred at the credit
union on the fourth block of Inoue.
The two suspects
are escaping by car.
A white van with a red
spade mark on the side door.
All patrol cars in the area,
be on the lookout. I repeat...
That world that Mr. Okajima
is standing on the border of...
...there's a city where only
gangsters gather and live.
That sounds good to me.
To become a Yakuza...
...making a name for
himself in a place like that.
The name of the city is Roanapur.
They say Balalaika's
from there as well.
I kept thinking how great it would be
if life in Takamachi would last forever.
Miss...
With musical bands, all the stores,
and you by my side...
...it's bound to be enjoyable.
But this is... This is
even more fun than that.
Either way, we're gonna have
to deal with the Russian lady...
...if we're gonna live in that city.
This is gonna be exciting.
This is patrol car Shinagawa 142.
We spotted a van with a red spade
heading north along the shoreline.
We ordered them to pull over,
but they picked up speed instead.
- We need reinforcements.
- We've got them, Gin.
The shoreline... Close to Tokyo Port...
This is Jodorowsky.
We're being chased by a police car.
Lose them.
Balalaika. They came
from Roanapur. But how?
With all those
weapons and equipment.
They could never get through
an airport. Which means...
A ship? Balalaika's at the port.
He lost them. We'll get rid
of the car now.
How? How did the police find
out what car we were using?
Is that girl challenging me with
her first effective countermeasure?
Amusing. We'll just have to
crush her especially thoroughly.
Knowledge exists so that
we may forget reality.
The intoxication of reality
that cannot be found in books.
A land that symbolizes that,
Roanapur.
Oh, boy. With Balalaika away,
this place is falling to pieces.
How are things outside?
The number of gunshots
has gone up again.
The Triad's doing a pretty good
job keeping things together, but...
It's a gun paradise, Benny.
That's the true appearance of this city.
Everyone's in a great mood.
Chang really understands
that about this place.
It's a good thing Rock's not here.
Guns are just not his thing.
You've gotta realize that
one of our biggest blessings...
...is the fact Rock hasn't
had to hold a gun.
Is that so?
If he fires, his bullets will
ricochet right back at us.
It's too damned dangerous.
I'm serious, man. Really.
- Sorry I made you wait.
- Not to worry. So what's the next job?
Another meeting with the Japanese.
If we can finalize this sufficiently,
we can return to Roanapur.
A meeting?
But the Washimine Clan is...
The people we're talking
to now are the Kousa Clan.
This will get rid of all of our troubles.
It'll be very helpful.
Because you don't
actually want to save me.
You don't want to lose that normal
life that you thought you threw away.
- That's all.
- Well...
...as long as what they have to say
isn't insulting, maybe we can...
- ...consider one of their conditions.
- Hey, Rock?
Are you going to stay in the
twilight like that again?
Miss Balalaika.
You have no reason to ally
yourself with the Kousa Clan.
Rather than destroying the Washimine
Clan, you'd be better off...
- ...destroying the Kousa Clan.
- Rock!
The Washimine Clan
is already weakened.
It's no longer a threat to Moscow.
Am I right?
- And the Washimine Group's...
- Rock!
Don't misunderstand your position.
You are my interpreter.
You're not my fellow soldier, comrade,
or a member of Moscow.
You understand?
The new leader of the Washimine
Clan is still a teenager!
Hey, hey! Let's stop there!
There's gotta be a justice
that you believe in!
Enough, Rock.
You're being a pain!
Damn it.
Let's all calm down, Sis.
We don't wanna reenact a scene from
"My Bloody Valentine" here, do we?
Stop howling, Revy.
Rock, look at me.
Justice?
There is no other word
more loved by the people.
It's a wonderful word. However...
Without exercising
your own strength...
...you seek the death of others
by the hands of someone else.
The justice you refer to
smells pretty rotten too.
The stench of a bloodbath lingers.
Don't you agree?
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not upset with you.
Sis!
I just never thought I'd hear
words like that coming from you.
I'm so amused, I can't help myself.
You've made your point.
Now let him go.
My fingers are getting tense.
Our lives are very insignificant.
Much like a candy wrapper.
- Yours is, and so is his.
- I don't really care to talk.
Just let him go.
Two-Hands, I have something
to say to you, too.
I don't know what you're thinking...
...but you should not wish for
the same way of life as his.
Shut up.
I know. I know what you're saying.
So please, shut up.
I can't keep my fingers
still for much longer.
Miss Balalaika.
Your victory is assured...
...and you no longer have
anything to lose. Yet still...
- Rock.
- Is it still not enough?
Shut up, Rock!
No, it isn't enough.
Remember, there are two successful
ways to beg for your life.
One is to entertain the person
who's about to take your life.
The other is to give that person...
...a persuasive reason to
keep you alive.
You haven't fulfilled either one yet.
Now, dance!
What obligation do you have
to save them, anyway?!
You're misunderstanding.
- Oh?
- It's not an obligation.
And justice is
just a convenient word.
I only have one reason.
It's my hobby.
Hobby?
Yeah, my hobby.
Some people consider it
a hobby to die in the gutters...
...and then there
are hobbies like mine.
Deep down inside, I'm just like you.
Things are gonna pick
up again tomorrow, Rock.
From now on, you'd be wise not to
risk your life on stupid games.
Park the car in the garage, okay?
Rock! You piece of shit!
The only reason we're
still breathing...
...is because of God's grace...
...and the fact that the
crazy war maniac in the coat...
...for some reason decided
to put her gun away!
Yeah sure, I'm your gun here!
I'm confident I can protect you
through Tarawa or the Alamo.
But, you know, it's just not
possible to protect a guy...
...who's trying damn hard
to get killed, you blockhead!
- Are you mad?
- Not even close. I'm damn pissed!
If it wasn't you, I would've shot
two or three holes into you by now!
Revy.
I have a favor to ask. Will you
come to my town one more time?
I don't need to have the Sis tell me.
Your place is a good place.
That's why I got a little lost.
But it's so far away,
there's no way I could reach it.
Until now, I've lived my life
breathing rotten air.
I had even forgotten that I don't
know how to live anywhere else.
In the end, it's just the Sis.
She's always had her eyes
set only on war.
Go on, and never look back.
You're about to wake
up from your nightmare.
Revy. Have you forgotten?
I'm already dead.
I died that day I met you.
If Roanapur is the city of the walking
dead, this is the city of the living.
Being so familiar with this view,
I had almost forgotten that.
For a dead man,
this is like a mirage.
No. This may have been a mirage
even back when I lived here. Revy...
I didn't come here to return
to my former life.
I came here to forget.
I came here to keep watching
everything that will happen.
I'm sure you'll regret it.
I finished regretting a year ago.
I just didn't have enough resolve,
but now I think I've got that, too.
I see.
Hey! It's the lady from
the other day!
Yeah, you're right.
Will you show us what
you did last time?
Yeah, shoot those cans
down again!
Come on!
Well, Rock?
Put on a show for them, Revy.
All right.
What kind of gun is that?
It looks real.
This here's a Beretta M92 Custom...
...the Praiyachat Sword
Cutlass Special.
Now watch those cans
carefully, you brats.
Those cans,
watch them close, okay?!
Your mommy's waiting for you.
Now go home you kids!
Gin. I'd like to have
a more powerful gun.
But...
There should be one in this house.
I'm not very familiar with projectiles.
This one's apparently a
Russian "Stechkin" handgun.
I understand the bullets are big and
it can keep firing like a machine gun.
This may be too much for you, Miss.
No, I want to be less of a burden.
This will do.
Next Episode
This city, Roanapur...
It's a wonderful place...
...where you can blow away
everything with barbaric power.