I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Who was it, big brother?
Who was it that said
"The ultimate love is cannibalism"?
Edgar Allen Poe?
No, big sister.
He had a case of necrophilia.
Richard Matheson?
You may be right.
I wonder if they ever enjoyed this scent.
The smell of life flowing out.
The scent of iron rust
and seawater.
The smell of
a man's last gasp.
We're very fortunate, big sister.
Perhaps the people of this city
will start moving now.
This makes eight people.
We even ended up killing some
we hadn't planned on killing.
Everyone will be coming to kill us.
This'll be fun, big sister.
Yes, big brother.
Yes, I can't wait.
Yes, Lagoon Company here.
Oh, hi Mr. Boris.
What? The meeting is canceled?
Yeah. Sorry.
I'll be in touch as soon as there's
an opening in the captain's schedule.
What is it, Rock?
The meeting's apparently canceled.
Maybe something urgent came up.
- You think maybe it's that, Dutch?
- Yeah.
It's got everyone running around.
- What are you talking about?
- Come on.
Haven't you heard anything, Rock?
No.
Killings. There were killings.
I hate to say it, but there's nothing
unusual about homicide in this city.
Yeah, there's nothing unusual
about killings...
...but when they're targeting
Hotel Moscow, that's a different story.
Hotel Moscow?
Five corpses with ties to the Russians
have been laid down...
- ...this past month alone.
- Revy.
That info's outdated.
It's now six.
In any case, someone out there is trying
to light the sky with fireworks, Rock.
In this city where the balance of power
walks a tightrope on its hands.
There's gonna be blood shed
before this one's said and done.
Another one's been killed.
This time it's an accountant. Are we
in Beirut? Mogadishu, perhaps?
Stop it, Balalaika.
This is why we're having
these information sessions.
We're living in a period of coexistence.
I'd prefer to
place some importance...
...in this equilibrium we've earned
after all the bloodshed and bullets.
Miss Balalaika.
Oh, Mr. Chang?
When did I ever say
I wanted coexistence?
There you go
blabbing away again, Fry Face.
An Ivan from the countryside trying to
be a queen? You've gotta be joking.
Go back to digging your potatoes
at your sovkhoz.
You know, I hear the bowels
of an Italian smell like those of a pig.
- Is that true, Verrocchio?
- You bitch!
Watch your mouths, both of you!
What do you think the purpose of
this information session is, anyway?
Sure, we have grudges against
each other that stick with us.
However, we're living in a time
when we should be cooperating...
...for the sake of our own benefit.
If it'll help our business,
then you're free to say anything.
But you can feed your damn
personal honor to the dogs.
That's what it means
to be part of the mafia, right?
Miss Balalaika.
This may be news to you...
But my men have fallen victim as well.
A member connected with the 14K
and one directly affiliated executive.
In the whore house
on Rachiada Street.
Killed the same way as your guys.
What's going on, Chang?
Someone's trying to shift the balance!
Abrego! Look at me!
You've gotta be kidding me, Balalaika!
Sure I've had my
share of issues with you...
...but our differences
have been resolved!
Then Abrego.
You can direct the questions
about the true culprit to Verrocchio.
Don't be ridiculous, Fry Face!
We also lost one of our recruiters!
That makes nine bodies.
Chang. These killings weren't done
by anyone from the city.
These were done by a drifter.
Someone who doesn't know
how things work in this city.
So, now that we've determined that
these incidents were committed...
...by an outside force, we'll work
together to hunt down the perpetrator.
We will also
make a joint declaration.
It'll avoid unnecessary bloodshed
through misunderstandings.
Any objections?
- I don't like this. It's a farce.
- What the hell did you say?!
Cool it with your rashness, Balalaika.
I doubt it's in your best interest
to blow up this whole city.
Is this supposed to be
some social gathering, Mr. Chang?
Shall we play a hand of gin rummy?
The reason I came here today is so that
we can make our positions clear.
Hotel Moscow will not forgive anyone...
...who is involved in obstructing
our operations in any way.
We will denounce and destroy them,
then kill their parents and siblings.
If necessary, even their pet dog.
Oh, boy.
Look. Everyone's carrying a gun.
It's as if we've made our way
into the world of Clint Eastwood.
Naturally.
There's a lunatic wandering the streets
thinking he's some sort of punisher.
Punisher.
A giver of punishment.
But punishment for what?
Who knows. Right now,
Roanapur is like popcorn.
It's simmering on heat,
waiting for the right moment to burst.
Have you heard, Revy?
They've announced a reward.
- How much?
- Fifty grand.
And that's not local currency.
It's U.S. dollars.
Wow. They're really serious about this.
We should go for it, too.
You have any leads?
Nothing. But normally an outsider
shouldn't be too difficult to find.
That's right. An outsider would
stick out like a sore thumb.
It's not that big of a city, after all.
That was the case with
the Lovelace family's maid.
But no one has a clue...
...which could only mean
that someone's providing a hideout.
But we don't know who.
So, like the saying goes,
suspicion creates a bugbear.
Well, I really couldn't care less, as long
as it doesn't lead to a shooting spree.
You worry too much, Bao.
This is a neutral district.
No one's gonna start anything here.
Howdy, Two-Hands.
You're drinking the cheap stuff again!
How's business?!
Eda! D-Damn you!
Who's she?
Th-That sister from the
Rip Off Church!
Well, well. You brought
the handsome boy with you.
Hi! How've you been?
Ditch this boar-girl
and hang out with me, won't you?
You might've come fishing for men,
but this one's off limits. I'll kill you.
Wow, you're scary.
Hear that, handsome boy?
This girl's eternally nagged
with irregular menstrual periods.
You asked for it, Eda.
Come on, we'll take this outside!
Don't get so excited, Two-Hands.
I didn't come here
to pick a fight with you.
I've got a great story.
One that's worth some hard cash.
It has to do with
catching that culprit, right?
- You know?
- Revy and I were just talking about that.
I doubt there's a single soul left
in the city that doesn't know.
Oh? Is that so?
Man, this isn't fun.
Well, at least that means
less explaining on my part.
There are some already
on the move for the bounty.
The mafia go without saying,
but they're also freelance assassins.
From what I hear, the Yun brothers,
Big One Emilio, Ronny CK...
That's incredible. This place
is a sample city of assassins.
There are others, too. Tooth Decay
Johnny, for example, is laughable.
He came to order a rifle to hunt
elephants. What's he thinking?
He probably thinks he's
up against some dinosaur.
If he shot a human with that,
he'd have nothing left to show but dust.
We'd better get moving if we want
to get our hands on that money.
Fifty grand is too large an amount
to ignore, Revy.
You're right about that. Haven't you got
any other new information, Eda?
There's one thing.
Early this morning, the Caribbean Bar
on Buran Street was crushed.
Hotel Moscow is
in position to battle.
Having a subordinate killed,
I hear Fry Face is furious.
Hey. Good to see you.
Right. Any information?
A waiter was found alive.
Though he's on his last breath.
This is what happened.
They arrived early morning,
at about four o'clock.
Twins, dressed like
they were gonna attend a funeral.
I hear they were spooky brats...
...like something
outta the movie, "The Shining".
As the bartender tells them,
"This is no place for kids"...
...they pull out one of your Bougainvillea
Trading business cards, and say...
We get our customers
from Miss Balalaika's place.
We were told that tonight, we could find
our customers here. Haven't you heard?
Go around to the back.
Yes. Thank you, mister.
Our customers will recognize us
as soon as they see us.
We'll use that corner, okay?
If at that moment...
...the bartender had the foresight to
contact you he wouldn't have been killed.
His luck ran out when he decided
not to call you at such a late hour.
Moments later, your staff came on
time to collect the evening's earnings.
The collector asked how
business was...
...and as the bartender said,
"Not too great"...
Hi there.
You wanna play with us?
Please, mister. Let's play.
Sakharov! It's them!
They're the ones!
They figured it out.
These men are pretty clever, big sister.
You're right.
Big brother, we need to do this better.
It can't be helped, can it?
What should we do, big sister?
Guess we have no choice.
We'll call upon an angel for them.
They say heaven's a nice place,
after all. Right, big brother?
No, you mustn't.
You mustn't run away.
Big sister. Let's bring that one
back with us!
We'll play with him until
our next job!
Yes, let's do that, big brother.
Yes, big sister.
Damn!
This guy's heavy, big sister.
Help me.
You're a boy, big brother.
Ladies don't carry heavy things.
Then, after they pushed
the collector onto a car...
...that had been parked close by...
...they returned and fired rounds
until no remaining body moved.
What's the make of the car?
It's license number?
A black sedan. All we know
is that it's a Japanese make.
We're still searching for its whereabouts.
Oh, and one other thing.
They're white, but not from
an English speaking nation.
They apparently gave greetings
in an unusual language.
Right. Buna seara.
And also, they said the following
when calling each other.
Fratti mai soul. Soula mai mare.
Watsap. Don't let any of this
information leak to the outside.
If the peace corps interfere,
it could be troublesome.
Yeah, I know.
I like this city too.
That's right, hey, Balalaika!
We're also joining in on the hunt!
The reward's open to
cops too, right?!
He disgusts me. I could puke.
But this was an error on my part.
I believed that as long as
I sent my soldiers in two-man cells...
...they would be safe.
Sakharov and Menshov clearly
had their guard down, Captain.
I mean, who'd expect the assassins
to be children?
Remember Panjshir.
Half the enemies were children.
Even souls can accumulate fat.
Our souls included.
Exactly, Captain. We shall
be cautious about this in the future.
Comrade. I do not wish for our
combat power to dip any further.
Hire an investigative team
from outside our organization.
- Think of them as pawns we can discard.
- Right.
Eight soldiers from that joint base
have now died in battle.
No matter how many die,
it's not something you ever get used to.
Ever since that day we pledged,
we're prepared to die in battle.
I'm sure Private Sakharov
would have said the same.
I won't let them kill any more, Sergeant.
I will have those kids pay for Comrade
Sakharov's life with their blood.
I will direct my anger and hatred
at them as I kill them!
Oh boy.
How are things coming along?
Has anyone caught the fish yet?
Not yet. But this isn't good.
One mistake, and this thing
could get outta hand.
It'll make a typhoon
seem like a summer breeze.
Balalaika is planning on using
the services of Visotoniki.
Visotoniki?
She's nuts.
Is she trying to flip the city
upside down?
Commando unit. In their Ivan language
they're known as the Visotoniki.
They're subordinates of that woman
from before Hotel Moscow existed.
With her at the head...
...each and every one of them
functioned as a killing machine.
Repatriated soldiers of the Afghanistan
war with significant battle experience...
...they're known to have received enough
training to fight a Third World War.
That's what sets them apart
from other mafia.
Each having the ability to command
and show no mercy.
I'd hate to be anywhere near them
when they're pissed off...
...I need at least
a two hundred mile radius.
My mother has killed me...
My father's eating me...
My brothers and sisters
sit under the table...
Pickin' up my bones,
and they bury them...
Under the cold...
What in the hell are you guys...
What? We're changing our clothes.
The blood has dried and is like glue,
so they can't be worn any more.
It's a lot of fun, you know.
If you stick a needle into his head,
he twitches like a fish.
He still moves even though
he's no longer breathing.
I think it's called "spinal reflexes".
The boss is red as a lobster with anger!
Look. I only said to dissect
that Ivan bitch!
I never said anything about
kidnapping subordinates...
...and using them
as dart targets!
Now would be a good time to
put an end to this and leave the city!
I've had enough of babysitting you!
I can't believe those damn brats!
They're far worse than having
a couple loose screws up there.
Moretti! Those two are totally
sick in the head.
No kidding. Now we've gotta
get rid of that corpse, too.
We can't just call a cleaner
to do the job, damn it!
Does the phantom killer
know what he's dealing with?
If so, the killer's gotta be crazy.
In this world, we come across them
every once in a blue moon.
They're known as seeds of evil.
They're outsiders considered
to be extra baggage...
...even in the underground world.
Usually they go recklessly wild
and wind up dead...
...but once in a while you get one
that's got instincts like a beast...
...and a clever mind,
they somehow survive.
The only way for these guys to live
is to go nuts and spread calamity.
The one thing that they all have in
common is they hate all kinds of things.
Not only do they hate things...
...but because they hate so many things
with a vengeance...
...they no longer remember
what they hate.
In the end, they involve
everything around them...
...and blow everything up.
Well, only the individual really knows
what's going on in his head.
My own mind's filled with
second hand knowledge from prison.
Rock!
She asked for you by name.
It's the lady of the hour. Miss Balalaika.
Hey, big sister.
What is it?
What should we do?
I'd love to give it a try.
We've never tried an Ivan before.
No, big sister.
I mean those guys.
Oh.
We'll get rid of them eventually.
I hate being scolded and being hit.
It makes me wanna cry.
Don't you agree, big brother?
Buna seara.
It has the nuance of something Italian.
I thought, given the work you're in,
you might know.
I'm sorry. I meant former work.
Buna seara.
Then how about the phrase,
"Soula mai mare"?
Anything will do.
Whatever comes to mind.
A place... A name...
I sorta recall someone
from the European branch...
...teaching me something similar.
But I can't quite put my finger on it.
Vampire?
What was that?
What do you mean by that, Rock?
Those words have something
to do with vampires.
It smells very strongly of blood,
big brother.
Let's take a bath.
But it's such a nice scent.
You're wasting a good thing, big sister.
Next Episode
The Chinese woman
from Lagoon Company...
...and the sister from the
Rip Off Church are also with them.
Crush them if necessary.