I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Your selfishness is causing
us problems, young lady.
Sure, we'd prefer a better product.
But everything has a time limit to it.
Soccer, baseball, the stock exchange,
and even fucking.
You people are fools.
It's incomplete. Too incomplete.
I can't allow something like this
into the world.
We're not trying to trick
the people of the Mint Bureau.
You and that fellow
from the computer shop...
...are the only ones in this room
saying anything like that.
And yet, you've already gone over
the estimate you initially submitted...
...by two hundred thousand dollars.
And the promised completion date
was two months ago!
I wouldn't think such a thing,
but a few of the directors tell me that...
...well, this girl is screwing with us...
...as if she thinks we have
the brains of a reptile.
- Theo. Don't stop.
- And that girl would be you.
Oh, sorry. Of course,
I would not think such a thing.
If it were true, sadly, I might
end up crushing you to smithereens.
Do I look like a man who would raise
his hand to a woman? I don't, do I?
There's not much that I can do.
Come on. Put yourself in the position of
the guy who has to clean up this mess.
- What did you do that for?! Now, now...
- Oh, stop screaming.
We don't have the time to stand
around enjoying your hobby with you.
And we're not wealthy enough
to be wasting money on you.
Have something impressive completed
within 48 hours, young lady.
Damn, it's hot! Oww.
Sheesh! How much did
I drink last night?
Well, I'm known as Revy...
...the girl who becomes stingier
the more drunk she gets.
But oh, boy.
Shit! It's damn hot enough as it is.
What a pathetic start to a day.
How about this?
It's all mine!
What?!
I'm taking a piss.
We'll start over when I get back.
There. No, I wasn't fixing
the game or anything. I was just...
Let me out! Hey!
Man. What's with this city?
It's so damn shady.
The Shepherd.
What would his weapon be?
The Book of Psalms.
Psalm 23, verse 15.
"Though I walk through
the valley of the shadow of death".
What I wanna know is,
what did the shepherd take with him?
Model Jericho, 941 FBL.
You serious? That's lame.
Then what's your answer?
Isn't it obvious?
This guy.
That's stupid.
He was Jewish, right?
Then he had to have
taken something made in Israel.
Quit your impertinent talk.
You're nothing but a monkey.
It's hot. If I knew your air conditioner
was broken, I wouldn't have come.
And the boat's way out in the dock.
It's not my day.
You don't have to tell me
over and over.
You're not a broken jukebox.
By the way, that guy,
your handsome sailor.
It's almost a year now
since he came, right?
He's nothing special. He won't get
rid of that stupid business suit.
If he encounters an enemy,
he gets kidnapped.
And his jokes are so lame, damn it!
Who cares about any of that?! I wanna
know whether or not you did it with him.
Hey, what's wrong?
You're no fun.
Man, it's hot!
Hello! Hello! I'm being chased!
- Help me!
- Someone's calling.
- We're closed!
- Hurry! Open it! Open up! Please!
Open this door!
Do you know what Jesus
said in John 5?
"Don't bring trouble
into my home, you bitch!"
But this is a church, right?
So?
God's not in. He's gone to
Las Vegas on vacation.
Please! I'm being chased!
I can't count on anyone in this city,
and I'm not from here.
I was told that the church
might be able to help, and...
I can't believe this!
And you're supposed to be a Sister?
Come back on Judgment Day.
You do that, and God will...
Jane. Don't make things any more
difficult. Come on. It's time to go home.
Mister Elvis.
Put your gun away.
I've told you repeatedly that this isn't
the same as the cities you're used to.
Sister. I need to have
a little talk with that girl.
Eda!!
All right!
Bastards!
Any idiot who dares to fire at us...
...has gotta be prepared
for some payback!
What's going on?! Shit!
Shoot at them! Kill them!
Stop it! Don't fire!
Guys, do not fire back no matter what!
You idiot! Fire!
- Damn it!
- They're pissing me off!
Sis! I've come to help!
Call me Sister! Dimwit!
I've never seen you.
You new here?
Yes! I'm Ricardo,
in training to become a priest.
I've heard a lot about you
from Sis. Call me Rico.
Rico! I'm telling you,
don't call me Sis!
Revy! Can you hear me, Revy?!
It's Lobos!
Please put away your guns.
This is a misunderstanding!
Please! We got
a little crossed up...
- ...in our communication!
- Don't take me for some idiot!
Don't try and brush this off
as some accident!
Like she says! You Manneken Pis!
If you think you can
walk away unharmed...
...after drilling bullets
into the church...
- ...you've got another thing coming!
- Oh, dear God! We're doomed!
My, my. What's this here?
Oh, boy.
Eda!
What have I told you about
doing this in the chapel?
Oh, well that, Sister...
We can deal with that later.
We must first take care
of these unbelievers...
...the same way as
the people of Beit Shemesh.
Shit! Guys!
We're leaving! Mister, you too!
Damn it! Those damn bitches!
I'll be back!
I'll make minced meat outta you!
My, my.
Who's gonna pay for the repairs?
And for the bullets we used.
The cash just keeps floating away.
Give me a break. Now...
You've got a lot of
explaining to do, young lady.
Those guys are from
the Nouveau Laredo Cartel.
The organization works directly
under the Gerolamo Familia...
...who claims Florida
as its territory.
I was hired by the cartel to
fabricate old dollar bills.
Although my counterfeit bill design
team is scattered all over the world...
...thanks to the internet, we've never
had any problems with the work I do.
I'm the team's chief organizer.
The leader, if you will.
So, what did you screw up
to end up having them chase you?
We didn't screw up!
That was rude. It's just that
those guys had no patience.
Let me make this clear.
The reason I accepted the job...
...is because I was told I'd be able
to make perfect counterfeit money.
I was shocked with the Super-Z.
The paper it created was
absolutely perfect.
What's most impressive
is the composition percentage.
The percentage of cotton to linen pulp
is controlled at exactly 23 to 76.8.
Although there are those out there who'll
produce their product on a laser printer...
...in my opinion,
that is unacceptable!
In comparison,
these guys are pros.
It's a printing machine
custom made in Switzerland.
We would do anything
to get our hands on it...
...but security is so damn tight
that it's really difficult.
By the way, we print ours
on a Heidelberg MF521...
...but it has its limits and it shows.
Pretty pathetic, don't you think?
But those guys, they give it a name
like "enemy nation assault bills"...
...and create a budget for it!
I'd be able to make something just
as good for a lot less! Really!
But that machine causes
a strain in the progress of work.
Take the pressure along
the outside of the faceplate number.
We use an adjustment method...
...for applying rubber in order to change
the ink pressure in each section.
But frankly,
this method isn't too clever.
The reason being...
...using infrared hardening ink will allow
the red blow ink to print naturally.
We've had no problems with the green
and black double layer printing sections...
...but with the method
I just explained...
...you'd have to really perfect the details
of the Department of Treasury label.
Otherwise, the mounted section on
the outside would come out uneven.
- And then...
- Hey, hey, hey! Question!
- Ah, yes?
- I'm sorry to interrupt you, but...
- What is it?
- Where does this story end?
Do we get a bathroom break like
they had in "Battle of the Bulge"?
You're the ones who asked
why I'm in this mess.
- What's wrong? Are you bored?
- Eda.
This girl's attitude
just reminded me.
She's just like the bitch
at my childhood welfare center.
Well, whatever.
Anyway, this type of research
requires money and time. And so...
All right, all right.
I get the general picture. That's enough.
So you tried to screw those
fellows with that introduction.
You say the same thing that
those fools were saying.
Very well. Proof over theory.
You want me to judge your work?
I can tell with a glance. This is stupid.
Look here. On this one,
the print is off by half an inch...
...and the green of the Department
of Treasury mark is too strong.
On the other hand, the thread work on
this one is very detailed. Bingo, right?
Oh, yeah? Then you'd take
that bill in your right hand...
...and hope to enjoy a day
of shopping at Sears?
Oh, I feel sorry for you.
You're on your way to jail.
Look carefully at the
Federal Reserve Bank Seal.
I was certain you would be fooled.
It's not unusual
to see a printing shear...
...or unevenness in the bills
from the seventies.
However there is no bill printed by the
Mint Bureau with an 'M' in its label.
It's clear now that Miss Revy's eyes
are made out of glass.
Okay, I believe you. Now then,
let's get to the core of this story.
We missed our deadline
by a significant margin.
But since I had an objective,
I refused to compromise.
Then they came and shot our operator
who came with me from Germany!
His job was to manage the data created
by other members over the internet.
All our effort so far
has gone down the drain.
They don't get it!
So then I got fed up
with everything...
...and said goodbye
to that band of wild gorillas.
- And that's everything.
- You're the one at fault here.
Well yeah. You are.
- You made a promise.
- What?!
No, I don't expect you
to understand!
Not anyone who spends their day,
sunrise to sunset...
...wasting their time either fiddling with
their gun or watching "NYPD Blue".
I guess you wouldn't believe it if I told
you I watch the Oprah Winfrey Show.
The correct answer,
after the sound of gunfire.
Young lady.
You've been guided here by the Lord.
You're very fortunate.
That girl pointing her gun at you
is an escape specialist.
Though I wouldn't mind making
a deal with you for that plate.
I don't wanna give you
anything that's not complete!
But I'm pressed for time,
so I can't be picky.
Won't you buy it for thirty grand,
separately from my escape expenses?
I guess you're on your own.
Make your request to some other god.
Wha... But you people
serve God, right?!
Luke says, "You shall make friends
even if you use false money to do so."
Never mind her, Eda. You can go
ahead and die if you want, girl.
I don't need your help anyway.
But I do thank you for saving me
from a difficult situation. Goodbye.
Hey. Wait one moment.
Where are you staying tonight?
I'll find some place.
Any one of the regular motels,
and you'll have fresh holes in your ass...
...before you have a chance
to take your socks off.
Now, to avoid that...
...there's a cheap lodge called Ramsap
Inn just past the Chalquam market.
Tell them you came from the church,
and they'll get you a room.
I don't like how this feels.
Of course,
I'm not telling you this for free.
Place an offering of about three
hundred dollars in that tray there.
I see. Although it's rotten, this is
a church after all. I can agree to that.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's the big idea, Eda?
What do you mean?
Very well done, Sister Eda.
That's a tree that grows gold. Keep a
close eye on her so you don't lose sight.
Yes, Sister.
Those from the country
are so easy to manipulate.
- Hey!
- Hi Leroy! Long time no see!
You know that girl that Choros
and the guys are chasing after?
- Yeah, that East Indian girl.
- Damn you!
What's the going rate
for info on her whereabouts?
You're playing dirty!
- You found out where Jane is?
- Yes boss.
That bastard Lobos is nothing but
a cowardly airhead. You go instead.
- Yes boss.
- Listen, Russell!
Aside from the clothes they wear...
...the people living in this city
are no different from the Moros!
Can you believe it?! Even nuns
at the church are firing guns! Ow, ow!
- Boss?
- Damn.
I wanna leave this god's manure
sink made of overcooked lunatics...
...and return to civilized Florida.
I wanna get back right away, damn it!
Yes boss.
Russell...
Capture the Indian girl and bring
her to me, no matter what it takes.
I'll give her a beating that'll
make Dachau seem like paradise.
Yes boss. I accompanied you from
Florida for times like this.
In three days...
...you'll be watching the Caribbean
sunset with Don Gerolamo, boss.
Leave it to this trouble buster,
"Groovy guy" Russell.
What's wrong?
Get pricked by a thorn?
I'm gonna kill you! Making money off
a cheap trick like that! Gimme half!
Like I said. You're being a fool.
With something like that...
You've gotta let it rest
before you feast on it.
Let it rest?
What do you mean,
let it rest?
Like the slot machines
at the casino.
Show them how easy
it is to win...
...then they all come
throwing their money at you.
What are you planning?
We're here, carpool customers.
You've got that evil
look on your face, Eda.
- What trick do you have up your sleeve?
- Come on.
I work under
an extraordinary trickster...
...the man who walked
on the Sea of Galilee.
A trick like this is nothing.
Now, Rock's bringing
the car around, right? Let's go.
- Hey, tell me. Where are we going?
- I dunno.
Hey, Eda. Eda, come on!
- A nun?
- Come on! Hey, Eda!
Damn.
Who are the guys
Lobos called here?!
Everyone you see sitting
at these tables.
Very well.
I'll give out your orders.
One thousand dollars per person.
She's staying in a motel
called Ramsap Inn.
Your job is to bring her back alive.
If she retaliates,
you're free to beat her up.
It's an easy job that even
a child could do.
Forget the unnecessary
comments, stupid idiot!
It's only because we have the free time
that we're accepting such a cheap job!
You...
Shen Hua's right, cowboy!
Get back to inseminating...
- ...your cows in Austin!
- Damn you!
How dare some guy who just arrived
here try to order us around!
Get Lobos here!
You won't do!
Would you shut up and listen to
what I have to say, you bastards?!
Just introduce us to the new faces,
and there will be no trouble.
Who are you?
Not a face I recognize either.
Which organization is she
getting her work from?
What are you talking about? Shen Hua,
you hired me for a job last Tuesday.
I did?
Hi! I'm late, I'm late.
Sorry about that. Are you ready?
Oh, how to cut him up? Boss Chang
wanted to make an example outta him.
He didn't tell me whether he wanted
the meat chopped or minced.
I guess it doesn't matter which.
Well, he's all yours now.
You can take care of things from here.
What?!
You're Sawyer the Cleaner?!
So that's what you look like.
You're always wearing those
goggles and white facemask.
No wonder we didn't recognize you.
All right.
Hurry up and get to work, guys.
Those are new faces over there.
Oh, you're right.
Haven't seen them before.
You two.
What are your names?
I'm Claude "Torch" Weaver.
Lotton the Wizard.
Sorry to bother you while you're showing
off, but is that milk you're drinking?
I'm a nondrinker.
Beer makes me puke.
I don't drink for religious reasons.
How unfitting.
So what do you use for hunting?
This.
And you? Doesn't look
like you have a gun.
You idiot! Are you trying
to burn down the bar?!
Y-Y-You guys cut it out, already!
Oh, well. At least now
we know what we'll be using.
- Is everyone okay with that?!
- Right on.
Let's get this over with
and have a drink.
Hey, is Ramsap Inn far from here?
- Let's take our cars.
- You're picking up the bill.
- Damn it.
- Cowboy.
What are you just standing there for?
We'll leave without you.
Okay, this path is good.
Bring it to the side and stop.
Alright, thank you sir.
- Are you sure this spot will be okay?
- I don't understand the logic behind this.
Shut up. Just wait here and something
very favorable for us will happen.
You know, there's this ominous
tone to what you just said.
Next Episode
Okay guys! Let's get going!
To our clownish
one-grand-a-person job.