Can I ask you a couple questions?
I don't mean Issei.
I'm talking to you, Welsh Dragon.
so
no
mu
If you listen to the voice of your heart
You'll be born anew again and again
born
born
new
mo
u
ko
I can't hide it anymore
The purported salvation is but a mirror paradox
Trying to come to terms with myself
I realized my soul must lie with my wishes
The moment we met, the warmth of the tears
de
ta
shun
shun
ta
kan
shun
Falling off your palm ignited my heart
And we understood the DxD each other felt
I've been waiting
What's there to be gained amid all the despair?
It's not bliss but rather a good feeling
feel
feel
ing
so
no
mu
Until I reach deep inside your heart
I'll call out your name again and again
your
name
your
name
Episode
The Occult Club Disappears?!
I see. He's still...
Yeah, he's still in a coma.
His body and demonic power are
recovering without problems, but...
It seems his injuries are still pretty bad deep inside.
Deep inside?
A lot happened to him.
It looks like we'll just have to wait this out.
Issei-san went through all of this to save me.
Asia, it's not your fault.
That's right. The Khaos Brigade is to blame!
Yeah.
Oh. That's right, Asia.
What?
You haven't tried it yet, have you?
I'm talking about the results of your training.
Huh?
It seems the dragon inside of Issei is dysfunctional due to the incomplete transformation.
I was informed that's why his left arm is still in dragon form.
Who told you something like that?
Asia's Sacred Gear might be able to solve the problem.
"Might"? Are you sure it's safe for Asia?
I can't be sure of that.
No way!
It's only a possibility.
Please, let me try.
Asia...
Issei-san said he'd protect his family, and he saved me!
That's why I want to save
Issei-san as well, Rias-oneesama!
Please be careful, Asia.
Your training was to heal people at a distance.
This time you'll need to reach deep rather than far.
Deep...
You need to heal the injury deep inside of Issei's heart.
Is it okay to leave Asia-senpai alone?
If she focuses all her healing energy,
it will become a powerful force.
We don't know how it will affect the area around her.
Are you okay with this, Rias?
I trust my sister Asia.
That is also one of my duties.
Issei-san, you are a precious person to me.
You have always been beside me.
You always cheered me up.
You always protected me.
Issei-san, this might be a chance given to me by God,
a way to finally do something for you.
Please!
Please open your eyes, Issei-san!
Huh? It's rare to wake up with just Asia.
Wait, what's going on?
Why are your clothes like that?!
Issei-san!
Thank goodness!
H-Hey.
Thank goodness. I'm so happy!
Ah, I see. You healed me.
Thank you, Asia.
No, I was just so desperate.
W-Well, let's go. Everyone is waiting for you.
Yeah. I caused a lot of trouble for everyone.
Issei-san...
Huh?
Issei-san. I love you.
I'll always stay by your side.
My, my.
So passionate.
U-Um, President! This is...
We'll have to let Asia have you for the day.
Yes, you're right.
By the way, Asia, I'm really thankful for what you did!
Oh, no! There's no need to thank me!
No, I really do. Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine!
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Everyone! Now that Issei's gotten better, let's eat.
Yes, President!
It seems the Old Satan Faction that had joined the Khaos Brigade has fallen apart due to that incident.
Vali never thought of them as comrades to begin with.
Great Red.
Ophis wants to kick him out of the Dimensional Gap.
They shared a common interest.
Right now, the lines between the worlds are stable
because Great Red rules the Dimensional Gap.
If something like that were to happen...
Who knows what could happen to the entire world?
We have to stop that from happening at all costs.
He probably appeared because Loki's failed attempt to destroy time and space
created a small fissure between the worlds.
At least, that's what Ajuka believes.
Loki, huh? A pain in the ass to the very end.
That damned Ouroboros.
She just had to butt in.
However...
What's this?
I'm not done yet.
Feel this down to your very bones, Red Dragon Emperor.
You, too, Ruin Princess.
We're finally back home!
To think I was out cold for three days...
I feel bad about everyone missing school because of me.
I told the school we were overseas for a practice match,
so I'll just say we couldn't return due to the weather.
That's such an obviously made-up excuse.
Saying that an occult club has practice matches is already stretching it.
Putting school aside...
So mean! Odin-sama is so mean!
I thought he came to pick me up,
but then he suddenly sent me out to battle.
Even though... Even though I worked so hard...
He left me behind again!
He seemed to have his hands full trying to tie up loose ends.
I'm sure he'll come to pick you up again.
He won't!
If I, his bodyguard, go home after our Great Father returns,
they'll scream, "What kind of nerve do you have returning after Odin-sama?!"
Um...
And I'll probably get demoted!
They're downsizing.
I felt bad leaving her behind in the underworld,
I must have been laid off!
so I brought her back with us...
I'm just a woman who can't do her job!
Jeez. That old man is really irresponsible.
A virgin!
He should just come and pick her up already.
I've been alone my entire life!
Well, it's fine.
If that's the case, I have an idea.
You do?
It's a secret.
Asia, is your body holding up okay?
Now, please cheer up.
Yes!
I'm really happy that Asia helped Issei get better.
But for a second...
Why?
One, two! One, two! One, two! One, two!
All right, we look pretty good!
Let's take a short break.
O-Okay!
Hey!
You know, this kind of peace is really nice.
Um, Sensei?
You see, I talked to the one inside of you while you were unconscious.
Inside of me?! To Ddraig?!
Yeah.
What does the Governor-General of fallen angels want to ask?
I wanted to ask about the power Issei released at the very end.
He invoked the Juggernaut Drive that was sealed inside of him.
That forbidden skill that forcefully releases all the power sealed within a sacred treasure...
If invoked, the user will temporarily have power that surpasses even the gods.
But in exchange, they either lose their life or shorten it dramatically.
Sensei, no matter what, never tell that to Asia!
I wondered why something that dangerous was invoked.
It was invoked because my partner's despair and anger surpassed their very limits. However...
Something was controlling my partner's feelings at the time.
But I am not exactly sure what it was.
I wouldn't know either.
So you have no idea what it could have been?
No. Nothing in particular.
That's fine, then.
Sensei...
Don't worry about it too much.
Rias said that I didn't have to worry,
but I can't let myself become a freeloader.
At the very least, I have to clean.
From Valhalla?
So he finally came to pick me up?
Huh?
It's almost time for Koneko-chan to come. Oh, no.
Ah! Issei-senpai!
Hey, President!
Oh, Issei?
Did you finish practicing for the school festival?
Yeah, I came to pick up my school bag.
Oh, so it's already this late?
President, what are you doing here?
Not much.
Are you worried about something?
I have no worries.
Well, that's good.
It's just that you look like
you're depressed sometimes.
Sorry. I said something I shouldn't have.
Don't be. Thank you for worrying about me.
I'm fine.
It's not like I can really help, but...
President, aren't you pushing yourself a little too hard?
Huh?!
I know.
Even if it means lying to yourself, you always try so hard.
Issei?!
You don't need to think about anything.
That's right. I understand everything about you.
One, two! One, two! One, two!
Looks like our rhythm's synced up pretty well!
Yeah! This is all thanks to you!
All right, let's go a little bit faster this time!
Wait.
What's wrong?
I left our stopwatch in the club room.
Sorry! I'll go grab it real quick!
Koneko-chan!
Issei-senpai!
I came to pick up Gya-kun so he can practice the bread-eating race.
That guy's entering the bread-eating race?
Gasper!
Gya-kun!
What happened?!
Issei-senpai...
Oh, thank goodness! The real one!
Huh? What are you talking about?!
Issei-senpai!
Me? What's going on?
You bastard!
What are you trying to pull,
looking like me?!
It's dangerous, Issei-senpai!
President?
This ki...
President! Get a hold of yourself!
That isn't me!
President...
No way!
I didn't make it in time?!
An explosion?
But nothing in the old school building was explosive!
It's dangerous! Please stay back!
Issei-san, what happened?!
We still don't know the details.
Gasper-kun stopped time right before the explosion
and pulled these two to safety.
Thank you, Gya-kun.
Good job!
I can't believe something like this could happen on our school grounds.
Where's Rias?
Dammit!
Sensei!
Valhalla sent over an emergency message to Rossweisse.
Loki did this.
What did you say?!
An impostor Issei-kun?
It's true. I saw him, too.
He practically had the same aura as Issei-senpai as well.
The same?
If the real Issei-senpai weren't in front of me,
I probably wouldn't have noticed the difference.
Are you sure that Loki is behind this?
It seems the man himself said so.
You placed a curse on Princess Rias and the Red Dragon Emperor?
I failed against the Red Dragon Emperor because someone interfered.
However, I was able to think of a different plan.
So I thought I'd report it to our Great Father.
How far you've fallen, Loki.
You attack the weak because you are no match for Sirzechs or me?
Do not underestimate me, Odin.
Why would a god like me need to get revenge on a few young devils?
So your motive lies elsewhere?
It's already too late.
The twilight of the gods is approaching fast.
The reason why those two received my curse
was that one of the Satans sent his own sister to battle,
while you placed your hope and Mjolnir into the hands of that young devil.
I hope you grieve deeply over your own decisions!
Loki!
After he said that, he sealed himself away.
What a coward!
This is a lot more effective than just defeating the enemy.
I suffered a long time myself.
S-So what is Loki's real motive?
The twilight of the gods—Ragnarok.
He wants to destroy this world.
Um, where's Issei-san?
Rossweisse is speaking with him.
A curse?
Yes.
It seems he placed curses on you and Rias-san right before his capture.
What do you mean by that?
Curses attack and eat away at a person's heart.
It exploits what's deep within your heart,
perhaps something you don't even realize yourself.
Loki used those feelings deep inside against you.
Does anything come to mind?
I'm probably scared.
That's right.
I'm scared about finding out how girls really feel.
It's not that I doubt them.
But... I am scared.
You don't have to force yourself to speak about it.
I'm sorry.
No, I should apologize as well.
I was ordered to confirm Loki's words.
Then, you're saying that President has some doubt in her heart like me?
You will have to ask her about that.
Actually, it may be so deep within her that she doesn't even realize it herself.
With her crimson hair and dignified stature,
how could there be something dark within the heart of the person I admire?
President Rias...
Are you all right, Sirzechs?
I am Satan Lucifer above all else.
I will do what I must as a Satan.
You're trying too hard.
According to Asgard, it will take some time to break Loki's seal.
If we could find out Rias' location from him at the very least...
It seems she is in the Dimensional Gap.
Dimensional Gap?
The place that Asia-chan was sent to?
I've searched using various methods, and it is the only possible location.
So we'll be able to save the president if we go there?
There's no systematic method of searching the Dimensional Gap.
If Vali didn't happen to pass by at the right moment,
we never would have found Asia, either.
In other words, entering the
Dimensional Gap means death.
Then how can those people enter it?
The Khaos Brigade is a gathering of various factions.
They may be using a method we aren't aware of.
This is a guess,
but it's probably possible to lock the existence of this world and use it as a barrier.
Koneko-chan!
I want to get in touch with your sister.
With Kuroka-neesama?
I'll go see Vali.
sou daitai no koto nante
Well, yeah, I do think that
mou wakatte wa iru na tte
I've got this stuff mostly figured out
omou yo dakedo ne
But still, you know
kokoro wa bannou ja nai
Feelings on their own can only get you so far
daiji na koto bakka ishin fudenshin
The stuff that matters isn't getting across
saishuuteki ni wa analog tsuushin
So we have to rely on analog communication
dakara ima sugu
That's why, right now
motto chanto katachi ni shite yo
I want you to be more concrete
kimi ga
Do it
ijiwaru na voice
With your flirty voice
give me kikasete yo
Give me, just tell me
nee
Come on
chotto dake de ii no
Just a little hint is fine
aimai na no wa yada na
Don't leave me hanging
no secret sansei
No secrets, yeah?
do you do you know
Do you know?
answer todokete ne
Give me your answer
hora
See
kowaku nante nai shi
I'm not afraid to hear it
ienai kedo ne wakaru desho
I don't have to actually tell you, right?
wakatte yo
Take the hint
tell me heart tell me heart
Tell me your heart
subete wo kaeru no wa
If you want to take it to the next step
give me word give me word
Give me your word
itsu de mo kimi dakara
The power is in your hands
Next Episode:
The ones involved with the red or white dragon
have never had a good life.
Couldn't this be destiny as well?
Who cares?!
Even if it is destiny, I'll change it!
Episode
I Will Fight!
Rias! Is that you?!