Maximum Titillation OVA Vol. 4
Levia and So
Oh, I can't decide!
Pink is nice, but it's hard to say
no to the limited-edition blue!
Are you serious, Sister?
Of course!
I'm auditioning for a
live-action magical girl after all!
It's okay! I have the whole day off!
Honestly, now. Everyone coddles you so much...
Hey, So! Try this costume on!
Come again?
It helps if I see other people wearing it.
Please?!
I refuse.
If you won't wear it then
I'll give up being a magical girl!
I won't care about that work anymore!
You're wrong if you think
tantrums can get you everything.
Fine! I'll destroy all the
angels and fallen angels then!
Okay, okay. I'll put it on.
Will that make you happy?
Hurry, hurry!
Why do I have to dress like this?
Hmm. I think pink fits the
"Milky" image more after all.
I'll go with pink, then!
Ugh. I feel dirty.
Honestly...
Huh? What? It's stuck.
Sister. This outfit...
Oh, that costume is designed to come off
only when a certain spell is chanted!
Huh?! Then tell me the spell!
Sure! Watch closely!
Milulun! Milu-milu!
With my bright magic
I'll destroy lots and lots of bad guys!
You tricked me, Sister.
Go on! Say it already!
Milulun. Milu-milu.
With my bright magic
I'll destroy lots and lots of bad guys.
It's not coming off, Sister.
No, no! That's no good, So!
The spell doesn't work
if you don't say it cutely!
Cutely?!
Here, I'll do it with you! Okay?
F-Fine.
Milulun! Milu-milu!
With my bright magic
I'll destroy lots and lots of bad guys!
Oh!