Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
We're ready to stage an all-out
missile attack on the colonies!
You guys can't fight, can you?!
Mission accepted.
The Whereabouts of Happiness
There's really no way out,
with all this security.
Besides, to swipe a carrier...
...I'd have to cross the
desert to get to an airport.
That guy...
We're in the same boat.
With all those planes
looking for us...
...you're stuck, too.
A large sandstorm
is coming.
That's when we'll cross
the desert.
Wanna join us?
Yeah, I do.
I could use some sympathy.
And I need time to think.
We've collected what we could.
But the important parts
have all been destroyed.
I thought so.
That's why he self-detonated.
So even Gundams end up
as mere scraps of metal.
Or rather, scraps of Gundanium.
This Gundam design was
based on the Tallgeese.
So the basic technology utilized
for the Tallgeese should apply.
Zechs?
Noin.
Would you mind if I took
this Gundam with me...
...to the Lake Victoria Base?
Huh?
Are you planning to fix it?
Yeah...
Why bother?
Perhaps I'm preoccupied
with that pilot.
But the Gundam pilot died.
I get the feeling he's alive.
It's pretty well impossible
after that explosion.
But I hope he's alive.
As a fellow mobile suit pilot,
I was destined to battle him.
I'm terribly sorry!
Your Excellency...
I shouldn't have acted
on my own...
...to plan a direct attack
on the colonies.
That's water under
the bridge now.
Now we know that the
Gundam attacks were planned...
...by certain people,
to retaliate against us.
Our target is still to destroy
all of the Gundams.
But their supporters concern me.
In outer space.
I'd prefer to keep the enemy
from becoming more powerful.
Can I rely on you, Lady Une?
Yes.
I'll eliminate them at once.
Uh, Your Excellency?
The peace-minded people
of the colonies...
...won't stand any militarism.
You can do away with
some of your formalities.
Announce your trip to outer
space when you're in Moscow.
Many noble people who
understand OZ live in Moscow.
They should be able
to assist you.
Sir!
Nothing on the radar.
That doesn't mean
a damn thing.
Spread out and watch
for enemies.
Crap, I can't see a thing
in this sandstorm!
What could be out here?
There's a middle east
nations' military base...
...unaffiliated with the United
Earth Sphere Alliance or OZ.
Let's take refuge there.
A base?
No problems here.
Here either.
Or here.
Roger.
An underground base?!
Let's go.
H- Hey!
This base belongs to our
Maganac Corps' homeland.
It's your base?
Good of you to come, Quatre.
It's been a while,
Commander Sadaul.
The missions have been tough
since you got to Earth, huh.
I owe the Maganac Corps
for all their help.
How can I thank you?
It was their personal decision;
they wanted to help you.
If we had more strength
we could've done...
...more damage to OZ.
That troublesome OZ!
A sensible person wouldn't
use the colonies as a shield!
We're to blame, for not
stopping them.
Yeah, we're totally to blame.
Oh, no, Quatre.
No one would blame you.
Here, come this way.
Master Quatre, we'll get started
with the mobile suit repairs.
Yeah, thanks.
Oh, and Rashid...
Yes, I know.
We'll repair both Gundams.
Okay?
Just fine by me.
I appreciate it.
I haven't introduced myself.
I'm Quatre Raberba Winner.
Winner?
You're the Winner family's heir?
The influential and financial
power of the Arabic Nations?
No wonder everyone looks up
to you around this place.
Our family is all pacifists.
I disinherited myself
to come out here.
Yeah?
It takes all types, I guess.
I'm Duo. Duo Maxwell.
I might run and hide,
but I never tell a lie.
We were told that the colonies
have sent mobile suits to Earth.
That's her!
It's true that a number of
mobile suits...
...were sent to Earth and tried
to destroy certain targets.
However OZ is currently taking
steps to expose the rebels...
...so it can maintain
world peace.
It's only a matter of time
before we solve this issue.
That rose doesn't suit
her one bit!
Thank you.
My pleasure.
My, isn't she cute!
Excuse me.
Do you have an invitation?
No.
Forgive me, but this party
is open only to invited guests.
Katrina...
Do you know any
other guests?
Relena, you're early.
Oh, Marquis Weridge!
I'm terribly sorry; I had
no idea she was your relation.
Not to worry.
Shall we go, Relena?
The party's about to begin.
Uh...
Don't mention it.
This place is full of old folks.
Young people like yourself
are a rarity.
My, Mr. Weridge.
What a pretty young date.
How do you do. I'm Relena.
May I have this dance miss?
I couldn't allow that.
The first dance is already taken.
If you wouldn't mind,
could I have this dance?
Why should I mind;
I'd be delighted.
It'd be my pleasure.
What's this?!
We've guarded the
front entrance.
No problems at the rear
gate or along the channel.
Radar picking up nothing
in the sky.
Roger.
Continue to post guard.
I can see the Peacecraft
influence in you.
Do you know the Peacecrafts?
Of course I do.
Thank you.
I was close to the Sanc Kingdom
monarchy, the Peacecrafts.
Till 13 years ago, when
the family was overthrown.
Why was the Peacecraft
family overthrown?
It seems absurd, but while
some people hope for peace...
...others try to gain
through disputes.
The former was the
Peacecraft family...
...and the latter was the
United Earth Sphere Alliance.
Their talk of peace interfered
with the Alliance's objectives?
Yes, and even the Romefeller
Foundation...
...which opposed the Alliance,
started developing weapons.
Blasted OZ!
OZ?
I invited Treize today to ask
what he was trying to pull.
But he sent over some
representative!
What's wrong?
Don't worry; I'm a guest too.
Show me to Marquis Weridge.
I must see him personally,
on behalf of His Excellency.
Roses don't belong on
military uniforms.
A rose is more suitable for
someone kind like you, Relena.
Marquis Weridge.
I come on behalf of
Treize Khushrenada.
My name is Lady Une.
I need to talk with you.
Before that, would you
give me that rose?
I'd like to give it to
my granddaughter.
Relena Darlian!
What're you doing here?!
Grandfather, roses don't
look good on me either.
I'd look better soaked
in the blood of OZ!
Here's for my dad!!
Damn!
After her!!
Marquis!
Standing in your way is
about the only thing I can do!
I can't match her courage!
How dare you!
We're all fans of that girl.
- Take the main entrance!
- Yes, ma'am!
We need her kind of courage
in order to move forward.
There's so much for me to learn.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
All clear?!
Yes!
Wow!
A festival!
Looks like a gas!
They're celebrating the return
of us 40 Maganac soldiers.
Yeah?
The nation opposes the Alliance
Military and defends itself.
The Maganac are the
front-line troops.
They are?
Okay, I'll go!
Don't push!
You're more like heroes
than front-line soldiers.
Everyone's completely united now.
That's why this nation's
so positive.
This nation is unified and is
gonna stick it out to the end.
What about us?
There's a lot I wanna
talk to you about.
Okay, Quatre?
Of course.
I've got questions, myself.
Now we're all alone.
There's five, right?
That's right.
Just the five of us that
met at New Edwards.
I came here from the colonies.
I did as well.
The five of us are very
similar, don't you think?
Our mobile suits and
our missions.
Not to mention our goal
to destroy OZ.
OZ destroyed peace in
the colonies.
This mission is revenge.
I've been fighting under
those orders.
Me too.
That's when I was given
the mobile suit.
Same here.
Don't worry about the colonies.
"Destroy them first."
"That's your responsibility."
Just the same.
Yeah word for word.
I've always fought believing
I'd be better off dead...
...than live under OZ's rule.
Me too.
But to kill yourself...
Heero ended up doing it.
He took his life.
The colonies have no
intention of fighting.
The colonies can't be sacrificed.
Your friend was the
perfect role model.
I never would've imagined
that Heero was so stubborn.
The colonies were a clear target
once the Gundams got going.
A battle where the nation
isn't unified as one body.
There's nothing more difficult
for a lonely soldier.
Captain!
Come to headquarters!
OZ's mobile suit troops
are coming.
What?!
Take a look at this, Rashid!
Looks like their reconnoiter
troops!
What do you think, Rashid?
If we start fighting here,
the civilians will get involved.
Then keep on guard but send
the soldiers underground.
Sir!
Is this some kind of festival?
Some nomadic friends stopped
by at the village...
Something wrong?
Will you let our troops rest
and share your food and water.
We'll do what we can.
Thanks a lot.
You're quite intimidating.
We hear middle east rebels
are hiding out in this area.
We're here for precautionary
purposes.
Damn them!
All right!
OZ has left.
Check those boxes!
Well?
We can't move it.
It's set so any movement
will trigger it.
Rashid, what's the matter?
Master Quatre.
OZ played dumb.
Meanwhile they were setting
twenty bombs across town!
Huh?!
If they're time bombs we
just need to trash them all!
They're designed so we
can't move them.
They've narrowed our troops'
location down to this town.
Which means they're gonna
force us to surface.
They've set the bombs to
go off at 12 midnight.
They must be hoping for
a nighttime battle.
So OZ is preparing to battle
with us overnight.
Or they think we're gonna
surrender before then.
Aren't the Gundams causing
this problem?
That's right!
They must be after us.
Their attack is well planned.
They've probably been
watching this town for awhile.
Everyone, listen up!
OZ has discovered this town
and will be attacking.
I doubt if we'll be able to
deceive them any further.
Therefore, we'll aim at one
area of their besieging line.
...and resist while helping
the civilians escape!
One other honorable
duty remains.
We must get the two
Gundams out of here.
The Gundams are heroes that
arrived on Earth to destroy OZ!
Because of OZ's scheming, the
Gundams can't fight this battle.
But there will be a day when
the Gundams will save us all!
Be thankful that you can return
the favor in advance!
Do you understand?!
YEAH!
All units, to battle!
Hover suits from the middle
east troops are attacking!
Tragos troops, fire!!
The enemy's hover suits
are too quick!
Tragos Hover suits,
shift to the back!
Close combat's too dangerous!
Yes, sir!
Tragos ready to fire at enemy's
underground exit!
What?!
Did you think that was
our only exit?!
Got them!
By the North Gate!
There are all kinds of enemy
carriers to choose from!
Good job.
Take them at once.
Yes sir!
Don't rush.
They haven't guarded
the North Mountain Gate.
Don't get separated from
your families!
Take this to the North Gate,
where Abdul's waiting.
Thank you.
Sorry I can't do anything
in return.
I'm so ashamed!
Huh?
For me?
The Gundams are our heroes!
Never forget that.
I know we'll fight together
again some day!
For the future!
Hey, Quatre!
Yeah?
I've got some flowers
here for you!
I promise!
One day my Gundam will
definitely fight again.
Decoy operations are complete
and we're fleeing to the hills!
We can't have civilian casualties.
It'd blemish the Maganac
Corps name!
Secure a path for Master
Quatre's carrier!
Maganac Corps, gather up ahead!
Don't let the enemy
through the barrage!
Quatre...
Yes?
Could you circle the sky
just once?
I can't help them now.
But I wanna do something.
Sure thing.
Hang in there!
Keep firing!!
Master Quatre...
Good! Mission complete!
All Maganac Corps,
retreat at once!
See you again, Maganac Corps.
Next time we meet, the colonies'
thoughts will be united.
Count on it!
There she is!
Silly girl! Keep still!
Let me go!!
Who are you?!
I'll be taking care of her
from now on.
We have special orders
from Colonel Une.
I can't take orders from
you, Lieutenant.
These orders are from
His Excellency, you know.
Are you satisfied?
Yes!
Excuse our misunderstanding!
You're being reckless.
I wonder who your
temperament takes after.
You're part of OZ right?
So who are you?
I have come for you.
Miss Relena Peacecraft.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
One must use weapons
to win back peace.
In a battlefield filled with
inconsistencies...
...Wu Fei meets Sally Po.
Wu Fei states that the weaker
should not be fighting.
But with those words...
Sally senses the complexity
of a cornered warrior.
Lost in his emotions, Wu Fei
returns to his Shenlong Gundam.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 12,
Bewildered Warriors
"Bewildered Warriors".