Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
The attacks by the Gundams
sent by the Space Colonies...
...reflected the colonies'
retaliatory intentions.
OZ has masked its identity
in the Alliance Military...
...and the Gundams' mission
is to attack them.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite soldiers
at his command...
...Treize Khushrenada has begun
to wipe out the Alliance Military.
The battle between OZ and the
mobile suits sent to Earth...
...causes serious repercussions
on the Earth.
The Treize Assassination
Explosive devices with
infrared sensors.
That won't stop me!
I'm going after Treize!
Treize Khushrenada was using
us like a bunch of puppets...
We screwed up this mission.
Let's go after Treize!
We can still catch him!
That's not wise!
Stay outta my way!
Want me to shoot you?!
Our tactics have always been
a surprise attack.
But now the enemy
has the advantage.
You've got a point.
So we didn't get them all!
Let's get out of here!
Sure!
Hey kid! Look out!
You'll get shot!
Don't just stand there!
I ordered Lieutenant Zechs
to take control...
...of the Luxembourg
Headquarters...
...where they continue
to retaliate.
Good.
He should be able to get
things under control.
How shall we handle the
Gundams at New Edwards?
I'll leave that up to you.
Sir!
This base is completely
under our control.
Request permission to head
for New Edwards.
For New Edwards?
That won't be necessary.
Just activate the missile
self-detonation devices...
...at New Edwards.
Self-detonation devices?
I'm sure you can activate
them from where you are.
That's correct.
Then get to it!
That's over-kill.
Demolishing an entire base
just to kill a few mobile suits.
The Alliance Military couldn't
do something this simple.
What's all this commotion?!
An unusually large number
of aircraft are asking to land.
Probably the ones that escaped
from New Edwards!
It's too chaotic to be
a mere Gundam attack.
This doesn't make sense.
Major Sally!
I've intercepted an
OZ transmission!
They're gonna detonate the
missiles at New Edwards!
No!
They're trying to destroy
the Gundams and the base!
We must land at once!
We can make a belly
landing on the sand.
System locked on.
Preparing to activate
detonation devices.
Leave the premises.
I repeat.
These babies should get rid
of those Gundams.
Stop!
You can't be serious!
Your colleagues and injured
officers are still there!
They'd be glad to die
with such honor.
You're crazy!
I'll take that as a compliment,
ex-Alliance Forces Major.
How could you?!
Final safety device deactivated.
T-minus 900 to detonation.
Major Sally, what are you
trying to do?
The system's locked.
There's nothing more you
can do.
Nothing you try will work.
There's only 10 minutes
before the base is wiped out!
There's one person we couldn't
eliminate if we wanted to.
A Gundam?
A Gundam pilot I'm
interested in.
I was hoping I could
see him again.
I didn't think this
would happen.
Hey!
Quit relying on us like this!
Your friend's just gone
through too much!
Heero!
I know you can hear me!
Listen to me, Heero!
Heero?
So his name's Heero?
Detonation devices on the
base's large missiles...
...were activated!
OZ is planning to blow
the entire base apart...
...to kill you Gundams!
I've confirmed that.
There are 47 large missiles
at the New Edwards Base...
...and if they were to
explode at once...
...it'd instantly wipe out a
radius of about 300 kilometers!
I'm not sticking around!
Let's get out of here!
There's less than 10 minutes
before the explosion!
We can't get 300 kilometers
away in that time!
You'd be able to cover
that distance in time.
But please, grant me
my one last wish!
Deactivate the missiles, Heero!
You coward, Heero!
You leaving us?!!
You're wrong!
He isn't running away!
Missile base location confirmed.
Proceeding to enter base.
What's he doing?!
Roger that, Heero.
I'll stake my life on you!
A failed mission means death!
But my card isn't up yet!
The detonation device
has been activated...
...on the largest missile;
Model 304.
Model 304's explosion...
...will trigger the explosion
of all the other missiles.
Hurry to the model 304
control room.
They're in good shape.
I've secured two carriers!
The runway will be
cleared soon!
Let's hope we're not
wasting our time.
Could you get one more carrier
ready for departure?
Another one?!
Heero's gonna need one too.
His mobile suit's probably
low on fuel.
You're totally confident
that he's gonna succeed?
Yes.
It's up to you now, Heero!
He's got a 10 percent
chance of succeeding.
But he can do it for sure!
It's no use.
The detonation system
hasn't stopped yet.
Major Sally!
I still can't believe anyone can
stop the explosion at that base!
I understand.
Who would ever believe
such a thing.
But I can.
I'm proud of him.
I wanna brag that I know Heero,
who prevented the explosion.
I have to say you're
quite the guy, Heero!
It was a miserable mission.
I... I totally screwed up!!
I'm sorry I couldn't
eliminate the Gundams.
I'm surprised.
That's not like you.
How were you planning
to destroy them?
I tried to activate the
self-detonation devices...
...of the New Edwards
base missiles.
And?
The Gundams deactivated the
bombs and stopped the explosion.
Saved by the Gundams.
The Earth is a confined area.
We can't go around
thoughtlessly polluting it.
Human beings are weak
and vulnerable.
Anybody is capable of
killing anyone.
But we mustn't abuse
this capability.
This time we'll have
to thank the Gundams.
And Lady Une.
You must learn more
about the OZ organization.
Learn about OZ?
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Even after all this damage there's
no sign of surrendering.
Brigadier-General Daigo
Onegell's such a tenacious man.
But I hope he's also
a hateful person.
Otherwise Zechs could feel
less resolute.
How dare you!
You expected the Alliance
Headquarters to fall so easily?
I'm not letting OZ come
one step closer to this base!
I agree that security at
this base is splendid.
But if your people were
even briefly careless...
...this base would be taken
over immediately.
Zechs Merquise!!
So you knew it was me.
You were cautious around
me during the Alliance days...
...so I thought you could
tell me apart from any others.
It was the era!
The war made me do those things!
Annihilating the Sanc Kingdom
wasn't my personal desire...
...but the Alliance's decision.
The Sanc Kingdom had no
intention of resisting...
...against the Alliance.
But you staged an attack and
destroyed the Kingdom.
Many countries opposed the
expanding military powers...
...of the United Earth
Sphere Alliance.
The Sanc Kingdom was
one of those opposed.
You said you could
eliminate the revolt's cause...
...by destroying the
Royal family...
...since it influenced
neighboring countries.
You personally led the attack!
Milliardo Peacecraft...
May you rest in peace...
...the betrayed and outraged
Milliardo Peacecraft.
Learn about OZ...
Could it be that I don't
understand Treize?
Impossible.
Captain.
Two carriers from the 505
support troops...
...want to contact us.
What type of carriers?
Aries, from our own forces.
Contact approved.
This is Big Nose;
begin communication!
Wait.
Which base did they
come from?
One moment.
The New Edwards base.
You fools! Those are enemies!
The other carrier's headed
for this Mother Ship!
Shoot it down!
I'm running out of fuel.
This carrier wouldn't cause
a big explosion.
So I'll leave on the
mobile suit.
It's a Gundam!
A Gundam is here!
What?! On the ship?!
Fight him with the Leos!
Twenty Leos have been destroyed!
What's your problem?!
Throw him into the sea
and get him with the Cancer!
Where's Treize's ship?!
It left the fleet!
Good!
This one!
A Gundam!
It came out of the
carrier that went down!
What?!
The Gundam on the ship has
destroyed the bridge!
70% of our Leos have
been destroyed!
Can't we use the Aries?!
No, all of our elevators
will be targeted!
Why now; on this happy day
of our new beginning!
Lieutenant Colonel Une!
Gundam's still attacking
on the ship!
I told you; throw him
into the sea!!
Don't inform me of
his every move.
Just follow my orders!
Yes, ma'am!
Gundam's now on the
takeoff catapult line!
Good!
Send a Leo and shoot
that Gundam into the sea!
How are preparations?
Complete!
With this advanced mobility,
it should move like an Aries!
As long as I can fly over
to the other Gundam!
That Gundam's attacking
Treize's ship?!
Not for much longer!
Destination reached!
Here I go, Nataku!
Don't be so sure of yourself,
Gundam!
You won't get any
closer to that ship!
Nobody can stop me!
I wasn't expecting this
much resistance!
But it's game-over now!!
Die!!
Stupid move, getting emotional.
Step aside!
You can see for yourself
that you'll never beat me.
I never knew Gundams
were so powerful!
Damn!!
Mr. Treize!
Looks like your superior
wants to fight with me!
Fine by me!
I'll stop him in his tracks!
Mr. Treize, it's dangerous!
Get away from here!
Lady Une...
Leave him to me.
Treize...
So you're the real Treize.
I'll gladly accept.
My name is Wu Fei!
I'm Treize Khushrenada.
The duel is mine.
Kill me!
It was a good fight.
Kill me now or I'll
come back until I get you!
That sounds interesting.
I hope we can battle again.
Blast!
Treize, how come you
let that pilot escape?
He's the pilot of a mobile suit.
I thought it'd be fair to
give him another chance.
It was honorable to leave the
mobile suit and duel with me.
I can see why he makes
such a good Gundam pilot!
Next time we'll fight with
his specialty, the mobile suit.
But Treize...
Did that guy actually
accomplish his mission?
Hey! Can you hear me?!
I understand.
Let's just drop it.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The United Earth Sphere
Alliance collapses...
...and the world heads down
a path to chaos.
Heero and Duo continue
to battle OZ...
...the reason behind the chaos.
Zechs heads for the Sanc
Kingdom with his Tallgeese...
...to reclaim the homeland
of the Peacecrafts.
But Tallgeese is an extremely
dangerous mobile suit.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 9,
Portrait of a Ruined Country
"Portrait of a Ruined Country".