Whoa!
So this is President Rias's...
...family home.
I'm home.
Welcome home, milady and her peerage.
so
no
mu
If you listen to the voice of your heart
You'll be born anew again and again
born
born
new
mo
u
ko
I can't hide it anymore
The purported salvation is but a mirror paradox
Trying to come to terms with myself
I realized my soul must lie with my wishes
The moment we met, the warmth of the tears
de
ta
shun
shun
ta
kan
shun
Falling off your palm ignited my heart
And we understood the DxD each other felt
I've been waiting
What's there to be gained amid all the despair?
It's not bliss but rather a good feeling
feel
feel
ing
so
no
mu
Until I reach deep inside your heart
I'll call out your name again and again
your
name
your
name
Episode
Gathering of Young Devils
I-I'm so nervous!
I feel like we really don't belong here.
Rias-neesama! Welcome home!
I'm home, Millicas!
You've grown so big since I last saw you.
Um, President. Who is he?
This is my big brother Sirzechs Lucifer-sama's son.
So he is your nephew?
You should introduce yourself.
Okay!
I am Millicas Gremory. Nice to meet you.
So cute!
That makes him a genuine prince, huh?
Wait, so then who's Sirzechs-sama's wife?
Everyone, please enter.
Rias-neesama has come home!
Now, now. Have you forgotten your manners?
Such a pretty person. Is she President's big sister?
Issei.
Y-Yes?
No matter how passionately you stare at my mother, nothing will come of it.
Wh-What?!
It has been a long time, Venelana-sama.
I am glad you look well.
It is nice to meet all of you newcomers.
I am Rias's mother, Venelana Gremory.
President's mother? This person?
You must be Hyoudou Issei-san.
Huh? How do you know who I am?
I would never miss as important an occasion as my daughter's engagement party.
I am her mother, after all.
Rias Gremory-sama's virginity is mine!
I-I am truly sorry for causing such trouble that time!
Do not worry yourself.
That taught my husband a valuable lesson:
Never pick a fiancé without considering your daughter's feelings.
Mother!
Now, let us sit down for dinner.
Rias, show everyone the way.
I will.
Everyone, please think of this place as your own home.
I'm really hungry,
but if I just stuff my face,
I'll embarrass the President.
What's wrong?
I'm so nervous eating in such a large room that I can't taste anything!
Koneko-chan?
By the way, Hyoudou Issei-kun.
Y-Yes?
How are your parents?
Th-They are doing well thanks to you.
They're really happy with the house's remodeling!
Well, I wished to prepare a larger castle, but...
C-Castle?!
Father, we cannot force our culture onto others.
At the very least, I wished to give you fifty young maids.
Maids?!
If there were that many young women, it would affect Issei's daily life!
And so, I was stopped by my daughter.
I'd expect no less from the President. She understands how I function.
Also, Hyoudou Issei-kun.
Y-Yes?
From now on, you may address me as "Father".
Darling, you are far too hasty.
There is an order that must be followed.
Goodness! Father! Mother!
I wonder what President's parents were trying to say.
I'm worried about Koneko-chan as well.
Also...
This room is so big, I can't relax at all.
Oh. Yes?
Well...
Um, Issei-san.
What's wrong?
Why?
I can't sleep in such a big room all alone!
We lived a simple life at the Church,
so this luxury makes us uncomfortable.
Even without that simple life, any normal person would feel uncomfortable here.
But that doesn't mean we need to sleep together!
Why not?
Three people can easily fit in a bed this large, right?
That's not what I meant!
Oh, what about Gasper?
I'm more worried about him.
Oh, he's fine.
I went to check on him earlier.
This place is the best!
W-Well, as long as Gasper's happy with that.
The real training starts tomorrow.
It's still early, but we should probably sleep now.
Yeah!
I doubt I'll be able to sleep well like this.
P-Please! Wake up, Xenovia!
I can't breathe!
Xenovia, why do you have to be in the crazy-sleepers club too?
Hey! Xenovia!
Sirzechs is busy preparing to welcome an important guest and is unable to stop by.
Brother seems busy, as usual.
It looks like Governor Azazel is helping out quite a lot.
The governor of the fallen angels taking care of you kids...
Until recently, I would never have imagined that.
He's just an odd person.
All right! Looks like everyone's here!
I created a training regimen for twenty human-world days.
We're going to train for twenty days?!
Issei, let's start with you.
The old dragon from yesterday!
He'll be your personal trainer.
This is my first time training one who wields Ddraig.
I want you to activate Balance Breaker before your training's complete.
Well, work hard, and try not to die.
Everyone, there are better ways to word things!
Issei!
President.
Pull yourself together!
Oh, right.
The gentle President becomes a ruthless demon when it comes to training.
President!
You already have comprehensive strength.
On top of basic training,
you need to improve your strategies and decision-making as a King.
You must utilize your peerage to its fullest.
Why are you here?
It's been a while, Akeno.
Don't talk as if you know me.
You should accept the blood that runs in your veins.
If you use the power of fallen angels within you,
you could imbue your thunder with light to create lightning.
So that's what this was all about.
This is a direct order from the governor.
I never expected an order to train my own daughter.
No need to hold back!
Do you understand the meaning of these clothes?
I do not have a father.
Hone your Balance Breaker and
maintain it for as long as possible.
I will assign a teacher to train you in swordsmanship.
I look forward to training with you!
Holy Sword Durandal!
The Holy Sword Durandal is a fickle sword that's picky about its wielder.
You must use the sheer power of will to tame it completely.
Your abilities are already advanced.
Your greatest weakness is your own fear, so to overcome it
you need to stop being a shut-in.
Step one, go out in front of people.
That's all you need to do.
I'm already feeling overwhelmed with step one!
Release the power you have sealed within yourself.
If you are unable accept yourself,
you will not be able to develop your skills as you wish.
No...
The power of Twilight Healing depends on the user's ability.
If you can release the aura from your entire body,
you should even be able to heal someone from great distances.
I'm working hard, too, Issei-san!
That was dangerous!
Looks like you were able to avoid it this time.
I've already been chased around for three days!
I won't let myself get burned to a crisp so easily!
I like your spirit.
If that's the case, I should raise the firepower a little.
What?
That's enough for today.
Th-Thank you very much!
I'm surprised you've lasted this long with Tannin-dono's training.
I guess that's expected of the Red Dragon Emperor.
Who are you?
Just an observer.
I wanted to see how much you'd improved since your battle with Riser-dono.
Huh?
Well, try your best.
But, just being tough...
isn't enough to become one of the best.
President! It's been such a long time!
I wanted to see you so badly, President!
I dreamed of your warmth as I slept every night with just a leaf for a blanket!
Issei!
Oh, Issei! You've gotten so strong!
It seems his endurance has increased dramatically,
but he wasn't able to activate his Balance Breaker.
He's right. I'm sorry.
As I thought, you need some drastic catalyst for it.
Drastic catalyst?
I have returned.
How's Koneko doing?
She's resting now.
I heard she fainted while training.
Just what happened to Koneko-chan?
She added a huge amount of training to the regimen I gave her.
She completely overworked herself.
Koneko-chan...
Tonight, representatives of various clans will gather for a reception.
I have to head there first.
I'll have someone come for you, so be prepared.
We're attending such a high-profile event?
Not only us.
While my brother has us
attending as guards for a VIP,
its purpose is to deepen the relationships among the young devil leaders.
As devils under the President, we mustn't do anything that would make her look bad.
Young devils, huh?
I bet even their servants are strong.
No! I can't let that get me down!
I have to surpass that guy!
Isn't this Koneko-chan's room?
Koneko-chan?
Are you sleeping?
I shouldn't wake her.
Just a glance and I'll try again later.
Huh?
Come to think of it, I haven't told you.
President.
She is trying her best to face her own power and very existence.
Power and very existence?
A long time ago, there were two Nekomata sisters.
By Nekomata, do you mean the Japanese cat spirits?
After losing their parents and home, the two were always together.
Relying on each other, they lived as best they could.
One day, both cats were picked up by a devil.
Eventually, the older sister became part of that devil's peerage,
which got her back on her feet.
But by turning into a devil,
her hidden power was unleashed at once.
Unable to control her power,
she killed her master and disappeared.
She became a dangerous stray that could annihilate an entire pursuit force.
Worried that she would go
berserk like her older sister,
the devils tried to dispose of the younger one.
But my brother took her in under
the condition that he would watch over her.
He passed her on to me, so I could teach her to smile and the meaning of life.
And I gave that girl a name.
Th-Then that little sister...
...is me.
Koneko, is it okay for you to be awake?
I am sorry for worrying you.
Koneko is a survivor of the most powerful family of Nekomata—the Nekoshou clan.
She is a descendant of high-class spirits that mastered the sage arts.
I've never seen so many Satan-class
devils gathered in one place like this.
It's truly an incredible sight.
Make sure not to offend anyone.
Especially you, Issei.
I-I know!
Akeno-san?
What's wrong, Issei-kun?
Oh, nothing.
Come to think of it, what kind of training did you do, Akeno-san?
Just your average training.
I see.
Someone of Akeno-san's level
wouldn't need special training anymore.
Good evening, Rias.
Good evening, Sona.
How is your training camp going?
So-so.
Hey, Hyoudou. How are things going?
Okay, I guess. What about you?
Me? Actually, your teacher's been helping me.
Welcome, Sona-chan!
O-Onee-sama!
It has been a long time, Serafall-sama.
Oh, Rias-chan! And it looks like the
Red Dragon Emperor is doing well, too!
Y-Yes.
Michael-dono should arrive soon.
And according to Baraqiel, the head of security, Odin should be on his way.
Baraqiel is guarding him?
Just in case.
There are many Norse gods who do not approve of their chief god Odin's alliance with the devils.
It seems there are always people like that in every group.
The problem is that the Khaos Brigade is recruiting those people.
We are to wait in this room until the ceremony begins.
The other young devils are here, too.
I hope nothing bad happens.
Me too.
It looks like you really want to die, Zephyrdor.
You stink like a virgin! I merely stated the truth!
You bitch!
What's going on?
A fight?
I knew this would happen.
When young devils gather, this tends to occur.
Sairaorg.
Let's exchange pleasantries later.
Stop fighting, you two.
Princess of the Agares family, Seekvaira.
Problem child of the
Glasya-Labolas family, Zephyrdor.
Who you callin' a problem child?! Watch your mouth, or I'll—
I know it's sudden, but this is your last warning.
Any more, and you'll have to deal with me.
You incompetent Bael retard!
Are you all right?
Ah, yes.
A-Amazing!
He is the next leader of the Bael family, Sairaorg.
He is my cousin.
Seriously...
I see.
So that's how he knew about Riser and me.
Also, he's number one amongst the young devils.
I-It has been a while, Red Dragon Emperor.
You're the little sister of that fried chicken!
My name is Ravel Phenex!
This is why I hate low-class devils!
How's your brother doing?
He's out for the count because of you.
Well, it's his fault for getting so big-headed about his abilities,
so I'm sure it was a good lesson for him.
You're tough on him.
Aren't you a part of his peerage?
After that, I was traded to my Mother's peerage.
Since Mother doesn't enter any games, I'm a free bishop.
Free? There's such a thing?
Also...
This is a symbol of our friendship.
I couldn't accept a gift like this from you.
This is normally a gift for a high-class devil, you know?
Red Dragon Emperor,
you're just a low-class devil,
so you should accept it gratefully, like a gentleman.
Can you stop calling me Red Dragon Emperor?
I have a name. Just call me "Issei".
Th-Then, I'll take the liberty of calling you "Issei-sama".
Do you have to?
Then, Issei-sama,
I will be more than happy to treat you to
some refreshments the next time we meet.
L-Lately, I've been baking my own cakes.
W-Well, then! I must greet the others, so I shall take my leave!
Farewell!
H-Hey!
She's harder to follow than Xenovia!
Koneko-chan?
Koneko-chan!
She's going down.
Which floor?
President?!
What's wrong? You look troubled.
Koneko-chan suddenly ran out of the room.
It was like she was chasing something.
I don't want to make a big deal out of this.
Let's look for her together.
Good work.
My familiar found her.
I'm sure I felt it—that presence.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
As I thought.
Hello, Shirone.
Kuroka-neesama...
sou daitai no koto nante
Well, yeah, I do think that
mou wakatte wa iru na tte
I've got this stuff mostly figured out
omou yo dakedo ne
But still, you know
kokoro wa bannou ja nai
Feelings on their own can only get you so far
daiji na kotoba ga ishin fudenshin
We're not using the right words
saishuuteki ni wa analog tsuushin
So we have to rely on analog communication
dakara ima sugu
That's why, right now
motto chanto katachi ni shite yo
I want you to be more concrete
kimi ga
Do it
ijiwaru na
Stop teasing me
give me kikasete yo
Give me, just tell me
chotto dake de ii no
Just a little hint is fine
aimai na no wa yada na
Don't leave me hanging
no secret sansei
No secrets, yeah?
answer todokete ne
Give me your answer
kowaku nante nai shi
I'm not afraid to hear it
iwanai kedo nee wakaru desho
I don't have to actually tell you, right?
wakatte yo
Take the hint
tell me how tell me how
Tell me how, tell me how
subete wo kaeru no wa
If you want to take it to the next step
give me one give me one
Give me one, give me one
itsu de mo kimi dakara
The power is in your hands
Next Episode:
It's been a long time.
We'll never hand over Koneko-chan!
Right, Kuroka?
Your big sister is really moved.
Please let me poke your boobs!
You're the worst.
Episode
Cat and Dragon
I am part of Rias Gremory-sama's peerage!