Gin.
I've woken you.
Excuse my impoliteness.
The dream you drew for us...
To leave this dirty country and raise
a flag of justice on foreign soil.
We'd eventually call in members of
the clan and take on the city of villains.
That was quite attractive.
We've learned from experience...
...how much those Russian soldiers
are capable of.
I will cut a path through them
until I reach Balalaika...
...then challenge her one on one.
She is undoubtedly worthy
of this white sheath.
I've come this far with you, Gin.
So I'll be with you from
now on as well.
Even to Roanapur?
Yes.
Good work.
Thanks to you, our job here will
end without incident.
My work here is done.
Someone from Moscow will
take over from here.
It's a shame I won't get
to see the aftermath.
It really is a shame.
Hey Ishiguro.
About those three that came here.
- Huh? What about them?
- What do you mean, "huh?"
The two Caucasians and
one Japanese that came here.
Did you check into them?
I'm having someone check
the ICPO data, but nothing...
What's happening with the request to
have an international specialist on it?
Right. Someone named Kouno is
supposed to be on his way here.
That white woman is definitely
involved in the conflict...
...between the Washimine
Clan and the Kousa Clan.
She may even have something...
...to do with the shooting incident at
the bowling center in Adachi. Listen.
In any case, don't you
take your eyes off of them.
What is it?
What do you mean?
You're the one who looks like
you have something to say.
Was it my imagination?
- Miss Balalaika.
- Rock...
...is this about what we
talked about last time?
I've already spared your life.
Is there something else
you desire?
If it were possible.
I'll listen, but that's all.
One thing. Just let me
say one thing.
If everything is about to settle down,
then before that...
I'd like you to completely
crush the Washimine Clan!
To the point that the group will
no longer be able to survive.
Wipe them out completely so not a
single withered tree remains standing.
It's the only way to free her.
I... see... your... point.
I see. I see. Indeed.
That certainly is the only way to push
the princess back into a normal life.
You're a villain, Rock.
That is the correct decision.
You'll become a good villain.
Please forgive my delay.
I'm certain you must be exhausted
from these long discussions.
Please don't worry about it.
This accomplishes one
of our goals as well.
Let's wipe the slate clean
and move forward.
Mr. Kousa.
We must prepare plans over
who will succeed us in the future.
If certain contingencies
should occur in our absence...
...it will be difficult for us
to respond properly.
I wish to know your
state of readiness over firearms.
Is it adequate?
Well, ah...
I can't say it too loud...
...but compared to other clans,
we have many more guns by far.
We've even bought a machine
gun from the guys in Hawaii.
Would you oblige me?
Morozumi.
I'd like to see the bullets as well.
I see. Quite the competent
body guard you have.
Do you have any backup
means of protection?
Boss...
There'd be no profit in having a shootout
at this point in our discussions.
I don't want any trouble later.
Hand it to her.
What is this?
Absolutely atrocious!
Keep up with me, okay, Rock?
Th-This is a terrible gun.
Take a look, sergeant.
Atrocious, isn't it?
This is simply terrible.
I doubt if even low life punks in
the gutter would use guns like this.
Absolutely atrocious.
What a hideous gun.
Have you ever stopped to consider?
What it would feel like to
be shot with a gun like this?
That's it.
I can't work with scum
who shamelessly...
...sport shoddy guns like this.
Mr. Yasuda! Gun shots! Go in!
Enter the premises!
Open up! Open this door!
Open up! If you don't open this door,
we'll force our way in!
Oh? This gun isn't all that bad.
Sergeant, how are we for time?
It's not a problem, Captain.
But how do we explain this to the boss?
Pyotr told me to start a war
and burn it all to ashes.
I simply followed
orders obediently. Rock.
This is your gun.
Wanna take it as a souvenir?
I don't like guns.
And I don't carry things I'm
not accustomed to. However...
I will not forget that I
pulled this trigger.
I'm returning this to you.
Sergeant, throw that gun away here
as well. We're returning to base.
Everyone on the
premises! Nobody move!
This is Yasuzawa of
department four!
I am Ishiguro of department one.
I'm in charge of this case.
I'd like to ask a few questions about
the gun shots we just heard.
Please come with us.
- How are we doing?
- Right on time.
Rock, give this message
to the Washimine girl.
Hotel Moscow will cease all
attacks as of this moment.
The Washimine Clan you
seek to destroy...
...has already
dispersed underground.
That girl thinks more
flexibly than you imagine.
According to the information
Bulgaziviri gathered...
...their clan members believe that
their princess will eventually...
...invite them to Roanapur
to raise their flag.
Of all places,
she chose Roanapur.
My ride will be arriving.
Make way, civilian policemen!
Hey! I'm not done talking.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The ambassador is waiting
at Mamiana, Miss Vladilena.
Hey wait!
You can't, Mr. Yasuda.
It's a diplomatic number.
Rock!
- Hey!
- Wait!
Get him!
Calm down!
We're the ones you want to talk to.
Don't be so easily distracted
by the small fry.
Farewell Mr. Civilian Cop.
If you ever need to reach me,
please contact...
...V.N. Valezhnov, First Secretary,
Embassy of the Russian Federation.
Visit me whenever you wish.
- Excuse me.
- Hey!
Damn it! I didn't make it in time!
Who are you?
I'm Kouno with international
investigations.
Why didn't you arrest them,
if you witnessed gun shots?
It occurred within the premises,
so it was only based on assumption.
So who was she? Did you find out?
She's an incredible big shot.
There's a mafia group
called Hotel Moscow...
...who have their headquarters
in Moscow...
...as well as a powerful presence in
places like Chechnya and New York.
She's known as "Balalaika".
She's a high ranking
officer of Hotel Moscow!
What?
Damn it!
Emergency! Crime
scene to headquarters!
Send an urgent message to
all patrol cars in the area!
Did we get a picture of her face?
A description of her appearance?
Nothing.
Then put together a
profile or something.
We'll at least find out who
her Japanese contacts are!
Revy! We need to tell her
that the war's over!
You're outta your mind!
In just over thirty minutes this
area is going to be quarantined!
You're not gonna see her!
We don't have time.
Contact them from the ship.
We're close to departure time!
But!
Mr. Okajima.
Y-Yukio?
Please escort us
to the Marya Zeleska.
Miss.
Damn it! I can't believe it! He's even
been kidnapped by a high school girl!
You drive too?
Well I'm a delinquent, aren't I?
Yukio, what's with the talk
about taking over Roanapur?
I'm standing in the twilight,
just like you say.
But there are some things
I can see because of that.
Doesn't it sound like fun?
Hotel Moscow has announced
an end to fighting! It's over!
What kind of promise is
Balalaika's word?
Yukio.
How can anyone trust
that rabid dog...
...who has broken all promises,
betrayed us, and spit on faith.
Hey! Hey! This is a hold up!
Don't you understand?
If I could honestly believe that
I'd be able to rebuild...
...the clan in Roanapur...
...that would have been wonderful.
But it was just a passing wish.
As long as Gin and I are here,
Washimine and its emblem exists.
- It has not fallen to earth.
- So you're coming back to that again.
I was born into the side of the
night, and grew up with the night.
Sure, I have enjoyed pretending
I was meant to lead a normal life.
Bottom line, this is the path of reality.
I have no value as a hostage
against Hotel Moscow.
Then we'll use you
as a shield. Or...
...I'll have you witness where this
all-or-nothing decision is headed.
There's nothing but a
massacre waiting for you!
But there is a flower that
may bloom there.
Have you forgotten?
We are Yakuza.
Damn it!
Gentlemen, our operation is
complete. Let us return to Roanapur.
Miss.
I'm not letting you get away!
We cannot be the ones to hit
the brakes first in this battle.
Knock it off!
Rock! I told you!
She's already the walking dead.
Revy!
I hear that the Kousa Council
has been dissolved...
...as a result of an internal dispute.
However, the one who betrayed
and slaughtered Tsugio Bando...
...our clan's leader, still lives.
She is Balalaika, the head
of our enemy, Hotel Moscow.
We pride ourselves in living
with honor, seeing justice through...
...and rewarding honor.
There is no duty that you must be
bound to! That's simply a front!
Please allow us to pass.
Gin.
Mr. Gin is no longer with you.
I shouldn't have brought
the Miss here.
We're all the same. No matter
how far we go, we're not normal.
This is a place where only
those like us should be...
...don't you agree, Lady?
There was an option
that you could've taken...
...that would've allowed you to avoid
taking the same path as Miss Balalaika.
I assumed you would choose that.
That's where I was wrong.
You're not here to save
face as Yakuza.
You struggled against being
absorbed into the night, that's why.
There are things that I can see
because I stand here in the twilight.
You should've forced Gin to throw
away his sword...
...and run away with him.
And become wanderers together...
...seek a far away land,
and open some shop.
That's a joke as well.
It's no joke!
Where is the real you?!
Sure. I often wondered,
"What if I were able to live like that?"
But I had already thrown my dice.
I kept thinking how great it would be
if life in Takamachi would last forever.
With musical bands, all the
stores, and you by my side...
...it's bound to be enjoyable.
Too late. You were too damn late.
You know that the only place we'll
end up is in a coffin of mud.
But you tried to live.
I screwed up.
Revy! Revy!
I'm all right. Damn. I'm seeing black.
Those words you made her say.
That was the real bullet.
If it weren't for that,
I'd be the one on the ground.
Don't talk! This is gonna hurt.
You'll have to withstand it.
Raise your leg Revy!
I'm gonna rewrap it!
Why?
Why did it have to come to this?
Where you became distorted...
...is when you lied to
yourself that you wanted this.
You were too smart to fool yourself.
Eleven...
That's the number of people...
...who have been killed
under my orders...
...since that night I threw the dice.
Our city is filled with people
who live their life like that!
Now that I've woken up,
that land is too far away for me.
I apologize for having troubled you.
As of this moment...
I will bring everything to an end.
Don't look at her, Rock!
It'll scar you!
Is that you, Rock? I feel like I haven't
seen you in ten thousand years.
How'd you like that fake
Chinese-Canadian passport I got you?
It came in handy, didn't it?
Dutch.
Yeah, I heard.
"People are like dice,
we throw ourselves into life."
Do you know about the
Frenchman who said that?
Jean-Paul Sartre.
An existentialist philosopher.
But the phrase,
"Quickly put a hole in a guy...
...who tries to put five eggs
into three baskets"...
...hits closer to home for me.
Yeah, I hear you.
There's work waiting for you
as soon as you get back.
They want us to deliver a pile of guns
to Tsanwi by the day after tomorrow.
All right then. Later.
It's time for our flight, partner.
From Miss Balalaika to you.
This city, Roanapur...
You've got the power of guns
and the power of liquor.
A wonderful place
where you can...
...blow away everything
with barbaric power.
It's not such a bad place.
That's what I'm beginning to think.
Yeah, it's not bad.
I plan to see everything that
goes on here, from the twilight.
All right. Let's go then.
Into our city.
So? How was Japan?
Well, Balalaika was there and we
were there. It's the same anywhere.
What are you talking about?
I'm asking about Rock!
You two were away together for so long.
You did do it this time, right?
- I don't wanna say.
- Huh?
When it comes to you.
Why don't you just die?
We villains don't die so easily.
Bang.