My name is Hyoudou Issei.
I'm a high school sophomore aiming
to become the Harem King!
However, I am NOT your
average high school student.
That's because I am actually a devil.
No, really. It's the truth.
By a strange turn of events,
I was reincarnated as a devil.
I became family to President Rias,
who I greatly admired…
...and I enjoyed a happy youth
with my many comrades
and the legendary
Red Dragon Emperor inside of me.
One peaceful day, as we were
nearing the sports festival,
a suitor wanting Asia's hand
in marriage appeared.
It was the upper-class devil, Diodora Astaroth.
No matter how handsome he was
and how good his family was,
I would never accept him!
I could never accept anyone who'd step on
Asia's feelings and forcefully make her his!
Consumed with anger, I was able
to defeat Diodora and save Asia.
Issei!
Yes. Please allow me to pray before we go.
What are you going to pray about?
That's a secret.
Asia?
Who's there?!
Nice to meet you.
The little sister of the fake Devil King.
My name is Shalba Beelzebub.
I am the true descendant of
the Great Devil Beelzebub.
Beelzebub?!
Help me, Shalba!
That's right.
If both the old and current devil kings
combine their strength...
Shalba, you...
Fool.
How dare you align yourself with me.
Little sister of Sir Zechs.
This is sudden, but I will have you, relative of
the current devil king, die here as well.
The reason you murdered Astaroth
and the Glasya-Labolas heir...
You planned this all along.
And you even involved Asia!
Asia?
Where did you go? Come on, we're going home.
Issei...
Let's go home, Asia.
We're doing the three-legged
race in the sports festival.
We need to practice.
Issei!
President, Asia isn't here.
We have to find her quickly.
She's my... She's our treasured family!
Issei.
Truly, the princess of the
Gremory household has bad taste.
You, red filth.
Give up.
I sent that girl far beyond the dimensions.
She has taken her last breath by now.
In other words, she is dead.
life.00
「Holiness Behind the Gym」
Hey, devil. You called yourself Shalba?
You made the wrong choice.
Issei!
I, who shall awaken...
It started.
Looks like it's going to start.
...am the Heavenly Dragon who stole
the principle of domination from God.
It has always been like this.
Right you are. It's always been so.
I laugh at the infinite and fret over the dream.
What the world desires...
What the world rejects...
I shall become the Red Dragon of Domination.
...has always been power.
...has always been love.
I shall drown you in the
depths of crimson purgatory.
What... is this?!
This amount of aura and power!
Dangerous.
Asia!
Juggernaut Drive!
Issei...
Bastard!
Don't joke around!
Divide! Divide! Divide! Divide! Divide! Divide!
Vali's power?!
Just how much do you plan to stand in my way?!
Issei...
President!
President, that isn't Issei anymore.
You monster! So, this is the Juggernaut Drive?!
I cannot die in a place like this!
My legs won't move...
The power of Gasper's Sacred Gear?
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
This is bad. If we stay here, we'll also...
Let's retreat for now!
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
But...
Rias!
I'm sorry, President!
Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost! Boost!
Impossible. I am the descendant
of the true devil king...
By a mere dragon...
Longinus Smasher!
Damn you! Red Dragon! White Dragon!
Where is Issei?
Issei...
Why?
Even though he defeated Shalba,
he isn't reverting back...
Looks like you're in a bit of trouble.
Vali?!
I only came to observe.
To see the Juggernaut Drive
of the Red Dragon Emperor.
Also...
Asia?!
Isn't she part of your family?
This little healer.
We happened to come across her while we
were moving through the Dimensional Gap.
Don't worry. She's alive.
Asia! Asia!
However, it looks like Hyoudou Issei
had an incomplete transformation.
No way...
Is there a way to change him back to normal?
Who knows. If he can't revert himself back,
he will continue to use his
life force until he dies.
--If we tell him that Asia is safe...
--Asia... Asia...
That's pointless.
Just approaching him will kill you.
I won't stop you, though.
I know that it's not our place to ask...
Please, lend us your strength!
We will do anything that we can.
So please lend us your strength to save Issei!
If we could give the depths
of his psyche a good shake...
Depths of his psyche...
A good shake...
I guess...
We just need to show him some boobs?
Either way, we can't reach him in that state.
Then, what should we do?!
Song is said to calm the anger
of a dragon since ancient times,
but I've never heard such a tune.
Song?
It exists!
Isn't that...
Shidou... Irina?
Whoa! This is worse than I expected!
Shidou, why are you here?
The bigwigs all have a pretty
good idea of what's going on.
Things looked pretty bad.
So Devil King Lucifer and Azazel
had me bring in a secret weapon!
And Lord Odin was able to
transport something this big!
The God of the North is amazing!
What a bushy beard!
And, there.
Here we go!
Boob Dragon!
It's starting!
Boobs!
The Boob Dragon Song
Lyrics by Azazel
Music by Sir Zechs Lucifer
Choreography by Serafall Leviathan
In the corner of a certain land
there lives a boob-loving dragon
When it's nice out, he takes
a walk in search of boobs
Dragon dragon Boob Dragon
Squish suck squeeze
There are all kinds of boobs out there
What the hell is this?
but big ones are definitely the best
The best!
The Boob Dragon flies again today
In the corner of a certain town
In the past, Issei was summoned
alone to the television station.
the boob-loving dragon smiles
He recorded this song for a kid show.
Even when it's stormy out,
poking boobs cheers him up
Even so, the lyrics and music...
The Boob Dragon Song
Lyrics by Azazel
Music by Sir Zechs Lucifer
Choreography by Serafall Leviathan
I can't believe they made
this for a time like this.
Dragon dragon Boob Dragon
This is terrible.
Boop poke aaaa
He's seen so many boobs out there
He's reacting!
He's reacting to a song like this.
but big ones are definitely the best
Shidou, please continue playing the song.
The Boob Dragon pokes again today
Yes, ma'am! Leave it to me!
Boobs...
I, who shall awaken,
am the Heavenly Dragon who has
lost all to the principle of domination.
I envy the infinite and yearn for the dream.
I shall become the White Dragon of Supremacy
I shall take you to the
limits of a white paradise.
Can you do it?
Vanishing Dragon Balance Breaker
In the corner of a certain land
there lives a boob-loving dragon
Divide! Divide! Divide! Divide! Divide!
When it's nice out, he takes
a walk in search of boobs
Dragon dragon Boob Dragon
Squish suck squeeze
There are all kinds of boobs out there
Now, Rias! The only one
who can save Issei is you.
but big ones are definitely the best
He is yearning for your breasts!
What?!
The Boob Dragon flies again today
Issei grabbed your breasts and
achieved Balance Breaker.
In the corner of a certain town
Then, it should be able to
do the opposite as well.
That is the only way he can be saved.
the boob-loving dragon smiles
But...
Even when it's stormy out,
poking boobs cheers him up
Your breasts can do it, Rias.
It's frustrating, but you fit this
role better than anyone else.
Dragon dragon Boob Dragon
Boop poke aaaa
He's seen so many boobs out there
Squeeze... Squeeze...
but big ones are definitely the best
Seriously?!
As I thought.
Yeah, all we can do is laugh.
Issei, he's really...
The Boob Dragon pokes again today
No... Poke.
In the corner of a certain land
I understand...
there lives a boob-loving dragon
When it's nice out, he takes
a walk in search of boobs
Boobies!
Dragon dragon Boob Dragon
Squish suck squeeze
Boobs...
There are all kinds of boobs out there
but big ones are definitely the best
If Issei will come back to us with this...
The Boob Dragon flies again today
In the corner of a certain town
the boob-loving dragon smiles
Even when it's stormy out,
poking boobs cheers him up
Boobies...
Dragon dragon Boob Dragon
Boop poke aaaa
Noo!
He's seen so many boobs out there
but big ones are definitely the best
The Boob Dragon pokes again today
Are Rias Gremory's breasts a
limit switch for Hyoudou Issei?
No way!
Issei, you are already a
full-fledged Boob Dragon.
President?
Thank goodness.
Asia. Asia?
Asia!
Issei?
Are you all right? Thank goodness...
Asia!
We'll be friends forever!
So don't leave me behind ever again!
Yes. We'll always be friends.
Let's stay together forever.
Looks like I caused you a lot of trouble.
Well, I don't mind it every once in a while.
More importantly...
Look well, Hyoudou Issei.
That's what I wanted to see.
What is that?
It is the Apocalypse Dragon,
written in the Revelation, Great Red.
He is considered to be a true dragon.
Dragon of Dragon.
I will defeat him one day and become
the true White Dragon God Emperor.
That's your dream...
Great Red. It has been a while.
Who is that?!
Orphis. The Ouroboros Dragon.
She is also the leader of the Chaos Brigade.
Seriously?!
Someday, I will definitely obtain silence.
Hey, Issei.
Looks like you're back to normal.
Azazel. Old man!
I knew you would definitely
come back to us with that.
It was worth writing the lyrics.
No, I think you went too far!
Just so you know, it was Sir Zechs idea.
Hyoudou Issei! Do you want to defeat me?
I do. But, the person I want
to surpass isn't just you.
There's still Kiba and Saji...
There are a lot of people!
Me, too.
It's strange to have many goals and
dreams more valuable than our fated battle,
but we are probably unusual
vessels this time around.
You're probably right.
But, someday...
Yeah, let's settle things!
I can’t have Akeno and the
presidents boobs split up!
Get strong, Hyoudou Issei.
See ya later, Boob Dragon!
The switch princess, too.
Sorry. I promised that I would
protect you, no matter what.
Asia, let's go back for real. Back to our home.
Yes!
Issei!
Shalba has fallen.
Vali won't stand at the top, either.
Should the Hero Faction make a move soon?
No.
We'll have to make a move sooner or later.
The all-powerful Sacred Gear
within you will urge you to.
The True Longinus, huh?
Will this spear lead me to domination? Or...
Next is the three-legged race.
All runners, please gather at the start line.
Asia!
Issei, you came.
Of course. I always keep
my promises with you, Asia.
Hey, hey. You don't need to cry.
I’m so happy, I couldn’t help it…
Next in line, please be ready.
Okay! We're going to get first place!
Yes!
Asia, stay with me forever.
Don't leave me ever again.
Yes!
Issei! Asia!
--Try your best!
--We got first place! All right!
We did it! We did it, Asia!
Yes! We did, Issei!
Asia, please heal him with your Sacred Gear.
You won't be seen behind the gym.
Yes!
Issei, please lean on me.
Sorry.
Asia, try your best.
Thanks, Asia. I feel a lot better.
I'll be able to participate in
the rest of the events now.
Issei, I wasn't able to say this because
you were sleeping the whole time.
A-Asia?
Issei, I love you!
I will always be by your side.
Issei?!
I will love you forever, Issei.
Next time
life.01
「That's Right, Let's Go to Kyoto」
That's Right, Let's Go to Kyoto!