Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
The attacks by the Gundams
sent by the Space Colonies...
...reflected the colonies'
retaliatory intentions.
OZ has masked its identity
in the Alliance Military...
...and the Gundams' mission
is to attack them.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite soldiers
at his command...
...Treize Khushrenada has begun to
wipe out the Alliance Military.
The battle between OZ and the
mobile suits sent to Earth...
...causes serious repercussions
on the Earth.
Yeah and I think it'll be
a big hit with the soldiers.
Wow!
Trowa's usually so quiet,
so it must be a good idea.
There's nothing wrong with
acting on your emotions.
Least that's what I was taught.
Yeah. It'll be my last...
...grandstand show.
Catherine's Tears
Prepare to drop the Tallgeese.
Colonel Zechs.
There's turbulence in the area
where we're making the drop.
Please be careful.
Tallgeese gauges in order.
Ready for drop.
Exit in ten seconds.
Starting countdown. 5... 4... 3...
2... 1...
...Exit!
Colonel Zechs, you can be
picked up on the radar now.
We can locate you.
Colonel Zechs?
Colonel Zechs, are you
all right?!
Yes, I read you.
Commencing tests.
Colonel Zechs, anti-aircraft
missiles are ready!
They're locked on the Tallgeese!
Roger! Fire them!
Are you sure?!
That's what this mobile
suit is demanding!
The Tallgeese is speeding up!
All right!
- Fire anti-aircraft missiles!
- Sir!
Colonel Zechs has conquered
that Tallgeese monster!
You've mastered it.
The super vernier engine seems
different from the blueprint.
If we went by the
blueprint output...
...its operations would be
seriously affected.
Doesn't matter.
It's up to the pilot to overcome
such operating difficulties.
Yes, sir.
Fire fighters! On the double!
Rescue the injured!
This is Red Cancer.
I've crossed the defense line.
Proceeding to front-line base.
Blue Angel here. Roger.
Watch your back, Alex!
I won't let my guard down!
Our advance guard's destroyed!
How many enemies?!
Model signal confirmed!
One OZ Cancer and one Aries!
You're kidding! Only two?!
Our mobile troops are
destroyed!
Enemy mobile suits are unharmed!
The motley troops we put together...
...are no match for OZ's
mobile suits.
We're disarming our front-line
base as we speak.
We're preparing to surrender
so take appropriate actions.
Surrendering?
I think you misunderstand.
This is an execution!
No! Don't fire on us!
You poor relics from the past,
let this new age baptize you!
Stop!
You're not starting a war!
It's a massacre!
We told you.
It's an execution!
You're laughing too much,
Muller.
Lake Victoria.
This brings back memories.
I wonder how Instructor
Noin's doing?
We'll always be children
in her eyes.
The least we could do is
show her our improved skills.
Lieutenant Alex!
We've got Victoria base
on the line.
Good!
This is Alex of the No. 33
Independent Troops...
...of the Northeast Africa
Somalia front!
Isn't Lieutenant Noin there?
Lieutenant-Colonel Noin is
on a mission in Moscow.
Moscow?
With Colonel Une?
No, the Lieutenant's trip
is unrelated.
Fine.
We'll still attack the former
Alliance's Mogadishu Fortress.
We need to pick up supplies.
We're coming in to land.
You have no soldiers with
combat experience?!
When did this base become
a repair shop for old suits?
Lieutenant Noin approved it.
Are you sure?
Didn't Colonel Zechs twist
her arm or something?
I heard her trip to Moscow
concerns Colonel Zechs, too.
That's partly true.
But Lieutenant Noin planned
this trip on her own.
Think she'd do anything for
a killer of his own men?!
Everyone here would do what
they could for Colonel Zechs.
You fool!
We only follow His Excellency,
Treize Khushrenada!
Lieutenant Noin taught us to
make only His ideals a reality.
That's enough, Muller.
We can't change their minds.
But...
We can still request soldiers.
I already explained.
We don't have experienced
soldiers here.
You do have one...
An elite soldier by the name
of Zechs Marquise.
We can determine the
combat skills of the pilot...
...by matching this data to
the Zero One's capacities...
...as we can judge from
its remains.
What do the remains tell you?
It's completely destroyed.
Zero One's self-detonation device
couldn't have worked better.
Could the pilot have survived?
Doubt it.
- This can't be!
- What is it?
It says this pilot wasn't human.
I must've input something
incorrectly.
What do the results say?
Response speed was unusual.
Physical strength and G-force
endurance, too.
I heard that the pilot was
still a boy.
These figures are unthinkable!
Not surprising.
He must've had special
training courses in outer space.
But these results undermine any
psychological advantages I had.
I thought our differences lay
only in our suits' capabilities.
Perhaps that pilot can realize
the Tallgeese's full capacity.
Impressive piece of work!
Didn't know you had
a taste for antiques, Colonel.
You're not really expecting to
use this in combat, are you?
In fact I've already used it.
I heard a nasty rumor that
Zero One self-detonated in Siberia.
It also attacked the Sanc
Kingdom in Northern Europe.
I bet the pilot who
died in it...
...would've preferred something
a little less antiquated.
What're you getting at?
We're attacking the
Mogadishu Fortress...
...of the former Alliance,
tomorrow.
But our mobile suit troops
alone aren't enough.
We wanted to get help from
some soldiers at this base.
Fine.
I'll go on the Tallgeese.
As your subordinate.
As our subordinate, Colonel?
What's your problem?
You head the front-line
battles of Somalia, right?
Then here are your first
orders, Colonel Zechs.
Prepare to leave at 0400 hours
tomorrow on the Tallgeese.
This is Red Cancer, taking off!
Don't let them see us.
They'll fire the Noventa cannon
the Alliance is so proud of.
Yes, sir!
Aries troops all prepared
for take off.
Lieutenant Muller.
What is it?!
Won't you need to use some
debris against the radar?
No.
But the enemy will detect us.
Don't worry.
They'll detect Zechs' mobile
suit long before they find us.
Are you using Colonel Zechs
as a decoy?
The enemy will point their
Noventa cannon inland.
That's the plan's objective.
I understand.
Now let's see the Lightning
Count's true abilities.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
We're at our drop-off point.
Roger; drop the Tallgeese.
Colonel Zechs.
What?
Message from Red Cancer.
"Good luck on your mission."
I won't need any luck.
Releasing the Tallgeese!
Enemy detected.
It's headed directly for us,
from the inland.
OZ has come all the way out
to these remote regions.
Use the Noventa cannon and
don't let them get any closer.
Target detected!
Height and angle confirmed!
On standby to fire!
Fire the Noventa cannon!
High pressure explosives
strike confirmed!
What?!
Energy mass approaching
from 6 o'clock!
Headed for the Leo troops!
The enemy hasn't been shot down!
Let's try out the modified
super vernier engine.
What's wrong?
Why aren't you firing
the Noventa cannon?
The enemy's mobile suit is
so fast we can't lock onto it!
More enemies!
They're attacking from the sea!
I never realized this fortress
was so fragile!
Enemy mobile suit transmission!
I'll connect him!
I'm Colonel Zechs, from the
No. 33 Independent Troops.
You've lost your defensive
advantage.
Any further battle would
be meaningless.
We demand that you disarm
your weapons at once.
That's what the peace-minded
Noventa would've wanted.
All our mobile suits have
been defeated...
...and the No. 5 block
has been annihilated!
All right, we'll surrender.
Alex! Muller!
What are you doing?!
Stop your assault!
They've already surrendered!
Colonel Zechs.
You're overstepping your
authority.
You can leave everything
to us from now on.
Including the execution of
these former Alliance members.
Execution?!
These fools continually
opposed the changing era.
It's up to us to correct
this stagnation.
So, it's an official punishment.
Punishment!!
Damn you, OZ!
No one stands a chance against
your cruel and immoral methods!
I've hit the command tower!
Going in for a second attack!
Stop this!
How dare you call
yourselves OZ soldiers!
You should be ashamed.
Your conceit is appalling!
Even vulgar!
Lieutenant Muller!
Colonel Zechs is telling me
to stop the attack!
Die, OZ!
Zechs!!
You killed a comrade!
It's your fault!
He died because of you!
Die!!
What?!
Damn you!
Looks like you underestimated
my suit.
My next shot will finish
you off for certain!
Say your prayers!
Blast; where'd he go?!
Your skills are impressive.
But for one of Noin's students,
you lack intelligence.
You scum!
Don't talk to me about her!
Has this era made him insane?
You're so darn perfect!
These men have no right
to be given any power!
Fools!
The vernier engine is
working beautifully.
Thanks very much.
What's this?
A report regarding
Alex and Muller.
I'd like you to send it to
Lieutenant Noin for me.
Lieutenant Noin?
Tell her to reflect on the error
of teaching merely techniques.
W-Wait...
Wars are heartless.
Wars truly are heartless indeed.
But I'm recreating a mobile suit
from an enemy suit's remains.
So as a soldier, that makes
me no better than them.
That carrier's transporting
enough fuel for 20 shuttles.
So OZ has started to position
their space army for conquest.
Allow me to present our
new performance!
Introducing the rising star
of our circus, Trowa Barton!
Hey, isn't that a Gundam?
A mobile suit!
Trowa?!
That's a good looking suit!
For sure!
He's scaring me.
That Trowa...
What on earth has
he got planned?
Wow! This is gonna be the best!
A show like this would bring
the house down anywhere!
Now for my self-detonation
show.
Trowa...
Run for it!
Next I'll destroy the
storage tank.
This is my last battle.
No worry about running
out of bullets.
Trowa, what's going on?!
What's gotten into you?!
You're planning to die!
This is the end.
Trowa!
What are you doing?!
Catherine, stay away.
I'm self-detonating with
this mobile suit.
Say what?!
Come down here and talk!
Come on, hurry!
Catherine!
Stay away, Catherine.
I've got to self-detonate.
Trowa?
Trowa!
Don't you think your life's
too valuable for that?!
Self-detonate?
What are you thinking?!
What would your parents think
of such a selfish decision?!
Did you give a thought to the
people you'd leave behind?
You're the most pathetic
person I've ever met!
You didn't think about us...
the people you'd leave behind...
We'd have to live in sorrow.
You're the one that brainwashed
Trowa with your strange ideas!
You won't get off so easy
next time!
Her tears stopped me.
If you were in my shoes
you would've done it, right?
That's why I admire
your strength.
I said this before.
The way to live a good life
is to act on your emotions.
Let's get going.
Yeah.
Sorry to see him leave.
He really was pretty good.
He could've been the
best in the business.
What're you saying?
You've gotta let kids go
if you want them to grow up.
We raised Trowa in this circus;
he'll come back one day!
He'll come back for sure.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Heero tries to make up
for his mistake...
...of killing Noventa,
pacifist of the former Alliance.
Within the war zones
created by OZ...
...Heero confronts Sylvia,
Noventa's granddaughter.
How can he compensate
for his wrong-doing?
Zechs is handed an order
from the Romefeller Foundation.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 14,
The Order to Destroy 01
"The Order to Destroy 01".