I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Roanapur. In this city, gangs from
around the world fight for territory.
It's a strange balancing game.
This is a terrible tragedy.
The exterior of the building
no longer has shape or form.
What we know so far is that...
...37 embassy employees
have been killed and 150 wounded.
The Zaire military is currently
continuing with its rescue efforts.
Right after the bombing, a terrorist
organization calling themselves...
...the Protectors of the Islamic Front...
This sure is a dirty room.
...claimed responsibility for the attack.
Revy, are you awake?
We have a job.
Dutch says it's an emergency. Revy!
Is that you, Rock?
Yeah. It's a big,
last minute request.
He told me to hurry and wake you up,
so I flew down here from the office.
Damn it.
Who's this job for?
Mr. Chang.
From the Triad.
I've been waiting
for a while now.
Doesn't this shop even offer a cup
of coffee? You call this service, Dutch?
Well... I never knew
we were running a café.
You know why we have a torpedo boat,
don't you, Mr. Chang?
Such cold words, Dutch.
We were burned out of our place
and came straight here.
Isn't it common courtesy
to at least offer a cup of tea?
That sure was a tragedy,
Mr. Chang.
Did I hear right, that half
of your office has collapsed?
Yeah, we got hit hard.
Was it the Russians?
Of course not.
We're always very friendly with
Miss Balalaika. Hey, Two Hands.
Did I miss a lot?
No, we're just about to get started.
This is the cause of everything.
But it's certainly worth it.
I took this from a stupid Bulgarian...
...who tried to make a quick buck
in my territory.
I don't recall giving permission
to anyone to sell weapons...
...other than old Yolanda
from the Ripoff Church.
But this guy clearly misunderstood.
He was casually selling guns on the
street as if he was selling hot shrimp.
To make matters worse, he mistook
my warnings for some crazy joke.
He finally understood
and made a deal with us...
...when we were about to crush
his balls like nuts.
The guy was a real idiot, but it turns out
he had an interesting job.
Oh?
He worked for
Bulgarian Intelligence, Dutch.
This city is a comfortable place
for folks like that, too.
Normally a guy like that
is very useful, but...
This time his playing
with fire cost him.
You know what he offered us
to save his balls, Dutch?
Documents.
Oh?
The hiking charts of a certain
amusing little group.
The job they did just before us
has been on TV all morning.
The U.S. Embassy!
I smell danger.
The "ball boy's" real job
was with them.
The world's full of folks
who want Uncle Sam to disappear.
I told one of those groups
that they dropped something.
But as soon as I quoted the guys
what it would cost them...
...they told me to get the hell out of
there before my ass becomes roast.
And this is how I answered.
"All right, then I'll go elsewhere."
Thanks to that, my office
has been blasted all the way...
...to somewhere around Jordan...
...and as they predicted, my ass
nearly became roast before I got here.
Those guys are really not much fun.
So, Dutch. Here's the deal.
I want you to deliver this.
Five teams will leave Roanapur
at the same time...
...each heading
to a different destination.
There are five cases,
but only one bingo.
- A feint.
- As insurance, of course.
Your goal is the local base on Basilan
Island. The time limit is two days.
After that, my company
will have left Basilan.
Chang, my man,
two days doesn't give us enough time.
It's always going to be too soon.
Last night's embassy bombing
was the beginning of a chain.
In two days the next schedule starts.
When they're done hiking
there's gonna be a new president.
Uncle Sam came to me
because their embassy...
...was launched into the air
like the Apollo.
We'll provide you
with a getaway driver and guard...
...upon your arrival to the island.
I'm counting on you, Dutch.
Did you bring our pay here with you?
Expenses will be calculated separately.
I know. I...
R! P! G!
Well, well. They sure are quick.
They're already here.
Boss! Are you all right?
Your information's leaked, Mr. Chang.
This job's canceled.
Are you gonna quit? If so, you're gonna
have to pay the repair bills for this.
I'll at least escort you to your boat. However...
I haven't been in the field in a while.
Where's your emergency exit?
I'll lead the way, Chang.
Yeah, thanks.
- A grenade?!
- Don't panic, Two Hands.
In this situation...
...if you hesitate, you lose.
Chang's cleared the way.
Let's go!
Yeah, let's go.
- You're getting careless, boss.
- Keep the bragging down, Two Hands.
You have the skills, but you
still fail to see the overall picture.
I admit I'm not at your level.
I'll be wise and stick with you.
Good answer.
I'm sending a car.
Go to the harbor with that.
Oh, boy. One of these days, I'd like to do
a job that doesn't require risking my life.
Stop complaining, Dutch.
We're about to do the dirty work. Hurry!
I'll leave the rest to you,
Mr. Chang!
This is such a pain in the ass.
When you get there,
don't forget the password.
The password is...
Okay, I understand.
Our comrades have found the
delivery boys on the main road.
We can shed their blood
near Ban Kantang.
I wonder about that.
This job should've been finished
after the bombing of the Triad office.
I'm in no mood to judge
the failure of our comrades.
You mocked those guys
as simple gangsters...
...but Chang turned out to be a much
smarter gangster than you thought.
"See the enemy you should respect,
not the enemy you despise."
The words of Mao Tse-Tung.
You could learn from them, Ibraha.
The moral discourse of a man who
doesn't believe in God. It's worthless.
But he's right.
Besides, I don't believe in God either.
But you're my comrade,
Takenaka.
Well... More importantly, maybe we
should speed up the plan in America.
Don't be ridiculous. The FBI
has been keeping a close watch.
If we move now before the feint,
the plan will be ruined.
To figure out which
of the five routes they've taken...
...the first one to rule out is over land.
And flying is too visible.
That only leaves a sea route.
Do you have proof?
It's intuition.
I will ask a comrade commander
in the Philippines for assistance.
And the sea route,
I guess I'll have to take care of that.
This is the final step in
changing the world, Takenaka.
Yeah.
The sea is so wide, and it is so big...
Did you hear the password?
"The Triad is super cool!"
Boss Chang can handle himself
and has great style...
...but when it comes to telling jokes,
he couldn't be worse.
Well, you're never gonna
find someone perfect at everything.
You found it? A torpedo boat?
Chang's got some interesting friends.
You've determined their path, too?
That's perfect.
It's just as we predicted.
Now I don't have to trade in my ticket for
another flight. I'm already in transit.
Just don't do anything
until I arrive.
We need to confirm
a few things. Later.
E- Excuse me.
Please lend me your lighter.
- Are you from Japan, too?
- Thanks.
How did you know?
It's obvious...
- ...the way you held your hand.
- I see.
You know, we're on a family trip
to Cebu Island.
I imagine any place
outside Manila would seem far...
- ...when traveling with a family.
- Right.
Huh? Could we possibly
have met before?
I get this feeling
this isn't the first time we've met.
I'm sure you do.
You're thinking of Mr. Ken.
People always say I look like him.
Well, bye now. I'm awkward
when it comes to conversations.
Bye.
You sure are aloof.
If you recognize
me from somewhere...
...it would be
at the police station.
We've got them, Dutch.
The noisy little fly.
Okay.
Rock, bring me the Remington.
- And the Hydra API for ammunition.
- Sure.
We've taken out the enemy's eyes,
but it may not be the only one.
Rock. We'll be bait,
and charge past Basilan.
I want you and Revy
to get off at Zamboanga...
...and use the Zodiac
to get to Basilan.
Got it.
Ibraha! I can't hear you!
Hurry and get down here!
Takenaka! Where are you?
Basilan? Hey! That's where
our diversion team is!
Don't panic!
Yeah, I'm at their camp.
The lighthouse's base
is always the darkest.
We're waiting here
for the first blow...
...among the local guerrillas...
...but it's the same for them, too.
The only place an American imperialist
can come and go...
...is the anti-guerrilla special
operations camp.
It's just further on from here.
I can see Chang's next move.
This is gonna be fun.
This isn't a game, Takenaka! This is
an important precursor to the plan!
Think of this as an exchange
of pawns, brother.
In fact, do you think there's anything
in this world that isn't?
We're the ones poised
to take the next piece.
He sure is hard-headed.
What good is it if you can't have
a little fun along the way?
So, once we deliver the documents
we'll meet you at the base.
Yeah. I'll come and get you
when I lose those guys clinging to us.
People who fight for a cause
are so damn persistent.
Oh, right. I have an additional message
from Mr. Chang.
When Rock comes back
from the bathroom, tell him too.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The target is moving further north
from the Zamboanga coast.
So they passed Basilan.
Basilan is already behind us.
We believe they'll be heading
due north from Negros.
- We will continue our pursuit.
- Good work.
It's not what it seems.
They're coming here...
...right here to Basilan.
There's no mistaking it.
Such an uninteresting, dull island.
What time is it?
It's almost six. That was more trouble
than we expected...
...finding a place to come ashore.
The village should be right ahead.
It sure is quiet here.
It's a ghost village with no people.
There's been martial law here
for the last two years.
The police and the guerrillas are
shooting lead...
...at each other day and night.
The people here must have run away
to more developed islands.
Did I keep you waiting?
You're from Lagoon, right?
I heard that there were four of you.
- And why should I answer that?
- No reason you should.
Just me, him and a briefcase.
That's it.
By the way, I don't see your partner.
Where's your guard?
He's running around
looking for a bathroom.
He doesn't know the difference
between beer and Volvic.
So, let's cut to the chase.
The Triad is...
Now, how did that one go?
This isn't the time for jokes. If you don't
get to the point, I'll shoot you in the face.
Hey, hey. Don't get so hot.
It was just a little joke to break the ice.
The Triad is super cool. Right?
I must say, his sense of humor
is a little off.
You think so too?
Yeah. But I didn't think it was
that bad for Mr. Chang.
Exactly, asshole.
I have a message
from the boss for you.
"I am tai san fu kwan."
Do you know what that means?
The god of death and punishment shall
hereby bring down judgment on you.
I don't know where
you got the password...
...but Boss Chang isn't the pathetic
idiot or fool you assume him to be.
He prepared a new password
because of shit heads like you.
You hopped into this parade
with your ass hanging out.
What? Laugh, won't you? This is
the part where you laugh. C'mon, laugh.
Oh, boy. I guess I got
a little carried away.
Getting handled like this by a little girl
like you. How embarrassing.
Rock! Get back!
That idiot!
Damn you, Rock!
You screwed up!
The gunfire's started.
I don't wanna do this.
Leigharch!
It's such a pain.
I told you not to relax too much
before work. I made that clear.
I don't wanna move
until the gunfire dies down.
If they die,
we don't get paid.
- I don't feel like it.
- No, work's important.
Damn! They keep coming!
That dumbass idiot Rock!
Damn him!
Sister! Lower your head!
- Are you the getaway driver?!
- Do I look like an attorney?
That was rude, bitch!
Don't go after them! The military's
left their camp! Retreat! Retreat!
I heard from Mr. Chang that
there were four of you.
Where are the other three?
Plans changed and it became two of us.
Then one messed up and was captured.
Oh! That is pathetic!
We're going straight to the base.
I wanna finish this job and go home!
Where's their hideout?
North of the village. Six miles.
It's in the jungle. Yes it is.
We're not going to the military base.
We'll take care of those other guys first.
Wipe your own damn ass.
Or tell that to the cavalry, Mary Read.
Our job is to take you to the base.
That's all. And we get paid.
We're not interested in
doing anything else.
My partner has the documents. Get it?
Understand you yes? "Yes it is" lady.
Don't stain the seats, Shen Hua.
If you're gonna do it, do it outside.
My English is not too good
because I'm pure Taiwanese.
Is it no big deal if your head gets
separated from the rest of your body?
You don't get it.
Why do you think the boss hired you?
The documents.
Without the documents...
...it'll be us three idiots
in this car who will...
...have to do the twist in front of the boss
with dimwitted looks on our faces.
Hey, you're here.
We've formed an alliance.
This camp is now under our command.
That's perfect. Now, welcome to
our demilitarized zone.
We saw what's inside
the briefcase. It's empty.
I know nothing about it. And even if I did,
I couldn't answer. You know that.
An untwisted answer. At a time like this,
you should at least crack a joke.
Anyway, we have time.
We can talk this through.
Now, shall we do this
in Japanese, young man?
If you're gonna get involved
in this kinda stuff...
...you really need to be
a bit more careful.
You're Japanese, aren't you? How long
have you been doing this kinda work?
Well, you're no fun.
Are you gonna stay quiet?
It wouldn't hurt
for us fellow countrymen...
...be friendly to each other,
now would it?
This is a problem.
Next Episode
Has the launderer's delivery boy
arrived yet?!
You're late, Langley boys!