I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Roberta.
Get down, you two!
Move outta the way!
No! Don't shoot Roberta!
If something like this could kill her,
we wouldn't have this problem, kid.
Roberta!
Shit! Damn it!
Dutch! We're off the main road!
This way leads to the ocean.
It's a dead end ahead.
This is not good!
Oh, no!
There is a payoff for being religious.
All survivors, answer me.
We're safe, somehow.
What about Revy?
She's still unconscious... peacefully.
How about you?
What in the world
is that woman made of?!
Damn it.
Revy.
Damn it. Hey, what happened to
that damn bitch? Is she dead? Well?!
You'll be glad to know
that she's alive and well.
That's just delightful.
More than anything else.
Revy! Wait!
Rock. I'm about to become
as red as a tail light.
When that happens,
it's over.
I won't be able to warn you even if
I'm about to give you extra assholes.
That shell she used
to blow me away...
...is gonna cost her more than
anything she could stick up her ass.
I'm gonna go beat that into her.
C'mon draw, Senorita.
Or are you scared?
You have no need
to use filthy words and be afraid.
Knowing you could not
defeat me with skill...
...you pointed a gun at the
young master and kidnapped him.
You coward.
Rock. Watch out for stray bullets!
I can't see either of them.
Roberta.
Oww... Damn it.
She managed to get a bullet into
the great Revy. Who is that woman?
There's no way you could've had
a good upbringing.
Where did you come from?
Tell me.
I see.
It's no surprise that's the smell
you have on you.
The stench of gutter-mud
stuck to your feet.
Even more reason
why we'll have to settle this.
I can no longer...
I can no longer go back there.
Roberta.
Now... What should we do now?
Maybe we should get outta this car.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
Roberta!
Impossible.
Yeah, impossible. We'd never make it
no matter how many lives we have.
I'm not about to go anywhere
near that fight.
Same here.
There's an end to every beginning.
They'll settle things eventually.
Hey, kid! Wait!
Garcia.
Roberta!!
Do your best!!
Don't you lose to that woman!!
The gunfire is getting closer.
This bitch! I'm gonna kill her!
I'm gonna kill her!
You're going to hell!
Don't move!
Why don't you
call it quits now, you two.
There's nothing to gain
from fighting anymore.
Don't waste your energy,
Two Hands.
Shut up.
I'm gonna kill her.
Let me tell you something
interesting, Miss Maid.
We, at Hotel Moscow...
...had intended to start a war...
...against the Manisarela Cartel
from the beginning.
Taking care
of them was my job...
...but you saved me
the trouble.
Right now, their headquarters in
Venezuela should be in ruins.
Therefore, all of the problems
have been solved.
The case of Garcia being kidnapped
has also been dealt with.
You have no reason to fight.
Those are no doubt the three
most terrifying women in the world.
This feels like Ground Zero.
It doesn't matter.
I agree.
You think so?
Don't misunderstand me.
I'm not making a request. It's an order.
Who are these guys?
They don't seem like
the usual Russian mafia.
Military uniforms?
Are they soldiers?
Roberta!
It's all right, Roberta!
As you can see, I'm not hurt!
Okay?
Let's go home!
I don't wanna see
you with a gun anymore.
I agree, kid. But...
...what does the Bloodhound think?
Bloodhound?
Oh, my. So you don't know? She's...
SHUT UP!!
Keep quiet, bitch.
This isn't some servant
who looks good walking the dog.
"The Bloodhound of Florencia".
Rosarita Cisneros.
Trained as an assassin in Cuba,
she's a former F.A.R.C. guerrilla.
She's wanted internationally for
multiple kidnappings and murders.
And she's suspected
of being involved with...
...the bombing of the
U. S. embassy in Tegucigalpa.
She's a real hardcore terrorist.
Roberta...
Is it true?
I... I had no intention of
deceiving you, young master.
However, young master.
There are things in this world...
...that you're better off not knowing.
It is the truth.
I... I believed it.
In the morning of a revolution that
would bring justice to this world.
For that reason,
I became a soldier.
In my pursuit of the ideal,
I killed in every place imaginable.
Politicians, entrepreneurs...
...anti-revolutionists,
election management members.
I even killed women
and children.
Dying many nights with blood...
...and facing many
cold hearted mornings...
...what I realized in the end was...
...that I was no revolutionist.
I was nothing but a guard dog for
the mafia and their cocaine fields.
Isn't it ironic?
The revolutionists joined forces
with the cartels.
Saying that a revolution
would not happen solely on ideals.
As they blurted out those words,
they sold their souls.
I left the military.
The one who took me in then was
my deceased father's friend...
...none other than your father,
Master Diego Lovelace.
Young master.
Allowing your kidnapping to happen
was negligence on my part.
I did not have any other
way to save you...
...than becoming my old,
steel self that I once abandoned.
Bloodhound.
Guard dog.
That was the only way that I...
...being called a dog,
could repay you with my life.
Don't call yourself a dog, Roberta!
You're my family!
We're family, right?!
Don't talk like that,
about being a dog! You can't!
I don't know any Bloodhound!
She probably died somewhere!
That Rosarita woman has probably
gone to some unknown...
...far away place...
...burdened with her sins!
So she's got nothing
to do with you, Roberta!
The only one here
is my Roberta!
Young master.
So...
So, okay?
Let's go back to our home.
Young master.
Boys should not cry so easily.
Well, I'm glad that's settled.
You must be kidding.
I'm sure they're all delighted with
this teary-eyed happy ending.
But who the hell is gonna close up
this tunnel in my shoulder?
Well?
Why don't you just
put up with it?
Come on, Sis.
That stinks, don't you think?
In our world,
settling things is important.
You know that perfectly well, Sis.
Well, I suppose you have a point.
That's easy.
Have them go at each other
in a fistfight until they're satisfied.
There's no prize at stake,
so no one's likely to get killed.
Fine by me!
Young master?
Don't you lose to that woman!
You're strong, Roberta!
Then it's decided.
You're free to continue
as long as you wish.
Go ahead, bring it on.
Your shoelace is untied.
She got one in!
Must be nice to be so young.
Damn it!
Come on, Roberta!
Don't lose to her!
Who are you betting on?
I'm betting two
on Revy.
Then I'm going with three on Roberta.
How about you, Rock?
W-W-Wait a minute!
We should be stopping them! Right?
We've gotta make
them stop!
Why's that?
It's too barbaric, and you guys
are crazy not to stop them!
It's absurd to have two girls
going at it like that!
Then why don't you go
and stop them?
You don't like this, right?
- Well...
- Then go and stop them.
We don't mind.
Umm... You two...
Haven't you had enough?
You could maybe, you know,
like, sit back and...
...praise each other's
combative spirit as you gaze...
- ...at the rising sun together?
- Stay out of this!
I-I understand. I'll do just that.
What did you expect?
They just won't give up.
This is getting boring.
Why don't you die already?
Damned four-eyes!
You too...
just let me knock you out.
Damn it!
Okay, it's a draw!
Roberta!
Young master.
I am so sorry.
Don't talk.
You were the last one standing.
So it's all right.
- What a terrible face.
- She's unconscious.
Can you stand?
Come on, hang onto me.
I'm sorry.
Stop that, Roberta.
You wanna hand, kid?
Leave us alone.
Roberta is a maid at my house.
So I don't need anyone else's help.
I will be sure to take her home.
A wonderful future
head of the clan.
- Comrade Sergeant.
- Ma'am.
Treat her wounds,
then take them to the airport.
If any remaining cartel members
attempt an assault, dispose of them.
Roger.
Young master.
I have one favor to ask.
What is it?
Could you please go
and pick up my glasses for me?
Why? Those are fake,
aren't they?
But I need those glasses...
...to continue being
your Roberta.
Hey! It's morning, Revy!
Wake up!
Absolutely no sign of waking up.
She's gonna take time to recover.
Oh, boy.
But who were those guys?
Balalaika and the Russian mafia guys.
They were like the military.
Those guys are ex-military.
They were either in the paratroopers
or the Special Forces.
Her immediate subordinates
had enough training...
...to carry out World War III.
Afghan vets with an insane amount
of experience and skill.
With her as the brains, every one
of them acted as a killing machine.
And eventually they returned from
that hell of hot sand and slaughter.
Everyone's feet are covered
with mud from the gutter.
Next Episode
Five teams will leave
Roanapur at the same time...
...each heading to a different destination.
There are five cases.