Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
The attacks by the Gundams
sent by the Space Colonies...
...reflected the colonies'
retaliatory intentions.
OZ has masked its identity
in the Alliance Military...
...and the Gundams' missions
is to attack them.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken
center stage.
With an army of elite soldiers
at his command...
...Treize Khushrenada has begun to
wipe out the Alliance Military.
The battle between OZ and the
mobile suits sent to Earth...
...causes serious repercussions
on the Earth.
I've mastered many mobile suits
in the past, so what gives?
What am I afraid of?!
LONG LIVE, KING ZECHS!
My hands are too stained
with blood.
I'm completely unfit to head
the Peacecraft monarchy.
Heero, Distracted by Defeat
So that's the Tallgeese.
I can see that it's no
ordinary machine.
And that only Zechs
could be its pilot.
Giving Zechs too much special
treatment might not be wise.
We're giving a superior
suit to a superior pilot.
Any problem with that?
I'm concerned that it might
give him an attitude.
Lady, there's no need for
you to worry about that.
Focus only on the major issues.
Sir.
We've awaited you,
Your Excellency.
Sorry to cause you
so much trouble.
Thanks for your concern.
And Lieutenant Noin.
I commend you on
your front-line battles.
I'd like to thank you personally.
You're too kind, sir.
Why should Mr. Treize have
to thank his own soldiers?
And some of them shamelessly
accept his praise.
I've put Lady Une in charge
of our latest plan.
Shall we get started?
Yes.
I'll be giving an explanation
of our strategy at 1600 hours.
Almost time.
Then be on your way.
Yes, sir!
Colonel Zechs, Lieutenant Noin,
you two shall attend.
Come with me!
Oh, there was something else
I wanted to discuss with Zechs.
I'll send him soon.
Right.
Lieutenant Noin!
Move it!
Ma'am.
I believe you have a better
grasp of your feelings...
...toward the Alliance by now.
Well, Lightning Baron?
Or may I call you
Lightning Count?
Your Excellency, I was hoping
to serve you for a little longer.
There's nothing that'd
make me happier.
But you're sure?
As it is there's only one name
I could give myself.
Killer of His Own Men.
The Gundams?
Yes, sir.
In that case, do as you wish.
I'm very grateful.
By the way, won't you be
taking your mask off?
You've carried out
your revenge.
There's no need now
to hide your face.
I still bring my personal hatred
onto the battlefield.
Just think of this as my
mark of distinction.
You're a very devoted soldier.
That's the reason I can trust
you with anything...
...Milliardo Peacecraft.
That name...please don't.
I'm looking forward to the day
you remove that mask.
Yes, sir!
The latest plan involves
transporting the Tauruses...
...to the Siberian Base to
install our new mobility system.
A new system?
I hadn't heard of it.
Our lack of confidence in
the facilities and security...
...at the Lake Victoria base
has led to this transfer.
The Tauruses will be transported
across the Arabian Peninsula...
...under the heavy guard of
our African branch.
We'll take over the
transfer there.
So far there haven't been
any real threats...
...but we've considered
everything.
We've already announced
a false transport plan.
We won't let the enemies
have it their way this time.
Enemies?
The Gundams?
The Gundams have attacked
practically all of OZ's operations.
This should be another
attractive target for them.
But as long as I'm in charge,
I'll prevent such interference!
If they're going to Siberia...
...they can pass through
OZ's protected areas.
So the Gundams
won't be able to attack.
No, we want them to come.
I consider annihilating the
Gundams a big part of this plan.
Our losses up until now were
because cowardly soldiers...
...were too slow compiling
their data.
But this time OZ is serious.
I'd like to give an example of
how to eradicate the Gundams.
It might not come to much use,
but let me provide you...
...with some background.
Dr. J!
We'll refer to the unit that
fell over the Pacific Ocean...
...as Gundam Zero One.
Most remarkable is
its mobility...
...as an aircraft.
We'll lure it to an Aries air
zone and shoot it down.
Without its wings, we can
overcome it in a long battle.
Next, the Gundam Zero Two.
The Taurus is a problem.
It has the ability to learn
from accumulated battle data.
I wanna trust OZ's control
system, but it's possible...
...the machine will ignore the
pilot's commands and act alone.
If the command to kill
overrides the pilot...
...the consequences could
be significant.
Destroy it, otherwise it'll
be a menace to mankind.
Mission accepted.
Who's there?!
I've come to say good-bye!
I have a bad feeling about this.
OZ's transport plan is good.
They'll be taking two routes;
by air and land.
Heero, could you take
the air route?
I'll fight them on the ground.
We'll lose unless we have
our own plan, this time.
Zero Two's features allow it to
remain unnoticed.
It specializes in close combat.
It is important to make
Zero Three use up...
...all of its firepower at
an early stage.
This is true for all of them...
...but not one mobile suit
excels in organized battle.
There's no choice but to attack
while they're transporting.
Even with such basic tactics...
...if they can trick us...
...our fighting power will
be dispersed.
By air?
We'll take the land!
They might come by air.
If we hit their land
transport early...
...we can tell everyone
which one's the decoy!
You think the other Gundams
will come?
We can't win by ourselves.
But I'm positive the
others will come.
I'm no longer able to fight
in my current state.
Denounce me, Nataku.
Zero Four is also a close-range
battle type...
...but we believe its battle
range is broader than Zero Two.
Avoid direct combat with Zero Five.
Barrage until it's destroyed.
Be extremely cautious of
the firepower in its left arm.
That concludes my briefing.
Gather the troops of the
respective bases...
...along this route to standby.
Yes, ma'am!
Colonel Zechs, I was hoping
you'd take on the task...
...of fighting Zero One with the
Tallgeese, one on one.
What do you think?
You can't expect him
to go alone!
I'll back him up.
But Noin...
There are still some Aries
left in the Lake Victoria base.
I request orders to lead
the Aries to battle.
I'm appointing you
to the headquarters.
But why?
You'll be assisting me.
Any problems with that?
No...
Colonel Zechs previously
received a serious blow...
...at the hands of Zero One.
Now that he has the Tallgeese...
...this would be the perfect
opportunity to get his revenge.
Convenient.
If he loses it all becomes
Zechs' fault.
Noin, it suits me fine.
I was hoping you'd be
stationed at the headquarters.
Zechs?
When we fight we'll need
quick, accurate information.
I'll need your support.
Sir!
Count on me!
Commence operations!
Relena!
Good morning.
Relena, something awful's
happened!
Heero has changed schools,
right?
You already knew about it?
We hadn't even become friends
with Heero and Duo yet.
Off to fight again, Heero?
Well, I'm headed for my
own battleground.
Mobile suit troop preparation
for both the flight course...
...and the railway course
are complete!
Check the observation satellite
for course irregularities.
Yes, ma'am!
It's only a matter of time.
Excuse me, Colonel Une.
Which carrier route will
they be using?
Both are extremely important.
Gundam Zero Four located 9.0 kilometers
from land route point A.
Right!
Aries No. 4 squadron, attack!
There's our target,
Master Quatre!
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
No mistaking this security!
It's this route!
You wish!
Hey, are you okay?!
I'm fine.
Glad you came.
Sure.
But this route's the decoy.
What?!
Radar plane reporting!
A high speed carrier's
headed our way.
Release mobile suits
for counterattack!
The Taurus carriers have
arrived at its fueling point.
Backup Defense Army, attack!
Flying object approaching
from south-east at high speed.
Probably Zero One.
It'll arrive at the supply base
in T-minus 300.
Zechs!
Zero One has just arrived!
It's headed for the air route
supply point...
...where we're fighting off Zero Three!
That's fortunate.
He's headed for the air route.
It'll be close, but I'll
take him out midway!
That an Aries?
No it's bigger...
Data checked.
No match to the latest
OZ weapons?!
What speed!
That's enough, Gundam Zero One.
We have no need for beam
rifles or cannons between us.
We'll fight for recognition
of superiority.
I'm sure that'll suit you!
You ARE a Gundam pilot.
There's the flight type.
Is that a new OZ model?
I believe I've won this battle!
I feel no fear whatsoever!
I can defeat you without taking
Tallgeese to its full limit!
Prototype Leo!
So OZ has completed them!
It won't be easy,
but I'll destroy it!
My mission's to destroy
the Taurus.
I'm checking out!
Half the land route Leo
troops have been defeated...
...by Zero Two and Zero Four.
Zero One is battling the Tallgeese.
But Zero Three is headed for
the supply base.
Who would've guessed
Gundams had this much power?
The Taurus carriers are on
standby for emergency take off!
I'll give the "okay".
I didn't approve that!
My strategies never fail.
Get Space Fortress Barge
on line!
A Space Fortress?
Colonel Une, positioning
is complete.
Good!
Calling all Gundam pilots.
We're ready to stage an all-out
missile attack on the colonies!
We've seized all missile
satellites from the Alliance.
Now we truly control the
destiny of all colonies!
This isn't a bluff.
I demand all pilots to
surrender at once...
...and hand over your Gundams!
They've targeted the colonies!
Hand over our Gundams?!
Sounds like OZ's tricks.
Hell of a time for tasteless
tactics!
You guys can't fight, can you?!
I can't fight either!
Noin!
Get me Lady Une!
The Gundams have stopped,
but they aren't surrendering.
Launch a missile!
I don't care where!
Colonel!
Get a grip on yourself!
I know exactly what I'm doing!
That isn't what His
Excellency wants!
I'm merely fulfilling
His Excellency's ideal!
You clearly don't understand
His Excellency!
You're the one that doesn't
understand him, Zechs!
No, it's you.
Colonel Une.
The objective is to eliminate
the rebels.
His Excellency doesn't want
battles that involve civilians.
The colonies can be flattened
with the most minute of attacks.
They're insignificant worlds
for the pathetic.
What about the rebels?!
I'll sweep them all away
with this single command!
Launch missiles!!!
No, don't!!
What on earth?
Who is this guy?
Attention OZ.
I never imagined you people
could be so foolish.
The Space Colonies have
no intention of fighting OZ.
This is MY personal battle
I'm staging against you!
Who's he?
Dr. J...
So the rebel's finally
showing his face!
Transmission is on a regular
line from outer space.
Transmission origin is
Colony C-1013.
Who's this guy?
The person who's been
sending orders!
To one of us five Gundams!
To you, inhumane moves like
colony assaults are justified...
...if that's what it takes for
you to come out victorious.
I have no choice but
to surrender.
Very well!
Your surrender's accepted.
Abandon your Gundams
immediately!
A kid.
The pilot of a Gundam is
a little boy?!
I surrender.
But I will not hand over
the Gundams. I repeat.
I surrender, but I will not
hand over the Gundam.
Mission accepted.
Zero One just...
...self-detonated...
That pilot sacrificed
his life!
He self-detonated in
exchange for the colonies?
He sacrificed his life
without a second thought.
The pain!
My body!
My soul!
Can you hear me?
We must leave here at once!
Trowa!
That you, Trowa?!
Without resolution we
cannot fight.
He's accepted all orders.
Because they bluffed with
the colonies.
We can't fight any longer.
Hurry and move out!
I won't attack you in
a position like this!
All Gundams are retreating
from their battle points!
Don't expect this to be
the end, Gundams.
Or you, Lieutenant Noin!
Colonel, I have a call in
from His Excellency.
Here!
Colonel...
He says for you to
be more graceful.
About everything.
More graceful...
LADY Une.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The Gundams have been defeated.
With the colonies used as hostages,
the warriors don't have a chance.
They face a time of humiliation
when they are unable to fight.
Also, no one can confirm
whether Heero's dead or alive.
About that time, Relena heads
to Moscow alone...
...having been informed that
Lady Une is there.
She aims her gun straight
at her father's killer, Lady Une.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 11,
The Whereabouts of Happiness
"The Whereabouts of Happiness".