Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Heero, Distracted by Defeat
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The Whereabouts of Happiness