Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Colonel!
Grief Stricken Quatre
Hey! Look at that!
It's an Alliance mobile suit!
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
This is a satellite for
mining natural resources.
What were you doing in
that mobile suit, anyway?
You don't appear to be
a soldier with the Alliance.
I'm not!
Don't try to move, yet.
If you'd continued drifting
in space, you would've died.
Why...
Why did you save my life?
I'm a doctor.
Nothing to do with OZ
or the Alliance.
Besides, this is a neutral zone
outside both group's control.
Forgive me.
I didn't even say thanks
for saving my life.
Do you know where
I could rent a shuttle?
You mustn't!
I can't let a patient in your
condition out of my sight.
Forget about my condition!
Calm down.
I see you're in a hurry, but
it's not good for your health!
What you really need to do
is rest your body and mind.
I can make arrangements
for the shuttle.
Promise you'll wait?
Yes.
Sorry to ask you.
Not a problem.
But you have to get some rest.
Promise me.
It's no use.
The target is accelerating.
The Leos can't keep up
with it.
The route is unchanged;
still headed for the Bay Area.
The Leos are no match;
just as I thought.
Reports suggest that it
might even be the Tallgeese.
I don't care what it is!
We can't allow a mobile suit
with weapons to get too close.
We can probably get rid of it
with the mobile dolls.
However...
The scientists have completed
the new mobile suits...
...and they're ready.
I'd like to test the abilities of
the Vayeate and the Mercurius.
We can't test them in
real battle, you fool!
Who do you recommend
for the other pilot?
Allow me to pilot it,
Colonel Une.
It's got be an excellent pilot
to conduct a complete test.
Otherwise he'll get in the way.
What's that?!
I understand.
Colonel!
Trowa Barton.
You've got command to
destroy the Tallgeese.
Ma'am.
Come out!
What do you think?
How do you like the
Vayeate and Mercurius?
They're excellent!
They certainly reflect your
skills as Gundam designers.
You were right to leave
things in our hands.
But this is dangerous!
Why are you letting that Gundam
pilot take out the Mercurius?
Because HE IS a Gundam pilot.
OZ should know his piloting
skills better than anyone.
Can the Mercurius'
self-detonation device...
...be activated from Trowa's
Vayeate?
Yeah, just as you requested.
Trowa, you have the authority
to blow up Mercurius...
...if your pilot acts
suspicious!
That shouldn't be necessary.
He fought against the
Tallgeese before, in Siberia.
He'd think of this
as finishing the battle.
Now the colonies won't be a...
...shield to prevent him from
finishing it.
How could you have
found out about that?
It's not hard, seeing as
I'm a soldier for OZ.
It's a good thing he
self-detonated.
I was living in the
colony at the time.
So I might not have survived.
I should be grateful myself.
I found an excellent
subordinate like you.
How is it?
Not too bad.
The operations are practically
identical to the Gundams'.
Not surprising.
Hey, Gundam pilot.
How would you fight
a mobile doll?
First I'd sneak behind
the enemy...
...to make sure I was
out of its target range.
Don't overdo it.
Or I'll have to blow you up.
The mobile dolls' weak point...
...is that they have the same
abilities as the manned models.
They're identical down to their
mobility and reaction times.
The rest depends on how well
a human pilot can fight them.
Personally, I have a harder
time with space mines.
We don't need the mobile dolls.
I'll handle that white suit
on my own.
We've caught up.
We'll send the mobile dolls.
Why's he in outer space?
You got me.
Mobile dolls!
My reaction time's a little
slower than theirs.
But I can make up for that
in close-range combat...
What?!
There's two of them!
It reflected the beam!
Gotta move in on
this one too!
They're destroying the
mobile dolls...
...at the same time they're
fighting me.
Not many pilots could
do that in outer space.
I haven't got time to
play games with you.
Just haul me in.
Never would've guessed
you'd sneak into OZ.
I'm Officer Trowa Barton.
I don't believe we've met,
Zechs Merquise.
I'll introduce myself.
I go by the name
Milliardo Peacecraft.
I've come from Earth
as a goodwill ambassador.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
The majority of people
living in space...
...are either technicians
or laborers.
Enduring an environment inferior
to that of the stable Earth...
...these people have the guts
to improve their conditions.
This gives rise to a new power.
It's the Winner family who
supports this spirit.
The Winner family master
immigrated...
...and became the central figure
in negotiations...
...with the United Earth
Sphere Alliance...
...to fight for the rights
of the colony residents.
Even since the disintegration
of the Alliance Military...
...he confronts OZ on
behalf of the colony...
...but always acts
as a pacifist.
Excuse me, Mr. Winner.
What?!
Quatre has come back home?!
How old were you in that photo?
I really appreciate your
bringing me here.
It wasn't any trouble.
I needed to come anyway.
You've been very disobedient.
I still believe I'm right!
Simply living in outer space
is difficult for people!
Involving yourself in a war
is a waste of time!
That's why we've been
searching for solutions...
...through discussions with the
United Earth Sphere Alliance.
But you had to go to Earth
in a mobile suit.
You even gave them an excuse
to attack the colonies.
But someone has to fight
or the war won't end.
Well?!
Has it ended?!
Did your battle end the war?!
What could you accomplish?
What could a child like you
accomplish?!
The least you could do
as an heir...
...is listen to your father.
Use your head.
I think he'll grown up
to be an excellent heir.
Irea, don't you start on me.
Father.
It's wrong to think of a child
as being incapable.
My little brother will make
an excellent heir!
Deep inside, Father understands.
That dialog with OZ won't
lead to any solutions.
But he thinks things will
come out all right...
...if the whole colony
works together as one.
Why didn't you tell me
you were my sister?
I'd heard from Father...
...that my little brother
was a Gundam pilot.
But he gets so upset.
I couldn't decide whether
to say anything.
I heard my sisters were
stationed...
...in different resource
satellites.
We're all rooting for you.
And Father is no exception.
Right after you left...
...it was Father who
worried about you most.
Really?
It's true I gave refuge
to Instructor H...
...who was fleeing from
the Alliance.
But from our family's
perspective...
...mobile suits aren't needed
to attain peace.
Still, Quatre ignored me and
cooperated with the instructor.
Aggressive solutions only
lead to more problems.
But Quatre just can't see that.
This is where my Gundam
was built.
But I had to destroy it
on Earth...
...because of my incompetence.
What are you going to do?
The instructor's not here.
I have to make another Gundam,
to fight.
Quatre...
Can you really fight for
the people of the colony?
Huh?
Another Gundam pilot who
fought like you was caught.
His Gundam was destroyed
to set an example.
The people of the colonies
were overjoyed.
No one in space considers
Gundams their allies anymore.
Quatre, are you sure you
can still fight?
I wasn't fighting to be
recognized by the people.
But one day I believe
they'll see the truth.
I'm probably feeling sentimental
without Sandrock around.
I'm sorry.
I'm your sister, yet
I'm always mean to you.
Sis...
We all love you.
So don't be sad,
my dearest Quatre.
Thank you, Irea.
Then how would you gentlemen
define future development?
Why do you need arms
for defense?
Mr. Winner.
I understand your point.
But we're already in a dangerous
strategic position.
And the people want to be
responsible for their safety.
Safety?!
This is safety?!
You saw these weapons,
and armed yourselves.
How dare you use words
like "safety" or "peace"?!
Development of this colony
wouldn't have been possible...
...without your financial help.
However the current prosperity...
...is a result of the
citizens' efforts.
I question your
continued dictatorship.
When did I act as a dictator?!
I've merely objected to OZ's
intervention...
...so we could maintain
colony peace.
If anyone is guilty of trying
to dictate the colony...
...it's you men!
Mr. Winner.
At this point, we can't allow
your exclusive control.
Let's decide on a fair offer
for jurisdiction over this area.
The manufacture of arms
and murder weapons.
Why should I cooperate?!
Hand over your rights,
Winner family!!
The colony belongs to
us laborers!!
Hooray for OZ!!
What are they yelling about?
Public opinion is getting
stronger.
Saying we shouldn't
monopolize natural resources.
That's absurd.
It's true that we own many
natural resource satellites.
But we've never monopolized
the resources.
We've practically given
them away...
...for people's prosperity
in space.
But everybody knew that!
People's feelings have changed.
About you, and about Father.
But we're only... we're only
doing the right thing.
The votes are unanimous.
From now on, this natural
resource satellite...
...is under OZ's jurisdiction.
You won't manufacture weapons
on this satellite!
Are you serious?!
Father's disconnected the
satellite?!
What?!
Yes, and it's accelerating!
This could disrupt functions
in our entire colony!
That's what he's really like!
He's prepared to sacrifice the
colony's future for his benefit.
And he won't stop at anything!
Should we allow this to happen?!
Since there are no objections...
...we'll proceed at once to take
any necessary steps...
...to maintain peace in
our colony.
Father, you've got to stop this!
This isn't going to resolve
anything!
They'll be coming after you!
Are you telling me to sit back
as OZ invades the colony?!
I'm not mistaken!
Father!!
Quatre!
Promise you won't fight
in those mobile suits anymore.
Aggression won't solve
anything.
But Father...
You fools!
Get away from here!
That wicked beam cannon
is aimed at this satellite!
Father, please escape!
Quatre, I am escaping.
I'm not putting up a fight.
There is no end to this fight,
so I've opted to run away.
If I should die, then so be it.
I'm not so attached to space
that I'll compromise myself!
FATHER!!!
Father?!
FATHER!!
Quatre!!
Father...
Quatre.
Father fought very hard.
He wasn't running away.
He put up a brave fight, right?
Irea, try not to move.
You'll only make it worse.
You're a kind person, Quatre.
And Father was kind too.
But what did Father do
to deserve to be killed?!
Kind people are shedding tears.
But nobody understands them.
And the colony is satisfied now.
You people are satisfied!
I'll never forget this.
And I'll make sure the people
don't forget this day, either.
Outer space...
It's so quiet...
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The era plummets into
the depths of confusion.
The colonies head down a path
leading toward armaments.
Zechs has left Earth and
confirms...
...the existence of a Lady Une
who promotes peace.
In her goal to achieve
Treize's ideal...
...Lady Une acts on her own...
...against the orders of
the Romefeller Foundation.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 22,
The Fight for Independence
"The Fight for Independence".