Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Mission accepted!
Heero ended up doing it.
He took his life.
I promise!
One day my Gundam will
definitely fight again.
Bewildered Warriors
After staging a coup d'état...
...to overthrow the United
Earth Sphere Alliance...
...OZ continues to create one
disaster after another...
...in its quest to demolish
the Alliance.
Since the Alliance has a
presence in every nation...
...the number of casualties
is expected to rise.
Relena...
Hey, you've come to!
Wait, I'll go get Trowa!
Trowa?
You should take it easy!
Trowa, your friend's woken up!
Oh, you must be hungry!
I'll go make some soup.
Where am I?
With a traveling circus.
Where I hide myself.
Why'd you save me?
I was supposed to die.
You died a long time ago.
The forces retaliating against
OZ have ignored our advice...
...with regards to disarmament...
...and are causing unnecessary
carnage around the world.
One month has passed, and OZ
hasn't touched the colonies.
They're just fighting militaristic
nations on Earth.
A month has passed?!
In OZ's eyes, you're
already dead.
You're no longer restrained
to the colonies.
My case isn't that simple.
They found you?
No.
But there hasn't been one
mission since that day.
I see.
I'm not sure what to do.
What if OZ used the colonies
as a shield again?
Or should I be following
your example?
In that case, I've got
one warning.
It hurts like hell.
Hey, I think that's probably
the first time...
...I've heard Trowa laugh
out loud.
I've got a favor to ask;
the first since I came to Earth.
What happened around the world
while I was unconscious?
I'll tell you.
What a strong flap.
Hurry up, get on!
Hurry, Sally!
We're all out of there!
Sally here.
Explosions successful.
We're retreating!
What's all the racket?!
The guerrillas, Colonel Bundt.
Go after them!
We'll crush them this time!
Sir!
In former China, within an
autonomous mountainous area...
...a political leader proposing
peace was assassinated.
He advocated demilitarization
and raised objections...
...to the present military.
The Alliance's army targeted
him in a coup d'état.
Colonel Bundt, the ringleader,
opposed this push for peace...
...and said the military
must be strengthened...
...in order for the nation
to achieve independence.
Now that OZ was dismembering
the Alliance...
...civil wars were increasing
in such independent nations.
Got them!
What's wrong, Sally?
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry.
It's your first time home
in a long time...
...and we've put you
in such danger.
Don't apologize.
It was my decision.
Hey you guys!
Are you all right?
Yeah, it was a huge success!
What?!
It's Leo, the land mobile suits!
Colonel Bundt has ordered
that no one escape!
You fools!
Found them!
They're climbing the slope!
That weapon's useless
against suits!
If I can destroy its
main camera!
I won't tell you to drop
your weapons!
I'll have you die!!
I told you, it's no use!
Their back up?
It's a Gundam!!
A Gundam?
What?
Fire!
Fire! Fire!!
I don't intend to fight.
Hurry up and retreat.
We can beat this thing!
Don't underestimate Nataku!
Damn you!
It's a Gundam...
What's a Gundam doing here?
Weaklings like you shouldn't
be fighting.
What's that?!
Why fight an enemy you
don't stand a chance against?!
Because it's a fight we
must take on!
Somebody ordered you?
No!
We're acting on our own!
I don't understand.
You look pretty exhausted.
Come with us and rest.
Sally!
No problem.
We know he's not an enemy.
Well?
It was a Gundam?!
Are you sure?!
Yes!
I'll bring up the image!
That's a Gundam all right.
Even OZ is having trouble
controlling those Gundams.
I'll return to the base!
Right.
Sleep well last night?
Yeah.
You didn't need to help
out with getting the food.
I'm returning your favor.
It's us that owe you a favor!
It wasn't me that saved you.
It was Nataku.
Nataku?
Is that your Gundam's name?
Oh...
Here's the last.
Better watch what you say.
I'm begging you, please stop!
Shut your trap!
I was just asking you
to pay for what you ate!
You should be grateful to us
that you could have this shop!
Huh?
You want money from
the soldiers who protect?!
What are you claiming
to protect, anyway?
What?!
All you do is stick to Bundt...
...and trample over the
nation's peace efforts.
What did you say?
You swine!
This is for opposing us!
You asked for it!
Stop it! You're defeated.
Wh-What's gotten into you?!
Calm down...
Damn it!
We'll get you next time!
Thank you, Wu Fei.
You saved us again.
You're too weak to fight.
Huh?
I don't have any right to fight.
Wu Fei...
I'm such a coward.
I can't understand how you
could call yourself a coward.
Because I lost.
To a man stronger than me.
I'm a coward who can only
fight those weaker than myself.
Is that why you're giving up?
Weren't you fighting
for the colonies?
To win back peace?
I have no right to fight
with Nataku.
You saved my life yesterday!
Because you people are weak.
You're right.
We are weak.
But we won't give up!
People join our fight because
we're weak!
The same way you did.
I have no right to fight
with Nataku.
Wu Fei...
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
From this data, we've
determined that this area...
...is probably the guerrilla's
headquarters.
I see.
We finally know where
they're hiding.
But they have the Gundam.
The Gundams are incredibly
powerful in battle.
If we fought it head on, it'd
considerably damage our forces.
Given the situation, why don't
we ask for OZ's assistance...
...and stage a joint attack?
I disagree!
That'd give OZ an excuse to
establish themselves in our nation.
What about our self-government?
We've got to fight to alone to
prove ourselves to the citizens.
Do you still favor this idea?
Major Nanaki.
I wouldn't want to risk losing
even one of your elite soldiers.
I appreciate it, but we swore
our lives to this nation...
...when we declared
independence.
That's right, Colonel!
We must protect our nation
by ourselves!
That's what makes us an
independent nation!
Right!
I understand your determination!
We'll wipe out the guerrillas
using our own forces!
For our fatherland!
Yes, sir!
Hi Sally; how did it go?
Hey, I thought that kid
went with you.
We had a little fight.
I see.
Well, he's probably not gonna
leave that thing behind.
You're right.
It would sure be great if
that kid would fight with us.
Nobody should be trying to force
him into fighting right now.
Why not?
He's very confused now.
So much was expected
of him during the war...
...but he couldn't deliver.
So now he thinks he's a loser.
Well, if you say so.
You're the military doctor.
Former...
What?!
It's the government military!
They're attacking!
Counterattack!
Choppers have confirmed mobile
suit combat missile launchers!
We'll fire the rocket guns then
send in our mobile suit troops.
Roger!
Okay, fire!
Ignore the backup firing...
...and focus on the mobile suits
that move in to gain control.
Helicopter unit; where's
the Gundam?!
Locate it at once!
Hey, look!
Major Nanaki!
We found the Gundam!
Major!
The Gundam's not fighting back!
I'll transmit the image!
There's a camouflage net!
The pilot's not on it!
Colonel Bundt!
The Gundam isn't fighting
back.
We can win this battle!
I see.
The main force will join you.
It appears that things are
now in our favor.
Favorable for me, and
for you people.
There it is!
Mobile suit troops, proceed to
the Gundam to suppress it.
All backup firing units!
Aim at the Gundam and
standby to fire.
- Take shelter!
- What's wrong?
Backup firing unit here!
We're under attack!
Those are OZ's Aries!
Colonel Bundt!
OZ is staging an attack
on our forces!
Our forces?
But Major Nanaki, OZ is
part of our forces!
They sent support troops
to assist us...
...in protecting our nation
from the Gundam menace.
But a number of soldiers were
disgruntled over OZ's support...
...and betrayed us to join
the guerrillas.
Colonel!
What are you saying?!
Exactly what happened.
Once OZ takes over, peace
will be restored to our nation.
I believe the citizens will
feel the same way.
That's absurd!
There's no way the citizens
would want OZ to rule!!
OZ says they'll recognize our
nation's desire to self-govern.
And of course, they'll keep
me on as the Head of State.
Thanks for all your help to date,
Nanaki!
Colonel Bundt!
Can't you think of anything
other than your own rank?
Damn!
That traitor!
Bundt's sold off this
nation to OZ!
It's happened again.
A repeat of senseless wars
by senseless people!
All right!
One more shot will do it!
Hey!
Hey! Hang in there!!
It's you.
I guess I got hit because
I'm weak.
But you can get them...
Destroy OZ.
I'm begging you...
Wu Fei?
Oh no!
Wu Fei, run for it.
It's hopeless now.
We can hold off the enemy
for a bit, so hurry!!
What are you saying, Sally?!
Hey kid, why won't you
fight and help us?!!
I don't have any power.
Don't give me that crap!
If I had even half the
strength you have...
Move!
You're not hurt are you kid?
Help me.
End it for me.
Put an end to our misery...
Wars use people's lives
as mere playthings...
That's why we need
a strong sense of faith!
Sally, what're you doing?!
Wu Fei, you have everything
it takes to help save the weak.
I hope you never lose
sight of your kind heart.
Sally; have you lost your mind?!
I've realized that
healing your heart...
...is more important
than my life.
I'm sure of that.
Run, Sally!
Wu Fei!!
Nataku, I've got no right
to pilot you!
But for now I'm asking you
to lend me your strength!
We're more or less finished.
We just need to secure
that Gundam.
Colonel!
The Gundam's started moving!
What?!
It moved!
It crushed five Aries
with ease.
Colonel, that only leaves us
with a couple more Aries!
Get them to cover our retreat!!
You won't get away.
Wu Fei.
Bundt is out of the picture but
I'm sure OZ will come back...
...to try to take over
this nation.
Are you gonna keep
on fighting?
Justice...it's become such
a cheap word now.
The Alliance and OZ said peace
and justice were their goals.
I have my own sense of justice.
Everybody has their own
sense of justice.
Even you do.
You have it.
Those who are righteous
must also have strength.
The weak have no right to take
advantage of Nataku's strength.
You were different this time.
You had the strength
of your heart.
What good is strength
if it's not from the heart?
Wu Fei, when you're able
to fight with Nataku...
...please help me again.
Even though you're so weak
you're still gonna fight?
The most important thing is
that my heart is strong.
Hey!
Everyone gather around!
Our next performance
is confirmed!
Hold onto your hats!
We got a request from
an OZ base!
From OZ?
And to celebrate I wanna
try something new.
Something special and ex citing
the OZ soldiers might enjoy.
Could you leave this new
performance up to me?
Have you got some ideas?
Yeah and I think it'll be
a big hit with the soldiers.
Wow!
Trowa's usually so quiet,
so it must be a good idea.
Right!
You handle this, Trowa!
I'll leave food and
the car keys.
Stay here and concentrate
on getting better.
What'll you do?
Not everyone in my colony agreed
to fight using the Gundams.
The Gundam attack was started
by a small group...
...who felt strongly about it.
I was one of those people.
There's nothing wrong with
acting on your emotions.
Least that's what I was taught.
I mustn't give OZ an excuse
to invade the colonies.
It wasn't rational.
So I did what you did.
I followed my emotions.
Is this what you'll be
using in the performance?
I promise it'll be a real blast;
like nothing you've seen.
That's the spirit young man!
Make it the show of your life.
Yeah. It'll be my last...
...grandstand show.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Many of OZ's leading officers
are young and relentless.
Is there no one there who
can calmly interpret the war?
Their excessive military power
flies wildly out of control...
...resulting in one unnecessary
massacre after another.
OZ begins its advancement
toward outer space.
In order to save the colonies,
Trowa heads to his final battle.
But Catherine stands before the
young man who hastens his death.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 13,
Catherine's Tears
"Catherine's Tears".