Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
In the year After Colony 175...
...the leader of the colonies
was assassinated.
Five Gundams were sent
to Earth to take revenge.
However, since OZ's activities
in space...
...took the form of cooperation
rather than control...
...the colonies decided
to accept OZ.
The year After Colony 195.
As OZ moves to take over
both Earth and outer space...
...Gundams are labeled rebels
and are isolated from society.
With no place to return...
...the Gundams and
their pilots...
...must fight for a reason to
exist in the changing world.
It's an astro suit!
The astro suit has also
been set as a target!
Cancel it! Hurry!!
I'll eliminate all obstacles.
The Lunar Base Infiltration
Did you say the lunar base?!
That's right.
A large amount of
Gundanium alloy...
...is being brought into
the Lunar Base factory.
It's probably for making
a new type of mobile suit.
So what are your plans?
Just stay here.
- You'll get in the way.
- What do you mean?!
I'm gonna need time to recover,
considering all that's happened.
But how about being a little
kinder to me once in a while?
Why not go to school
instead of me?
I've already got the admission
taken care of, under your name.
What?!
You've gotta be kidding!
Sure, your name would
stick out here, but still!
Instead of complaining,
just rest and get better.
Don't overdo it.
Like he's gonna listen.
Of course he'll overdo it.
I'll decide once I get
to the moon...
...whether to steal the new
mobile suit or destroy it.
With only one sixth the
gravity of Earth...
...the moon wasn't suitable
for human inhabitation.
Upon completion of
the Space Colonies...
...construction was started
on lunar research facilities...
...and major factories of
various sorts.
The moon further developed...
...into a popular tourist
destination for Earthlings.
It prospered until its
suppression by the Alliance.
After OZ dismantled
the Alliance Military...
...the moon was again allowed
to be a tourist destination.
People saw it as a sign that
peace was returning to space.
People are now free to travel
between the colonies.
It seems that OZ has already
seized much of outer space.
They've been handing out
a lot of gifts these days...
...to try and win people over.
Once people trust OZ,
the rest is easy.
Resources and labor will
soon all be controlled by OZ.
Let's build OZ a real rascal
to keep them occupied.
The Mercurius defense system...
...is looking pretty impressive.
And the Vayeate should
start taking shape...
...once the mainframe is built.
Just a matter of time
before it's completed.
I don't intend to work
under OZ forever!
Officially speaking, this is
Lady Une's project.
But they'll be selecting
mobile suit pilots...
...from among the
colony citizens.
This could all become
quite interesting.
I doubt if things will
work out that well.
Heero won't bother with
the selection process.
It's more his style to go
straight for their throats.
In any case we'll complete
the powerful mobile suits...
...that OZ wants so badly.
Then prove that OZ can be
destroyed by its own weapons!
Is OZ really thinking to
establish a nation in space?
Now that we're free from
the Alliance's control...
...civilians can communicate
between the colonies...
...and with the Earth.
We have OZ to thank for that.
But I don't see why they must
try to control our future.
Perhaps, but given the present
size of the Space Colonies...
...it'd be strange for us not
to consider becoming a nation.
That's right, but this is
our problem here.
It says our main industries
will be military technology...
...and mobile suit production.
Colonel.
The colony delegates are having
problems with that document.
That seems natural.
They've seen the Alliance's
reckless use of arms.
To them, a mobile suit
manufacturer...
...is like a merchant of death.
The nations supporting OZ
like space technology...
...only because they can use it
to improve military power.
I can't see the peace-minded
colonies going along with it.
They can think of our plan
for the arms as a deterrent.
Arrangements will be made
to bring what space is lacking.
What space is lacking?
Proper public order.
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
Have you had a chance to read
through our document?
I believe one of the reasons...
...the Space Colonies were
considered a threat to Earth...
...was that the colonies lacked
an organizational structure.
I think forming a nation is
a step in the right direction.
But you're having problems
with the major industries?
Exactly.
How can there be world peace...
...based on this idea that arms
are needed as a deterrent?
History's taught us otherwise.
We can establish a new public
order different from Earth.
We're proud this technology will
be the source of our capital...
...but we shouldn't be
considering military power!
In my heart, I feel this war
has already come to an end.
OZ is a military organization.
We've made an effort to settle
repeated disputes on Earth.
The goal of the United
Earth Sphere Alliance...
...was to achieve peace without
relying on military power.
Just as you're suggesting.
But think what those
strategies gave rise to.
There's no need for
reckless battle.
But you can't discuss
mankind's beauty...
...without acknowledging
the desire to fight.
Am I the only one who
admires man's will to fight?
I hadn't expected OZ to
restore it to this extent.
But I can't hand this
Gundam over to OZ!
Who's there?
I was gonna ask you.
You've gotta be some kind
of expert...
...to sneak in here at night
and set explosives.
Hand me that detonation switch.
I don't care what happens.
You're not getting that Gundam!
No way!
All those explosives and they
didn't even make a dent!
That's disappointing, but
the Gundam's sure impressive!
Damn! She's pretty aggressive!
OZ has found us!
Let's get outta here!
No way!
We've gotta be at least
as brave as that lady!
We must recover Master Quatre's
Gundam at all costs!
Leo troops, get a move on!
The enemy's in the hangar
with the Gundam Zero Four!
There it is!
We barely managed to sneak in
and now look what's happening.
Abdul's plans never work out!
What was that?!
Did you say something?!
I'm in a hurry, so get Master
Quatre's Gundam here pronto!!
What's taking you, Auda?!
Don't fight so close to me!!
It wasn't easy swiping
this carrier!
Don't blame me!
We were supposed to wait
until OZ rebuilt the Gundam!
I didn't expect things would
get moving this quickly!
Hurry up, Ahmad!!
I hear you!
Well?!
We did it! Perfect!
Mission accomplished!
What's that?!
What's wrong?
Why'd you stop?
Damn it!!
Don't even think about fighting!
It's that bloody woman again!
Hey, that's Auda!
I don't think we're enemies!
I sensed that.
But the guy I know would
try to destroy the Gundam.
The guy I know would be
sad if it were destroyed.
We're hoping to restore it
to make him happy.
Does she know a Gundam
pilot as well?
We belong to the Maganac
Corps of the Middle East.
Please leave this Gundam
in our hands!
Sounds like a great kid,
this pilot of yours.
So does your pilot.
Now, I'd better go and
pick up...
...what the other great
kid left behind.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
The following footage is
of an event held today...
...that is very significant
for the colonies' defense.
These young volunteers
are vying for a position...
...to fight for the safety
of the colonies.
Why is everyone going along
with OZ's every word?
The youngsters fared well...
...in a firing test designed
to reflect a real battle.
In the next test, obstacles
representing enemies...
...will be placed along each
mobile suit's path.
The bombs are imitations.
But they carry an impact.
Be careful!
Yes, sir!
Here they come!
Commence attack!
What a disaster.
But they're just amateurs.
I don't believe that guy!
What's with him?!
This is test pilot 1.
I'm finished with the test.
Test pilot 1, confirm your name!
I'm Trowa Barton.
Colonel, Trowa Barton
is extraordinary!
Even though he's been
through some simulations...
...he couldn't make such
maneuvers in his first battle!
What are you implying?
He must've had some
previous training.
At an extremely high level, too!
But his background has
been checked hasn't it?
Yes, and there were no problems.
Then it sounds like he's got
some natural talents.
Talents that he never had
the chance to use before.
But isn't it possible that he's
been sent to destroy OZ?!
He might even be a Gundam pilot!
We'll find out soon enough.
Trowa Barton.
One more test.
Completely destroy the
next target!
That's the...
What?
What's the matter, Trowa Barton?
Fire at the target!!
Colonel!
He is a Gundam pilot,
just as I figured!
I'll get rid of him!
Lend me that beam cannon.
What?!
It's made of Gundanium alloy.
A Leo rifle won't do the job.
A Gundam, responsible for
the misunderstandings...
...between Earth and the
colonies...
...and causing destruction...
...will be destroyed by a colony
citizen wishing for peace.
Ladies and gentlemen,
stand by to witness this!
Hey, Deathscythe.
Don't give up too easily.
You'll be okay, right?
You'll come out fine, right?
About to commence second test.
Damn!
NO!!!
Trowa Barton's brain waves
and pulse remain unchanged.
Then he's the perfect pilot.
But I still have some doubts
about him.
That boy's clearly willing
to cooperate with OZ.
People with talent are capable
of understanding us.
What's this?
Those sparkles...
They're my tears.
The new type of mobile suits.
Many of the parts are
still being designed.
I'll go destroy them.
Test pilot No. 1; Colonel Une
wishes to speak with you.
Wait there!
I understand.
Colonel Une!
It's dangerous!
It's still possible that
he's a Gundam pilot!
I think it'd be wiser
to meet him by myself.
Huh?
He's come to try and
understand OZ.
It'd be rude not to meet
with him.
I'm sure we'll have a lot
to talk about.
As two individuals who
love outer space.
Colonel!
Lieutenant Nichol,
what are you so afraid of?
Afraid of?
Let's put an end to
the fighting, shall we?
My name is Lady Une.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
So this is Lady Une.
Chief Commander of
OZ's Space Operations.
So you've had experience
with labor mobile suits...
...in your job repairing
the colony's outer walls.
Your outstanding test
results today...
...have the OZ soldiers
completely baffled.
I've always felt I had what
it'd take to be a soldier.
So then I'm hired?
Let's work together to bring
peace to outer space.
I'm just hoping that my
abilities will come in handy...
...to defeat the Alliance's
Space Forces.
I'd never thought about
peace in outer space.
Then I thought of myself as
the right type of person for OZ.
The right type of person?
I'm impressed how OZ is
gradually taking over space...
...while appearing to act
out of friendship.
People may think of it
as foul play, but it suits me.
Taking over?
What do you mean, "foul play"?
OZ is a place where the
crafty are acknowledged.
That's what it's about.
No.
No...
It's not true!
Colonel!
She needs to get some rest!
Please, Colonel.
Come this way.
What happened to her?
You might have tricked
the Colonel, but not me.
Trowa Barton.
The Colonel has ordered
you...
...to come back in two hours
to test OZ's new mobile suits.
But just now the Colonel...
Lady Une is a much stronger
person in her uniform.
She might feel like killing
someone as questionable as you.
So I'm Lady Une of OZ?
Or do I work under Treize?
Didn't take you long
to find your pilots, did it?
These five have been selected
from the colony citizens...
...as prospective pilots.
And this is Trowa Barton.
He's outstanding.
He should be able
to control any suit.
These mobile suits of ours
won't be simple to control.
I hear they're better than
the Gundams.
I can't wait.
How far have you gotten?
The Mercurius is 80%
complete...
...and the Vayeate is about
50% complete.
What's the reason for
developing two models?
We designed these two
suit models...
...as opposing principles in
battle...
...that is, offense and defense
in their extremes.
With the Vayeate, we added the
largest possible beam cannon...
...without affecting mobility.
And with the Mercurius
we added a defense shield...
...to withstand such a beam
cannon attack.
Which would win if they
were to fight each other?
Naturally, the one with
the better pilot would win.
Who are you kidding?!
So the race to determine the
superiority of mobile suits...
...is meaningless, since
their value...
...is directly dependent on
the abilities of the pilot?
You're sharp; I see why
you were selected by OZ.
You're right!
Silence Trowa!
Leave him alone!
He'll be piloting one
of those suits.
I'll allow his questions.
Uh, yes ma'am.
What tests will you be
demonstrating for us today?
Right!
I'll show you the defense
system of the Mercurius.
It's the latest system, which
creates an electric field...
...to allow it to reflect any
beam fired by the enemy.
And the Vayeate?
The Vayeate still needs
some work.
It isn't even charged
with energy yet.
What's that?
The Vayeate's moving!
Activate the Mercurius shield!
Got it!
Colonel!
Are you gonna make it?
Ouch...
What'd I tell you?
My weapon, he's something,
don't you think?
That's for sure.
He even came after us!
That's some weapon!
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
A white mobile suit
approaches a colony.
Once it's determined to
be Zechs' Tallgeese...
...Lady Une orders Trowa
and Heero to attack it.
The injured Quatre returns
to the Winner residence.
But, to his great sadness,
there he finds his father...
...being solely blamed and
criticized by the people.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 21,
Grief Stricken Quatre
"Grief Stricken Quatre".