I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Well? Are we out of the missiles' range?
Seems like it.
We're safe at this distance. Damn them.
We'll keep our distance and observe.
Come on. What the hell are you doing?
Hey, are you all right?
You said nothing about detonating it
without any warning!
What if we'd flooded the place?
Your method is too violent!
We can't be screwing around.
The more we fuss the less time
we have to do our job.
Fine, but you could've said
something to me ahead of time!
How do you expect me
to talk underwater?
You could pay closer
attention to what I'm doing.
In any case, give me a signal or
something before...
...you do anything like that!
B-Bones! Bones!
Well yeah, there're gonna be bones.
They're all over the place.
Rock, this is a graveyard that people
living on the surface have forgotten.
It's where they reluctantly
ended their lives...
...when confronted by the Grim Reaper.
No flowers or candles.
No one comes and no one remembers.
A sickening catacomb without any saints.
I've never liked these kinds of places.
It smells like something's rotten.
If we stay too long, it'll affect our lungs.
Hey, Revy.
How do you think these guys felt
while they waited down here?
What went through their minds
once the lights faded...
...and they struggled to breathe?
That's too damn gloomy.
How do you expect me to know?
Dying without air could only
feel like dying without air.
How strangers die is just
how strangers die.
Thinking about it isn't gonna
do a damned thing, Rock.
Just think of things that won't bother you.
Look at this. These guys...
Looks like they had their own
"Gunfight at the OK Corral" right here.
Captain.
Captain! You bastard!
How dare you shoot the captain!
Revy, this is probably
the skeleton of the captain.
That Ahbe guy, right?
Is his iron cross lying around
somewhere? It'll be worth something.
Come over here.
This guy's uniform is different.
He's the SS.
Where's the painting?
I don't know.
If it's not here it's got to be in a safe.
But what made them engage
in a gunfight, anyway?
Panic caused by desperation?
That's a laughable theory.
Despair is the same as the end of cancer.
You've got nothing left to lose.
Well, I don't know the details but this
Gestapo was the one that shot first.
The sailors came in here
to avenge their captain.
And it ended with the
"Last Stand at the Alamo".
Aboard a ship, everyone's
practically family.
They wouldn't have fought amongst
themselves knowing they were gonna die.
The only one that would start
a fight would be the outsider.
Is that how it works?
That's how it works.
What is it, Rock?
Is that the goods?
This is it. It's the same
as the image on file.
Yeah! This is it, Rock! You put it away.
I'll go get the rest.
The rest?
This is what we're after.
We're not kids on an errand, Rock.
If we don't grab everything that's
worth some money, it's a wasted trip.
The captain had an iron cross
with a sword.
It's a valuable piece with a diamond on it.
It's a little too valuable
to leave behind as fish food.
But... Hey!
I'll be back as soon as I've got everything
worth taking. Keep those guys company.
Shut up. Don't stare.
I don't think it's the right
thing to do either.
What's the distance, Benny-boy?
It was 5,200 yards when I last checked.
We're well out of range.
What a dangerous bunch.
They're maniacs.
And seeing that they launched three
at once, they're well equipped too.
They're directly above that U-boat.
We can't do a damned thing.
All soldiers line up in position! Standby
for the Commander's instructions!
Gentlemen! My beloved braves of
the White Aryan Socialist Union.
Today, at this moment, you will witness...
...the creation of a new world!
In one stroke, we will reclaim
the great order that was lost...
...in the great war due to the interference
of the Zionists and Communists.
True patriots are counting on you,
gentlemen on the front lines!
This is an act of courage for
strict order and patriotism!
To restore the racial hierarchy
to the way it was meant to be!
Suicide Corps, salute!
Kruppen Feller!
You are the hero chosen
to fulfill this objective.
You represent the courage
of the Aryan race.
There has never... There has never
been a more glorious moment! I...
I cannot find words to express
this through my emotion and tears.
I'm filled with emotion, Commander!
I will fulfill this sacred duty
at the cost of my life!
Commence singing of the anthem!
Raise our flag up high!
Pave the road ahead of us!
We, the strike force...
Will firmly march forward!
Towards the last battle...
Hey, hey, hey.
Take a look at this, Dutch.
They're holding a concert.
It's some distasteful marching song.
I can hear it.
You have a worthless guy live it up by
raising his useless self onto a podium...
...and you end up with
a march-loving idiot.
It's a common formula
you'll find anywhere.
What do you think, as a white man?
That kinda machismo doesn't
agree with me.
Besides, I'm Jewish.
"Fuck the Nazis" was a family creed.
Oh right, I forgot.
By the way, are the beacons on yet?
They're both still in the submarine.
Unfortunately, there's nothing we can
do but pick at each other's politics.
I'm not worried about the job,
but I am worried about the time.
Yeah. That'll always be a problem.
If we had the time to retrieve it
I'd take the whole sub back to port.
That way, I could show those
parading idiots...
...on that piece of crap ship
what their Fuhrer went through.
I feel the same way.
Hey, this isn't good.
Those guys are up to something.
They're lowering a pod.
At this rate they're gonna face
each other in the submarine.
What should we do, Dutch?
There's nothing we can do.
They still have TOWs.
It bugs me to say so, but we'll wait for
our chance like a snake.
If you want, you can pray while you shit.
That's about all we can do now.
Phew. Big catch, big catch.
I found everything from the iron crosses
to stuff maniacs will drool over...
...a treasure mountain worthy
of a grave robber's dreams.
Revy.
I've been thinking a lot and...
Let's leave that here.
Hey now, give me a break.
"Thou shalt not steal"?
When did you become a priest?
That's not my point.
Those medals are proof of what
these people did.
We don't have the right to strip
them of those.
If anyone has the right to those medals...
...it's these people. Isn't that right?
It was right next to his body.
The captain had this on him
right until the end.
The captain left his family to come here.
To us the medals are nothing
but antiques.
But to the people who were left behind
they're priceless memories.
So that's how you think.
I see. Given this location and all.
I've got a story that's
perfect for this atmosphere.
I'll tell you a little secret, Rock.
Let me ask you this.
This, and this. What would
you call these?
A medal and a human skull.
You're wrong, Rock.
These are things.
When you strip away their meanings,
that's all they are.
Just the word "things".
And if you were to once again
give these things meaning...
...their value wouldn't be determined
by some rosy, so-called memory.
It would be determined by the one thing
everybody agrees on.
Money.
That's all these are worth.
The rest is nothing but fancy
words to add appreciation.
Is money... God?
It's power. Something a lot
more useful than God.
Rock. Besides this,
what do you put value on?
God? Love? Don't make me laugh.
Back when I was a brat, and crawling
the streets of that dump...
...for whatever reason, God and love
were always out of stock.
Before I knew better,
I clung to and cried out to God.
Well, I believed in God...
...right up to the day cops beat the hell
outta me for something I didn't do.
It was just because I lived
in a poor neighborhood.
With no power and no God,
what can a Chinese bitch rely on?
It's money. And guns.
With those two things,
the world's a great place.
I'd rather not have heard that. Sorry.
Shut up.
If I wanted pity I would've added
more color to the story.
The moral of the story is that when
you're living on life's edge...
...that's all that matters.
Not everybody can get off
on being normal, Rock.
And one more thing.
There are wealthy fat bastards
living by palm trees...
...and bitches who think putting on
makeup is life's greatest work.
I don't want you speaking your mind from
the same viewpoint as those hypocrites.
There's nothing worse than being treated
like a whore by your companions.
So the next time you try telling me what's
proper, you'll no longer be one of us.
When that happens... I'm gonna kill you.
Yeah, I got it.
Revy. What was that?
Revy!
Go somewhere where bullets won't
find you, and keep quiet, Rock.
The only ones that knock on a door
in a place like this are ghosts or villains.
And since ghosts don't
exist in this world...
...that would mean we've
got troublemakers.
We left our gear on the other side.
There's only one passageway.
There's no escape.
One.
Two.
There are more.
Rock, you have a lot to learn.
What you need to listen for are
the guns on their belts.
What do we do?
Why, that's obvious. Kill them all!
Rock, get our air!
Grave-robbers. There are two of them.
John! Around to the other side!
Rock! Get down!
Damn it. The painting.
It's Brunhilda. We got it!
Cover me. I'm off.
They got the painting.
Yeah.
They're not getting away that easily!
Disconnect the pod!
But Richert and the others
are still down there!
Forget them.
They're already dead. Hurry!
Run Rock! We need to get to our gear!
The beacons are on.
Where are they?
Directly above the submarine.
What are they doing?
Where are they going?
Their position isn't changing.
They're going straight up.
Towards the Nazi mother ship.
We did it, Captain. We have the painting.
You did well!
But we have enemies.
She can't be planning to do it.
Revy and Rock don't know who they're
up against. She's probably gonna do it.
Damn it. These guys shoot
anti-tank missiles without warning.
Revy's equipment isn't gonna be enough.
If she surfaces without a clue,
it's gonna be over.
Not yet. It's too soon.
But Dutch.
Want to show some bravado,
charge in, and all go to hell together?
It may paint a great picture, but it won't
be much of an ending, boy.
Just pray that
Revy hasn't snapped yet.
The grave robbers are coming up.
The grave robbers are coming up!
Get ready to fire the machine gun!
Fire!
They started.
Is it all right?
If they're still shooting,
it means they're alive.
They've stopped shooting.
Looks that way.
We got them! They've sunk!
You idiots.
It was your misfortune to touch our
glorious inheritance with your dirty hands.
You can regret it at
the bottom of the dark sea.
Retrieve the pod. We're leaving this area.
The beacons are still active. They're
drifting southeast, away from the ship.
I can't tell whether they're dead or alive.
Can you hear me, Dutch?
Yeah. Their mother ship is moving.
Shall we go and pick up some bones?
That's a harsh remark, boy.
My nerves aren't as tough as yours.
I know.
Revy, look. There's our boat.
So they got away with the goods.
Who the hell are they?
Those bald bastards.
They're Nazis.
Leftovers from the dark ages.
I don't know which country
they came from, though.
Damn it, this isn't funny.
The skinheads got one over us?
It's not over yet, Revy.
The job we took on isn't finished.
Let's do it, Dutch! Let's turn
the Nazi Party into a bloody party.
Agreed.
Putting politics aside, it's not good for
business to let them have it their way.
Idiots playing heroes need some bitter
medicine. Let's give it to them.
Yeah.
Next Episode
But Dutch, it's just not possible.
I can't partner with him.