I only sent a little bit of my ki your way, and you came rushing over.
Your big sister is really moved.
Nee-sama, what is the meaning of this?
Don't make such a scary face.
I heard there was a big party happening around here.
And it just happened to pique my curiosity.
so
no
mu
If you listen to the voice of your heart
You'll be born anew again and again
born
born
new
mo
u
ko
I can't hide it anymore
The purported salvation is but a mirror paradox
Trying to come to terms with myself
I realized my soul must lie with my wishes
The moment we met, the warmth of the tears
de
ta
shun
shun
ta
kan
shun
Falling off your palm ignited my heart
And we understood the DxD each other felt
I've been waiting
What's there to be gained amid all the despair?
It's not bliss but rather a good feeling
feel
feel
ing
so
no
mu
Until I reach deep inside your heart
I'll call out your name again and again
your
name
your
name
Episode
Cat and Dragon
I hope Koneko-chan's okay.
She's been acting strange lately.
Koneko is trying her best to face her own power and very existence.
Are you adjusting well?
I'm sorry.
It's fine. I know that you're always trying your hardest.
I want to become strong.
I understand that, but there's no meaning in that if you sacrifice your health.
Yuuto-senpai, Xenovia-senpai, Akeno-san, and Issei-senpai...
I want to strengthen my mind and body like them.
Even Gya-kun is getting stronger.
And I don't have the power to heal others like Asia-senpai.
Koneko, you've also—
At this rate, I'll become useless.
Even though I'm a rook, I'm the weakest out of everyone.
I don't want to be useless!
But I also don't want to use my Nekomata powers.
If I use them, I'll end up just like my sister.
I can't!
I can't ever let that happen again!
Her existence and her power...
This is a hurdle that Koneko must overcome by herself.
Yes. It's the same for everyone.
I don't see Issei-san anywhere.
Now that you mention it,
I don't see President Rias, either.
Oh. Good work, Baraqiel.
It's been a while, you old,
Northern-countryside piece of shit.
It's been a long time, you cheeky fallen angel.
It has been a long time,
Odin-dono, God of the North.
Sirzechs, I am here in accordance with your invitation.
Welcome, Odin-sama.
Not good, Serafall.
What do you mean?
A young lady such as yourself should not be dressed in such drab clothing at a party.
Well, then.
Mirurun mirumiru spiral!
Oh? What is this?
Oh, you don't know? This is a magical girl.
Hmm, that's not bad.
Please remember why you're here, Odin-sama!
You represent all of Valhalla!
Goodness, you're always so serious.
That's why you can't get a single hero for yourself.
I'm just an unattractive Valkyrie
who's been single her whole life!
Sorry. This one here is Rossweisse-chan.
She's talented, but she's too serious. She can't even get one boyfriend.
I am very sorry for making you wait.
Odin-dono, I am glad to see you in good health.
Irina!
Did she come to accompany Michael-sama?
To think we'd meet again at a place like this!
Why did you come here?
Shirone, I came to pick you up.
I ran away so desperately that
I wasn't able to take you with me.
Kuroka.
Could that cat woman be Koneko-chan's...
She's her sister.
Hey, Kuroka!
The Khaos Brigade!
What is it, Bikou?
Are you just going to ignore
the rats hiding in the shadows?
With our knowledge of the sage arts,
we can easily sense others by the flow of ki.
Issei-senpai! President!
Kuroka, Koneko is a member of my peerage.
I won't let you lay a finger on her.
My, my. What are you saying?
That's my little sister.
I'm not going to give her to a high-class devil like you.
Hey, you monkey piece of shit. How's Vali doing?
He's okay.
Who is this boy?
He's the Red Dragon Emperor.
So this is the breast-lover that made Vali retreat?
What did you say?!
Well, it is true.
Nee-sama, why?
Ophis and Vali will happily accept you.
You have the same power running through your veins as me.
I am part of Rias Gremory-sama's peerage.
We'll never hand over Koneko-chan!
I'll take her by force if I have to.
Well, it'll help to kill some time if you're putting up a fight.
Kill some time?
Devils, gods, and fallen angels have reflected on the past and allied together,
but there are ones those wish to start another war.
We lured her little sister out so we could kill some time while we waited.
The new alliance with the Norse gods of Asgard is truly heartening.
Vali asked us to bring a certain man out here.
Odin-dono, if you have no objections,
please sign the pact monument.
Very well.
I guess he wanted to complain about the gathering tonight.
I have an objection!
So you came, after all.
Foolish man.
I am the Norse god, Loki!
Well, this is a rare guest.
Loki-dono, although you are a Norse god,
you have no right to create havoc here.
Seeing our Great Father mingling with other mythologies brings me intolerable pain.
Loki, if you return to Valhalla now, I will forgive you.
Forgive me? Don't make me laugh, you old fart.
You dare speak to our Great Father like that!
If he allies us with other mythologies,
we will be unable to achieve Ragnarok!
I've heard this argument before.
You're connected to the Khaos Brigade, aren't you?
I admit I've partnered with them.
But this is of my own will!
Come forth, my beloved son!
Issei! Koneko! We have to hurry back!
What?
I created a barrier over the entire forest and locked us in.
I hope you can provide me with some
entertainment, Red Dragon Emperor!
Th-These guys are strong!
Such dark auras.
Old man Tannin!
So you followed my power's energy signature.
Huh?
That's right.
I've been keeping track of the power signature emitted by the Red Dragon Emperor
since there was something about
Hyoudou Issei that was bothering me.
Bothering you?
Hey, look! It's the previous dragon king!
You look so happy, monkey.
Jindou Yun!
Extend, Ruyi Jinbu Bang!
You're good! Previous dragon king!
No way!
That firepower is on a completely different level from the training!
Son Goku! How entertaining!
Son Goku and a dragon.
Well, that's a fitting pair.
Anyway, could you hand over my little sister already?
If you don't, I'll kill you on the spot.
Rias! Hyoudou Issei!
I will take care of this monkey. Defeat that cat.
Aren't you two the Red Dragon Emperor and his master?
He makes it sound so easy!
The enemy is Koneko's sister.
I can't fight her in front of Koneko.
Nee-sama, I will go with you.
Koneko-chan?!
What are you saying?!
Please let these two go.
Koneko! You are my servant and a member of my household!
I refuse to let you do as you please!
I know my sister's power
better than anyone else.
Don't worry.
I will protect you.
I understand Shirone's power better than someone like you.
Come here, Shirone.
I'll train you to be one of
the best in the sage arts.
No. I don't need powers like that.
I don't need powers that
bring misfortune to others.
Kuroka!
When you were indulging in your own power,
you traumatized her for life.
When you left after killing your master, her life became hell.
When I first met her, she was nothing but an empty shell.
Koneko was betrayed by her only family.
She had no one to turn to.
The other devils despised her so much that she almost got eliminated.
This girl has seen many painful things.
President Rias.
And that's why I will show her many wonderful things.
I don't want to go.
Kuroka-neesama, I don't want to go with you!
I am Toujou Koneko.
I am going to live... live together with President Rias!
This girl is Rias Gremory's rook, Toujou Koneko!
She is a treasured devil within my household.
I will not allow you to lay a finger on her!
President! This is why you're the best!
I will protect the President and Koneko-chan!
Issei!
Even though you know you can't win?
Are you stupid?
Then die.
Wh-What?
This is...
President! Koneko-chan?!
It always works well on devils and spirits.
I guess it doesn't affect dragons, though.
You bitch!
I used a weaker poison, so their lives aren't in danger just yet.
I want to kill you all slowly.
I will not allow you to attack this girl!
You fool.
Too many openings.
Beelzebub?!
Ajuka.
Are you all right?
That was a nice attack, but it's futile!
Boosted Gear!
Huh? H-Hey!
As I thought.
What's the meaning of this, old man?!
This is the result of your training with Tannin, partner.
You now have to choose whether you
want to power up or to Balance Break.
Does that mean it's possible to reach Balance Breaker?!
But you cannot reach Balance Breaker without an extreme catalyst.
Extreme?
The rest is up to you.
Even with you telling me that right now, I still have no idea what to do!
Oh, my.
So the Red Dragon Emperor is going to die without activating his Sacred Gear?
I'm still going to attack!
Issei!
You can't, President!
If you move, the poison will spread faster!
Issei-senpai, I beg you. Please, stop.
So weak! This is Vali's rival?
Did he really make Vali retreat?
Shit!
I'm always like this!
I helped Asia? I saved the President?
Everyone praises me, but it's not like that!
It's not like that at all!
I once let Asia die!
I once made President cry!
If I can't save them the first time around,
how can I call myself a legendary dragon?!
Issei!
I can't bring out my power
until after someone gets hurt.
There's no meaning to a power like that!
Even if you are Koneko-chan's older sister,
I can't forgive anyone who makes her cry!
I feel bad for Shirone.
Saying that while covered in mud and blood will only creep a girl out.
You're so gross!
Issei-senpai...
Koneko-chan.
Even though I have a legendary dragon in me, I can't do anything.
I'm a useless devil with no talents.
I've heard that Red Dragon Emperors are often consumed by their power.
My sister is the same.
Even if they're powerful, they go berserk if they lack kindness.
I think you are the first Red Dragon Emperor in history that's kind.
So even if you lack some power,
please become a kind Welsh Dragon.
Koneko-chan, I...
...you cannot reach Balance Breaker without an extreme catalyst.
I see! So that's what it means!
You finally realized it.
President! I think I know what I'm missing!
I think I need your power to reach Balance Breaker, President!
I will do anything I can for you.
Please let me poke your boobs.
Very well.
If that's what's needed to culminate your feelings...
Really?! I'm going to poke them!
I'm going to push in your nipple!
Is that okay?!
Hurry up!
It's embarrassing.
What are you doing in the middle of battle?!
Old man! Fend them off while I poke President's breast!
Poke her breast?! You're going to poke her breast?!
What are you trying to do in the middle of battle?!
Isn't it obvious?! I'm trying to reach Balance Breaker!
Was training with me useless?!
Are you really that stupid?!
Hey, Bikou. Is that some kind of strategy?
Rias Gremory just exposed her breasts to the Red Dragon Emperor.
Don't ask me!
Old man! We have a problem!
What is it? Did something happen?!
The left boob or the right boob! Which one should I poke?!
You idiot! They're the same!
Just poke her breast already!
Don't mess with me!
There's no way they're both the same!
This is important!
This is my first time pressing the buzzer!
A wrong choice here could ruin my life! Answer me seriously!
President! Which do you suggest?
You idiot!
Just poke both of them simultaneously!
Simultaneously?!
What an ingenious piece of advice!
Here I go, President!
Press it, and a sound comes out.
If I push them, a sound will come out!
No!
It did!
You've reached it! You've really reached it!
Welsh Dragon Balance Breaker!
You're the worst.
What a perverted Red Dragon Emperor...
Balance Breaker Boosted Gear, Scale Mail!
I have come forth after poking my master's breasts!
Partner, congratulations.
That said, you're truly terrible.
Your actions will make me weep with sorrow one of these days.
All things aside, you've finally achieved it!
Such a powerful energy signature!
How interesting!
Then, let me welcome you with a mix of sage and demon arts!
That's it?
Don't get so cocky!
Don't make my cute junior cry!
If you ever come after Koneko-chan again,
even if you are a woman or Koneko-chan's big sister,
you are my enemy!
You stupid brat!
What are you doing?!
It's not over yet!
You got so excited that you didn't notice?
Huh?
Loki's presence... But why?
Who knows? What matters is that we don't have time to play around anymore.
I see. His accomplices from Khaos Brigade were...
...Bikou and Kuroka.
And the girl? Is she all right?
She was a bit shocked,
but she's fine now.
She is a member of my peerage, after all.
Looks like I was right to give her to you.
Rias, you've grown wonderfully as the master of your peerage.
It was a crazy day.
Relaxing like this seems so unreal.
Irina-san seemed to be doing well.
How sad. Your sister has become your enemy.
I can't erase a bond made of blood.
Very true...
That's why...
I've decided not to worry about it.
Also, I will become stronger.
My, my. That's very reassuring.
Oh, Issei. What's wrong?
Oh, President.
I was going to take a bath,
but I got separated from Kiba and the others.
I'm heading that way, so let's go together.
Um, President. Can I ask you something?
What is it?
How did you realize so quickly that I was chasing after Koneko-chan?
You thought that I wouldn't?
I am always watching over you.
You're amazing, President.
You're always looking after us, no matter what.
Looks like we made it through, for now.
Ajuka teleported Loki and Fenrir to a far-off land,
but that is only a temporary solution.
Indeed. I am sure that he will attack again.
As the leader of the Norse mythology, I take full responsibility.
sou daitai no koto nante
Well, yeah, I do think that
mou wakatte wa iru na tte
I've got this stuff mostly figured out
omou yo dakedo ne
But still, you know
kokoro wa bannou ja nai
Feelings on their own can only get you so far
daiji na koto bakka ishin fudenshin
The stuff that matter isn't getting across
saishuuteki ni wa analog tsuushin
So we have to rely on analog communication
dakara ima sugu
That's why, right now
motto chanto katachi ni shite yo
I want you to be more concrete
kimi ga
Do it
ijiwaru na voice
With your flirty voice
give me kikasete yo
Give me, just tell me
chotto dake de ii no
Just a little hint is fine
aimai na no wa yada na
Don't leave me hanging
no secret sansei
No secrets, yeah?
do you do you know
Do you know?
answer todokete ne
Give me your answer
kowaku nante nai shi
I'm not afraid to hear it
ienai kedo nee wakaru desho
I don't have to actually tell you, right?
wakatte yo
Take the hint
tell me heart tell me heart
Tell me your heart
subete wo kaeru no wa
If you want to take it to the next step
give me word give me word
Give me your word
itsu de mo kimi dakara
The power is in your hands
Next Episode:
I have come to accompany our Great Father, Odin-sama.
My name is Rossweisse.
Look, Hyoudou!
She was wearing a suit last time,
but what a wonderful form this is!
Episode
Interception, Commence!
Ow ow ow!