This guy's the leader of the Angels.
He's a real big shot, right?
So why's he...
What the?
My whole body's tingling.
No, it's not from him.
Hyoudou Issei-kun.
Y-Yes?
This is a Dragon Slayer,
a Holy Sword which can end a Dragon's life.
The Ascalon.
Takaga shireteta terai ga uzumaite
My puny arrogance came back to me
Oisugaru koto mo dekizu ni ita yo
and I couldn't go to you for help
Namida no wake kimi ni ienai mama de
I couldn't tell you why I was crying
Kuchibiru wa itsumo sora wo nirande ita
and always frowned up to the sky
Uzumoreteta yami yori kimi ga koete kita kyoukaisen
You dug through the darkness to cross this line
Sekai system wa kakumeigire
The world's out of changes to make
Kaikan itami hakai souzou
Pleasure, pain, destruction, creation
Kaete yuku watashi no yowasa wo
I'm going to change my own weaknesses
Ima oshiyoseru kanjouron
All I can make are appeals to emotion
Inochi gake no ai wa amakunaiwa
Love's not easy with my life on the line
Tsuyoku motto tsuyoku
Stronger, even stronger
Donna uso ga matteita to shitemo
No matter what lies I face
Eranda michibiki shinjite
I've already chosen which signs to follow
Furumau koto wa nai to yasashii akuma no hohoemi wa
The devil smiles at me, telling me to be myself
Hakanaku subete wo terasu no
and shines a faint light on the world
Episode 10
Various Three-Way Deadlocks!
I-It kills dragons?!
The name "Dragon Slayer"
refers to those who hunt Dragons for a living,
and the equipment that they use.
So this is what that tingling was.
I would like to give this to you.
Huh?
T-To me?
Perhaps I should say "merge it with your Boosted Gear."
Since you're said to be the weakest host in history,
I believe it would give you a fine boost in power.
The weakest...
I'm doing the best I can, you know?
Though I can't say I'm not weak.
But why help me?
There have been no large battles since the end of the Great War,
but as you may know,
skirmishes between the three factions still occur from time to time.
So that was just a skirmish, then.
If this situation continues,
all three will some day come to ruin.
Or... even before then, some other faction may take the opportunity to attack us.
Another faction?
The three factions are only the
largest of many mythical factions.
I believe this conference will be a great opportunity.
An opportunity?
For the three factions to work together,
and stop war once and for all.
Stop war...
In the Great War,
there was a time when we fought together...
to slay the Red and White Dragons who were running amok on the battlefield.
Back then I put a charm on you, or rather, the Emperor of Red Dragon,
to bring us together once again.
Issei-kun, let us accept his gift.
O-Okay.
If you say so, Akeno-san.
I'm meant to merge with a Holy Sword?
Is that even possible?
A Sacred Gear answers to its wielder's will.
If you have the will to do it, it shouldn't be a problem.
If I have the will...
Partner, concentrate on your Boosted Gear.
All right!
Synchronize your energy with the sword's!
They fused?!
My task here is complete.
I'll be leaving now.
Hey...
I...
I need to ask you something.
I'm afraid I haven't any time to spare.
I will see you during or after the conference.
Please do.
I will. I promise you that,
Hyoudou Issei.
Akeno-san, you and Michael-san brought the sword here and...
That's right.
We performed a few rituals to alter the properties of the Ascalon.
Oh, thank you.
Um, can I ask you something?
What is it?
During our fight with Kokabiel, he said...
You dare try to stop me, wielder of Barakiel's power?
Do not...
associate me with that name!
Akeno-san, you're...
the daughter of a Fallen Angel...
That's right.
My birth was the result of the union between Barakiel, a leader of the Fallen Angels, and a human.
My mother lived at a shrine.
One day, she found Barakiel, wounded, and helped him.
I was conceived as a result of that encounter.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have pried.
That wing...
Yes.
I have both Devil and Fallen Angel wings.
It was in the hope that I could be rid of these... wicked wings,
that I met Rias and became a Devil.
However, all that did
was make me an abomination with both Devil and Fallen Angel wings.
Perhaps it's fitting for a woman of wicked blood, like myself.
Akeno-san...
What do you think of such a monstrosity?
Don't you hate Fallen Angels?
You and Asia-chan had your bodies and hearts scarred by them.
They took both your lives,
and they even tried to destroy your hometown.
There's no doubt that you would hate them.
Yes.
I do hate Fallen Angels,
but, Akeno-san, I like you!
Sorry.
I shouldn't have asked.
Sometimes, I'm just so insensitive!
Don't concern yourself.
My father is...
It doesn't matter to me.
But what if the reason I had been aggressively approaching you
was so that you wouldn't hate me for being a Fallen Angel?
You would never do such a thing!
Yes, I would.
I truly am a "witch".
No!
No matter what happens, to me you'll always be my caring senpai.
I-I mean, uh...
I do hate Fallen Angels,
but no matter who you are,
you'll always be the same Akeno-san I've always known,
the Occult Research Club's strongest Vice President!
And I don't know how to put this,
but even if you're a half-Fallen Angel,
I still like you, Akeno-san!
So, uh...
I don't think it's a problem.
Wait, what the hell am I saying?
You just...
stole my heart.
What else can I do but love you now?
Sorry, I really don't know what I'm saying.
I really wish I did, though.
I'm just dull as a brick.
Sorry, Akeno-sa-
A-Akeno-san?!
I've made my decision.
Huh?
Y-Your decision?
Hey, Issei-kun...
Yes?
I don't mind being third.
Third?
Yes, third.
It's not too bad of a place to rank.
Not to mention,
it feels like I'm having an affair. It's thrilling.
Wh-What would you happen to be talking about?
Issei-kun.
Ask anything of me, and I'll do it for you.
If President won't let you,
you can rest on my lap, instead.
O-On your lap?!
Issei-kun,
would you please call me "Akeno?"
I-I can't just call my senpai by her name alone.
Just once!
Please!
A-Akeno...
Thank you, Issei!
There's nothing quite like having boobs pressed up against you!
Hey, when it's just the two of us.
would you please call me "Akeno?"
She's so adorable...
I feel like my brain's melting.
First President, and now the older woman of my dreams!
I'm at a loss for words!
It looks like I've taken some of Rias' exclusive rights.
This feels so scandalous.
Issei-kun,
how do you like it?
I'm in heaven!
I've never been so comfortable,
but if President saw this...
What was that about your president?
Hm, Issei?
P-P-P-President?!
I'm gonna die!
My, my.
I-I can explain!
W-We just...
I...
I, uh...
P-Pres...
I can't take my eyes off you for a minute, can I?
Did you get the sword?
Yes!
Where's Michael?
He's gone.
Then there's nothing more to do here.
Let's go.
Yes, Ma'am.
I wish I were the furthest up on the list.
S-See you later, Akeno-san.
President!
Yep, she's pissed.
Hey, Issei...
Y-Yes?!
Akeno will always be Akeno, won't she?
Uh, yeah?
We call Akeno "Vice President,"
but she's still Akeno, isn't she?
What about me?
You're President Rias.
That's right.
I am "President,"
but am I not "Rias," too?
Yes!
You're my master,
and you're the High Class Devil Rias Gremory-sama!
I'm not the furthest up.
I'm the furthest away.
P-President?!
The conference is tomorrow.
I need to finish the preparations.
Issei, what are you planning to do?
I'm going back to the school.
I've got to train Gasper.
All right.
See you later, then.
President?
Good!
You're getting one in twenty now!
Yeah, that's great progress!
Asia, next one!
All right!
Ready, Gasper?
Yes!
Gasper-kun!
Issei-senpai, I'm tired!
Stop whining!
We have a dream!
We're going to make it come true, Gasper!
Issei-senpai!
I'm just dying for you to master your time stopping
and to allow me touch all those girls!
Forgive me!
I'm making you go through all this,
but it's all for your own good!
I've learned my lesson, Issei-senpai!
Gasper!
Issei-senpai!
What a touching moment...
Okay! Let's go, Gasper!
Yes, Issei-senpai!
Gasper, you're not supposed to stop my arm.
I did it wrong again!
I'm sorry!
Well, don't sweat it.
Practice makes perfect.
B-But...
You're definitely improving.
You stopped me completely back when we started.
I'm neither a complete Devil nor a Vampire,
so I never get anything-
Gasper!
Wh-What?!
Don't think about nonsense!
It'll only distract you!
Give me all you've got before you start crying!
Then I'll really know what you can do!
Don't... think?
I like you!
Naturally, Asia does, too!
I do!
Gasper-kun.
I like you, Gasper-kun!
Y-You like me?
Why wouldn't we?
We're in the same club,
and we're all President Rias' family.
Issei-senpai, Asia-senpai, I'll do my best!
That's the spirit!
Right!
Okay, I'll put this on to power up.
Quit it! You're creeping me out!
Keep going, Issei-san, Gasper-kun!
Gasper, you've got a pretty girl rooting for you!
You'd better get it right!
Right!
Thank you, Asia-senpai!
Aren't you going to help them?
For some reason, Gasper cries at the sight of my face.
I was trying so hard to train him, too.
I've seen that look on Issei-senpai's face before.
Before?
During our club trip...
when he was working on his lewd move.
Are you talking about Dress Break?
Yes.
Let's make our dream come true!
A hundred more throws!
Any time!
Okay, one more!
Um, Issei-san.
Huh?
What's this dream that you and Gasper-kun are talking about?
I'll tell you!
I'm going to freeze the girls-
I'm afraid I can't tell you just yet.
It's not that I'm really qualified to teach anything.
I've still got so much to learn.
I need a master who really knows about Sacred Gears.
I need someone like a trainer.
Azazel, do I have to attend tomorrow's conference?
Of course, Vali.
You're the Emperor of White Dragon.
Hey, Azazel.
Do you think there won't be any more wars?
I've heard that plenty of times from the hosts of Dragons.
You won't live long.
That's fine.
I don't have to live long.
I'm just...
disappointed to have been born in this era.
It's a godless world,
and I wanted to kill God.
Now that's something the Emperor of White Dragon would say.
I'm not interested in this bland world.
Akeno-san, she always appears happy...
But it was just a façade to hide her true feelings...
And here I am, merely wondering if the President likes me,
my problems are nothing in comparison.
Ah damn-it, I upset her again.
Enter...
P-President?!
A-Akeno-san?!
Why is Akeno-san here?
We lost track of the time while we were talking,
so I asked her to stay the night.
Yeah...
Great, they're both okay.
They genuinely are best friends.
Also, Akeno-san wanted to apologize to you.
Apology?
Issei-kun, for burdening you with my troubles, I am very sorry.
No, it's fine, really.
I heard...
Akeno confided in you about something,
I want to know how you feel about it.
I'm so very sorry!
Huh?
I-I was unable to control myself after
Akeno-san kindly offered her lap to me.
I'm not talking about that incident,
but what came before.
What?
Issei-kun, remember when you said that you liked me, no matter what.
D-Did I say something wrong?
What you said was very kind and compassionate.
I'm proud of you Issei.
Y-Yes!
I don't know what I have done, but I am happy to receive such adoration.
My my, Rias...
I have decided that Issei-kun will be mine.
A-Akeno-san...
Hey, Akeno. You might be my best friend, but you're pushing the boundaries.
There shouldn't be any boundaries in this competition. I won't hold back.
If that's the way you want it...
I wont lose to you.
Neither will I.
Ah, I don't understand how...
or why...
but I am in paradise right now...
Not fair, what about me...?
Ah, of course.
So it's today...
The big conference to talk about a new dull peace.
Hmm...
"I'm not interested in this bland world"
Ophis?
Vali...
Isn't that what you always say?
That's right,
this bland world doesn't interest me.
Okay, let's go.
Gasper, you be a good boy while you're here, okay?
Okay.
I don't want your powers running wild if anything happens.
Okay?
Y-Yes.
Koneko will stay with you.
Keep an eye on him. Okay, Koneko?
Yes, President.
Gasper, be good.
I'll lend you this.
Okay!
Thank you, Issei-senpai!
I have lots of snacks.
Thanks, Koneko-chan!
She must've got them for herself.
I'll put your paper bag right here.
If you're feeling nervous, just pop it on!
All right!
Good boy.
That said, I'm still worried that you might not make it.
Still...
That doesn't stop me from
wanting to try and help Gasper.
We're coming in.
Irina?
Allow me to introduce them.
This is my sister and her family.
They did very well in their
recent battle with Kokabiel.
Thank you very much.
We appreciate your efforts.
Sorry about that.
My guy got a little out of hand.
Where'd you learn your damn manners?
All of the representatives are here.
Let's begin the conference.
These are the incidents in which I, Rias Gremory
and my family, have taken part.
I, Sona Sitri, testify that she has said nothing but the truth.
Thank you.
You may step back.
Thank you, Rias-chan, Sona-chan.
I'd like to hear the General of the Fallen Angels' opinion on Rias' report.
There's nothing much to say.
Kokabiel acted of his own accord.
It has nothing to do with you?
I was waiting to find out what he was up to.
Looks like he never expected me to come to the city personally.
I like this place.
Please stay on topic.
I got the Emperor of White Dragon to take care of it!
Kokabiel's locked up in an ice prison in the depths of hell for eternity.
He won't be coming back.
Our concern here is Kokabiel's motives.
He said that he was not content with your decisions.
Yeah, he was pretty mad that I decided
to pull out of a war that we were winning.
I've got no interest in war, anyway.
He was an unstable individual, then.
I've heard a bunch about you guys, too.
That has nothing to do with this conference.
Today's conference is-
Yeah, enough small talk.
Let's sign that peace treaty already.
You guys were getting ready to do that anyway,
weren't you?
I-I hope everyone's okay.
What if they disagreed and started another war?!
Just the thought of it scares me!
What do you want to do?
churuchuchu doushitai
Hey, girls
churuchu hey girls
chu
ru
hey
girls
Lovely devils
raburi debiru
ra
girls
bu
ri
girls
de
bi
ru
You know what we wanna do! Yes!
churuchuchu aa shitai yes
They've descended upon us again
yes
kyou mo kourin
kyou
mo
kou
yes
rin
Girls are always greedy for more
shoujo wa shinkakei ni yokubari na no desu
I want this, I want that
are mo kore mo
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
kinou to kuraberun ja manzoku dekinai
Uh-oh
arere
a
i
re
Let's have a strategy meeting on how to upgrade
appugureedo sakusen kaigi
Agreed!
sansei
san
sei
I'm sure you have at least one of these
daredemo hitotsu kurai motte iru desho
You too, and you too
kimi mo kimi mo
Original magic words that protect your heart
orijinaru no jumon kokoro no omamori
Uh-huh
aruru
a
ri
ru
Positive thoughts that give you strength
purasu shikou taishitsu kyouka
Never compromising our love or dream
koi mo yume mo totteoki wo ne te ni ireru tame ni
Everyone
minna
mi
ni
n
na
We want to follow our heart
fiiringu juushi de
risaachi
de
Research
ri
saa
de
As we grow up
seichou shitai na
You see, girls are lovely devils
onna no ko wa ne raburi debiru
Deep down in their hearts, so treat them with great care
mune no naka kakushiteru no toriatsukai youchuui
They're only interested in having fun
tanoshii koto shika kyoumi nai no yo
Their whimsical temper makes them cute
wagamama ni kawaiku narun da
Promise!
yakusoku
ya
ku
so
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
A terrorist attack?! And Gasper and
Koneko in the clutches of the enemy?
Then we'll have to fight no
matter who our opponent is!
Next Episode:
"The Leaders' Summit Begins!"
The Leaders' Summit Begins!
Episode 11
Fire up the boobs!