Rage on! Rage on! Rage on! Gundam!
Moeagare! Moeagare! Moeagare GANDAMU!
You must run forth!
Kimi yo hashire
If you are still burning with furious rage...
Mada ikari ni moeru toshi ga aru nara...
You must fight the towering foe!
Kyodai na teki o
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Uteyo! Uteyo! Uteyo!
Bring to bear the rage of justice, Gundam
Seigi no ikari o butsukero GANDAMU
Mobile Suit Gundam! Gundam!
Kidou senshi GANDAMU! GANDAMU!
Rise once more! Rise once more!
Yomigaeru! Yomigaeru!
Rise once more! Gundam!
Yomigaeru GANDAMU!
You must seize the power!
Kimi yo tsukame
Fly toward the galaxy, Gundam!
Ginga e mukatte tobeyo GANDAMU
Mobile Suit Gundam! Gundam!
Kidou senshi GANDAMU! GANDAMU!
A half-century has passed
since humanity began moving...
...its burgeoning population into space.
These gigantic space cities
orbiting the Earth...
...became a second home to humanity...
...where people were born and raised...
...and where they died.
It is the year 0079 of the Universal Century.
The space city Side 3 proclaimed itself
the Principality of Zeon.
It launched a war of independence
against the Earth Federation.
During this war, the Principality of Zeon
and the Federation...
...caused the deaths
of half the total population.
Humanity was horrified by its own actions.
The Core Fighter's Escape
Ms. Sayla, how are the patients?
They're doing all right.
- Room 107, situation is stable.
- Roger.
All right, ma'am,
please be patient a little longer.
Hello! Hello!
How are you? How are you?!
Hello!
Hello! Hello! Hello...!
- Hello!
- Haro, don't cause a ruckus.
Here you go, sir.
Fraw Bow, everything's fine here.
All right.
Well, folks, if you need anything,
please let me know anytime.
See, this one valve here is shot, so...
I see. That's why the output is down 8%.
Can you calculate it
with a 12% output loss, please?
Roger!
It's not going to work.
We won't make it to orbit.
We can connect it to that circuit, right?
Sure.
- Will the catapult have enough strength?
- Yes. That should be fine.
The central catapult was designed for
the Gunperry. It'll handle a Core Fighter.
- Thank goodness.
- But sir...!
We are soldiers.
We have a duty to protect civilians.
Well, that proves my point.
If we let these hundred-plus refugees
off the White Base...
...we can return to satellite orbit and...
This territory is controlled by Zeon.
There are children and elderly...
Are we landing the refugees?
No, Mr. Bright wants to keep us on the run.
I didn't say that!
Was I too harsh?
But you know...
What are you going to do about food?
There're a hundred people who can't fight.
Kai!
It's just as the young man says. Right?
We were forced to emigrate to space...
...and we've come back to the Earth
we thought we'd never return to.
We can't bear to die before
we ever step on the Earth.
Don't you all feel that way?
So, I have an idea.
Use the White Base's energy
to launch the Core Fighter?
That's right. With a ballistic trajectory,
it'll definitely make it to the target.
It seems quite possible.
You already did the calculations, right?
Yes.
If we attach the main engine's steam valve
to the central catapult, we can do it.
But...
Hayato, Fraw Bow...idor B are In an uproar.
Come right away.
Nothing will happen as long as
we keep up this stand-off.
Why not try Amuro's idea?
There's the question of whether
we can modify the catapult.
Besides, even if we can do it,
who can withstand the shock of the launch?
I suggested it. If this plan fails,
there will only be one casualty.
- Amuro...
- Well, well. That's some big talk, kid.
I'm not saying it'll fail.
Mr. Bright. Please approve
the catapult modification.
All right.
Is this all right, Lt. Reed?
Permission granted.
It's vital that we contact General HQ.
Is all the Gundam data loaded already?
Yes, sir. All of the data
that we were able to estimate.
Amazing.
Based on the data we could
observe from the outside...
...its performance is far beyond that
of our Zaku mobile suits.
If only we knew more about
its internal workings...
Char. With that mobile suit as your foe...
...you did well to pursue it for two whole days.
Garma. Believe me,
it was tougher than you think.
I know.
- We shouldn't waste any more time.
- Right.
You're sure you can finish it in 15 minutes?
Yes. All we have to do Is attachine.
Get to it, Amuro.
Eat something first. But make it light.
Yes. I am.
- All right, listen...
- Yes.
The first 30 seconds will be toughest.
It's awful! The refugees have started a riot!
- A riot?
- Why would they...?!
The old folks have taken Katz,
Letz, and Kikka hostage...
...and demand that the White Base land!
Don't eat anymore, or you'll be sick.
- Yes, sir.
- Next...
Furthermore, Fraw Bow felt sorry
for Katz, Letz, and Kikka...
...and offered herself as a hostage as well.
How many hours have you logged
on a Core Fighter?
Huh?
18 hours in simulation...
35 hours in training, and 2 hours in combat.
Combat, with so little training?
I guess that's just how it is these days.
Just gather up your courage and do it.
- Yes, sir.
- Aren't you worried?
About what?
Your best friend Fraw Bow is a hostage.
Show some concern.
Hayato. Mr. Bright, Ms. Mirai,
Ms. Sayla, and Mr. Ryu are here.
I trust them to take care of
the White Base's problems.
I just have to do what I can.
Amuro's right, you know.
I'm off to the central hangar.
Good luck.
Hey! You better be ready for enemy fire
when you leave the White Base.
You...
Just who the hell do you think you are?!
No need to get so serious.
I'm just warning you.
Mr. Kai!
That's right. I'm just a coward.
Not somebody worth getting upset about.
Is that so.
You're an adult, aren't you, Mr. Kai?
Then stop being so unpleasant to people!
Captain, the Trojan Horse is on the move.
I believe it's on an ascending course!
- Inform the base.
- Yes, sir!
Captain Garma. We have Information
The Trojan Horsethe move.
What?!
- Can you send me the data?
- Yes, sir. Sending now.
Estimated data based on laser measurements.
What do you think, Char?
Are they trying for an orbital escape?
Not fast enough for that.
Or maybe...!
Get Dren for me!
Prepare the Komusai for launch!
Char! What's this about?
They're cut off from the Federation Forces,
and trying to do something about it.
Beginning countdown.
All right, Amuro?
10...
8... 7...
6... 5... 4...
3... 2... 1...
0... !
Core Fighter on ballistic trajectory.
The Trojan Horse launched something!
- Is it on a ballistic trajectory?
- Yes, sir!
They're trying to shoot over us
and make contact with Federation HQ.
The radar's no use above the base
because of the Minovsky particles.
- What should we do, Char?
- We pursue! Can we intercept it?!
We can launch in a minute,
and intercept in 2 minutes 50 seconds!
- All right!
- Char!
He hasn't changed at all.
All right. Contact the Gaw attack carrier.
Tell them to cover Char!
I gave a rough explanation
of our situation. But...
We don't want to hurt anybody here.
We just want to hear the truth.
Then you shouldn't need to take hostages.
- Everyone, holster your sidearms.
- What?
Put them away!
My dear grandson
is supposed to be on Earth.
I want to see my home town one more time,
and the river nearby.
I want to see the husband
I was separated from.
I never said we weren't
going to land on Earth.
How long until we can land?
I want you to tell me exactly when it will be.
I feel bad that you have to deal with this...
...but in order to talk directly to you
as equals, in a war situation...
...it was necessary to take these children.
We are doing the best we can.
Bright, please come right away!
What's wrong?
Please come quickly! Quickly!
Amuro, we should have radio contact now!
Amuro! This is the White Base!
Please respond!
Please respond! Core Fighter? Amuro?
- Maybe he was shot down.
- Don't joke around!
Enemy approaching!
Enemy craft pursuing Core Fighter!
Contact in 1 minute!
- Is it Char?!
- l-It can't be...!
Amuro! Amuro! Please respond!
Amuro! Answer me! Amuro!
Amuro! This is the White Base!
Mobile Suit Gundam
- How much longer?
- We should see it in 30 seconds.
- Amuro!
- Has the enemy spotted him?
- There's no answer!
- Give Amuro some cover!
Missiles checked! Ready anytime!
Mirai, full speed ahead!
He's going to have to lower
the Core Fighter's course.
Roger.
Main engine, I need the maximum output
at our current state.
Can't we use the radar?!
Only at 30% accuracy.
The Minovsky particles are too dense
considering we're on Earth.
I can make it out. You want to try it, Bright?
Fire! It'll be a diversion!
All right! Launch!
Missiles!
The Trojan Horse is just firing at random.
Move in on the enemy fighter!
Those missiles won't hit us.
Yes, sir.
Amuro! Wake up! Amuro!
Amuro! Amuro!
Please respond! Amuro!
Where...?
Are you awake, Amuro?
Ms. Sayla...
There's an enemy Interceptor nearby.
Calm down! Calm down!
Dren, these vulcan gun sights
aren't properly aligned!
Amuro, you mustn't get shot down!
Listen... Watch the enemy carefully.
Watch carefully.
That's right...!
That craft is merely
an atmospheric re-entry capsule.
It's not a fighter!
You're finished, Char!
- That's a direct hit!
- Don't worry. The damage isn't fatal.
Go into a dive!
Can't the White Base
give me better support?
Why can't we launch those missiles?!
The Dopps are positioned
between us and the Core Fighter.
If we fire missiles, there's the possibility
that we could hit the Core Fighter!
Friendly fire, huh?
Mr. Bright! I don't have a chance
against six fighters!
Bring Amuro back to the White Base.
All hands! Prepare for anti-air combat!
Amuro, return to ship. Nice and steady.
Hug the land contours as best you can.
But...
Bright and Lt. Reed are ordering it.
- He bit off more than he could chew.
- Why, you...!
What's your problem? What did I do?!
Take that attitude again
and I'll throw you out! Even into space!
I got it, Mr. Bright.
The Core Fighter is returning!
He seems to have given up.
Dopp team, don't lose him!
Dren, can we give chase?
- Yes, sir. We'll be fine for a while.
- All right, go!
The Gaw attack carrier is ascending.
Have them launch more Dopps.
I want to end this in the air.
Yes, sir.
I got away! There's the White Base!
The Core Fighter has entered firing range.
Bring it in while setting up a defense net.
Transfer to the Gundam ASAP!
Amuro, do you read?
Do you think you can fight
an aerial battle in the Gundam?
An aerial battle?!
But the Gundam is
a ground combat weapon!
Don't worry. You can safely spend
You can do It!
You're asking too much!
I don't have those kinds of skills!
Don't you want to live through this, Amuro?
Hurry back to the White Base.
Oh, come on...
Begin firing!
Lower the Core Fighter landing hook!
Landing alignment is OK. I'm coming in.
Control conversion, complete!
But Ms. Sayla... I don't know if...
Amuro, no one's doing any of this
But Amuro, you have real talent.
Believe In yourself.
The hatch will open now.
A mobile suit!
Enemy mobile suit has emerged!
I'll fight in my Zaku!
Move the Komusai above the enemy!
Yes, sir!
- A Zaku is descending! It's Char!
- What?!
Char!
Here I go!
I've got 1 minute 20 seconds
before I hit the ground.
Can I beat him before then?
Damn you!
Where's Char?!
What they call freefall on Earth...
...isn't as "free" as the phrase suggests.
The Gundam is in the way!
H-Hey! What are you people doing...?
N-Now, wait a minute...!
This is the...!
What's wrong?!
You people are...!
So, it seems like we can't land after all.
Please get me on to the Earth.
I'm begging you.
I understand.
Please return to your rooms,
and don't worry.
Please, quickly...
Hey, what are you doing?!
We will not move an inch.
Not until we land on Earth.
I used the beams too much!
No, Amuro! You must retreat!
The armor may not hold upspot!
Y-You're kidding!
We'll give you missile cover. Get out!
Please, don't get hit!
Roger!
- Damn Trojan Horse!
- Char, can you hear me?
Oh, Garma.
The Federation mobile suit.
We're going to have toy to fight it.
What do you mean?
We can only guesster data.
But the enemy mobile suit appears to bee...
...changing type according to the situation.
What?!
You mean, what I've been seeing...
...is just one part
of the mobile suit's capabilities?
And yet...
Well then...!
How should we fight it, Garma?!
Return to base. Let's figure It out.
R-Roger.
Don't mind them, Amuro.
You did well, Amuro.
- Would you like some tea?
- Sure.
I know you, well, all of you...
have been fighting very hard.
We understand how difficult it must be.
We're not saying this
just because we're old and difficult...
We just want to walk on the Earth.
I understand.
Please let us get off the ship here.
We're just a stone's throw away
from Federation territory.
Why can't you wait until then?
Who's going to guarantee
our safety until then?
I want my son to live. Please save my son!
Why can't you just find us a safe place
and drop us off?
Can't you people think of anything
other than yourselves?!
How could a child know how the old feel?
Who would ever fight
only for themselves?!
We're fighting for all of you people!
You people make me want to quit!
Amuro!
Your tea is ready.
Please return Fraw Bow
and the kids to the bridge.
We're counting on you, young lady.
- Amuro!
- Hey!
- Were you injured?
- I'm fine.
Can we fly over it?
We'll have to use the mountains as a shield...
...and head for the sea.
I suppose so.
In order to drop off the refugees,
a ceasefire is declared.
However, plans are put into place
for the next round of fighting.
What will the mother and child
witness on the Earth?
Mobile Suit Gundam. Next episode...
Winds of War.
Winds of War
Will you be able to survive?
Amuro, do not look back
Amuro, Furimukanaide
The star shining far off in space...
Uchuu no kanata ni kagayaku hoshi ha
Amuro, it's your homeland
where you were born
Amuro, Omae no umareta furusato da
Do you remember the days
of your childhood?
Oboeteirukai, Shounen no hi no koto wo
The morning when you woke up in warmth?
Atatakai nukumori no nake de mezameta asa wo
Amuro, do not look back, Amuro...
Amuro, furimukanaide na, Amuro
A man must hide his tears, hide his tears
Otoko ha namida wo misenu mono, Misenu mono
Only look to tomorrow, to tomorrow
Forever...
Tada ashita e to ashita e to, Eien ni...