Rage on! Rage on! Rage on! Gundam!
Moeagare! Moeagare! Moeagare GANDAMU!
You must run forth!
Kimi yo hashire
If you are still burning with furious rage...
Mada ikari ni moeru toshi ga aru nara...
You must fight the towering foe!
Kyodai na teki o
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Uteyo! Uteyo! Uteyo!
Bring to bear the rage of justice, Gundam
Seigi no ikari o butsukero GANDAMU
Mobile Suit Gundam! Gundam!
Kidou senshi GANDAMU! GANDAMU!
Rise once more! Rise once more!
Yomigaeru! Yomigaeru!
Rise once more! Gundam!
Yomigaeru GANDAMU!
You must seize the power!
Kimi yo tsukame
Fly toward the galaxy, Gundam!
Ginga e mukatte tobeyo GANDAMU
Mobile Suit Gundam! Gundam!
Kidou senshi GANDAMU! GANDAMU!
The year is Universal Century 0079.
Luna II, also known as the second Moon,
is an asteroid that was brought out to obtain mineral resources in order to build the space colonies.
Next to it is Side 7, the seventh cluster of space colonies, which had been in construction for two years
when the war between the Principality of Zeon and the Earth Federation Forces broke out.
Four clusters of space colonies were decimated by the war,
and only a few space colonies within Side 6 still stand.
The space colonies which declared themselves the Principality of Zeon
are located furthest from the Earth.
There, the Zeon leader, Gihren Zabi, calls for an attack against the weakened Earth Federation,
suggesting that he is the one who will save all of humanity.
Cucuruz Doan's Island
Core Fighter, Amuro! Do you copy?
The Gunperry has launched.
Roger! I'll make contact.
We'll start the count from the docking searcher.
The objective is to cut it down by three seconds.
Are you ready?
Roger!
I'm coming in, Ryu!
Okay, we're ready!
Amuro, we're okay for docking standby!
Here we go!
Ryu, activate the docking searcher!
Laser searcher synchronized!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Releasing Gundam Module B!
Core change!
Go for docking!
Nineteen seconds flat.
That's too slow.
Can't you do it four seconds faster?
Is that even possible?
It seems the laser searcher isn't synchronizing fast enough.
Mr. Bright, we're receiving an emergency signal from the Federation Air Force.
An Air Force S.O.S.?
Where's it coming from?
And what about the enemy's numbers?
It couldn't possibly be an automatic signal.
I'll track its position!
Point 305!
Point 305?
That's not too far.
I'd better ask Amuro to check it out.
Amuro, separate the Core Fighter from the Gundam.
Understood?
I want you to patrol Point 305 in the Core Fighter.
Roger!
Ryu, I'm separating the Gundam modules!
Please pick them up!
Roger!
It sure ain't a pretty sight, though.
You think so, Ryu?
I'm heading out, Mr. Bright!
Honestly, it's too weird seeing the Gundam like that.
Is that island over there Point 305?
Is that it?
They're still alive!
Understood.
Get them to tell you what happened!
Amuro! If you need anything, let us know immediately!
Damn. We're going to have to save these Federation guys, aren't we?
The enemy may still be close by.
Sound the alarm for level two battle stations.
Yes, sir!
He didn't make it.
Try not to move!
Why were these pilots tied to their seats alive?
And how come only the fighter's weapons were taken?
Who's there?
Are you okay?
Don't come here, soldier!
Go away!
No, stop it!
I'm not your enemy!
Shut up! Go away!
Hurry up and get off this island!
I said stop it!
You're annoying! Shut up!
Let's destroy that fighter, too!
Stop it!
Damn!
It's Doan!
Doan!
T-This area shouldn't be completely occupied by the Zeon.
What's going on?
Doan, it's another soldier!
He was pointing his pistol at us!
I don't want to fight against you.
If you hand over your weapons peacefully, I won't hurt you.
Hand over my weapons?
Right now, you can do whatever you want!
Why don't you just go ahead and attack?
I'm asking you because I don't want to fight!
Stay here where it's safe.
Doan, beat that guy!
Please!
Do you think you can beat my Zaku with that small fighter?
I may not be able to destroy you,
but if I fire a missile at the right spot, you won't be able to move.
Here I come!
I just have to destroy the joints!
He's fast!
I'll get him this time!
Ouch!
Who are you?
Rollan.
Where am I?
This is Doan and the children's house.
Doan?
Cucuruz Doan.
He's the person who saved you.
What did you say?
Doan is going to send you back.
But until your wounds heal, you can rest here.
That's nonsense!
Anyway, where's my Core Fighter?
You're just like Doan said.
Doan is at the farm out back with the children.
Doan, it's him!
Are you sure you should be walking around, kid?
Where is it?
Your fighter?
I have to protect these children.
Someday, Zeon will find this place and attack me.
I also need weapons to protect myself!
Please return my Core Fighter!
If I return it, you'll just attack us, won't you?
I'm not like you, deceiving children to get them to obey you!
I'm fighting the Zeon invaders!
You're insulting Doan!
He's not deceiving us!
That's right!
What's wrong with him protecting our island?
If you're just going to be mean to Doan, then leave!
Yeah! Get out of here!
How dare you manipulate them!
What did you say?!
Stop it.
I've always told you to steer clear of pointless quarrels.
But he said...
I'm going to look for my Core Fighter.
I don't think he moved it too far.
Doan, he won't find his fighter, will he?
There's no way he'll find it, right?
Yeah, that's right.
You're more stubborn than I thought.
You were following me?
You don't seem to realize how beautiful the sunset is.
In battle, there's no time to think about beauty.
If you let your guard down, you'll lose.
Doan...
is not as bad as you make him out to be.
I guess Doan is pretty good at deceiving children.
You don't know anything!
Don't jump to conclusions!
If he's so great, then why did he hide my Core Fighter?
Don't you understand how those children feel?
Do you think those children follow him around this island because he deceived them?
Well, then why is Doan trying to take care of those children?
If you want to find out, ask him yourself.
Doan is looking forward to talking with you.
He said that once you shed that immaturity of yours, you'll become a good soldier.
It doesn't look like he's on this island.
Ryu, we'll call off the search until tomorrow!
Get back here at once!
Just give me a little longer!
Everyone's worried about him.
He at least should have contacted us!
This is Amuro we're talking about.
I'm sure he has a reason.
I hope so.
Maybe he was...
No, that's a stupid thought.
It's a Zaku!
There's still no sign of the Zeon.
You're still awake?
What are you going to do?
About the boy?
We can't leave him alone.
His main force should be nearby.
If he doesn't see things our way, it could be troublesome.
I just want to get away from this life of constantly looking over my shoulder.
Sorry.
You don't have to worry about me.
There he is!
Hurry up and leave our island!
Yeah!
Stop!
Looks like both of us had trouble sleeping.
Yeah.
I'll continue the search!
Unidentified aircraft approaching!
It's coming in pretty fast!
Is it headed toward us?
No, sir.
It's headed toward Point 305.
Let's send out Ryu.
All right!
The White Base will launch as well!
Yes, sir!
Go away!
Hurry and leave our island!
It's a Zaku!
Run!
Hurry!
Rollan, where are the children?
There!
Doan!
Doan, give me back my Core Fighter!
Look out!
Our house!
Doan!
Follow me!
What's that Zaku aiming at?
Damn, he's fast!
Amuro! Are you okay?
Ryu!
What the hell is going on here?
I'll explain later!
That one Zaku is on our side!
Here it comes!
It's the White Base!
Amuro, are you all right?
Yes!
Please launch the Gundam!
I'll dock with it in mid-air!
No, stop!
Come back to the ship and convert here!
Omur! Prepare for an emergency conversion!
I think I've got the skill to do it in mid-air.
I'm heading out!
This Zaku is all that's left!
Wait! Let me handle this guy!
But you don't have any weapons!
I'll show you mobile suit martial arts!
Watch and learn!
But Doan!
Stop!
But!
I'll continue to fight as long as the children are watching!
Doan! Beat that Zaku!
Doan will win!
Beat him up!
Yeah!
Amuro, what's going on?
Well, I'm not exactly sure.
Kid, I'll tell you now!
I'm the one who killed these children's parents!
All because of a stray round from my gun!
Zeon ordered me to kill the children,
but I couldn't do it!
I took the children and ran away!
I will protect these children with my life!
Doan!
I...
I'll...
I'll never let you...
kill the children!
Doan, you were really cool!
You're our hero, Doan!
They won't stop chasing me until I die.
As long as I'm alive, these children will face danger.
It will be tough.
You're wrong.
It's not because you're alive.
Don't you think it's your scent of battle that attracts pursuers?
Scent of battle?
Yes.
Let me wipe that scent away from you, Cucuruz Doan.
What have you done?!
That's awful!
How can you do something so terrible?!
Doan.
I'm gonna beat him up!
Hey, stop it.
Don't be mad at that boy.
Why not?
Doan, he sunk it!
What that boy did is a very good thing.
Rollan, I think he's a fine young man.
Do you agree?
Yes.
The Gallop and Gouf appear in the desert.
Wanting to know Char's whereabouts...
...Sayla disobeys orders
and launches into battle.
Her reckless actions
put the Gundam in danger.
Will Amuro's rescue attempt succeed?
Mobile Suit Gundam. Next episode...
Sayla's Agony.
Sayla's Agony
Will you be able to survive?
Amuro, do not look back
Amuro, Furimukanaide
The star shining far off in space...
Uchuu no kanata ni kagayaku hoshi ha
Amuro, it's your homeland
where you were born
Amuro, Omae no umareta furusato da
Do you remember the days
of your childhood?
Oboeteirukai, Shounen no hi no koto wo
The morning when you woke up in warmth?
Atatakai nukumori no nake de mezameta asa wo
Amuro, do not look back, Amuro...
Amuro, furimukanaide na, Amuro
A man must hide his tears, hide his tears
Otoko ha namida wo misenu mono, Misenu mono
Only look to tomorrow, to tomorrow
Forever...
Tada ashita e to ashita e to, Eien ni...