Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
The attacks by the Gundams
sent by the Space Colonies...
...reflected the colonies'
retaliatory intentions.
OZ has masked its identity
in the Alliance Military...
...and the Gundams' missions
is to attack them.
The year is After Colony 195.
OZ has finally taken center stage.
With an army of elite soldiers
at his command...
...Treize Khushrenada has begun to
wipe out the Alliance Military.
The battle between OZ and the
mobile suits sent to Earth...
...causes serious repercussions
on the Earth.
It's up to you now, Heero!
He's got a 10 percent
chance of succeeding.
But he can do it for sure!
It was a miserable mission.
I... I totally screwed up!!
Portrait of a Ruined Country
Thanks to the Lightning Count,
we saved the beautiful town.
The Alliance is probably
regrouping their force...
...after the surprise attack.
We'll use this base as our
headquarters for future fights.
The beauty of these towns
doesn't change with rulers.
Noin...
OZ's objective isn't to rule.
It's to free countries from
the stranglehold...
...of the United Earth
Sphere Alliance.
Currently, you mean.
This might be unnatural
coming from me...
...but I believe OZ should
be given due respect...
...for giving a second chance
to those countries...
...which formed the Alliance
in the first place.
The mobile suit carrier from
Victoria Base is arriving.
They're here.
Otto, I'm so glad to see you!
I'm here now, Lieutenant.
You need to rest.
What's the matter?
Lieutenant Otto shouldn't
even be standing!
His ribs are broken, and
he has internal injuries.
Keep it to yourself.
Lieutenant Zechs.
This Tallgeese you've been
waiting for is one vicious suit.
So this is the Tallgeese...
Doesn't look like a thing that
was scrapped 20 years ago.
No.
The revolution speed
applied by the verniers...
...allows it to reach more than
three times that of the Aries.
But we were unable to
determine its maximum speed.
I passed out during the trials.
You were the test pilot?!
The Tallgeese can't be
controlled by just anybody.
Lieutenant Zechs is an exception.
Aren't you overrating my skills?
No, I trust in your abilities.
All right.
I'll be using this right away.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Take him to the medical room.
Sir!
Noin.
Have the mobile suit troops
ready to leave at once.
We'll go to the Alliance's
Sanc Kingdom base.
The Sanc Kingdom?
We're freeing them
from the Alliance.
Any objections to this mission?
No, sir!
I'm going on this Tallgeese.
Without even a test ride?
Isn't that dangerous?
I'll be taking it easy.
I just want to stake my
chances on this mobile suit.
Sanc Kingdom.
Zechs' homeland.
Heero!
Nice shot, Heero!
Awesome! Heero!
Hey!
Wave back or something!
They're cheering for us!
So this is where you went.
Hey, that's pretty smart.
Changing schools when
you've gotta go.
It's natural for people our age
to be in school, after all.
What's the idea?
I'm just trying to act normal.
You stand out.
You wouldn't be as suspicious...
...if you acted natural instead
of being so secretive.
Why don't you just chill out
and have fun as a student?
Leave me alone.
And stay outta my way, right?
The two of us are going after
the same thing, here.
You can't hide it from me.
I can see it in your eyes
as plain as day, pal.
How about the first one to
destroy that fortress wins?
Hey, that's...
Relena...
I've found you, Heero.
Heero. I wanted to see you.
She's not typical, wanting to
see the guy trying to kill her.
Three mobile suit carriers and
seven escort planes approaching!
Confirmed as OZ troops!
What's going on?!
What are the OZ troops
trying to pull here?!
They've released the suits!
Keep the assault centralized.
We just need to take over
the main facilities.
Following OZ's coup d'état...
...the United Earth Sphere
Alliance Military...
...enters a state of confusion.
Alliance Military soldiers remain
confined in their bases...
...without an understanding of
what in fact is happening.
The United Earth Sphere
Alliance was initially formed...
...to handle disputes between
the countries.
But with its expansion in
military power, the Alliance...
...soon took over governments
with militaristic control.
OZ is now planning to
free the many countries...
...that were forced into the
Alliance in this manner.
But the increase in the
Alliance's military power...
...was a direct result of the
mobile suits provided by OZ.
As such, many countries
questioned OZ's activities...
...noting that after the coup
d'état, military control...
...would continue and conditions
would remain the same.
All mobile suits have left
the carriers.
Then I'll leave as well.
I'll be backing you up.
Concentrate only on achieving
your mission, Lieutenant Zechs.
I'm totally focused.
We'll lure away ground troops,
but some might fly toward you.
Don't worry.
If our data 's right, I should
be able to outrun them.
Good luck!
The mobility of this heavy suit
depends on the vernier output.
It's going to be tough...
This is going to take
a lot of effort.
But I can't falter now with
the Sanc Kingdom before me!
Take over the runway on
the east side!
This speed is deadly!
I could get away by
increasing the output.
Then why?
Why am I hesitating?
Transmission from OZ!
What?!
Disarm your weapons
and surrender!
We have no wish to
continue this battle!
You're the ones that attacked,
so you should be retreating!
Standby to fire laser beams!
Sir!
Headquarters didn't mention
those lasers!
Retreat at once!
Damned laser beams!
Noin.
Order all units to withdraw
at once.
I had no idea they had
this much firepower...
...but we're still in the fight!
No.
We should leave for now
and regroup.
We'll withdraw to where
we landed the carriers.
Yes, sir!
Why am I acting like
such a coward?
I could defeat them with
this Tallgeese.
I could ignore the lasers
and destroy their headquarters!
Zechs!
I've mastered many mobile suits
in the past, so what gives?
What am I afraid of?!
I'll die if I keep going.
This mobile suit is capable
of defeating any enemy it faces!
But it does have one weak point;
the pilot is a human being!
Is this the end?
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Lady, won't you join me?
Mr. Treize, what would you
suggest for our next target?
Let's just continue fighting
and winning.
You mean we should
conquer the Earth Sphere?
That'd suffice.
Then OZ would then be hated.
It'd become a target
for the entire world.
Mr. Treize...
Those that are hated must
remain strong.
It'd be the perfect
motivation for OZ.
Master Quatre, if anything
were to happen to you...
...how would we explain it
to your father in the colony?!
Don't you have confidence
in us, Master?
It's nothing like that.
Our sole purpose here
is to protect you.
Do you understand this?!
Master Quatre!!
Y-Yeah.
Right, that's enough.
But Captain Rashid!
Master Quatre has promised...
...that he won't leave on
his own any more.
Yeah, I promise.
Go on, there's no time
to stand around.
Load up the weapons on
your mobile suits or something.
Thanks, Rashid.
I'm upset with you too;
don't forget it.
R-Right.
So how was it?
There were five suits in all.
I'm pretty sure they're
all called Gundams.
They're all Gundams?
They're violent and dangerous
but they're all nice guys.
How can you be sure of that?
I can tell.
The soul of outer space
tells me.
The soul of outer space?
The soul of outer space...
Gee, you two!
You call that fun,
just sitting there?
You haven't said a word
for two hours.
What do you want?
Nice greeting.
I thought I'd be doing
you a favor bringing this.
Eat it up before it gets cold.
I'll leave it here
so help yourselves.
And clean the dishes
after you're finished.
Gotta learn your manners
while you're still young.
Bye!
I guess quiet people
attract quiet friends.
Might not be the best java.
I've got no right
piloting the Nataku.
Oh yeah?
Thank you.
Your pulse has now
stabilized...
...but there are irregularities
in the circulatory system.
You mean I should just
be glad to be alive.
Zechs, what in the
world happened?
I really underestimated
the Tallgeese.
It completely ignores
the pilot's safety.
It has an audacious design...
...that far exceeds today's
most advanced equipment.
It ignores the pilot?
It takes into consideration
all types of battle patterns...
...and makes it possible
for the one suit...
...to achieve victory
on its own.
At least that's how
I found it.
But I've become such
a coward.
The more I try to utilize
the mobile suit's abilities...
...the more I start doubting
my own abilities.
I start asking myself, "is that
all you're capable of doing?"
Rather than a suit for battle,
it's a suit for dueling.
It takes a brave pilot to
bring out its true potential.
A brave pilot?
Brave enough to risk
death for victory.
I still have a long way to
go to conquer my own fears.
Now, I've got to get back
to the Sanc Kingdom.
You've gotta rest!
Any normal person would've
been dead by now.
I'm leaving, but you have to
stay here and get some rest.
But I have to go.
Okay, but not on the Tallgeese.
Noin!
The Tallgeese is essential
to us.
I'm positive its design
is the same as the Gundams.
It is?
As I told you, I believe
the Gundams inherited...
...the reckless design of
the Tallgeese.
The mobile suits' origin.
That's why it's crucial for
me to pilot the Tallgeese...
...to defeat the Gundams.
Tallgeese is for suicide
missions.
Now I understand what
the Gundams are up to.
They're searching for a place
suitable for their deaths.
I know it's very difficult
for you to lie still...
...with the Sanc Kingdom close
by, but you must do as I say.
We'll attack tomorrow evening.
Sir! Tomorrow evening!
What's the matter?!
The Tallgeese has taken off!
What?!
What're you doing?!
Return immediately!
This Tallgeese should
be able to take over...
...the Sanc Kingdom's
headquarters!
I should know I understand
the Tallgeese's strength!
Stop it! You'll die!
I'd be honored to sacrifice
my life for you, Lieutenant.
Please allow me to assist
in fulfilling your dreams!
I want to do this for you
Lieutenant Zechs, not for OZ!
Otto...
I will attain victory in
return for my life!
You're not making sense Otto!
Return at once! Otto!
I've come all the way here
just to chase after a guy.
Are you surprised, Father?
But I couldn't help myself;
I wanted to see him so badly.
Can you understand
how I feel, Father?
I need to have Heero's
support...
...until I overcome
my sadness over you.
But he keeps running
from me...
Heero?!
All right!
Looks like I got here first!
What took you, Heero?!
Don't worry, I left
you some action!
I can't see a thing!
Mission complete.
Don't get in my way!
I don't know how long
I can stand this!
Hurry up!
Yes, sir!
If only I'd been able to
pilot the Tallgeese...
...this never would
have happened!
The new type of mobile suit
is approaching fast!
Direct all laser beams
at that suit!
LONG LIVE KING ZECHS!
Otto...
It took me 13 years to
return to these grounds.
Please forgive me, Father.
There's been much bloodshed
along the way...
...and I've only been able
to live a lifestyle...
...that counters your
pacifist teachings.
My hands are too stained
with blood.
I'm completely unfit to head
the Peacecraft monarchy.
But I'm sure she would
be able to head the country...
...as you'd intended.
I'll fight to make that happen.
I've failed you.
Please forgive me.
It was attacked!?
Think the colonies did it?
That's scary!
Heero!
Morning, good looking!
Pretty nice day today, huh.
Gotta get to class.
Let me stay by you
a little longer.
I wanna be stronger,
just like you.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Battles that risk lives
only produce mistakes.
Then what meaning does
Otto's death have?
Lady Une announces
a plan to transport Tauruses...
...the space mobile suits,
to the Siberian Base.
However, it's just a pretense
to wipe out the Gundams.
In his battle with Zechs,
Heero makes a final decision.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 10,
Heero, Distracted by Defeat
"Heero, Distracted by Defeat".