I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
The sea's so calm today.
The waters around here
can be really technicolor.
Dive in, and you're
treated to a masterpiece.
I'm sure it is. I did a little scuba
diving long ago at Ishigaki Island.
It sounds privileged. Like the
fruitful life of a bachelor yuppie.
It wasn't that great.
Drinking beer while feeling this sea
breeze on my skin is far more privileged.
_______________
Naval base at Kiel, 1945
So it's "Farewell Germany".
It's a shame that the last glimpse
I get of the German sky...
...is of its usual leaden color.
Thanks to that, the Allies'
patrol over us has thinned.
Once we get past the Shetlands
and out of the North Sea...
...we'll soon be under Spain's blue
sky, and then on to Africa's beaches.
You'll soon be longing for some
clouds, Lieutenant Colonel Matsuto.
Right. As a man here to
study aeronautics...
...I can't afford to be killed
by a plane.
Not after coming all
the way here to Germany.
It seems like we'll understand
each other on this long trip.
I'd like to feel the same about
that other passenger as well.
I just don't understand them.
Those men, the SS and SD's.
Darn. I really did
have a privileged life.
A little problem with the car, and
life takes a sudden nosedive here.
Mr. Lun, is that new? How much?
That's too much. I'll bet it's stolen.
Oh, well. It's not like anyone has
anything to spare in their wallets.
I'd better pass. I can just hear
Revy labeling me a softie again.
__________
Near the Cape Verde Islands,
Africa, 1945
Check.
Gentlemen, we can look forward
to sea turtle soup tonight!
__________
The Indian Ocean
They're moving with us at bearing 270.
It's a freighter out of South
Africa heading to Ceylon.
Captain.
We're in battle positions.
Please get inside.
I apologize, but I want
you to answer me one thing.
Are you going to ignore your
orders and attack that freighter?
What shall we do?
I will get you to Batavia
without fail Lieutenant Colonel.
Fritz.
Yes sir.
Are you incapable of even greeting
the enemy without confirmation?
And yet you consider
yourself this ship's...
Very well, sir.
I'll have them hurry with the loading
of the torpedo under maintenance.
You too, Lieutenant Colonel, get inside.
An attack would be a
completely unnecessary risk.
That is a transport of your
long-life enemy, England.
What's being carried is fuel
for an invasion...
...of the ally we'll soon
be guests of.
You're telling me to ignore that enemy?
Are you saying there was no point
in our fighting this war so far?
At this stage, sinking that ship will
have no effect on our fatherland.
Oh?
What?
Are you saying that we
cannot stop the inevitable?
Are you trying to force me to say more?
No. I just didn't expect
to hear what you said.
I thought you were worrying about
something more meaningless.
I apologize. Despite that, there are
still battles that you must take on.
Let's go. Prepare the
torpedoes for surface attack!
We'll credit this ship with its 31st hit.
Launcher is ready.
All right, let's go! We will keep fighting!
Aren't you going to go drinking?
I'll go. As soon as
I'm finished calculating...
...the fuel efficiency of the
torpedo ship.
Good job.
What's that?
I dunno.
Do I look like an off-season Santa?
During the day, you were looking
into a shop, weren't you, Rock?
Huh? N-No, that was...
Why don't you just tell me
when you want something?
W-Wait. Then you mean, that's for me?
The enemy ship just passed over us.
_______
Near the Nicobar Islands, Indonesia
__________
March 25, 1945
Set course to two-zero-zero.
We'll get behind the enemy.
If we turn twice we can get behind them.
The second turn will be in four minutes.
Good. We'll go with that.
We're detecting sound from another
vessel in front of us.
Wait! Yet another signal!
The enemy's coming out in numbers.
We are about to be subjugated,
with Batavia right in front of us.
Not yet, gentlemen.
Both engines full power.
Set course to one-seven-zero.
One-seven-zero.
Fire the Zigarren astern.
Firing Zigarren.
One of the enemy ships is moving away.
They took the bait. Stop
the ship. Silent running.
One ship is staying right
with us, and won't break away.
It's active sonar!
Full power to the engines!
Port 20 degrees! To depth of 40!
This is the forward torpedo room! We're
taking on water! We've lost control!
Close the fore hatch!
Captain! Please take care!
We've stopped taking on water,
but we can't blow the main tank.
Engines and the electric generator
are damaged beyond repair.
It is unfortunate that we couldn't
return the Japanese to his homeland.
Lieutenant Colonel Matsuto
has already...
The way of a samurai.
I didn't realize he had brought
a sword on board for that reason.
Brave and loyal soldiers
of the German navy.
We faced great opposition and
rough waters in the Atlantic...
...but we will finish our final battle,
without seeing the coconuts of Batavia.
Our ship is currently run
aground at a depth of 57 meters.
Both our engines and
ballast are beyond repair.
You have endured numerous
battles with courage.
At this moment I relieve
you all of military duties.
We will run out of air in about two hours.
You may each choose
how you wish to die.
Lieutenant Colonel, I have to talk to you.
Captain, I haven't heard the
engine running for some time now.
When will we surface?
As it turns out, we won't
be surfacing. Ever again.
I'm sorry.
You're worthless.
I agree.
You don't get it. You just
don't get it, do you?!
Get what?
The importance of your mission!
Do you have any idea what significance
this painting I'm transporting has?!
Oh, so the package was this painting.
It doesn't look like anything
of great significance to me.
What is its title?
"The Twelve Knights led by Brunhilda."
Listen! This is the only tableau
painted since the Fuhrer took power.
"Steadfast in our honor and loyalty,
hide this until the promised day.
On the day the Nazi flag flies again...
...this will be the guiding light for
our comrades who have scattered!"
So, you already know we
are going to lose this war.
And you wanted to prepare
for the next war.
You people make me sick!
Do you have family?
A wife and child in Stuttgart. So what?!
I am proud that I fought with
all I had for my country.
I have no regrets, even now as I
am destined to rot in the ocean.
However, if there is one dissatisfaction...
...it is the fact that I have to share
a casket with a bastard like you...
...who won't bother to remember his
family, even in his last moments.
Take back that remark, Captain.
You cannot compare family to the
righteousness of our country!
It's worthless. No
matter how you struggle...
...the empire of the corporal, whose
paintings won't sell, is over.
Shut up.
By tolerating your delusions, look what's
become of my country and my navy.
Shut up!
I'd say it was worth sinking, if
because of it, my children will never...
...have to see that
accursed Nazi flag again.
Shut up! Take it back!
It could very well be God's
will for our ship to sink here.
Damn it.
I shouldn't have opened
my mouth about it.
I only went scuba diving
once, at Ishigaki Island.
Dutch tricked me into this!
That's all you've said since we left port!
Be a little more interesting, you idiot!
There's no way I'm capable
of doing this salvaging!
Now, I explained it
briefly at the office...
...but I'll go through the details again
before we go in. Benny, will you start?
Okay. First, take a look at this.
An old story from half a century ago.
Some nostalgic talk by
some elderly gentleman.
IXC-type attack submarine
U-1324 of the German navy.
A submarine in the Wolf Pack
that tore up the Atlantic.
The captain was Major Venztel H. Ahbe.
The last order he received
from his falling homeland...
...was to take an officer of
the Japanese navy to Batavia.
But things weren't that simple.
To get there they had to go from
Kiel in Europe, around Cape Agulhas...
...and then past the Indian Ocean.
It's a voyage worthy of Magellan.
But Ahbe pulled it off.
But when he could finally
see his destination...
...his ship and passenger
suddenly ran out of luck.
While searching for the Japanese, the
U.S. Navy came across this U-boat.
Having nothing else to do, they
all decided to strike at once.
The poor U-1324 finally
ran out of strength.
The captain and 44 of his
crew disappeared...
...into the darkness of the sea.
Up to this point, that's historical fact,
but there is another, untold story.
A story about an SS officer...
...who appeared from Kiel Port
the night before departure...
...forcing his way on board with
papers from the secret police.
Take a look at this.
This is the painting he
held on to for dear life.
The artist is August
Janke, an unknown painter.
The title is "The Twelve
Knights Led by Brunhilda".
What a boring painting.
Even graffiti on the New York
Metro is more appealing than that.
Why did an SS officer board
a submarine with no gold...
...no secret documents, but
just a single painting?
Don't give it too much thought.
It's just an incredible story.
I have no explanation
for the reason behind it.
The one thing that we know
is that this painting...
...is sleeping in a sunken submarine.
We've been hired by an
antique collector in Spain.
His hobby is collecting the artwork
of artists from the Nazi era.
The guy's got a weird hobby.
Damn right. Most of Janke's work
was burnt in war disasters.
He had completely given up on it,
and the U-boat long ago. But...
Yeah, last year a French phone company
laying down underwater cables...
...discovered U-1324.
And they found that there
wasn't much water inside.
Several countries are fighting over the
control of water territories in this area.
No one can make a go for it easily.
And that's where we come in.
A nice 50,000 dollar job, plus expenses.
So, here are the steps for
the job. Take a look at this.
The French found that the bow
end is completely flooded.
The two of you will go in through
the torpedo tubes and then shut them.
Once you weld the hole shut, you should
be able to open the door in the interior.
W-Weld?
What do we do to get out?
Just make a hole in the
submarine's body and swim out.
Once we get what we want outta
there, who cares what happens to it.
All right then, let's get this over with.
I've never even done weekend carpentry.
And we're doing this all underwater.
I can't imagine how it'll work.
Hey, are you done
checking the equipment?
If you keep talking nonsense, I'll
throw you into the sea without a tank.
I'm mostly done.
What about the
buoyancy compensator?
Did you test the gauge?
If you end up drowning I'm
gonna leave you down there...
...in that casket, with those Nazi guys.
Don't be so difficult. I'll be fine.
If you die you'd be causing me trouble!
So stop talking back, you idiot!
Revy.
Once you dive I'll only be able
to track you with the beacon.
Be careful not to use up the batteries.
Got it.
And this. A souvenir from Balalaika
when she returned from her country.
An underwater rifle?
Does it have full-auto?
Of course. Take it as a protective charm.
Okay. Let's go. Follow me, Rock.
So you won her over with
a gun and saved Rock.
You've got a lot of tricks up your sleeve.
You could say that. As an employer
I've gotta deal with human relations.
The beacon's been activated.
The PLRS is working fine.
All right.
They're headed straight
for the metal body.
Revy sure seems used
to this kind of thing.
Of course she is. I wouldn't
have hired her solely on her...
...skill with guns. She's got natural
talent when it comes to swimming.
Dutch?
What's up?
Come up here for a second.
There's a ship.
What?
We're not on a regular sea route.
The cable company's about the only
one I can imagine coming here.
Cable company? It can't be.
I've been listening to their
communications...
...ever since we got the offer.
They shouldn't be out here
for another three days.
Besides, that's a research ship.
Look. It's got some large
equipment on the back.
This isn't amusing. Put
up a Thai navy flag.
Roger.
To the stopped ship. This is the
White Heather. Please respond.
They wanna communicate.
This is PT377 of the Thai navy.
We are currently on a mission.
We'd like to inquire about
your purpose in this area.
Tell us your nationality,
ship number and signal code.
We see that you are acting
independently.
Where is your mother ship?
That is a military matter
and I cannot answer.
I request your information
one more time, over.
They sure are demanding.
They're not normal.
I'm going back to the control room.
Keep track of them, and
tell me everything you see.
We've got some unusual cloud
activity. Fold up your umbrella.
All right. What'll we do about those two?
As long as their beacon is on,
we can pick them up any time.
Worst case scenario, we blast these
guys and then pick the two up.
Hail Uberfuhrer!
Upon checking communications
through radio interception...
...just as we suspected there are no
navy vessels of any nation in this area.
Therefore, we conclude that
they are hated bandits...
...who are plundering
this sacred grave site.
Your decision please, Commander.
They are such fools.
The proof of inheritance of this
grave site is rightfully ours.
Very well, Squad Commander. I will
allow destruction with an iron fist.
What's going on?
Dutch. There's movement.
Okay. I just started the engines.
What in the world are they doing?
Dutch! They have TOWs!
Damn it! I should've guessed
that's what they'd do!
Hang on, Benny!
Damn it!
Anti-tank missiles!
Run, run, degenerates.
This is our destined reunion with
Brunhilda. No one will stop us.
This underground grave is about to open.
Next Episode
You'll no longer be one of us.
When that happens, I'm gonna kill you.