He's here?
The other Bishop?
The seal breaks late at night,
and he's allowed to wander around in this building.
However, he refused to do so.
So he's...
a hikikomori?
He does make the most money out of all of us, though.
Are you serious?!
He makes special contracts via the Internet.
She said that he was sealed
because he was too powerful...
What's his ability?
The seal has been broken.
I'm opening the door.
Wh-What the-
Good evening.
I'm glad you're doing well.
Wh-What's going on?!
Your seal's been broken.
Now, why don't we-
No!
I wanna stay here!
I don't wanna go outside!
Damn, "he" is actually a girl!
And she's a blonde, just like Asia!
Is it a rule to only have blonde Bishops?!
What, Kiba?
This is a boy.
Huh?
President,
what'd you say?
He may look like a girl,
but he's actually a boy.
What?!
He likes to cross-dress.
His name is Gasper Vladi.
He is my family...
and my other Bishop.
He's a freshman at Kuou Academy,
and he was half vampire, half human before he was reborn.
V-Vampire?
A vampire?!
This kid?!
Takaga shireteta terai ga uzumaite
My puny arrogance came back to me
Oisugaru koto mo dekizu ni ita yo
and I couldn't go to you for help
Namida no wake kimi ni ienai mama de
I couldn't tell you why I was crying
Kuchibiru wa itsumo sora wo nirande ita
and always frowned up to the sky
Uzumoreteta yami yori kimi ga koete kita kyoukaisen
You dug through the darkness to cross this line
Sekai system wa kakumeigire
The world's out of changes to make
Kaikan itami hakai souzou
Pleasure, pain, destruction, creation
Kaete yuku watashi no yowasa wo
I'm going to change my own weaknesses
Ima oshiyoseru kanjouron
All I can make are appeals to emotion
Inochi gake no ai wa amakunaiwa
Love's not easy with my life on the line
Tsuyoku motto tsuyoku
Stronger, even stronger
Donna uso ga matteita to shitemo
No matter what lies I face
Eranda michibiki shinjite
I've already chosen which signs to follow
Furumau koto wa nai to yasashii akuma no hohoemi wa
The devil smiles at me, telling me to be myself
Hakanaku subete wo terasu no
and shines a faint light on the world
Episode 9
I Have a Junior!
There's no way!
This couldn't possibly be happening!
But he looks so cute.
That makes it even worse!
Nobody's gonna see you cross-dressing if you never leave this room!
B-B-But...
I look cuter this way.
Quit acting like a little girl, dammit!
For a moment, I was fantasizing about a pretty, blonde girl Bishop duo.
The kanji for "human" and "dream" together make "ephemeral".
Gasper, let's go outside, okay?
No!
Come on, President's the one asking-
Huh?
Don't get mad.
Don't get mad at me!
Please let me stay here!
What was that?
He just...
He definitely did something.
"Forbidden Balor View".
It's his Sacred Gear, dubbed the "Evil Eye of the Inert World".
When he's distressed,
he can stop anything within his sights for a period of time.
Because Gasper-kun can't control his power,
Satan Sirzechs-sama decreed that he be sealed in that room.
It also turns out that the power
naturally refines itself over time,
giving it the potential to be a Balance Breaker.
A Balance Breaker?
I don't want you to talk about me.
I don't want attention!
When did he-
Geez, get out of there!
I can live inside this box!
It will be my dragon-guarded castle!
What's that supposed to mean?
President,
it's almost time.
Indeed.
Akeno and I have to attend the preliminary meeting for the leaders' conference.
Yuuto.
Yes, President?
My brother would like to know more about your Balance Breaker.
Come with me.
Yes, Ma'am.
Could I ask you to train Gasper while I'm away?
Train him?!
No!
Keep running!
You'll meet my Durandal if you slow down!
Come on, show me some spirit!
She just looks like a vampire hunter.
Run! Run!
Why are you doing this to me?
A wholesome spirit can only exist in a wholesome body.
We'll start by giving you some stamina.
Xenovia looks like she's having fun.
Y-Yeah...
I guess she likes to be that kind of person.
I'm too tired!
I can't move an inch!
Gya-kun...
This will give you some energy.
No!
I don't like garlic!
It's not good to be picky.
No! Koneko-chan's being mean to me!
Koneko-chan seems to be enjoying it, too.
Koneko-chan's actually teasing someone?
Wait.
There you are, Occult Research Club.
Hey, Saji.
I heard about your liberated hikikomori family member.
A pretty blonde girl?!
A cross-dressing boy, actually.
No...
There's no way this can be happening.
I know.
I know exactly how you feel, Saji.
Oh,
it seems the Satan's family is playing games out here.
Do you know him?
Hello, Devil-kun...
Emperor of Red Dragon.
You seem well.
Azazel...
H-Hyoudou?
Did you say "Azazel"?
Yeah.
I've seen him plenty of times already.
You can gang up on me,
but you won't leave a scratch.
Even you Low Class Devils should be able to realise that.
Why are you here?!
Just taking a walk and looking around.
Is the guy with the Holy Demonic Sword here?
Kiba's not here.
And if you're after him...
Boost!
Geez.
Still as jumpy as ever, huh?
Anyway, the Holy Demonic Sword wielder isn't here?
What a pity.
Hey, vampire.
"Forbidden Balor View".
Sacred Gears like that are extremely dangerous if the user is too weak.
That must be the Dark Dragon Vein,
"Absorption Line".
If you're training, connect it to the vampire,
and absorb the excess power as he uses his Sacred Gear.
It'll give him better control over it.
Absorb...
his power?
What, you didn't know?
That holds the power of Vritra, one of the five Dragon Kings.
The Prison Dragon, or "Dragon King of Evil".
It can absorb and negate the
power of whatever it touches.
You can connect it to other things for a short time as well.
My Sacred Gear can do that?
There is a much quicker way, though.
Drinking the blood of the Emperor of Red Dragon.
Drink my blood, huh?
Vampires are supposed to drink blood, after all.
Well, give it a shot and see how it goes.
Later.
Hold on!
Why'd you hide your identity and approach me?
For...
my hobby.
The leader of the Fallen Angels...
I don't think we'll ever know what he's up to.
Let's go!
O-Okay...
Ready, Gasper?!
Whoa, he's gone.
It's really no use if he stops the ball and us.
He was running off again.
I'm sorry!
Simply getting him to train is a hassle.
His power really isn't helping.
Maybe it's still too strong.
Saji, could you absorb a little more?
No problem.
Thanks a lot for the help.
Don't mention it.
I'm benefiting from this, too.
Oh yeah, Azazel said one more thing.
Something about drinking my blood...
No!
I don't like blood!
Aren't you a vampire?
I don't like the smell!
Useless vampire.
Koneko-chan's being mean to me!
What a pain.
Gasper, come on out.
I'm sorry for dragging you out here.
I'm sorry, President.
I didn't want to interrupt your meeting, but...
It's okay.
You did your best to help him.
I don't wanna go outside!
We did the exact opposite of what we wanted.
There's a reason why Gasper's like this.
There is?
Gasper's father is a renowned vampire,
but his mother is a human.
Vampires value pure blood more than Devils do.
Consequently, Gasper was shunned by his family.
The humans called him a monster.
He even had the ability to stop time,
but couldn't control it at all.
Everybody feared him.
Or rather, they loathed him.
If he stops you in time, he can do anything to you.
Nobody wants to be close to a person like that.
I see.
Gasper was the same as Asia.
Of course, we know that Gasper would never do such a thing.
I-I don't want this power.
Everyone stops.
That's why everyone's scared.
Everyone hates me.
I hate it, too.
I don't want to see my friend's frozen faces anymore!
I don't deserve to be a King.
President,
leave the rest to me!
I will help him.
Issei...
Don't worry.
He's my first male junior.
I'll take care of him!
Issei, I'm counting on you.
You got it, President!
Gasper, I'm going to stay here until you come out of there!
That's okay.
Y-Yes, I will be alright, don't worry
Well, do your best.
Issei-san might not be coming home tonight.
So he really is going to wait for Gasper to emerge from his room.
I feel guilty leaving it all up to him.
I feel the same.
Though, is there any way we can help?
Thank you for inviting me to use your bathroom.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
I suggested this so we could have a long talk.
But, why in your bathroom?
In Japan, there is a tradition of having naked communication.
Oh, I didn't know about this custom.
It may be an unusual situation,
but you should enjoy it.
I get it. We can talk about Gasper,
while strengthening our sisterly bonds.
Exactly!
Chasing Gaper around made me all sweaty, so I appreciate this.
Xenovia-san and Koneko-chan,
you both did your best.
Perhaps, but Issei is still the most determined.
He is even still trying to help Gasper as we speak.
Issei-senpai is always there for us.
I understand that very well.
If it wasn't for Issei helping Kiba,
I wouldn't have the wonderful life I have now.
Issei-senpai is a very kind person...
When he isn't being a pervert.
Oh yeah, I thought vampires could only come out at night,
but Gasper-kun was outside in the sun.
Gya-kun is a "daywalker". A rare type of vampire.
I thought as much, that confirms my suspicions.
"Daywalker?"
They are vampires who are unaffected by sunlight.
Well, they might not like the sun,
but it won't kill them.
Okay, so what can we do to also help Gasper-kun?
Well, his biggest hurdle is he is afraid of people.
We can't train him if he runs and hides each time.
True.
Let's work on that.
Um...
Asia, do you have a suggestion?
No, I don't have a suggestion, but...
I also feel uncomfortable talking to people in person,
I understand how he must feel.
But I am fine with the telephone,
just face to face makes me nervous.
Face to face huh?
Hey.
Are you scared...
of us and your Sacred Gear?
I have a so-called "all-powerful" Dragon in me as well.
I'm scared, too.
Every time I use it,
I feel something in my body
changing into something else.
But I never hesitate to move on.
That power could take your precious things away from you.
Why do you still use it all the time?
Because I'm stupid and don't think before I act.
However...
However?
I know that I never want to see President cry again.
My allies went down one after another,
until I was the last one standing.
Even though I was beat up really badly,
and I don't remember much,
I can still recall the tears in her eyes,
as if it happened yesterday.
I really can't deal with it.
I heard about that battle, too.
I was locked up here, though.
No need to feel guilty.
You're going to be with us from now on.
But...
I'm just going to hold everyone back.
You're not going to hold us back.
You're my important junior,
my senpai as a Devil,
and a friend.
Senpai...
Lend us a hand, Gasper.
Let's help President together!
If anything scares you, I'll beat the crap out of it!
But...
You wanna drink my blood, then?
That'll help you get better control of-
I'm scared!
I'm scared of drinking the blood of living things.
The only thing I can force myself to do is drink from a blood bag.
My power's already frightening as it is.
What am I going to do if it gets even stronger?
I...
Is it that bad?
To be honest, I'm jealous of your power.
You're jealous?
Who wouldn't want to stop time?
I know I do!
I can crawl around and look up all the girls' skirts!
Better yet, I can stop President and grope her boobs!
Oh yeah, Akeno-san's boobs, too!
I can't stop imagining things!
S-Sorry, I couldn't help it.
You're very nice.
Nobody's ever told me that they envied my powers
or provided any specific examples.
Well, uh...
I only thought that people hated my power.
You idiot!
These Sacred Gears were bestowed upon us.
If we can't escape our destiny,
what good is sulking going to do?!
Are you just going to whine all your life?!
Hear this, Gasper.
I want to transfer my Emperor of Red Dragon's power to President's boobs!
That's my current goal!
Th-That's amazing, Issei-senpai!
You have a legendary power,
and yet you use it for such a lewd and bold purpose!
I-I could never pull off such a feat.
Your imagination is driven by pure lust.
Oh, stop it.
It's nothing.
I-I think I'm a little more confident now.
Of course you are!
You won't believe this, but...
my right hand's groped President's boobs before!
R-Really?!
The boobs of your master, a High Class Devil?
That thing about transferring my power was Satan Sirzechs-sama's idea.
He thought to use a Longinus, capable of killing even God,
for that purpose?
H-He's truly fit to be a Satan!
Yeah.
He earned all of my loyalty right there.
Nice job, Issei-kun.
Oh, you done?
You're getting along with Gasper-kun already.
Nice timing.
I was going to talk with Gasper about how the men of the Gremory family could work together.
Oh, let me hear it.
I give my power to Gasper,
then Gasper stops time!
I see.
What's next?
Then, I fondle all the girls that can't move!
Um...
What would you need me for, then?
We might get attacked by enemies as I do my thing!
You use your balance breaker and keep me covered!
Now that's teamwork!
Issei-kun, I'm willing to do anything for you,
but why don't we actually think of our future as a family?
Shut up, Prince Charming!
Stop looking at me like I'm hopeless!
You've got your looks!
Meanwhile, girls wash their eyes out every time theirs meet mine!
Why the hell are you in the box again?!
S-Sorry.
I just feel more comfortable talking to people like this.
Don't worry.
The top's open.
That's not the problem!
You can't stay here forever,
especially now that your seal's been broken.
B-But...
Oh, you're getting along.
Hi.
Huh?
Why are all three of you here?
We think that you shouldn't be the only one who's looking after Gasper-kun,
so we were discussing how we could help him.
H-Help me?
You're part of our family.
K-Koneko-chan...
Have a present.
Garlic!
How's that?
Huh?
I feel safe.
Huh? Huh?
I like this.
What's going on?
It was Asia-senpai's idea.
Oh, was it?
N-No.
I don't really like talking to people in person,
but I don't mind calling them.
I just told those two that hiding my face might help me.
That's when I remembered these things,
and thought to put something on his head.
You still have more of these?!
How is it?
How do I look?
You've got a very looming presence.
Yeah.
It's like a pervert's coming after you.
It's simply... overwhelming.
This is nice.
I like it.
I've never been this surprised about you.
Really?!
Maybe this'll help me become a full-blown vampire!
I don't think so.
Thank you so much, everybody!
I'd like Gasper to go to class,
except without the paper bag on his head.
It'll take him some time.
Oh.
President, Akeno-san.
Hello.
Good timing.
We'd like you to come with us after school.
Me?
Aren't shrines bad for Devils?
Welcome, Issei-kun.
A-Akeno-san?
Sorry for making you come here on such short notice.
No problem.
Where's President?
She'll be here after her final
meeting with Sirzechs-sama.
Don't you have to be with her?
I must welcome somebody here.
Somebody?
I probably shouldn't...
It's safe for Devils to come in here.
It's currently neutral territory.
Wow, I didn't know there was a shrine this big here.
It was abandoned after its last priest passed away.
Rias held on to it for me.
Is he the Emperor of Red Dragon?
Wh-Who's there?!
Nice to meet you,
Hyoudou Issei-kun.
G-Golden wings?
I am Michael...
leader of the Angels.
What do you want to do?
churuchuchu doushitai
Hey, girls
churuchu hey girls
chu
ru
hey
girls
Lovely devils
raburi debiru
ra
girls
bu
ri
girls
de
bi
ru
You know what we wanna do! Yes!
churuchuchu aa shitai yes
They've descended upon us again
yes
kyou mo kourin
kyou
mo
kou
yes
rin
Girls are always greedy for more
shoujo wa shinkakei ni yokubari na no desu
I want this, I want that
are mo kore mo
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
kinou to kuraberun ja manzoku dekinai
Uh-oh
arere
a
i
re
Let's have a strategy meeting on how to upgrade
appugureedo sakusen kaigi
Agreed!
sansei
san
sei
I'm sure you have at least one of these
daredemo hitotsu kurai motte iru desho
You too, and you too
kimi mo kimi mo
Original magic words that protect your heart
orijinaru no jumon kokoro no omamori
Uh-huh
aruru
a
ri
ru
Positive thoughts that give you strength
purasu shikou taishitsu kyouka
Never compromising our love or dream
koi mo yume mo totteoki wo ne te ni ireru tame ni
Everyone
minna
mi
ni
n
na
We want to follow our heart
fiiringu juushi de
risaachi
de
Research
ri
saa
de
As we grow up
seichou shitai na
You see, girls are lovely devils
onna no ko wa ne raburi debiru
Deep down in their hearts, so treat them with great care
mune no naka kakushiteru no toriatsukai youchuui
They're only interested in having fun
tanoshii koto shika kyoumi nai no yo
Their whimsical temper makes them cute
wagamama ni kawaiku narun da
Promise!
yakusoku
ya
ku
so
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
During that time, I found out
about Akeno's past,
and there seem to be a lot
of different ups and downs!
Next Episode: "Various Three-Way Deadlocks!"
Various Three-Way Deadlocks!
Episode 10
Hanging boobs!