Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Quatre.
What's going on?
Tell the others for me.
Tell them to stay away.
Otherwise...
I'll kill them.
I told you to stay away!
Is that all you've got
to say?!
If everything has gone mad...
...then I'll just fight,
believing in myself.
Quatre, I'm gonna kill you.
Quatre vs. Heero
The shield won't hold
much longer.
Heero...
Why are we fighting each other?
The colonies have
teamed up with OZ.
The colonies are my enemies.
They're your enemies
now too, Trowa and Heero.
People in space have
lost all reason.
That's why I'm gonna
destroy everything.
That's natural isn't it, Heero?
You'll die, Heero.
But I don't want to defeat
my allies.
Please Heero, get away
from here.
Are you listening to me?!
Quatre.
I'm not leaving.
Here's a colony that needs
to be defended.
Heero.
I can't stand that colony
any longer.
We've lost communication with
Trowa Barton's Vayeate...
...and the Leo unit that's
fighting the Gundam!
The whole unit, including the
Mercurius, may be wiped out.
And the colony?
Huh?
Is the colony still there?
Yes, so far it's been spared
any significant damage.
That means the battle
is still going on.
Righteous Gundam pilots would
fight to protect the colonies.
Hopefully they'll be able to
stop this new Gundam.
Images from the mother
ship of Leo's unit.
Good.
Now send these to the Gundam
engineers at the Lunar Base.
We should be able to find out
something from them.
But Colonel.
We can't communicate with
the Lunar Base right now.
What?!
Chief Engineer Tubarov!
We've just received orders
from Fortress Barge...
...to restore communication.
Never mind.
We must follow the orders
from Duke Dermail...
...to speed up mobile doll
production.
There appears to be some
unrest within Romefeller.
People cannot be trusted.
We're entering an age
where mobile dolls...
...will be our new warriors.
You old guys seem calm
considering it won't be long...
...before the air is gone
and we start passing out.
We haven't even got our
revenge against OZ yet.
What a lousy way to die.
I sure wish I could've seen
that new Gundam, too.
We didn't finish upgrading
the Deathscythe and Shenlong.
Such a shame.
My words, exactly.
I never would've guessed
I'd be dying like this.
Hey, Wu Fei.
My Deathscythe is pretty
cool, don't you think?
I'd demolish OZ with this
in no time!
What's wrong?
Are you already dead?
Come on, Wu Fei.
Don't go deserting me.
Stick with me to the end.
He's totally stopped breathing.
He's in a state of
suspended animation.
This guy's unbelievable.
He refuses to give up.
It makes perfect sense.
Who'd wanna die like this?
The Gundams...
The Gundams can't afford
to lose at this point.
I'd ask you to get out
of your mobile suit.
But you wouldn't.
So I'll just have to kill you.
Then get it over with.
I won't sit here and gab
with an enemy.
Good-bye, Heero.
Quatre.
Why don't you realize what
a big mistake you're making?
Trowa!
This battle is unnecessary.
Trowa, escape!
The Vayeate's gonna explode!
Well.
It's the end of the line.
Trowa!
No, Heero!
Save Trowa!
Trowa!!
Quatre.
It doesn't matter how the
colonies and OZ teamed up.
We have to keep
in mind...
...that it marks the end
to a war.
It also means our missions
have come to an end.
It's too bad that the colonies
we've been fighting for...
...have changed their
perspectives.
But that's what happens
in wars.
We've got to accept that.
The only question is what
happens to the soldiers.
What happens within
our hearts.
With us Gundam pilots...
...we were trained to be too
perfect as soldiers.
When you put everything
into a battle...
...you start to think you can
change the times by yourself.
Quatre, you're not the only
one who feels that way.
We all do.
But the kinder you are, the
bigger the toll it takes on you.
We have to fight with ourselves,
within our hearts.
And we have to be strict to
come to the right conclusions.
Even if it means our battles
to date are meaningless.
We have to acknowledge
the facts.
The five of us have become
redundant soldiers.
So Quatre, let's accept it.
Turn back into the kind
guy you once were.
I just hope something
triggers you to calm down.
Something triggers you...
Trowa!!
Heero, let me go!
Trowa's gonna die!
And you killed him.
Heero...
You've gone crazy.
I'll kill you.
Well hurry and kill me.
Then go and rescue Trowa!
Pretty halfhearted way
to fight!
I guess Trowa's death was
just a waste!
Quatre.
I'm...gonna...
...kill you.
Heero!
Heero!!
Don't be too hard
on Quatre, Heero.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
With the financial power of
the Romefeller Foundation...
...a revolution in technological
skills in space is possible.
The system for mass-production
of mobile dolls is almost ready.
As the ruling class to be,
we will position mobile dolls...
...in dispute-ridden regions
in each country.
Thus gentlemen, we will
show the entire world...
...how powerful we are,
and bring order to the world.
Is it not time for us
to recreate an era...
...with tradition and
formality...
...so we can govern
the world properly?!
Treize, OZ is relying on you.
Duke Dermail.
I can't support the Romefeller
Foundation's current path.
What?!
Tradition is a kind of history.
It's the history of sympathy,
built on people's true feelings.
I think fighting in wars
can indeed be beautiful.
I'd also like to express my
regret over the lost souls...
...by appealing to how
priceless man's life is.
I believe what mankind needs
is not absolute victory...
...but a certain demeanor in
fighting, an attitude towards it.
I fear the era of the soulless
weapons called mobile dolls...
...in other words the era
Romefeller is creating...
...may be an embarrassment
to the people of the future.
I used to think that the ideals
of Space Colonies people...
...such as their highly
praised pacifism...
...were pitiful complaints born
of their ignorance of tradition.
Hey, Deathscythe.
Don't give up too easily.
You'll be okay, right?
About to commence second test.
Damn!
NO!!!
What's this?
Those sparkles...
They're my tears.
But from those circumstances...
...new warriors who surpassed
even my ideals were born.
I'm referring to the
Gundam pilots.
Father?!
FATHER!!
You're afraid of dying,
aren't you.
Then you shouldn't be
fighting in the first place!
Tradition appears blurred
alongside their pure feelings.
From a historical point...
...warriors who lost what
they were protecting...
...and who were betrayed,
are losers.
But they don't recognize that.
Not only that...
...but they retain a strong will
to continue fighting.
I'm doing everything I can...
...in case "something drastic"
does happen.
If everything has gone mad...
...then I'll just fight,
believing in myself.
The emotions of those
considered beautiful...
...are always full of sorrow.
And honored tradition disappears
in the cry of the weak.
Winners of a war will eventually
decline in history to be losers...
...only then can they cultivate
a new energy.
Treize, what are you getting at?
I want to be a loser.
You're saying that you want
Romefeller headquarters...
...to take OZ out of
your control?
We don't wish to see any blood.
Besides, we must take your
services into account.
I hereby confine you to
Romefeller headquarters!
With a fancy gun that has
forgotten the meaning of war...
...I'd feel no emotion...
...even if I were to shoot an
enemy through the heart.
It's not that a pure person
has no direction.
It's that their mind is free.
The Lunar Base is entering
the firing range...
...of Barge's beam cannon.
A troop of Taurus mobile dolls
dispatched by the Lunar Base...
...is approaching.
They're ready to attack!
Communication with the
Lunar Base restored!
Lady Une.
Transporting the Barge wasn't
in today's plans, was it.
The mobile dolls were all
prepared to attack you.
A merciless weapon.
Is that what the mobile doll is?
Precisely.
We've completed our mass
production system here.
We've produced superb soldiers...
...that will allow Romefeller
to exercise order on Earth.
Now I understand why Treize
dislikes the mobile dolls.
Pardon?
Treize fell in love with people.
And with the death of people.
Something about death intensely
appeals to people's emotions.
The emotions that the dead give,
denying or affirming battle.
High emotions lead to
extreme choices.
The act of receiving death
is a true soldier's demeanor.
Isn't that how the weak
would think?
We created these immortal
mobile dolls...
...and will build a future
of battle that disregards death...
...and in which death isn't
a factor.
Tubarov.
Don't you realize?
It's not that mobile dolls
transcend death.
They're merely replacing those
who are afraid to die.
One cannot go into a war
expecting to be defeated.
It doesn't matter whether
you win or lose.
Emotions are honed by
continuing to fight.
And a day comes when
lost souls are rewarded.
I fail to understand
what you're getting at.
That's exactly why you
and I are enemies!
Order the mobile dolls to
attack Fortress Barge.
They'll have the beam cannon
targeting this base!
They won't realize Barge
is a decoy.
I can't predict the damage
Barge's beam cannon...
...would cause the Lunar Base.
Make it through this, Barge.
It won't be long.
Ten Leos have crossed
our defense line!
They're attacking the gates
where most of the guards...
...have gone to stop Barge!
They know where all our
mobile dolls are situated.
That makes it interesting.
Take over the production
factory of the mobile dolls!
Where are you going, Colonel?
I'm releasing the Gundam pilots!
Treize and I both want that.
The enemy isn't pursuing.
Then we'll defend this position.
Captain!!
What is it?
The new mobile suits are
already operating!
I hope I'm not too late.
Even if you're not, we'll
execute them anyway.
Then I ask that you
execute me too.
In the past, failure meant
certain death at OZ.
Shoot me, Tubarov.
To confirm your beliefs.
Lady Une.
You were far too lenient.
As a soldier, yes.
But as a civilian
I lived a strict life.
It's only 70% complete.
We can't put up much
of a fight!
It's amazing that
we're even alive.
Can't complain.
Wanna escape?!
After we pay them back.
The charm of you pilots
threw everything out of order.
Your pure hearts are suffering...
...in a world where answers
cannot be found.
Those that think tenderly
about you in that situation...
...realize just how powerless
they themselves are.
They become hasty,
and are crushed.
But please continue shining,
brave warriors.
And let me continue loving you.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Hearing of Treize's confinement...
...OZ soldiers called
the "Treize Faction"...
...enter a battle with
Romefeller.
The Virgo mobile dolls
sent to Earth...
...have tremendous assault
capabilities.
The Foundation wants to destroy
the Gundams and their allies...
...seeing them as a symbol
of opposition.
They order the Gundam pilots'
execution.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 26,
The Eternal Flame of the Shooting Stars
"The Eternal Flame of the Shooting Stars".