Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
"Those who've laid eyes on
a Gundam shall not live."
Those are my orders.
THERE'S A GUNDAM DOWN HERE!!
Are you all right?
I need you to reload
the explosives for Heero.
Forget that...
Stop worrying about that
right now!
Start thinking about what
your next move will be!
The Sorrowful Battle
We're above the Filchner
Ice Shelf of the Weddell Sea.
We should be at the Barclay
Base in five minutes.
Any signs of enemies?
Nothing on the radar
or heat sensors.
I see.
We'll expect Acht's search party
to regroup before attacking...
...rather than assume they've
given up pursuing us.
That's a wise decision.
So OZ has one able officer.
Colonel Zechs.
I've brought Heero Yuy and
Trowa Barton, as requested.
Thank you.
I'm Zechs Merquise.
Supposed to shake hands?
No.
It's fine.
Heero Yuy, huh?
The same name as the leader
who held the colonies together.
Is that your real name?
Are you using your real name?
Forgive me.
I suppose there's no point
using names from now on.
We've prepared a friendly
reception for you.
Try to make yourselves
at home.
My mobile suit!
Do you like it?
Colonel Zechs!
The repairs to Zero One have
been completed.
The only things left are
the operational adjustments.
I'll introduce you.
This is Meiser, in charge of
restoring your Gundam.
Pleasure.
All that's left is adjusting
the cockpit to suit yourself.
Meiser's young, but
his skills are top class.
When can we start?
How about tomorrow morning?
That's fine.
Heero Yuy.
Don't you wanna say
something to Colonel Zechs?
I'll thank him,
but in my own way.
I'll kill Zechs.
That's how I'll show
my gratitude.
That'd be fine.
To the soldiers fighting
to protect the colonies...
...this battle's merely an
obstacle.
And I'm a mere stepping stone.
I've never shaken hands
with anyone before.
I feel that I can't let
either of them die.
Of course not Zechs;
but not Heero either.
I've told you many times,
we've destroyed Gundam Zero One.
There isn't a single stabilizer
left here.
I'll wait until after I meet
Colonel Zechs...
...to decide if that's true.
The Colonel isn't here.
Then let me meet Lieutenant
Noin, who was in charge.
She'll meet me if you
tell her I'm Relena Peacecraft.
But as I said...
Forgive me a moment.
Hello...What?
Good, well done!
Relena.
Okay, that's fine.
Relena 's on her way here?!
Yes.
Even the Peacecrafts have
caught on.
I expect Romefeller's found
out by now.
Please be very cautious.
Thank you, I will.
From now on, many people
will probably try...
...sucking up to the
Romefeller Foundation.
Defeating Zechs, who's seen
as a Gundam defender...
...would prove one's
loyalty to the Foundation.
The search party's manhunt
could be intense.
But Zechs is practically
OZ's hero.
Why would they be after him?
Is the path Zechs is
about to take wrong?
Sorry.
Didn't mean to eavesdrop.
I might have at least
a partial answer.
During my many years
with OZ...
...I developed an aesthetic
sense in war.
I thought it's a spirit that
fighters could acknowledge...
...in each other, even
between enemies.
But those Gundam pilots
are desperate.
They'll battle even if it costs
their lives.
They live the true lives
of soldiers!
I'm much too weak!
They know they're fighting
for the colonies!
Zechs, you have someone
to protect too!
I don't have the right
to protect anyone.
They'd say that the very
thought itself makes me weak.
There's no need to bring
any pride into battle.
If I'm only capable of
that kind of battle...
...I'll simply be defeated
here by the Gundam.
This is war.
Some lessons can only be
learned by risking one's life.
Zechs...
Noin.
This battle will take awhile.
I hope we can fight without
any interruptions.
Leave it to me.
I'll prevent the search party
from interfering.
I'm more concerned about
the dignitary of the Peacecraft.
My dear Imperial Guard.
No.
The most important person
to you is Relena.
You'll fight your best knowing
you must protect that girl.
He doesn't trust me.
It's not that.
He just doesn't want anyone
touching his mobile suit.
That's all.
But still...
The self-detonation device
isn't connected.
Colonel Zechs says you
won't be needing it.
So Zechs had regrets after
their last showdown.
This time he really
wants to fight it out.
Aren't you gonna fight
in your own mobile suit?
I'm gonna use yours after all.
How come?
This generosity is blurring
the focus on fighting.
That wouldn't be an
issue with you.
No, I'm talking about him.
You're strong.
I see.
So he'll fight with Zero Three
rather than Zero One.
What in the world could
they be thinking of?
He sees our gift as
some kind of charity.
But my feelings are unchanged.
Colonel.
Should we restore the
left arm of the Tallgeese?
There's still time to take
the supply parts off Zero One.
No, just leave it.
But sir...
This is a continuation
of our last battle.
Tallgeese had its left arm
damaged there, in Siberia.
So this is a valid handicap.
Chief Engineer.
I guess that's the difference
between engineers and pilots.
I suppose so.
Backstage crew like us
don't feel that kind of pride.
I'm just trying to rid
myself of the weakness.
What time is it?
2:32 a.m.
I'll take over.
Appreciate it.
This weight will be tough
for his left arm to handle.
Has it begun?!
Yeah, just now.
Is my radar out?
He's below!
He's using snow clouds
to mask the heat source.
There!
We won't die in such
a low-caliber fight.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Almost three hours since
the battle started!
That's a long time for
a meaningless battle.
Meaningless?
What do you mean, meaningless?!
Am I wrong?
I dunno the details, but OZ
is after you people.
What's the point of two sides
with a mutual enemy...
...fighting against each other?
Think it's the pilots' fate?
That's stupid.
You might have a point.
But they've been out to kill
each other until now.
So naturally they feel
it's some kind of fate.
This battle will go on until
they realize it is meaningless.
Are people trying to stop time
in order to find themselves?
Enemies are necessary.
That's the soldier's fate.
No.
A soldier's rejuvenated when
he finds someone to protect.
Sometimes that takes time.
Right now we've lost sight
of how to protect the colonies.
We really can't afford to
be wasting time here.
I'll prevent any interruptions,
so they can get this over.
You mean the search party?
Trowa, how will you fight them?
I'll have Heero return my favor.
When you run out of bullets,
click that switch.
It'll make the left arm lighter.
So you're right out
of fire power!
A beam saber!
Trowa went out of
his way for me.
That's more like it!
I have no regrets.
That's what happens in war.
A wrong turn in the past
can be painful for anyone.
But you people are still young!
I hope you'll think about
building a new future!
Our family is honored
to have met with you!
Relena!
Civilian aircraft, land at once!
This is a strategic air zone!
Hurry, Pagan!
We mustn't stop!
But they're surveillance suits
from the search party...
...chasing Zechs Merquise.
We don't know what they'll do!
They won't follow us
to the Barclay Base.
Escape!
I'll try my best!
The civilian aircraft is
accelerating!
Shoot it down!
What the heck?
A mobile suit...
It's a Gundam!!
Heero?
He's fighting just up ahead.
What are you doing?
I'm stopping his fight
with Zechs.
This battle is meaningless.
I understand.
Then you'd better hurry.
The search party's becoming
more aggressive.
His left arm's not working well.
He's noticed.
You gave yourself a handicap!
You're being way too kind!
I'd like to rid myself of such
silly pride in this battle!
This'll finish you off!
Heero!
What?!
Is that Relena?
Heero, I've got a letter
to deliver to you!
You're in the way!
Get lost!
No, I'm not going!
This letter explains how
you should live your life!
You're obliged to read it!
Princess!!
Zechs Merquise!
Princess!
Please leave at once!
I must take revenge for
the death of my men!
I hereby order you under
the Peacecraft family name.
Stop this battle immediately!
You've become strong, Relena.
Fitting, for a Peacecraft
daughter.
See for yourself how dirty
and foul battles really are!
No...
If you're a true warrior
and a Peacecraft knight...
...you couldn't possibly
use such foul play!
Relena, call from
Lieutenant Noin.
Miss Noin!
I misunderstood you.
I thought you were sincere.
How can you just sit by
and watch this?!
This is neither a duel
nor a match.
They're just killing each other!
Precisely.
I deserve your contempt,
but I can't help myself.
I believe in Colonel Zechs!
I'm not about to interrupt
any of his plans.
Heero!
Defeat Zechs!
Anyone associated with
a foul group like OZ...
...is an embarrassment to
the Sanc Kingdom!
Go ahead!
Kill him!
Stop it! Relena!
Please stop.
It's a fact that he's
associated with OZ.
And I don't deny that some
mistakes were made.
I won't explain it away with his
love for the Sanc Kingdom.
But Relena, no matter what
fate has dealt you in the past...
...please don't ever wish
for your brother's death!
Brother...he's my brother?
Since the Peacecraft monarchy
fell to the Alliance...
...he's had his heart set
on revenge.
Assembling power in the ruined
Sanc Kingdom was hard.
He chose to join OZ, to get
closer to the Alliance.
He waited, donning a disguise
he called Zechs Merquise.
My hands have been stained
with too much blood.
Relena is the appropriate person
to revive the Sanc Kingdom!
Once OZ brought a new wave
of chaos to the world...
...Zechs must've lost a sense
of purpose in his life.
He can find the soldier
in himself...
...only when he fights
the Gundams.
That's what this is about.
Heero lives by his own rules.
And Zechs wants to battle
him on a level playing field.
To embrace the Sanc Kingdom
and the Peacecraft name!
He's even prepared to
lose his life for this!
I'll keep believing in him.
I want to stay by his side.
No matter what he does or
searches for.
You're fond of my brother.
Yes. I love him.
Please watch over my brother
forever.
I don't know if I can.
Colonel Zechs can be reckless.
It's in the Peacecraft blood.
Numerous carriers approaching
from 3 o'clock!
Probably from the search party!
How many?
Over thirty, but that's only
a portion of their fleet.
Get all the mobile suits ready!
We'll attack the search party!
They're here!
Do you read me, Heero
and Zechs?
Thirty suits in flight.
A hundred if they unload
all Aries suits.
Each of us should be able
to handle thirty easily.
No, wait!
I'll attract them away!
Glory to the colonies!!
Zechs!
Heero!
We'll meet again,
to continue our battle!
He'll be one tough guy
to fight from now on.
Yeah.
Colonel Zechs.
Aries troops are ready
to be deployed.
Then take Relena with you
and make your escape.
Zechs!!
Once I know you've gotten
away safely, I'll surrender.
Then I'm gonna fight too!
Noin!
I'll protect the promising
leader of the Sanc Kingdom!
Allow me to protect her!
I understand.
Take care, Zechs...
I don't care how it happened.
I'm just glad that battle's
finally over.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The war zone expands
into outer space.
OZ moves to finally finish off
the Alliance Military.
It also plans to reconcile
the colonies.
Quatre and Duo head
for outer space...
...to warn the colonies
of OZ's conspiracy.
But the colonies that had
been their home...
...declare the Gundams
to be their enemies.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 17,
Betrayed by Home, Far Away
"Betrayed by Home, Far Away".