I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Me, Uncle? To the Olympics?
Yes. One day, you should
aim for something like that.
There's no need to worry.
You have the skills for it.
If I do that, will I be able
to regain my father's honor?
As a member of your father's family,
that is the one thing you can do.
If I do that, then once again...
But before you do...
...you might need
some qualifications.
Lieutenant? Lieutenant!
- Menshov! The Dragunov!
- Here!
Excellent. If this were Los Angeles
you'd get the gold medal!
The first lieutenant has
paved the way!
Everyone, move out!
Leave behind the chemicals! Let's go!
The women's fifty meter rifle,
third place.
The gold medal goes to
Launi Meili of the U.S.A.!
Meili finished in sixth place
four years ago...
And what do you want me to do?
Captain.
Having been stripped of my
military rank, I'm no longer a captain.
And you aren't in
my company anymore.
The Soviet Union,
the country we fought for...
...no longer exists in this world.
No matter what
battlefield we're on...
...as long as we fight under you...
...a path will surely open.
We all believe that.
Even through this shameful poverty.
I never imagined that
my second-in-command...
...would lose his life
because of dirty money.
Comrades, raise your fists!
From this moment we will return
to our own active military duty!
We've fought through many battlefields
since that day at the cemetery.
Yes.
What we're doing now is
no more than a check point.
Let's take care of things swiftly.
After Bando, she's the next
leader of the Washimine Clan.
She's just a little girl.
The sun's setting a lot
earlier these days, isn't it?
Yukio, what's gotten into you?
You sorted all those
library cards in one day.
I'm glad that you finished, but...
It's even starting to snow!
It's a nice evening.
Huh? But Yukio, didn't you say
you don't like snowy nights?
Maki.
Try to get along with your mother.
You're a very good girl.
Y-Yukio?
Come on, Yukio. You sound like
you're about to die or something.
Yukio!
Miss Deputy, we've come for you.
Thank you.
Let's get started then.
Yukio.
I... Uh...
Take care.
I... I don't get what's going on. But...
Yukio.
Yukio!
Have you found
Balalaika's whereabouts?
Not yet. It won't be easy to figure out
where they'll come out from.
We've got people looking for them now.
No matter how they get around...
...people are gonna notice a bunch
of Russians roaming around.
Send people to Azabu as well.
And to the Russian Embassy
and any other place...
...they may be expected to frequent.
There's a political group in
that area that we know well.
I'll ask them to investigate.
Shouldn't we send soldiers to Narita
and Haneda airports as well, Deputy?
I'm sure they've taken any
counterattack by us into consideration.
I don't believe they have
any intention of fleeing.
That woman is willing to fight.
Deputy. Shall I stop somewhere?
No, I'm all right.
I'll just have to get used to this.
- Mr. Yoshida.
- Y-Yes?
I haven't thanked you yet...
for that time at the meeting.
Deputy! That was nothing!
That time...
This isn't a wake!
The Miss is here...
...so that you won't get taken
by Kousa's bastards...
...only to be thrown out!
She's putting her
own life on the line!
If there's any time to show
your chivalry, it's right here and now!
You were not even involved, Miss...
...but you still said you would
avenge our boss.
The least a yakuza can do is put
his life on the line for you.
Deputy, I will begin now.
I will see you later at home.
Gin!
This is your first job.
Please work carefully tonight.
You can count on me.
No one's answering, Boss.
I can't reach Balalaika
or any of the other members.
Try again. Keep calling until you
get a hold of someone, Makaruska.
They've left the hotel, and we have
no clue as to where they'd go.
Perhaps we should ask for
direction from Moscow.
Don't you ever blurt anything stupid
like "ask for direction" again!
When I say try again,
I mean try again!
Damn it. Damn it, damn it!
That woman must have
worked them up against me.
Otherwise, there's no way
Slevnin would betray me!
But why would she frame us?
Not you guys, it's me!
She hates the KGB!
But not only the KGB. The GRU
and the Nomenklatura as well!
There are plenty of others who
were crushed by that woman!
What did Slevnin say
about this woman?
Get down!
It's the yakuza!
Is it over?
Souga's Sukeroku has
come to play. Now...
Where can I find Ikyu the Bearded?
His only weapon is that sword!
Kill him!
Mister. Where are you headed?
You see, I have quite a few things
I'd like to ask you.
First of all, I need the phone number
of that lady boss of yours.
Wait a minute! Don't kill me!
- I was framed, damn it, lower your sword!
- Oh, you don't understand Japanese.
Very well. In that case,
you're of no use to me.
Tell those Ivans
to pay us better tips.
The higher-ups have been
annoying lately.
We've gotta be compensated
for it in some way.
Tell them yourself, Bro.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Rock.
She's gonna be pissed.
Now, let's hurry back.
I finally get to say goodbye
to that Tokarev.
I can't get far without these guys.
What's wrong?
It's started.
Yeah, the battle. I'll bet she's...
...laughing her head off right now.
- A big riot, just like she wanted.
- That girl...
Revy, I can't leave her alone.
Will you please come with
me to her place?
Don't be stupid. Think again for
a moment what we are to them.
Right now, we are their enemy.
Please, Revy! If she's at all
associated with Washimine...
...then it's certain that she's
gonna get dragged into this!
Now that I've seen how
Miss Balalaika handles things...
...I'm even more sure of it!
That girl is not like us!
- Rock.
- She's just a normal girl!
Rock!
And this isn't Roanapur!
How is it different?
How is it any different, Rock?
She's living on our side...
...and the Sis will sort
things out Roanapur style.
There's no difference anywhere.
But still, I...
Come on, Rock.
You're in a watershed.
If you leave this territory...
...you have no place to return to.
They're sold out of the Ameri-Pass...
...and the Greyhound will never
travel this road again.
What I'm saying is,
this is your country.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Sure I do. But still...
It's all right. Sorry 'bout that.
Forget what I said, Rock.
I forgot something important.
While we're here, I'm your gun.
My job is to protect your life,
not to interfere with it.
So I'll follow you, Master.
Um, so...
Don't connect any phone calls unless
they're from the Russian Embassy.
Is that correct? Um, Miss Vladilena?
That's right. Thank you very much.
If you need anything else,
please call for me by name.
That boy is at the peak of his
adorableness. Now, Sergeant.
Yes, Captain. We have a report
from the reconnaissance team.
Attack Point Two is in stage yellow.
The area surrounding the
Kousa Clan office is heavily guarded.
The police of this country
are very competent.
Police who do not accept bribes
are always competent.
It's a matter of quality, Sergeant.
Have you seen the news?
Yes. Comrade Laptev did a fine job.
You're right. He reconnoitered
the enemy well for a KGB agent.
His successor to the Tokyo post
will be Bulgazivry the Priest.
He's very skilled with the abacus.
But we'll handle the violence.
Let us begin our work.
Job well done, Miss. They will be
contacting the office with the results.
Right. Thank you, Mr. Yoshida.
Umm, Miss...
I'm sorry about what
happened at your school.
I knew it would cause
you trouble, but...
I know.
But it's something I would eventually
have to tell her at some point, anyway.
In retrospect, that was
perhaps the best timing.
Thank you, Mr. Yoshida.
You're being much too kind!
It's chilly tonight, so hurry in.
Huh? You're here sooner
than I expected!
I thought it would take you longer!
Chaka! What the hell
are you doing here?!
You've got your station!
Why aren't you there?!
Come on, man. Think of the
current situation. Right, Miss?
Chaka! You need to
know your place!
Nobody would allow this!
Are you listening to me, you shit?!
Chaka, are these your guys?
Mr. Yoshida.
Let me tell you something.
You're much too kind.
Did that hurt?
Sorry 'bout that, Mr. Yoshida.
Damn you!
You see, how should I put it,
it's our policy...
...not to associate ourselves with
anyone we can't benefit from.
Well, we don't care if it's
the Kousa Clan or the Russians.
They're not gonna treat us badly
if we can bring them a present.
- Right, Miss?
- Miss. Hurry up and run!
Would you stop being such a pest,
old timer?! Aw, the hell with you.
Hurry up and die.
Have another one!
Hey!
That hurt!
- Bitch.
- Oh, boy.
- Hana can be scary when he snaps.
- I feel sorry for that girl.
You can hurt people when you
run into them like that.
I said it hurt! I'm serious!
You're asking for it!
Don't you have anything
to say to me?!
Like "I'm sorry"? Or "I apologize"?
- Stand up!
- Hey, hey, Hanada.
Who told you to beat the shit
out of her? If you go too far...
...I'll kill you.
I guess I owe you an apology, Yuki.
Our group is full of guys who
lose control when they snap.
- You look lame, Hanada.
- Forgive me!
So you better listen to us and follow
orders, or it could get dangerous.
Rock, is this the only entrance?
We're uninvited guests here.
The back door would be...
That's not it.
Haven't you noticed, Rock?
This place is filled with a smell
I'm much too familiar with.
Footprints? Oh no! Yukio!
Don't rush in, Rock!
Yukio!
Damn it.
Did Balalaika do this?
If so, the girl would be
lying here too.
The girl doesn't have enough value
as a hostage to Hotel Moscow.
The Sis uses a Stechkin. The other
guys use military autos like Varjags.
An AKS wouldn't be out of the
question either, but look at the floor.
Why aren't there any cases?
A revolver was used.
Yeah, that would be it.
How unfortunate for Yoshida.
The breeze goes right through
his body now.
Look. These holes are huge.
A large caliber gun was used.
Show-offs who own these kind of
guns are idiots beyond all salvation.
One guy that fits that
description comes to mind.
It's him! But why would
he betray them?
I don't get it.
There's no smell of gunpowder.
Get it, Jumbo?
My gun had nothing to do with
how Yoshida bought the farm.
Mr. Ginji.
We didn't do this.
Hotel Moscow hasn't made it this far yet.
We came to get Yukio...
...so we could keep her
away from this sort of stuff...
...when we walked into this.
Please trust me.
We have nothing to do
with Hotel Moscow's...
Wait, Mr. Ginji!
I'm not done talking!
I didn't hear a car when you arrived.
You returned here on foot, alone.
There are tire marks
everywhere out front.
Judging from the footprints here...
...it looks like they came in
numbers from a distance.
Are you planning on going alone?
This has nothing to do with you.
We don't have time! The one who
did this is one of your own guys!
And he knows you'll be coming to
take her back, and he'll be waiting.
But what if a skilled
gunman was at your side?
That would be outside
of his calculations.
So you want to know where he is?
We have a fax from
one of our listeners.
It's all Japanese talk.
Don't you play any music?
I have no idea what they're saying.
- What about FEN?
- The DJ keeps playing lousy songs.
Yeah, it's Guitar Wolf! I know these guys!
They play some cool tunes.
Mr. Interpreter.
Turn left at the next intersection.
I don't understand why
you're helping.
Mr. Ginji. She's not the kind of
person who belongs on this side.
That's what I felt.
I hate the idea that a kid who
could've grown up normally, didn't.
If someone had allowed her to,
that would have been good for her.
If only someone
had allowed her to...
Strike!
If I get one more point,
take one more off.
What do you think, Okazaki?
- Top? Or bottom?
- Ahh... I say bottom.
If she's completely naked
then the bet's over.
Then when that happens,
let's do it!
Let's shave her pubes.
That would be hilarious!
It's the Dark Tower.
The knight has
arrived to save the princess.
Rock, we'll charge in from the front.
You go in from the back.
- What should I do?
- Simple.
Just cover our backs
when we need you to.
Revy, can you two communicate?!
No problem.
Once the fight begins,
our bodies will move on their own.
That's the way we're made.
Next Episode
This is Hell's Motel.
Run away, if you can...
...or the boogeyman's
gonna eat you up!