Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
With high hopes, humans
leave Earth...
...to begin a new life in
the Space Colonies.
But the United Earth Sphere
Alliance gains military power...
...and in the name of
Justice and Peace...
...seizes control of one
colony after the other.
The year is After Colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
To counter the Alliance's
tyranny, rebel colonists...
...bring new arsenals
to the Earth...
...disguising them as
shooting stars.
But the Alliance headquarters
catches on to this operation.
Just as I thought.
Others are attacking OZ
facilities besides just me.
Wish I could meet them all.
I'm not involved.
Scenario for Bloodshed
This is New Edwards Base reporting
the shuttle's arrival.
Including ground vehicles,
a considerable number are here.
I see.
Thank you.
I shrewdly spread rumors
that all top officers...
...of OZ will be coming
to New Edwards.
At least the part about you
and I being there will be true.
Are you counting yourself
in as a decoy?
Positioning is 100% complete.
We shouldn't need to
increase it any further.
So Zechs is in Nairobi.
Shouldn't we use him for
something more significant?
We don't have as many OZ
soldiers stationed in Nairobi.
We're expecting a fierce
battle there.
I see.
People will stop doubting and
will be devoted to a new future.
Mission accepted.
OZ leaders will assemble
at New Edwards.
Trowa's disappeared again?!
Yes, but he did say that
he'd be coming back.
That punk keeps wandering off!
Normally I wouldn't hesitate
to fire someone like that.
But he's too good to
get rid of.
Blast him!
I'll make him earn his
pay when he gets back!
Trowa, how come you
keep disappearing?
I can't believe Quatre suddenly
took off to a resort on his own.
He's still just a kid.
Must've been tired of hanging
around with old farts like us.
You fools!
Master Quatre's left
us behind...
...so he could go alone
on some type of mission.
What?!
Are you serious, Captain?
He was concerned about our
safety, so he left us behind.
But that'll put Quatre
in danger!
I couldn't refuse his kind
consideration for our safety.
But Master Quatre, I wish
you'd come to me for advice.
Is this the San Francisco
Starley Hotel?
I'd like to reserve a room.
I'm on my own,
is that a problem?
Isn't that Trowa?!
Hi! So we meet again!
Funny we ended up
at the same place.
I'm doing this alone.
So am I.
But it'd be better if we
helped each other.
Think so?
Two's always better than one!
Enemy attack!!
Enemy attack?!
Freight compartment?
That suit...
Hey! Load yours on too.
I'll come and take over
the cockpit.
Duo!
This time I definitely won't
let the mission fail!
How about trusting me a bit?
Do what you want.
What do you know.
He remembered my name
after all.
Man, this is gonna be quite
the battle isn't it.
I don't think you understand
how big this mission is.
You bet I do.
This is our chance to finally
destroy the OZ organization.
This time is different.
We're gonna eliminate
every OZ leader.
Yeah. Then I can return to space.
At the New Edwards Base, United
Earth Sphere Alliance leaders...
...including Field Marshal
Noventa as Chief Commander...
...General Septem, leader of
the Alliance's Space Force...
...General Ventei, leader of the
Alliance's Terrestrial Forces...
...and other top leaders
gather for a conference.
Of course the Specials'
Colonel Treize...
...and Lieutenant Colonel
Une would also attend.
But Treize secretly disseminates
false information worldwide...
...stating that this meeting is
in fact a general meeting...
...of top OZ officials,
rather than Alliance leaders.
Let's see how the future
will pan out.
It'll take whatever direction
you determine.
It's up to the Alliance whether
my plans to reform succeed.
That'll determine the future.
Lieutenant Zechs.
The Nairobi Base is inquiring
about our formation.
Say we're practicing
maneuvers...
...and conducting a simulation
air battle above Mombasa.
Yes, sir!
Noin.
This battle might leave you
feeling upset later on.
I trust you, Zechs.
If you say this is an important
attack, then I'll fight.
The Alliance and OZ...
It's not as if the world will
change if one replaces the other.
So why should we even fight?
The Alliance was formed to
deter the military powers...
...of nations around the world.
But now we've become such
a military power ourselves.
Expansion of armaments and
weapons development...
...wastes money and labor.
The Alliance shouldn't be
headed in that direction.
So we should reduce the forces?
That would only be the start.
Our ultimate goal is for
unilateral demilitarization.
I'd agree to that.
General Ventei?!
We've all shed blood at
one point or another.
We couldn't avoid it, to make
an ideal alliance a reality.
But for some reason our
objectives have changed.
The time's come for us to end
this period of bloodshed.
If only we could stop it.
But how would you deal
with the recent incidents?
We've been under attack by
Gundanium alloy mobile suits...
...made in outer space.
These indestructible suits have
the Earth in a virtual crisis.
What do the Specials think;
you fought with them.
We think the colonies made them
for purely destructive purposes.
Treize?
All we need now is an actor
from the Alliance.
An actor?
Someone to demonstrate the
true feelings of the Alliance.
It's natural for the colonies
to feel uneasy toward us.
To rectify this, we must open
up dialogue with the colonies.
I agree.
Let us begin a new chapter in
history through our discussions.
This isn't just between
the colonies.
We must also focus our
attention on more talks...
...between the world nations.
B-But what about the problem
with those mobile suits?
Once they understand our
desire for peace...
...the colonies will have
no cause for such destruction.
Let's talk.
I'm sure we'll be able to
find our way once again.
I thought so.
The future's about to head
in the wrong direction.
Shall we?
No, let's wait until the
final actors arrive.
Next, I'd like to focus on
peace negotiations details.
We'll start...
What's going on here?!
Marshal! We're under attack!
This base is under attack!
What?!
That's them...
This defense line isn't
like the others.
Ten times more of them.
A lot more than we estimated.
There's no turning
back now!
We're taking too long
to get through!
Let's move in for the kill!!
Lady, the actors are all here.
It's time to raise the curtain.
Right!
Lieutenant Zechs!
We've received orders to
commence Operation Daybreak!
Roger, all units start descent!
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Talk to those pilots!
Tell them we desire
peace with the colonies!
Impossible Marshal!
The enemy's on an
all-out attack!
We could receive considerable
damage wasting time talking!
Marshal, our priority should
be to evacuate.
But...
We can't risk your getting
slaughtered...
...while insisting on solving
problems through negotiations.
I'll ignore your sarcasm.
But you're right, there's
no point getting killed.
Not if we're to promote
peace negotiations.
Then allow me to offer you
OZ's high speed shuttle.
It's ready for immediate
take off.
I never would have expected
such assistance from you.
Marshal, I'm also a member
of the Alliance.
Of course.
I accept.
This way please!
The shuttle is standing
by at gate B12!
General Septem, this way please.
I don't understand.
I thought the shuttle
was that way.
I felt it safer for the
delegation to split up.
My personal shuttle is
on standby at gate F7.
It's the Specials' latest model,
but there isn't room for many.
In that case, I'll go with you.
This way...
Get as many mobile suits
out as you can!
There are only two enemies!
Colonel!
Urgent message from our
Fairbanks Base!
It's a revolt!
The soldiers are revolting
against the base!
Colonel!
Revolts are occurring worldwide,
one after the other.
What?!
Sergeant, it's no use!
Let's surrender!
Don't be ridiculous!
Are you one of the
traitors too?!
Sergeant!
What can those Specials
do anyway?!
This base is now under
our control!
Surrender at once!
I'm not taking orders
from any rebels!
Just see for yourself.
This is a revolution.
I won't surrender!!
Don't overdo it,
Lieutenant Noin!
Creating something new
is wonderful.
But isn't this a bit bloody
for the laying of a foundation?
Resistance is futile!
We need as many comrades
as possible!
The era of the Alliance
has ended!
Our OZ organization must
give rise to a true alliance!
Isn't it about time we created
a new system?!
Not bad if I say so myself.
This coup d'état had been
carefully planned.
OZ soldiers hid their identities
behind the Specials' facade...
...and were posted at each
Alliance military base.
Since the sabotage began
within the Alliance...
...the damage to its governing
body was significant.
In Asia, Europe, and
even Africa.
Our bases worldwide have been
taken over by rebel troops!
So where is Marshal Noventa?
I don't know! I can't
find any of them!
What in the world is going on?
Crap! They just keep coming!
Missiles?! Aimed at us allies!
'Cause you're all bunched up.
No time to sit and chat!
My work's cut out for me!
Are they OZ's newest models?
Yeah!
But they're attacking
the Alliance!
Trowa!
Those mobile suits are
just like ours!
Could they also be?!
Whatever they are,
they're in my way!
Those suits are identical!
What's wrong?!
Why haven't we left yet?!
We're waiting for Marshal
Noventa's shuttle to leave.
We'll leave next.
That's the one!
It's an unfortunate coincidence.
But I won't let it obstruct
our peace proposal.
M-Marshal!!
What on earth?!
Don't be rash now, young man!
Mission accomplished.
What's going on?!
What have they done?!
Marshal Noventa!
Thanks for those missiles
earlier, buddy!
Now I'll return the favor!
Cut it out!
Haven't you gotten tired of
these meaningless battles?!
What's that?!
Don't you realize?
You've all been lured
into OZ's devious trap!
We what?!
Check out the Alliance's report!
You guys just wiped out
the Alliance's pacifists.
Impossible!
It's the colonies' declaration
of war against us!
We were discussing plans for
peace talks with the colonies.
Marshal Noventa was
central to these plans...
...and he's been assassinated!
He was killed by the colonies'
invading mobile suits!
I repeat!
This was a brutal invasion
by the colonies!
Heero...
We will not yield
to the colonies!
We must fight them
to the bitter end!
Very nicely done,
General Septem.
We won't be needing you
any further.
What?
A magnificent performance.
It's a pity you had to
leave the stage so early.
We can't have any bloodstains
in Mr. Treize's wake.
The second act has just begun.
We'll be getting busy.
It was all planned out by OZ.
We became their puppets.
Controlled by Treize
Khushrenada's hands.
No... how awful!
Damn him!
I'm still gonna fight OZ.
Even if I've got to do it
on my own!
What have I... What've I done?
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Treize has taken the future
by the reins.
After being controlled
like puppets...
...the Gundams follow General
Septem as Lady Une's target.
Heero, Duo, and Quatre move
in to prevent the explosion...
...of the New Edwards Base.
Wu Fei and Trowa head
straight for Treize.
Treize is cornered by
Wu Fei's sword.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 8,
The Treize Assassination
"The Treize Assassination".