Maximum Titillation OVA Vol. 5
Steamy Grayfia
You have such a nice, big back, Issei.
Th-Thanks...
Oh, man. I didn't know
Grayfia was already taking a bath.
What am I supposed to do now?!
You may be a high school student,
but you're definitely a man.
You have a very strong back.
Actually, that might be
a rude thing for me to say,
given that you've defeated
countless foes for the underworld.
N-No, not at all!
I'm very honored to hear your praise!
You're such a funny gentleman, Issei.
Grayfia!
Are you drunk?!
Oh, am I now?
You're totally drunk!
Never mind that, Issei.
You looked at my chest just now, right?
I-I'm sorry! I-It was an accident!
I don't mind. You're a young man.
It's a natural reaction.
But, yes...
The only ones who've
seen me naked are Sir Zechs...
...and you.
A great devil... and me only?!
- Issei?!
- P-President!
What are you and my sister doing together?!
Oh, Rias. It's not proper to shout in the bath.
I was planning to bathe with Issei!
What's going on here?!
President! It's not what you think!
What if I said I'm getting intimate
with a cute kin of the Gremory Clan?
Grayfia?!
What?!
A-All right, then!
I'll defeat you and win Issei back!
That's an amusing idea.
Hold on a minute! Hear my excuse!
Grayfia's been drinking--
You're such a nincompoop, Sister!