Boost!
Not yet.
I'm ready, President!
Issei...
Boosted Gear, Gift!
Transfer!
Episode 6
Go, Occult Research Club!
President?!
W-Wow!
I can feel her magical pulse all the way out here.
That's some good magical power!
That's the power of an
Ultimate Class Devil, Rias Gremory.
I see that you're now as gifted as your brother.
Begone!
Excellent, sister of a Satan,
sister of Sirzechs!
President!
Akeno!
Lightning!
You dare try to stop me, wielder of Barakiel's power?
Do not...
associate me with that name!
Barakiel?
He's a leader of the Fallen Angels.
He controls lightning, hence his alias, "Lightning".
Lightning...
You actually defected to the Devils.
You've got an interesting family,
Rias Gremory.
The Emperor of Red Dragon,
a remnant of the Holy Sword Experiments,
and Barakiel's daughter!
What?!
Akeno-san is...
the daughter of a Fallen Angel?!
Rias Gremory...
I see that you like to collect junk, just like your brother.
I won't allow anyone to ridicule my brother, our Satan.
And above all, such words toward my servants
must be punished by death!
Then kill me,
sister of a Satan,
master of the Welsh Dragon,
Crimson-Haired Princess of Ruin!
You're facing your sworn enemy!
Only a coward would let this chance slip by!
Hey, you damn Fallen Angel!
Issei?!
Keep on insulting my President and Akeno-san,
and I'll beat the hell out of you!
Are you out of your mind?
I guess I am!
Stay right there!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Stop, Issei!
Hyoudou Issei, we'll buy you some time!
Build up your power!
G-Got it!
Boost!
Attacks from both Holy and Holy Demonic Swords?
Excellent!
Gotcha.
Koneko-chan!
Hurry up, Hyoudou.
I'm exhausted.
Saji!
Concentrate on your job!
Y-Yes!
Tsubaki and I may be all right,
but the others are running out of power.
Rias...
Boost!
Dammit.
Are you all right, Asia?
Y-Yes, but what about those two?
Not yet.
Still persisting?
Give me your best shot!
Sword Birth!
Is that the best you can do?
Fool!
I'm not done yet!
You...
Boost!
Dammit.
Just a little more.
I'm surprised that you're still fighting after losing your leader.
What?
What are you talking about?
Kokabiel, why did you say I've lost my leader?!
Oh, I wasn't supposed to tell.
Answer me, Kokabiel!
Of course, I almost forgot!
I'm stirring up a war, so there's no need to hide anything!
In the Great War,
when the Four Great Satans died, so did God!
I-It can't be.
God is...
dead?
You're crazy!
Such a thing would never happen!
The war brought an end to all Satans and many High Class Devils,
as well as most lower Angels and Fallen Angels.
Pure Angels could no longer reproduce,
and there are very few pure-blooded Devils.
There's...
There's no way!
All three factions needed to rely on humans to survive.
The leaders of the three major factions
-Angels, Fallen Angels, and Devils-
concealed God's death to make the humans, who believe in God, survive!
Liar. Liar!
That doesn't matter to me, though.
What I truly cannot bear is that after the deaths of God and the Satans,
we decided that war was no longer meaningful!
I can't bear it. I can't bear it!
They told us to lower our raised fists!
We would've won if we'd kept on fighting!
That asshole Azazel even proclaimed there'd never be another war.
Inconceivable!
If the Lord is gone...
then where is His love coming from?!
Michael's doing a good job.
He's taken God's role in leading both the Angels and the humans.
Archangel Michael is substituting for God?
Then... we were...
As long as the system is working,
prayers, blessings, and exorcisms should work, at least to some extent.
Asia!
She can't help it.
I'm surprised that I haven't lost my mind myself.
There has, however, been a decrease in the number of people who believe in God.
With the absence of an entity to maintain the balance between the holy and the demonic,
anomalies such as that Holy
Demonic
Sword are bound to happen.
The two elements should never come together.
I'll end this war how it was supposed to end...
and take your heads as trophies!
Rias.
Again.
Again, I refused to let go of my dignity,
and I...
Shut up!
Issei?!
Your little complaints are no reason to destroy our homes and our friends!
And...
And I'm...
going to become...
the Harem King!
What?!
I won't let you stop me from achieving my dream!
Harem King?
That's the Emperor of Red Dragon's goal?
Then follow me.
You'll become the Harem King in no time.
Wherever you go, I'll provide you with the most beautiful women.
They'll be yours to sleep with.
Th-Those sweet words of yours...
shouldn't fool me-
Issei!
Yes?!
I-I'm sorry!
It's hard for me to turn down a harem!
Since you love girls so much,
if we get out of here alive,
I'll do all kinds of things for you.
All kinds of things...
You serious?
Th-Then...
I can grope your boobs, and...
s-suck on them?
Yes.
That's a cheap price to pay for our victory.
What the-
I've never seen such an aura before!
A Sacred Gear's power is
determined by its wielder's will.
I can...
I can finally suck on them!
I have the power to punch God off his feet right now!
Oh, God's dead, isn't he?
All right!
You're gonna have to go, Kokabiel,
for me to suck on the president's nipples!
Geez!
Explosion!
The Emperor of Red Dragon can release this much power, just so he can suck on a woman's nipples?
What are you?
Who in the world are you?!
Listen carefully, Kokabiel.
I am Hyoudou Issei,
a man of libido and strong will, host of the Boosted Gear,
and a Pawn of Rias Gremory!
You may think you sound cool, but...
...you just listed a lot of your problems, Issei-senpai.
But that's who he is.
I'm sorry, Rias.
I guess I've also...
That's right.
We haven't lost yet.
We haven't lost unless we give up.
Follow Issei's lead.
Yes, President!
How dare a Low Class Devil like you hit my face!
How exciting.
This is exciting, kid!
Is that so?
Who's there?!
That light...
I can't stop shivering.
Who the hell is that?!
The Vanishing Dragon?!
The Vanishing Dragon?
Th-Then is he...
Has the Red One drawn you here, White Dragon?!
Get out of my wa-
Wh-What just happened?!
Even I can't tell.
They look like a crow's filthy wings.
Azazel's wings are much darker, like an eternal void.
You...
What are you after?!
There's no need for a man who has fallen below the ground to have wings.
Divide!
What?!
I am Albion.
My Sacred Gear is "Divine Dividing".
Every ten seconds, it halves the power of whoever I touch...
and gives it to me.
Halves the power?!
You'll be weaker than a human soon.
The Emperor of Red Dragon doubles its host's power and gives it to someone,
while the Emperor of White Dragon halves its enemy's power and gives it to its host.
The legends are true.
How boring.
I thought you'd put up a better fight.
You stepped too far out of your league.
Azazel asked me to bring you back at all costs.
Azazel!
The Magic Circle's power is dissipating!
Rias and the others won?
But what was that light?
I have some questions for that stray exorcist as well.
I'll finish this after I get answers.
Ignoring me, White One?
The gauntlet spoke?
So you were alive, Red One.
This wasn't exactly the best time to meet.
It's all right.
We're destined to face each other someday.
Coincidences do happen.
The Emperor of Red Dragon and
the Emperor of White Dragon meet.
I'll see you later, Ddraig.
See you, Albion.
Hey!
What's going on?!
Who the hell are you?!
Thanks to you, I...
I can't...
I can't suck on the President's tits!
You need power to understand the whole truth.
Become stronger,
my sworn enemy, destined to face me someday.
Rias.
Sona!
I never thought the Emperor of White Dragon would come.
He saved the city, though.
I guess so.
Now, Tsubaki,
let's repair the school.
We need to finish by morning.
We'll help out.
It's all right.
The Student Council maintains the school.
Is it over?
No.
Somebody else has taken up that man's research.
My battle is not over.
Nice job, Prince Charming!
Issei-kun?
Oh? That's a Holy Demonic Sword?
Looks awesome!
Issei-kun, I-
Let's forget the little things.
Don't you think it's about time for a break
with Holy Swords and your comrades and stuff?
After everything that's happened lately,
I'm too tired to think about anything.
Kiba-san, you'll come back to the club, won't you?
Asia-san...
I bet Asia's frightened by what she heard.
It's all right, though.
Are you okay?
Everyone's okay,
and the city is okay.
Yeah, I'm fine.
That's all we need.
Thanks for asking.
Yuuto.
President?
Thank you for coming back.
You even achieved Balance Breaker.
I could never ask for more from my servant.
President,
I turned my back on my fellow club members and you, my savior.
I cannot apologize enough for what I have done.
Nevertheless, you came back.
That's all I needed.
Embrace your friendships.
President,
I will pledge here once again.
I, Kiba Yuuto, will serve as Rias Gremory's kin and Knight,
and protect you and your friends until the end of my life.
Thank you, Yuuto.
Hey!
Get away from the President, Prince Charming!
Issei-kun?
I would kill to become Knight and Protect the president!
No person would make a better knight than you, though.
Don't forget your job.
Damn, I still can't believe I missed the chance to suck on the President's nipples.
Perverted as always.
Now, Yuuto.
Yes?
Th-That's-
It's time for your punishment.
One thousand spankings!
What?!
This is gonna be good!
Get ready for some pain, Prince Charming!
Hey, Issei-kun...
Hello, Emperor of Red Dragon.
Why are you here?!
Welcome.
What's going on, President?!
Let me introduce the newest member of the Gremory family. Knight, Xenovia.
Let's all be friends with her, all right?
A-A Knight?!
Don't tell me you're-
Sh-She was reborn as a Devil?!
We heard about it just moments ago, and we're still trying to digest it.
Yes.
After hearing that God was dead,
I volunteered to be reborn.
Volunteered?!
President!
I'm very glad that we have an ally who uses the Durandal.
Now Yuuto has a partner to fight along side of.
You can't be serious.
I've enrolled in second year in this Academy.
I'll see you around, Issei-kun.
Don't talk cute like that with a straight face!
I was trying to imitate Irina,
but I just can't get it right.
Are you really sure about this?
Now that God is dead,
my life is as good as over.
But should I really have sided with the Devils, who used to be my enemies?
She is the sister of a Satan,
but did I really do the right thing?
Tell me, Lord!
I've seen this happen before.
She's a pretty odd girl.
Oh, what about Irina?
She returned to headquarters.
We retrieved four pieces of Excalibur.
With alchemy, they can be reforged as Holy Swords.
Irina, this is the end of our quest.
I will miss working with you.
I also feel the same-
Then why?
Why did you want to become a devil?
You even turned you back on the church.
Now we can't work together anymore.
Traitor...
The next time we meet, we will be enemies.
Irina is more faithful than I am.
Telling her of God's death would devastate her.
Learning a forbidden secret has made me a hindrance to the Church.
I'm now a heretic.
That's why you were reborn as a Devil?
I owe you an apology, Asia Argento.
Huh?
With the Lord gone,
the salvation I promised didn't exist.
I'm sorry.
If it makes you feel any better,
feel free to hit me.
I-I wouldn't-
I went from being a noble wielder of Holy Swords
to a heretic who broke a taboo.
I still remember how they immediately started to view me differently.
You must have gone through the same thing.
Xenovia-san,
I'm very happy with my life right now.
I may be a Devil now,
but it brought me to these precious friends of mine.
I'm very happy!
I see.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
Yes?
Could you give me a tour of the school sometime?
Sure!
As a user of the Holy Sword Durandal,
I'd like to spar with the user of the Holy Demonic Sword as well.
I'd be happy to.
I don't really understand her,
but she seems like a good person.
All right, now that we have a new member,
let's get back to our club activities!
Yes, President!
Even for fated couples
unmeiteki ni mo hakarishirenai
The equation of love is complicated
koi no houteishiki
Love isn't always justifiable
ai ni riyuu wa iranai
The answer lies inside your heart
kotae wa kimi no kokoro ni aru kara
After worrying and hesitating
nayande mayotte
My brain stops functioning
shikou teishi
I keep writing then erasing stuff
kaite wa keshite wo kurikaeshi
I'm running a simulation of you in my head
atama no naka de anata simulation
It's unpredictable
yosoku fukanou
Will this work? How about this?
kou kana kou kana
But you never follow my calculations
keisan de ugokeba ii no ni
"Look, it's the beach!" "It sure is."
umi ne sou ne
I can't tell if you love me because you're so innocent
junsui na hodo futoumei
Don't be so kind to every girl
yasashisa wo furimaku na
You'll end up breaking many hearts
tsumitsukuri da wa
Why can't you just be normal?
futsuu ni misete
It's so unfair
zurui hito
Then you leave!
jaa kaeri na
I shouldn't let my rivals take you away from me
raibaru ni ukkari ki mi toraretara
I need a hint!
hinto ga hoshii
Quick, I need one!
hayaku hoshii
As I imagine a lovey-dovey future
love hidai na mirai
love
My expectations only go up
takamatta kitai
What should I try as the coefficient?
keisuu wa nan ni shiyou
There are too many variables
michisuu sugiru
To your feelings
kimi no kimochi
Rather than just work on the left-hand side
hidari yori mo daisuki
Look ahead to the other side of the equal sign
ikooru no saki wa
Although I'm not sure what it does
wakaranai kedo michibiku
It leads to the correct answer every time
kotae wa itsumo seikai deshou
I'll get over my worries and prove my love for you
nayande mo kono ai wo shoumei suru yo
Which swimsuit would Issei like?
Akeno, which one?
This...
Oh, that one looks a bit plain.
Well I think Issei-kun will like this one the best.
Hey, you have been awfully
quiet since that last battle.
My, my, I'm fine Rias.
Ah, perfect.
This one's perfect.
Asia, let's sing together.
What is it?
Ah, it's nothing.
He doesn't have a nosebleed.
Yeah, but he is bulging now.
Just where are you looking?
Huh?
Ah, excuse me.
Yes,Yes
I will get permission
No, there is no problem.
Okay see you then.
Who called?
Ah, my very rich "uncle".
Just when we are trying to relax, too bad.
I know right, but what can we do?
Well, he is one of my best clients.
Issei-kun...
Huh?
I wanted to thank you.
Thank you.
There is no need for that.
You are a comrade to President and the others.
So, no problem.
Oh yeah, before I have to go, lets sing a duet.
The Pawn and the Knight, what do you say?
Okay, okay.
I lost again!
I trained day and night to fight you.
You've skipped out a lot recently.
I'm sorry.
I had some things to do.
Bikini Armor Chronicles
You really spent a fortune, didn't you?
Our trip to the arcade got me hooked.
Bikini Armor Chronicles
Wow, you've even collected all the consoles.
Even the craziest of collectors wouldn't have all this.
I just can't stop when I start collecting things.
People always call me a fanatic when it comes to my collectibles.
I've heard someone say that before.
Ah, shoot.
How about another match, Devil-kun,
or should I say "Emperor of Red Dragon"?
I am Azazel,
leader of the Fallen Angels.
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
The pool's open! And the
push-up swimsuits are here!
I'm going to take all the good parts!
Next Episode: A new volume!
Summer! Bathing Suits! I'm in Trouble!
Episode 7
"Summer! Bathing Suits! I'm in Trouble!"
Boobs! Jiggle!