Boost!
Amen!
Look out, Issei-san!
That was close!
Sparring my ass!
You're trying to kill me!
I return to my hometown after many years,
only to have to slay my friend!
Oh, how cruel the Lord is!
Issei, don't take any direct hits.
All right, President!
Boost!
The Red Dragon's Gauntlet,
Asia Argento's Twilight Healing,
and your Sword Birth...
All of these Sacred Gears are truly unique.
My ability has its roots in the grudges of those held captive with me...
born as they were killed in the depths of despair!
And I'm going to use this ability to shatter the Excaliburs and their wielders!
Merely touching a Holy Sword will hurt a Devil.
We're at a grave disadvantage.
Yuuto can make up for it with his speed.
But as for Issei...
I suppose the Holy Sword has no effect on that arm.
That's right.
His left arm is a dragon.
You shouldn't be this strong, Issei-kun!
I've got no other choice now.
No, I'll only regret it if I don't do this!
No, this is the only chance I'll have!
Boost!
Stand up once again
Tomo ni mou ichido tachiagare
To protect a single life
Mamore hitotsu no inochi tayasanu yo ni
Waking up to another dawn
Futatabi otozureta yoake ni me ga samete
I was dreaming about you
Kimi wo omoi dasu yume no tochuu
I still see your afterimage and can't move on
Me no mae no zanzo susumanai ashidori
I still see your afterimage and can't move on
Me no mae no zanzo susumanai ashidori
Powerless, I drift away
Toozakatte yuku hiriki na boku
What is most precious to me?
Taisetsu na mono wa doko ni aru?
If you believe in the future, never forget
Ashita wo shinjiru nara wasurenaide
Now is the time to risk your life and move on
Ima koso saa inochi wo kakete susumi dasu toki
The stronger your will, the stronger you will be
Omoi ga tsuyoi hodo tsuyokunaru
A faint, fragile dream will never last long
Hengen suru tsugihagi darake no risou dewa
A faint, fragile dream will never last long
sugu ni kiete shimau kara
Let's make an eternal promise
Towa e tsuzuku kawasu chikai
From the bottom of our shivering bodies
Furue dashita karada no soko kara
I'll Destroy the Holy Sword!
Episode 3
Shidou Irina...
I'm going to enjoy every inch of that well-ripened body of yours!
What's with that dirty look?
Be careful.
Issei-senpai can annihilate the clothing of any woman he touches.
Her clothing?!
Koneko-chan!
Why'd you warn our enemy?!
You are the enemy of all women.
That was a low blow...
What a satanic ability, Issei-kun!
Not only have you become a Devil,
but you even let its evil stain your heart!
O Lord, I beg you not to forgive this sinful pervert!
He's the enemy of us all.
Burn to ashes and be frozen solid!
Weak!
There's a reason Excalibur Destruction is called the Holy Sword of Destruction!
Just one of the seven pieces holds this much power...
Destroying all seven is going to be an uphill battle.
Kiba, are you...
That Xenovia, she just goes and blows the ground away out of nowhere.
Well then,
let's finish this up.
Boost!
Now!
Explosion!
Dress...
Break!
How indecent!
I'm not giving up!
No!
Stop it!
Issei-kun's movements have suddenly become swift and fluid!
It's just a testosterone rush.
You're crazy!
Don't you underestimate...
my perversion!
Huh?
No!
Thank you so very much!
No, I mean-
Pervert.
You know what? I think that was karma.
Don't use such a lewd move again.
All right?
No...
No chance.
I devoted all of my magical power to this.
I chose this over the ability to see through clothes,
after days of deliberation.
I'm...
I'm going to blow clothes off more girls...
and...
and I will fight
to the day when I can do it
just by looking at them!
You must be mad to fight for such a goal.
Debauchery is power...
Debauchery is justice!
I suppose I underestimated you a bit.
You're very agile...
However...
Issei!
Ow...
What the hell's going on?
But it only scraped him!
It's the Holy Sword's power.
This is nothing...
Reset!
Dammit...
I can't...
move...
What's going on?
He has no more energy to support the Boosted Gear.
It's over.
I suppose it is.
Shidou Irina-san,
we acknowledge your victory.
Dammit...
Your Holy Sword
versus my Demonic Sword,
let's see which is more powerful!
Poor choice.
You are equipped with a variety of Demonic Swords and exceptional agility.
But not only do you lack the power to wield a giant sword,
you slow yourself down by doing so.
You even lack the ability to make that judgment.
S-Stop.
Try cooling off before your next fight,
my "senior".
It's done.
Would you agree, Rias Gremory?
Yes.
I appreciate you not finishing off my servants with your Holy Swords.
Well then,
we'll be counting on your cooperation.
There's one thing I would like to know.
Have you found out which Fallen
Angels stole the Holy Swords?
A leader of the Grigori, Kokabiel, was directly involved.
Um...
The Grigori?
Also known as the "Protectors of the Son of God,"
it's a group of Fallen Angels.
You were going to fight him alone?
Are you trying to kill yourselves?
We would rather destroy the Holy Swords than
let them rest in the hands of some Fallen Angels.
We know what we're doing.
One of us has already been killed.
He was a priest who was investigating in this town.
It was him.
It was Freed Zelzan.
Freed?!
That stray exorcist?
I happened to witness the scene.
He wielded a Holy Sword.
A stray exorcist, you say?
So that's who did it.
We appreciate the information,
but we ask that you don't meddle in our affairs hereafter.
Goodbye.
Hold on, Xenovia!
All right, we'll get going now.
Issei-kun, anytime you want retribution, just give me a call, okay?
Amen!
Stop right there, Yuuto!
I won't let you leave me.
You're a Gremory knight.
I'm sorry, President.
Yuuto!
K-Kiba-san...
Yuuto...
Why?
It's unbelievable that I can't even have a decent bath.
Oh, not fair.
God has imposed another trial I must endure, right?
It's your fault.
It is because you wasted all our allowance on that...
That painting of nobody is such an obvious fake.
What are you saying?
The painting is clearly that of someone who has become a saint.
That's what the man at the exhibition said.
Why is this girl my partner?
You're good at making others feel bad, you know.
Shut up!
First of all, we must find some way to eat.
Else we won't have the strength to recover the Excaliburs.
You're right.
For now, we should trick the local heathens into giving donations.
The lord would allow us if they are our targets.
I think...
Well...
We could also take whatever is in the donations box from this place.
Ah, that sounds like an easier option.
No, we shouldn't.
You're right.
We shouldn't do that.
I'll go to karaoke with you guys.
Will you, Asia-chan?
Yes, I'd love to!
Forget Kiryuu!
Asia-chan's coming!
Unleash your wildest fantasies!
Issei-san...
The filth of these men will rub off on you.
Oh. Hello, Saji-san.
Hello, Asia-san.
How do you do?
Shut up!
Look who's talking, Secretary of the Student Council!
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Right...
I can ask him!
Hyoudou.
Hey, thanks for coming on such short notice.
You needn't worry about it.
So...
A-Are you serious?!
Please!
I beg you!
You're out of your mind!
God knows what the Chairwoman will do to me once she hears that a Holy Sword's involved,
and you're telling me to destroy one?!
She's going to kill me for sure!
Rias-senpai may have some kindness behind her anger,
but when our Chairwoman gets mad, she really gets mad!
I refuse!
H-Huh?
I figured you'd try doing something like that.
I've really gotta go-
Cooperate with the Church?
They said they'd rather destroy the swords than have them used by the Fallen Angels.
It seems they would do anything to take them out of the hands of the Fallen Angels.
Kiba wants to destroy the Excaliburs for vengeance,
and the Church wants the Excaliburs, even if it means destroying them.
Their goals may differ, but the end result is the same.
That's why I think we should offer to cooperate.
I don't think they would be eager for our help.
It's worth a try!
I'll do anything to keep Kiba as our comrade!
Then first of all we'll have to find those two.
I am not fond of acting behind our superiors' backs,
but this is for our friend.
Why do I have to take part in this?
You've got the invincible Rook with you.
We need all the firepower we can get.
It won't be easy to find them.
I mean, it's not like they'd be walking the streets in white robes.
Your blessings!
Two stray sheep beg for your blessing.
Please take the Lord's role and give us your blessing.
Your blessings!
There they are.
Yes.
Your blessings!
Delicious.
Irina,
the food in this country is...
amazing.
This is the stuff!
I can't get enough of the meals at these family restaurants!
They're eating like animals...
They must've been starving.
Who ordered the Salisbury steak?
What has this world come to?
To support our faith, we're having to take the help of Devils.
We've sold our souls to the Devils!
Not a single word of thanks?!
Issei-senpai.
I guess it's no use making them mad...
O Lord,
bless these kindhearted Devils.
Ow!
Your lord can keep his damn blessings!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Force of habit.
So?
What brings you to us?
We want to help you destroy the Excaliburs.
What?
I understand now.
We could probably ask you to destroy one.
Hey, Xenovia!
Seriously?!
I thought she would flat-out refuse!
The enemy is backed by one of the leaders of the Fallen Angels, Kokabiel.
Frankly, the collection of three Holy
Swords is too difficult for us.
I understand that, but still...
At best, we have a 30% chance of making it out alive.
Didn't we come here to take that chance?
Yeah.
We were sent by our higher-ups to sacrifice ourselves, after all.
Isn't that the ideal test of faith?
I see...
but it's unfortunate that I am getting the approval
to destroy an Excalibur from its wielders.
Your words are full of contempt.
I heard that you left the Gremorys.
If you're a stray, I can slay you right here.
That's one idea.
Calm down!
Let's not fight before we've even done anything.
Your hatred toward the Holy Sword Project is understandable.
It is an affair that even we abhor.
That's why the leader of the project was deemed a heretic and was exiled.
His name was Valper Galilei,
also known as the "Genocide Archbishop."
Valper...
That man...
killed my...
He had a stray exorcist as his assistant.
Freed, huh?
It's common for exiles to work together.
There's a high chance that Valper has taken a part in this incident.
Now I no longer have reason to refuse cooperating with you.
That settles our deal, then.
We will repay you for the meal someday,
Emperor of Red Dragon, Hyoudou Issei.
That worked out great, huh?
"Great" my ass!
Never mind how we could've been chopped up,
we could've started a war between the Church and the Devils!
Issei-kun!
I owe you for helping us so many times.
I'd like you to take no part in this.
This is my personal pursuit for vengeance.
I'd rather not drag you into it.
But we're family!
We're friends!
Am I wrong?
You're not, but-
I won't let a good friend of mine go astray.
I'm not the only one.
I'm sure the President would be upset too!
You okay with that?!
President Rias...
Right, the first time I met her...
was because of the Holy Sword Project.
Day after day, they performed experiments on us.
With our freedom stripped away,
we were not treated as humans.
Yet, with the belief that we were chosen by God
and the hope of becoming a hero in our hearts,
we withstood the countless experiments.
However, not a single one of us could use the Holy Swords.
The experiment was a failure.
We were immediately disposed of
to hide every detail of the experiments.
Spitting blood onto the floor,
crawling on all fours to get away,
we kept begging for God's help.
Run!
Leave us and run!
Where did he go?!
Don't let him get away!
Dammit...
I can't let their deaths be in vain.
I need to avenge them.
I'm not going to die!
I'll survive.
If you're going to die,
I'll adopt you.
Live for me.
I can't thank the president enough for making me part of her family.
However, I was able to escape the laboratory only with the help of my friends.
That's why I need to use their grudges to power my Demonic Swords
and destroy the Excaliburs.
As the only survivor, it is my duty to get vengeance for my friends' deaths.
Kiba!
I didn't know that you'd gone through so much!
I don't care what the Chairwoman does to me!
Hyoudou, I'll do everything I can to help!
R-Really?
Thank you.
I'll also assist you.
Koneko-chan?
I don't want you to leave us, Yuuto-senpai.
Shoot.
I can't go off alone with you, of all people, trying to stop me.
Does that mean...?
Now that I know who my real enemy is,
I'll gladly accept your help.
Really?
Kiba-kun?
Was I mistaken?
Isn't he part of your family?
Of course.
No matter what Yuuto says,
I would never let go of him.
The Gremorys certainly live up to their reputation of caring for their family.
His emotions may have gotten the better of him.
However, Rias,
do keep in mind that he is a Gremory as well.
Kiba-kun will come back.
I'm sure.
Thank you, Sona.
Excuse us.
Good work, you two.
You're late, Tsubaki.
What's going on?
Things of great concern.
A-Asia...
H-How do I look?
Amazing!
No, I mean, what is with the outfit?
Issei-san, you looked worried lately, s-so I wanted to cheer you up.
So I asked Kiriyuu-san what I should do.
Kiryuu...
You think Hyoudou is depressed?
Yeah...
I want to do something for him.
Let's see...
Ah, I just had a good idea.
It should be good for the both of you.
So I borrowed these clothes from Kiriyuu-san.
She said that this dress will help people to be happy.
That pervert.
Um, isn't it working?
Thank you, Asia.
You don't have to worry about me.
It would be unfair to Kiba if I was depressed at this time.
Kiba-san...
Um, will Kiba-san be okay?
Yes, dont worry.
We should trust our comrade.
Okay!
By the way, Asia.
You should probably change out of that outfit.
Huh? But Issei-san, I should cheer you up more-
Uh, no, I feel better already.
Otherwise I will start to feel better in another way.
Huh? Another way?
In what way?
Asia, I can't...
It's too bad you have to leave so late.
It was an urgent call.
Tell President when she comes home.
Okay!
I'm glad you're getting regular clients!
Y-Yeah.
See ya.
Hello, this is Hyoudou.
I'm sorry, but I'd like to decline today's contract.
If you're busy, you're busy.
No, don't worry about it.
I'll summon you another time.
Later.
Haven't had a Devil cancel at the last minute.
Hey.
You here to keep a lonely man company?
You aren't the type to get lonely.
Even for fated couples
unmeiteki ni mo hakarishirenai
The equation of love is complicated
koi no houteishiki
Love isn't always justifiable
ai ni riyuu wa iranai
The answer lies inside your heart
kotae wa kimi no kokoro ni aru kara
After worrying and hesitating
nayande mayotte
My brain stops functioning
shikou teishi
I keep writing then erasing stuff
kaite wa keshite wo kurikaeshi
I'm running a simulation of you in my head
atama no naka de anata simulation
a
I'm running a simulation of you in my head
It's unpredictable
yosoku fukanou
Will this work? How about this?
kou kana kou kana
But you never follow my calculations
keisan de ugokeba ii no ni
ke
But you never follow my calculations
"Look, it's the beach!" "It sure is."
umi ne sou ne
I can't tell if you love me because you're so innocent
junsui na hodo futoumei
Don't be so kind to every girl
yasashisa wo furimaku na
You'll end up breaking many hearts
tsumitsukuri da wa
Why can't you just be normal?
futsuu ni misete
It's so unfair
zurui hito
zu
It's so unfair
ru
i
hi
to
Then you leave!
jaa kaeri na
ja
Then you leave!
I shouldn't let my rivals take you away from me
raibaru ni ukkari ki mi toraretara
I need a hint!
hinto ga hoshii
Quick, I need one!
hayaku hoshii
ha
Quick, I need one!
As I imagine a lovey-dovey future
love hidai na mirai
love
As I imagine a lovey-dovey future
My expectations only go up
takamatta kitai
ta
My expectations only go up
What should I try as the coefficient?
keisuu wa nan ni shiyou
There are too many variables
michisuu sugiru
mi
There are too many variables
To your feelings
kimi no kimochi
Rather than just work on the left-hand side
hidari yori mo daisuki
Look ahead to the other side of the equal sign
ikooru no saki wa
Although I'm not sure what it does
wakaranai kedo michibiku
It leads to the correct answer every time
kotae wa itsumo seikai deshou
I'll get over my worries and prove my love for you
nayande mo kono ai wo shoumei suru yo
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
Someone even more amazing comes
when we try to lure Freed out!
The battlefield is Kuoh Academy!
Next episode:
A Strong Enemy Appeared!
Episode 4
Let's get those tits!