Summer break's already over.
I wanted to go all out this summer,
but I didn't have any time with all that training.
Hey, Issei!
Ouch! The hell was that f—
You didn't go to the beach with us to hit on girls like you promised!
Did you forget about our gentlemen's alliance?!
I had to go to a training camp! I had no choice!
So, did you guys get anything good out of it?
Knowing you all, I'm sure you had a meaningless summer.
What did you say?!
Kiryuu Aika!
It's none of your business!
Hey, did you hear?
There's another transfer student on their way,
and I hear she's another beauty.
Wh-What?!
so
no
mu
If you listen to the voice of your heart
You'll be born anew again and again
born
born
new
mo
u
ko
I can't hide it anymore
The purported salvation is but a mirror paradox
Trying to come to terms with myself
I realized my soul must lie with my wishes
The moment we met, the warmth of the tears
de
ta
shun
shun
ta
kan
shun
Falling off your palm ignited my heart
And we understood the DxD each other felt
I've been waiting
What's there to be gained amid all the despair?
It's not bliss but rather a good feeling
feel
feel
ing
so
no
mu
Until I reach deep inside your heart
I'll call out your name again and again
your
name
your
name
Shido
Irina
Episode
Second Trimester has Started!
Shido
Irina
My name is Shido Irina. It's a pleasure to meet you all.
Shido
Irina
Irina?!
Whoa! Kiryuu's information...
...was accurate!
Oh, Issei-kun? We're in the same class?
Issei, you bastard! You know that girl?!
Hyoudou Issei-kun is my childhood friend!
I'm glad to see that you're well.
I'm so happy to see you again.
Me, too! Asia-san, Xenovia!
What's wrong?
The cross you have hanging on your neck.
It stings a bit.
Oh, that's right. Devils can't stand crosses.
I'm sorry!
That person is from the Church, right?
Yeah. Why is she at this school?
Looks like everyone's here.
Shido Irina-san, I welcome you to this school.
Rias-san—I mean, President Rias, everyone.
I look forward to working with you!
President, what's going on?
I told him that we didn't need her.
Azazel-sensei!
With the Khaos Brigade on the loose,
Michael was worried that fallen angels and devils weren't enough
to protect the school, so he volunteered his forces.
Well, we did form an alliance.
So there's no way we could refuse her.
You must be at ease now that I,
a reincarnated angel who received Michael-sama's blessing, am here!
Amen!
A self-proclamation?
A-Angels are scary!
I'm surprised that a human could become an angel.
After God's death, new angels can no longer be born.
They probably used the same methods that fallen angels and devils use.
A high-level angel is a King, and he has a peerage of cards from Ace to Queen.
I was chosen as one of those brave saints!
I see, we are chess pieces and you are cards.
So what card are you, Irina?
I'm glad you asked. I am an Ace.
I was honored to receive the Ace angel position from Michael-sama!
I could die from happiness, Michael-sama!
So now, the pillar in Irina-san's life is Michael-sama.
Yes, you can still be saved even if you lose your master.
Just like us.
Yeah!
We really bought a lot.
Well, it's all for Irina-san's welcome party.
I'm sure my parents will be really surprised when they come home!
We suddenly have new house guests.
Two of them.
Huh?
Rossweisse-san? Why?
Actually...
You were left behind?!
How terrible! Even though I worked so hard for Odin-sama!
I worked so hard, but he forgot to take me back with him!
I'm sure he'll come for you eventually.
I'm sure those titty bars consumed his thoughts, and he doesn't even care about me anymore!
I'm just a woman who can't do her job properly!
I've been single my whole life!
So that's how it is.
Oh...
Come to think of it, isn't the sports festival coming up?
Sports festival?
It's a big sports competition between classes.
Our sports festival is right after the start of second trimester.
I'm not very good at things like that.
Asia?!
Are you all right, Asia?
Y-Yes. This person saved me.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
We meet again, Asia Argento.
Huh?
You're...
Good day. Asia, I've come to see you.
Huh?
Weren't you one of the young devils from the underworld?
Have you forgotten who I am?
U-Um...
What are you saying to Asia?!
Haven't we met before?
Far before you met him.
What?!
That scar...
Could you be...
That's right. I am the devil that you saved with your Sacred Gear.
My name is Diodora Astaroth.
I was so surprised to see you in the underworld.
But it was hard to talk during all that commotion.
That's why I've come to pick you up now.
P-Pick me up?
Our meeting and our reunion.
I believe it to be fate.
Bastard, what are you doing to Asia?!
I want you to become my wife.
I am in love with you.
Diodora is the heir of the prestigious Astaroth family,
which produced one of the current Satans, Beelzebub.
I'm surprised you know him, Asia.
I don't remember his face well.
Many painful things happened during that time.
Asia was exiled from the Church because she saved a devil like him, and then the fallen angels...
He only came today to greet me and left soon after.
I'm sure he was just excited to meet the girl who saved him.
That sounds just like Diodora with his sheltered upbringing.
Just let him be.
Okay, I will.
The preparations for the welcome party are finished.
Good work. Now, let's go.
Okay!
Issei-san?
H-Huh? Oh, yeah.
Good looks are all he's got! I'll send him away if he shows up again!
Okay!
Once again, I am Shido Irina.
Hello, devils. I used to think of you as my enemies and hunt you.
The Church is scary!
Don't worry.
Michael-sama said that we must all get along now.
Personally, I wanted to become friends with you all.
I wish to work hard as the Church's representative.
Let's get along!
Our sides have fought against
each other for so long.
Some were definitely uneasy about the sudden alliance,
but all of you working together in the fight against Loki
served as a wonderful demonstration!
I have to thank all of you.
When you put it that way,
I'm glad we worked so hard.
Me, too!
Well, I feel bad that we weren't able to send in any fallen angels on such short notice.
That's wrong.
Fallen angels fought, too.
Well, half of one.
Akeno-san!
I see. You're right.
I wish he could hear those words just now.
Thank goodness for that.
Oh, right. Issei.
What?
I went to the underworld to take care of some things yesterday.
You're really popular there!
I'm popular in the underworld?
Wow! That's amazing, Issei-san!
You finished off Loki with Mjolnir. Of course you're popular!
No, that's not why.
There was a documentary about the true face of the hero
who saved the underworld from terrorists.
Please let me poke your boobs.
What?!
I have come forth after poking my master's breasts!
Th-Then...
I can grope your boobs, and...
s-suck on them?
This is for...
my president's boobs!
It seems the scenes where you talk about boobs in battle are a hit.
They even nicknamed you the Breast Dragon Emperor.
B-Breast Dragon Emperor?!
You're especially popular with the kids.
They're even making a theme song for you called "The Boob Dragon."
Seriously?
Me! Me! Me!
I'll enter the treasure hunt race!
It's decided.
Then, next is the three-legged race.
Stop crying, Ddraig.
I am one of the two heavenly dragons!
My name, the Red Dragon Emperor, brought fear to many!
I'm telling you, I understand.
Now I'm the Breast Dragon Emperor?! I'm the Boob Dragon?!
I never knew Ddraig was so sensitive.
Anyway, I sure didn't see that coming.
After all this time, a guy like that appeared.
I wonder what Asia thinks about it.
The past she had forgotten.
Shit. There it is again!
Hyoudou!
There's a rip around your armpit.
Huh? Seriously?
I don't see any rips!
Okay! It's decided!
Huh?
Hyoudou
You tricked me, Kiryuu!
You're a part of the three-legged race!
And your partner is...
Asia?!
Three-Legged Race
Hyoudou
Asia
It's decided.
Let's race, Xenovia.
I'd love to, Irina.
So fast!
Just what you'd expect from a devil and angel.
But if they move that fast...
Yeah! It's hard to see the swaying of their boobs!
The speed of their boobs need to be just right while exercising!
One, two.
Big ones!
Three, four.
Small ones!
I can't take my eyes off of them!
Gym clothes are the best!
Oh, Hyoudou.
Hey, Saji.
Saji!
What are you guys doing?
We're watching all the swaying boobs.
You never change.
What event are you participating in?
I'm doing the three-legged race with Asia.
I'm always so jealous of you!
I'm in the bread-eating race.
Saji, what are you doing?
Um!
The student council is lacking manpower as it is. Please get back to work.
Y-Yes! President! Vice-President!
The student council has it pretty tough.
Asia! Did your boobs grow during summer break?
Kiryuu-san! P-Please don't fondle them!
If I leave her alone with that girl, Asia's mind will be corrupted.
Asia! Let's practice!
O-Okay. See you, Kiryuu-san.
Hyoudou! Don't do any perverted things to her while practicing!
Don't lump me together with you!
Some pairs seem very good at this,
but it looks difficult if you're not in sync.
All right, Asia. Let's go.
Okay.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
No. No. I have to clear my mind.
This is Asia!
Self-control. Self-control.
Th-Then, let's try walking slowly first.
And one, and two, and—
Hmm. Looks like I'll have to match Asia's stride.
U-Um, Issei-san?
S-Sorry! That was—
I wanted to treasure Asia, but I ended up grabbing her boob!
I-It wasn't on purpose!
I'm fine.
B-But please tell me before you touch them.
I have to prepare myself.
So it's okay as long as I tell you first?!
Let's try it again.
I'm sorry. I'm not good at sports.
It's fine. We just need to match our movements.
Our combination!
Combination?
Yes! Combination!
Let's move one step at a time.
Okay!
One, two. One, two. One, two. One, two.
Issei-san, thank you for
everything up until now.
Today's the day I become a wife.
Huh?
Asia-chan! You've grown so beautifully!
Dad? Mom?
Asia.
You can come back any time.
Asia-chan, don't worry about us.
Huh?
What's going on? What is this?
Come on, Issei! You should say
something to Asia-chan as well!
She's like a little sister to you, isn't she?!
Even if you tell me that so suddenly—
I mean, who's the groom?
Onii-san. Please leave Asia to me.
A super-rich and high-ranking devil like me is sure to make her happy.
Come, Asia. It's time!
Let's move toward our bright future!
Okay! Issei-san, thank you for taking care of me until now.
I will be happy!
Asia!
As your big brother, I won't accept this marriage!
Issei-san?
Are you all right, Issei-san?
Asia?
I dreamt that you were getting married.
It was a lot more painful than I expected.
Please don't worry, Issei-san. It'll be all right.
I'm not getting married yet.
Really? I'd die from loneliness if you did.
Yes. It would be terrible if you died from loneliness, Issei-san.
Asia!
What's wrong?
President...
K-Koneko-chan...
Oh, my!
Either way, thank goodness that Asia getting married was a dream.
I hope it stays a dream.
Letters?
They're all for Asia.
Each one was sent by Diodora Astaroth.
Ever since that day, he's been sending me something every single day.
Movie tickets, dinner invitations, gift cards, and even large gifts.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
He's such a troublesome boy.
Not only did he propose to Asia,
but he's been doing things like this?!
Well, Asia. I'll dispose of these.
Okay, thank you.
Well, we have to practice for the sports festival.
Right. Do your best!
Okay!
Issei. Making a face like that...
Issei's always like that.
Something must be wrong with me.
One, two. One, two. One, two. One, two.
All right! You guys are getting pretty good.
Sorry about this, Xenovia!
I feel bad having you help us practice.
Don't worry about it.
How about a light jog this time?
Yeah. Ready, Asia?
Asia?
Oh, yes!
What's wrong?
I don't regret saving him so long ago.
But I love Kuoh Academy and everyone in the Occult Research Club
as well as your parents... and you, Issei-san.
To me, you are all something to treasure.
Right now, I am very happy.
That's right! You and I will always be together!
Okay!
How touching.
Irina, you were here, too?
Yes. Xenovia said that Kuoh Academy is nice early in the morning.
So I came and witnessed such beautiful friendship.
This must be God's and Michael-sama's will.
Amen!
I'm so tired!
Let's change in the club room and take a break.
Xenovia?
What's wrong, Xenovia-san?
Asia, I learned a bit of information.
It seems girls usually start having secret affairs around our age.
Huh?
Secret affairs?
It's when girls have men fondle their breasts.
B-Breasts?!
What are you saying so suddenly?!
That's not what it really means!
Asia, don't you think it's time we experienced it?
Even if you put it that way...
It's fine!
If we have a secret affair, you'll be able to do well in three-legged race, too.
That's your reasoning?!
Asia... We're friends.
Yes...
Let's have an affair together!
Wh-What? I-Is that how it works?
No, it isn't, Asia.
Then, let's start.
This will be practice for my baby-making as well.
Wait a second! In a place like this?!
Well, it's true that all men dream about the gym storage room—
No! That's not it!
Something like this happened once before!
Xenovia, do you enjoy situations like this?!
No, that's not what's important now!
Come on, Asia. You, too.
B-But... I'm still not ready.
Come on!
Xenovia-san!
Ouch! Hey!
Xenovia?!
Issei-san, I-I don't want to lose to the President!
As I thought, a man's touch is much different than my own.
Now, Issei.
Asia and I are ready.
Fondle them well.
Fondle them well?
I didn't know such excellent words existed!
No! I need to protect Asia!
But my hands! My hands won't listen to me!
This is the curse of man.
And here I was, worried because you guys didn't come back!
How dirty!
I-Irina!
D-Do it in the bed!
This place is dirty and poses a health risk!
That's what you meant?
Rating game?
Yes.
A tournament to witness the strength of the next generation of devils.
If Loki hadn't attacked, it would have happened during summer break.
I'm scared of fighting!
Fighting against young devils...
So we'll be up against Sairaorg-san?
He's currently the crowd favorite to win.
His strength is on a completely different level.
Fortunately for us, we won't face him in the first round.
The bracket's already been decided?
Yes. Our opponent will be Diodora Astaroth.
Diodora!
Him...
sou daitai no koto nante
Well, yeah, I do think that
mou wakatte wa iru na tte
I've got this stuff mostly figured out
omou yo dakedo ne
But still, you know
kokoro wa bannou ja nai
Feelings on their own can only get you so far
daiji na koto bakka ishin fudenshin
The stuff that matter isn't getting across
saishuuteki ni wa analog tsuushin
So we have to rely on analog communication
dakara ima sugu
That's why, right now
motto chanto katachi ni shite yo
I want you to be more concrete
kimi ga
Do it
ijiwaru na voice
With your flirty voice
give me kikasete yo
Give me, just tell me
chotto dake de ii no
Just a little hint is fine
aimai na no wa yada na
Don't leave me hanging
no secret sansei
No secrets, yeah?
do you do you know
Do you know?
answer todokete ne
Give me your answer
kowaku nante nai shi
I'm not afraid to hear it
ienai kedo nee wakaru desho
I don't have to actually tell you, right?
wakatte yo
Take the hint
tell me heart tell me heart
Tell me your heart
subete wo kaeru no wa
If you want to take it to the next step
give me word give me word
Give me your word
itsu de mo kimi dakara
The power is in your hands
Next Episode:
Look, Issei. Doesn't this look good on me?
My figure suits Issei-kun's tastes much better than Rias'.
Do I look good in this?
Episode
The Night Before Battle!
This is... quite an unknown destructive force!
Now it's my turn!