Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
You're telling me to get off?
Sandrock!
Thank you, my dear Sandrock!
Tallgeese Destroyed
We've confirmed the
engineers' identity.
All five of them?
Yes, ma'am!
As suspected, they were
all involved...
...in OZ mobile suit
development, in the past.
I see.
All five of them disappeared...
...and have been missing
since the Tallgeese development.
Or rather, since completing
the Tallgeese blueprint.
The Tallgeese?
Isn't that the mobile suit
Colonel Zechs is using?
Also called the Leo Prototype?
Yes, it was built twenty
years ago.
But it's still regarded as the
most powerful built on Earth.
Most powerful is hardly
the appropriate term.
Ma'am.
It wouldn't be the most powerful
unless all soldiers agreed.
We'll have them make us a suit.
A mobile suit that's more
powerful than the Tallgeese.
No, more powerful than
the Gundams!
Captain, I've brought Colonel
Zechs here to see you.
Thank you.
Please excuse the small room.
Have a seat.
You don't need that for
Colonel Zechs.
You're dismissed!
Sir!
Sorry to make you uncomfortable,
Zechs.
Don't concern yourself,
Your Excellency.
I'm prepared to face
a court martial.
As long as you continue
to be a strong force...
...for the Romefeller Foundation...
...I foresee no problems with
the court martial.
A strong force?
The Romefeller Foundation
is concerned about the Gundams.
They're the most powerful
mobile suits on Earth.
Would you continue to fight
as our knight...
...to defeat the Gundams?
Your Excellency.
I'm sorry.
I don't believe I can follow
Romefeller's ideas any longer.
Pardon?
I've been fighting the Gundams
out of personal feelings.
And that's something which
has no place in a war.
My battle with the Gundams
is over.
I see...
In that case, Zechs,
sacrifice your life for OZ.
A guilty verdict in court
for your conduct...
...would be a big blow to OZ.
But if you died an honorable
death, soldiers would mourn...
...and develop a stronger
will to fight.
Naturally, the higher powers
in Romefeller will be satisfied.
The name Lightning Count
will live on as a legendary hero.
That'd be wonderful.
Your death would have
that much value to it.
If you died, you'd be free.
Farewell, Zechs Merquise.
Once this ship has been
evacuated...
...fifty Aries and twenty
Cancers will attack it.
They'll be manned by
Alliance survivors...
...trying to win the
Foundation's attention.
I heard this mission is to
allow you to escape unnoticed...
...by the higher powers.
But given the enemy and
the sheer numbers...
...there's no room for escape.
That's right.
This is a test in order to
survive as Treize's friend.
No matter what I do...
...I can't escape from what
he has planned for me.
Commence simulation!
So this is the mobile doll
system.
We used an old model
of the Leo.
So we program them by remote.
But no such problem exists with
our Taurus space mobile doll.
Wonderful abilities.
These would reinforce our
soldiers, wouldn't they...
...Chief Engineer?
In fact, they'll replace soldiers as
the main force in the near future.
What's that?!
Someone's attacking us!
They're not responding!
Perfect target for
the mobile dolls.
Order to attack!
Enemy spy?! How foolish!
Transmission from the enemy Leo!
Colonel Treize!!
What?!
Discontinue attack!
Stop firing!!
I thought I'd represent
human soldiers...
...and propose a battle
against the mobile dolls.
Hoping to die, Colonel Treize?!
Mobile dolls don't show mercy
like a human soldier would.
If mobile dolls are superior,
then I don't belong here.
I think we could vie for
superiority here and now.
Here goes!
He's insane!
Never mind; kill the Colonel!!
Sir!!
It's an order!
He's trying to kill us!
Get him!
No! I can't!
Then I will!
Stop it, Chief Engineer!
Silence!!
This is Treize Khushrenada.
Murder Tubarov!
Yes, sir!
What the hell?!
No, stop!!
I'm assassinating you, under
the orders of Colonel Treize!
It's over.
Chief Engineer Tubarov.
Wars are about more than
fighting with mobile suits.
We claim victory.
I retract my order.
Mobile dolls and soldiers both
take their orders from humans.
I ask that you place more value
on humans and learn to love them.
Hurry up and return, Zechs.
If you're not around to help...
...OZ will allow worthless
actions by worthless people.
It's coming!
The shuttle that avoided
OZ's surveillance!
Just as I thought.
This course isn't frequented
by OZ.
Then we can capture ourselves
a Gundam sir?
More accurately, a Gundam pilot.
The shuttle coming isn't
equipped for mobile suit transport.
Then what do you plan to
achieve by restraining the pilot?
The Gundam pilot has returned
to space so it can fight OZ.
We're after the same enemies.
So I'll negotiate with the pilot
to join forces!
Shouldn't we hand the
pilot over to OZ...
...in exchange for a guarantee
of our safety?
Negotiations are meaningless
with an organization...
...that has a record of
playing dirty.
Our one and only chance
is to fight head on!
Objects approaching at
high speed.
Probably OZ's Taurus
mobile suits!
There's five!
We have twenty space Leos;
we have the advantage!
I told you not to
underestimate OZ!
OZ already knows
that survivors...
...from the Alliance Space
Forces are hiding here!
They CAN defeat us,
with just five Tauruses!!
We'll fight for the survival
of the Alliance.
Don't let them get
the Gundam pilot!!
Why were the Alliance
suits deployed?!
Flying object approaching
the retreating troops!
What?!
The Gundam?
Did these guys find one of the
Gundams that had left Earth?
All enemy suits headed here
are space battle Leos!
Roger.
Provide the mobile dolls
with all target information.
Take over here.
- I'm going after the shuttle!
- Yes, sir!
So, now they can utilize
unmanned mobile suits.
They probably saw them
as a valid weapon in space...
...since the battleground
has no obstacles.
Battling without getting your
hands dirty is merely a game.
Foolish are those who
start wars.
But the blood shed during
battle is never a waste.
Foolish people see the bloodshed
and learn to regret their actions.
But once war turns into a game
it becomes mere entertainment.
I wish they'd just declare
a winner to this game.
Then nobody would
have to die.
Assuming the opponent
has the technology.
We don't lack the technology!
But soldiers sense the
responsibilities of combat...
...if they don't use automated
functions!
You've got the technology?
Then you could earn
the right to live longer!
I can't do it.
I'd rather die than construct
such a thing.
Youngsters always want to
think things out rationally.
But war itself is anything
but rational.
I was going to give you the
chance to build a mobile suit...
...superior to the Tallgeese
and Gundams you built.
Kill us!
I have no intentions of
lending a hand...
...in a futile war drawn out
on a game board.
Negotiations are over.
Colonel!
Chief Officer Nichol
is on the line.
What is it, Nichol?
Colonel Une.
I intercepted the Alliance's
transmission.
They're gonna team up
with a Gundam pilot!
Those imbeciles.
Wipe out all of them!!
Yes, ma'am!
They're fast!
Five suits at once?!
The enemy suits' speed
has accelerated to 8G!
He's superhuman!
The main Alliance forces
are demolished!
We'll seize the shuttle!
Seize?
What's the point?
We don't need a Gundam
pilot without his Gundam.
- Kill him!
- Roger!
Wait!
Hand me the communication set!
Sure.
This is Quatre.
My good friends who have
returned to outer space.
Let's do our very best
to protect the colonies.
He's using Heero's frequency.
He's an outstanding soldier.
He has the ability to bring
the five Gundam pilots together.
This is Quatre.
My good friends who have
returned to outer space.
Let's do our very best
to protect the colonies.
Stop them from firing
at the shuttle!
Well, well.
So you can have pity
for your men.
Then we have an understanding.
Who'd have thought we'd end
up making a Gundam for OZ?
Not exactly.
I want you to make a mobile
suit better than the Gundams.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
He's just a kid!
This kid is a Gundam pilot?!
But he's so young!
Captain!
All the Tauruses are
headed this way!
That's fast.
Fight them as far away from
the shuttle as possible!
Roger!
I'm not going to let you die.
We've caught up with the shuttle!
Stop attacking the shuttle!
All Taurus units, move away
from the shuttle's route!
What?!
Stop our attack?!
Orders are to leave the
shuttle alone.
We're all free to roam
in space.
But we must get rid of the
junk we find along the way.
Nichol!
Blow it up!
Roger.
Look after the space Leos and
I'll head after the shuttle!
Still no word from the shuttle.
So I'll start to clean up
the route!
What?!
The shuttle just fired at a Leo!
Life on the shuttle!
All suits, destroy the shuttle!
Fire!!
Our forces don't have the
strength to retaliate against OZ.
But I'm sure that young
pilot can do it.
I certainly hope my instincts
prove to be right.
Let's do our very best...
...to protect the colonies.
Your ride has arrived.
How did repairs on
the Tallgeese go, sir?
Thanks to your people's help,
everything's in order.
Thank you.
Captain!
The radar's picking up objects
from point 0430 behind us!
They're here.
Just on time!
Which means they're gonna
sink this ship.
I'm sorry.
Give it your best shot.
I don't know what to think,
but, Colonel...
Win this battle!
Thank you!
Good-bye!
Let's get going, Tallgeese!
Fifty Aries and twenty Cancers.
I'll prove they underestimated
the value of my life!
How many more?!
Nice move!
But I'm not gonna die yet!!
Treize, stop following me
around!
Or else I'll just want to
fulfill your radical hopes.
This friendship of the past...
...will only last until the day
my mask breaks!
Treize...
I can no longer be your friend.
Farewell, Treize!!
The planet in the solar
system...
...that miraculously gave
birth to life.
We call it Earth.
The year After Colony 195.
With the colonies' development,
people live in new surroundings.
Thanks to plentiful natural
resources...
...and cultivated technological
abilities.
However, this new world is
nothing but an imitation...
...of humankind's motherland,
the Earth.
Why were the colonies
created in the first place?
I hear the main purpose was
technological development...
...to enrich mankind's life on Earth.
Did man start asking too
much from this fake world?
Its colony's self-sustained way of
life is more stable than on Earth...
...since it lacks the risk
of natural disasters.
It appears that this
unlimited growth...
...was guaranteeing the
eternal existence of mankind.
Perhaps there was an age...
...when people dreamed they
could start anew in outer space.
But it's unthinkable that
the colonies or mankind...
...will ever forget the Earth.
What did the colonies'
technology bring to the Earth?
The kind of technology the Earth
wants most; military power.
Destruction is in human nature
and can never be eliminated.
And now, the colonies are developing
a militaristic disposition.
The colonies cannot forget
the Earth.
The Earth has great beauty.
Animals known as humans
have acquired such strength...
...that they want to control
this planet for themselves.
From the point of view
of an entire planet...
...the life of a living thing
lasts no more than an instant.
But in the end, mankind only
thinks of itself.
Nothing changes.
The time spent by humans in
outer space has been a waste.
In reality, the ideal is
just a dream.
This false pacifism.
This false living space.
Outer space is a breeding
ground for even more battles.
Wars claim many lives.
Mankind hasn't forgotten
the sorrow caused by wars...
...yet they haven't stopped
fighting.
The blood and tears they shed
are merely ceremonial.
One can't speak of history...
...without referring to the wars
in each era as important events.
I'm sure the pale pep talks
of fighting for peace...
...have been repeated
numerous times in the past.
The colonies say they need
armaments to maintain peace.
It's no different from on Earth.
The colonies think they've
joined the big boys.
They believed the bloodshed
would lead...
Okay, that's enough
Duo Maxwell!
Let's avoid that subject.
It's making your classmates
uncomfortable.
I don't feel it was appropriate
for your greeting speech.
Now, Duo, please be seated
at the back.
So why do people fight?
The meaning of existence
could lie in their will to fight.
People feel accomplishment
through battle.
And it's also a fact that
the ones actually fighting...
...are never perceived as
being tainted.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
There's no glory or praise...
...for the Gundam pilots
returning to the colonies.
Only orders to destroy OZ.
Gundam Deathscythe battles
the Tauruses in outer space.
But Duo is defeated and
taken prisoner by OZ.
To keep confidentiality, Heero
searches for Duo to kill him.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 19,
Assault on Barge
"Assault on Barge".