Boobs!
But why am I waking up to a face full of boobs?!
Wh-Wha-
P-President!
What?!
I-I don't know what's going on, but...
I suppose my hand could accidentally...
Morning, Issei.
Good morning.
Wh-What exactly's going on here?
I'm sorry.
As you had already gone to sleep,
I decided to invite myself in.
Well, that's not really what was bothering me...
I felt like using you as my body pillow.
You felt like it, huh?
We've still got a little time to ourselves.
Perhaps I should use this time to "bond" with my servant.
U-Uh, President...
I am a man.
Do you want to force yourself on me?
Go ahead.
I'll do anything you want.
Anything I want?!
I-I've never heard such powerful words!
P-President...
Issei-san!
It's time for your morning training!
Asia?!
I completely forgot about your training.
Are you still in bed, Issei-san?
No, I'm up!
J-Just gimme a sec!
Please give us a minute, Asia.
Issei and I need to get ready.
H-Hey, Asia!
Morning.
Morning, Asia.
P-President!
I'm going to take my clothes off, too!
What?!
I don't want to be left out!
It's 5:00 a.m. sharp!
Come on, it's time for another day of hard work!
Tomo ni mou ichido tachiagare
Stand up once again
Mamore hitotsu no inochi tayasanu yo ni
To protect a single life
Futatabi otozureta yoake ni me ga samete
Waking up to another dawn
Kimi wo omoi dasu yume no tochuu
I was dreaming about you
Me no mae no zanzo susumanai ashidori
I still see your afterimage and can't move on
Me no mae no zanzo susumanai ashidori
I still see your afterimage and can't move on
Toozakatte yuku hiriki na boku
Powerless, I drift away
Taisetsu na mono wa doko ni aru?
What is most precious to me?
Ashita wo shinjiru nara wasurenaide
If you believe in the future, never forget
Ima koso saa inochi wo kakete susumi dasu toki
Now is the time to risk your life and move on
Omoi ga tsuyoi hodo tsuyokunaru
The stronger your will, the stronger you will be
Hengen suru tsugihagi darake no risou dewa
A faint, fragile dream will never last long
A faint, fragile dream will never last long
sugu ni kiete shimau kara
Towa e tsuzuku kawasu chikai
Let's make an eternal promise
Furue dashita karada no soko kara
From the bottom of our shivering bodies
Episode 1
A Bad Feeling, Once Again!
Another Disquieting Premonition!
Delicious!
I can't believe a foreigner made this.
I have lived in Japan for a long time.
He's right, though.
This is really good, President.
Thank you, Issei.
Asia-chan just moved in a while ago,
so when Rias-san wanted to live
here too, I was really taken aback,
but I never imagined you'd help me cook.
It's the least I can do, Mother.
And you, Asia-chan. You help me clean and do the laundry.
I can't tell you how much that helps!
I-I am a guest, after all.
It's the least I can do.
Mother, would you mind if I invited the club here today after school?
Go right ahead.
Why here, President?
The club building's going to have its annual cleaning,
so we can't hold our regular meeting there today.
A club meeting at home? Sounds exciting!
I'll make the tea, President-san.
All right.
Thank you, Asia.
Since that whole ordeal with Riser,
President has been overly nice to me,
but Asia gets grumpy every time.
Still, I wonder what President meant by "bonding".
Hey, Issei, what the hell are you grinning about?
Ow!
Matsuda! Motohama!
Hey, I've been hearing some sketchy rumors about you lately.
Rumors?
Rumors that Hyoudou Issei is taking one pretty girl after another,
and doing all sorts of evil!
What?!
By threatening Rias-senpai and
Himejima-senpai with some secret,
you force them to do the most lewd and gut-wrenching sexual acts with you!
Wha-
Your bloodied hands even have the academy mascot,
Toujou Koneko-chan, in their grasp,
and you devour her underdeveloped body like a beast devours its prey!
You have really nice hair, Asia-san.
It's nothing special.
I wish I were blonde.
Right, right.
You'll bewitch all the guys.
Bewitch?
And as if that's not enough, Issei's never-ending lust
reaches out to Asia-chan, the new transfer student!
That's such an old word.
What the hell?!
And we started it all.
What?!
I'd go crazy with jealousy if I weren't doing this!
Perhaps we've gone mad already!
Gimme a break.
Don't worry.
The rumors aren't limited to the girls.
There's also a rumor that you and Kiba are gay lovers!
I hear some of the girls love that one.
You assholes!
What's going on?
Are you Three Horny Stooges having another filthy conversation?
Kiryuu?
Aika?
Asia, there are plenty of guys out there.
Why'd you have to choose this one to be your boyfriend?
B-B-Boyfriend?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Plus, Asia's only just come to Japan.
I'm just looking after her.
It's not like we're dating...
Seeing how you two are practically bolted together,
nobody'd be surprised if it was because you were coupling every night.
Coupling?!
Coupling?
You're crazy!
We're not some giant robots!
We can't-
What the...
Sorry, I gotta go.
Go where?
To Akeno-san.
Your left hand?
Yeah.
The hell's the deal with him?
H-He has some club things to take care of.
Oh, so you really aren't going out.
P-Pardon?!
Because you told me-
Kiryuu-san, stop it!
Why him?!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
I-I'm sorry this is so sudden, Akeno-san.
It's not something you can control.
Now, let's get started.
Y-Yes, please.
Is there something wrong?
W-Well, your clothes...
I cleansed myself for the ritual.
As we're in a hurry today, I didn't have time to properly dry off.
I'm sorry.
Don't be! It doesn't matter to me.
If anything, I'm happier-
N-No, forget I said that.
Your Dragon Arm has much more power than we thought.
We can only change its shape temporarily using magic.
We need to directly remove the power from your fingers,
by sucking out what's inside.
Why does a girl's mouth...
feel so slimy...
so warm...
and oh so good?!
Dammit...
I'm gonna go mad!
Ddraig!
My life is perfect right now!
My, my.
Your adorable reactions are giving me an irresistible urge to play with you.
P-Play?
Yes...
I need to have a good relationship with my underclassman, after all.
A-Akeno-san...
I do like you, Issei-kun.
M-Me?
A-Akeno-san's body is...
so damn soft!
Y-You're not wearing anything down there, either?
It's part of the ritual; of course I'm not.
I-Is it, now?
All right...
But I'm sure Rias wouldn't be at all pleased if we were to exploit that fact.
After all, she...
You're such a tease.
Hey, did Akeno-san just call President "Rias?"
Does that mean they call each other "Rias" and "Akeno" when no one's around?!
I've extracted the Dragon's power.
You should be all right for the time being.
Thank you.
During the battle with Phenex...
Phenex?
No matter how many times you were beaten, you stood back up.
You were very heroic.
Then, you crashed President's engagement party to save her,
and even defeated a so-called immortal Phoenix to do so.
After seeing such a courageous and powerful man in battle,
I'm beginning to feel a little funny myself.
Is this love that I'm feeling?
We'll have to do this again.
All right, let's begin today's meeting.
We'll tally-up this month's contracts.
Akeno formed eleven.
Yes.
Koneko formed ten.
Yuuto formed eight.
Yes.
And Asia formed three.
You're doing great, Asia-san!
My, my! Not bad at all!
That's not a bad result for a rookie.
Thank you so much!
As for Issei...
Zero.
I-I'm ashamed of myself.
You need to get those contracts made,
or you'll never become a High Class Devil.
I know!
I'll make it to the top of the group next month!
Sorry for interrupting!
You didn't have to make those, Mother!
Don't worry about it!
You're having a Karuta Club meeting, aren't you?
Now, that's the first time I've ever heard anyone make that mistake.
Oh, and...
I brought something nice for you to look at!
Huh?!
This is...
Issei, back in elementary school!
Oh, my. He's stark naked!
He was so small. Isn't it adorable?
Issei-senpai's embarrassing history...
This was back in kindergarten.
He was already going after girls' skirts.
Just great.
Little Issei...
Little Issei!
I understand exactly how you feel, President-san!
Asia, you see the appeal, too?
I'm so happy.
Good god.
Why'd you have to dig those out, Mom?
She's a good mother.
Yeah, right!
It must be nice to have a family.
Oh yeah, Kiba, do you...
Hey, Issei-kun.
This photo here...
Oh, that boy used to be my neighbor.
We played a lot back then.
He moved because his parents had a job overseas or something.
What was his name, again?
I think it was...
Hey, Issei-kun.
Huh?
Do you remember this sword?
Nah, it was a long time ago.
It really is a small world.
I've got to make some contracts this month.
I'm losing not only to Kiba but to Asia as well.
Kiba was acting kinda strange today.
I never thought I'd be seeing it like this.
Seeing what?
This is a Holy Sword.
A Holy Sword?
Nevermind.
Thank you, Issei-kun.
What was the deal with that?
This's the place.
This person's probably gonna wonder why a Devil would ring the doorbell, too.
Hello!
Did you summon a Devil?
Do you think this is kind of strange?
Of course you do!
We grant your desires!
I would pop out of the magic circle on the flyer if I could,
but there are some problems with that.
Anyway, come on in.
You're a Devil, aren't you?
Wow, what a place.
He doesn't look Japanese.
I wonder what kind of work he does.
Have a drink.
Sorry, I'm underage.
Really?
That's a bummer.
I wanted someone to share a drink with.
That was your wish?
Is that a problem?
No, the contract will be made once I grant your wish, and it is duly compensated for.
Whiskey's all I've got.
Are you okay with water?
Y-Yes.
You came here on a bike because you didn't have enough power?
Yeah...
What a guy!
His laughing is starting to piss me off,
but I need this contract.
Just deal with it!
This has been fun.
What do you want for compensation?
Already?
As you're a Devil, do you want my soul or something?
N-Not a chance!
Just chatting with someone is hardly worth that much.
Oh, you're pretty generous.
My master prefers happy transactions.
Okay, then. What about that?
It's not a copy.
But it looks really expensive.
I don't have much else on hand.
If you can't take that, then I guess my soul's the only...
I-I'll take the painting, then!
What an odd guy.
Well, I've made the contract,
so that's another step toward my goal!
I'm gonna be the Harem King!
President?
An abandoned factory?
Over here, Issei.
Sorry to make you come out here.
It's fine, but...
Inside there?
It's definitely a rouge Devil.
We've received orders to slay it tonight.
That's how dangerous it is.
We'd be at a disadvantage indoors.
Stay out of this one, Asia.
Yes!
Akeno and I will wait outside.
Koneko, Yuuto, and Issei, you three lure it out.
Yes, President.
Yes.
Roger!
Boosted Gear!
Yuuto?
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Let's go, Kiba, Koneko-chan!
Yes.
Okay.
I wonder what this one's like.
If it's another monster...
Not even a heads up, huh?
Let's go.
Right...
There's nothing in here.
Koneko-chan?
There it is.
What?
Dammit, she's a monster?!
Boost!
Yuuto-senpai, if you would.
Yuuto-senpai!
S-Sorry.
Why, you...
Boost!
Explosion!
Dragon Shocker!
I need more power!
Quit standing around, Prince Charming!
Kiba!
Fly.
Akeno.
Yes, President.
A disobedient creature, who leaves its master and pursues its own desires.
Such a sin deserves severe punishment.
In the name of Lord Gremory,
I shall punish you!
Yes!
She had completely lost her mind.
You could no longer even call her a Devil.
I'd never want to end up like that.
No wonder the order was so urgent.
Koneko-chan, are you all right?
Thank you.
Did that wake you up a bit?
One misstep, and someone could have died.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
I've never seen you like this.
This hasn't been my best day.
I'll have to excuse myself for now.
Yuuto...
Kiba!
What happened?
You're acting all weird.
You'd never normally act that way around President.
It's none of your business.
I'm worried !
Worried?
About who?
Devils are naturally self-centered beings.
Dude...
Are you kidding?
Nevertheless, I'm sorry for what happened back there.
See you.
Hold on!
If something's got you down, just tell me about it!
We're friends, aren't we?
Friends, huh?
You're very passionate, Issei-kun.
I just remembered something very rudimentary.
Rudimentary?
Why I'm alive.
Or in other words, what I'm fighting for.
For the president, right?
No.
I live for vengeance.
Vengeance?
The Holy Sword Excalibur...
Its destruction is what I live for.
A Holy Sword is a Devil's worst enemy.
Merely touching the blade of one can burn a Devil,
and taking a slash from one could completely obliterate them.
A Holy Sword can kill a Devil.
That's a pretty fearsome weapon.
However, it's also true that only a select few can use them.
That's why the Church attempted to artificially create beings
that could use Excalibur, a Holy Sword.
That was...
The Holy Sword Experiment.
The Holy Sword Experiment?
I never heard of anything like that when I was part of the Church.
That's not surprising.
It happened a very long time ago.
I've been told that it was a complete failure.
Good.
Yuuto...
is one of the survivors.
Kiba-san?!
What?
O-One second.
Kiba saw this photo and said that it was a Holy Sword.
What?!
It's not as powerful as Excalibur,
but he's right.
It is a Holy Sword.
I think it was when he saw that photo that he started acting weird.
I can't believe you were so close to one!
I remember now!
I went to church with this kid's family a few times.
I see.
Now I know why the previous sovereign disappeared.
But...
President?
Oh, sorry.
It's getting late.
Now, let's go to sleep.
P-President?!
Why are you taking off your clothes?!
Why?
You know I can't sleep with clothes on, don't you?
Yeah, sure. But why are you doing it in my room?
Because I'm going to sleep with you, of course.
What?!
Then I'll sleep here, too!
I'll sleep with you, Issei-san!
Give him up for tonight, Asia.
I don't want to.
It's not fair for you to get him to yourself.
I want to sleep with Issei-san, too!
Wh-What a marvelous sight!
You're supposed to respect your seniors.
And it's a double whammy!
All men were created equal!
Quick, before it's too late!
You're getting crafty, aren't you?
Th-There, there, you two...
I-I'll do anything to get what I want!
Calm down.
Why don't we have Issei decide, then?
Wha-
All right.
Please, Issei-san.
No!
There's no way I could choose!
Come on in, Issei.
Issei-san...
Please, be gentle.
I've been living with Issei-san for longer!
No, he'll pick me!
Right, Issei?!
My boobs may be smaller than yours,
but my love for Issei-san is greater than anyone else's!
Mine is-
It's quite run-down.
Apparently a Devil and a Fallen Angel fought to the death here.
He's awfully late.
Are you sure we're supposed to meet him here?
Of course I am!
I lived here with my parents!
Back when I was little!
We're friends, aren't we?!
Forgive me.
I'm not supposed to enjoy being with friends.
I'm not worthy...
of such...
H-Help me!
A priest?
Hey, there!
What's up?
Been a while, huh?
Well, well, would you look at that.
It's Prince Scumbag, the scumbag Devil.
Freed Zelzan!
You're still roaming this city?
I can't hold back the tears this fateful reunion brings!
I'm sorry, but I'm not in the mood for your jokes today.
That is God damn awesome to hear!
I was starting to get bored of killing priests.
That glow...
That aura...
Is that...
You betcha!
You've got nice timing.
I'd like to test something to pay you back for what you did.
I want to compare your piece-of-shit Demonic Sword
with my Holy Sword,
Excalibur!
I will never forgive Excalibur.
Even for fated couples
unmeiteki ni mo hakarishirenai
The equation of love is complicated
koi no houteishiki
Love isn't always justifiable
ai ni riyuu wa iranai
The answer lies inside your heart
kotae wa kimi no kokoro ni aru kara
After worrying and hesitating
nayande mayotte
My brain stops functioning
shikou teishi
I keep writing then erasing stuff
kaite wa keshite wo kurikaeshi
I'm running a simulation of you in my head
atama no naka de anata simulation
It's unpredictable
yosoku fukanou
Will this work? How about this?
kou kana kou kana
But you never follow my calculations
keisan de ugokeba ii no ni
"Look, it's the beach!" "It sure is."
umi ne sou ne
I can't tell if you love me because you're so innocent
junsui na hodo futoumei
Don't be so kind to every girl
yasashisa wo furimaku na
You'll end up breaking many hearts
tsumitsukuri da wa
Why can't you just be normal?
futsuu ni misete
It's so unfair
zurui hito
Then you leave!
jaa kaeri na
I shouldn't let my rivals take you away from me
raibaru ni ukkari ki mi toraretara
I need a hint!
hinto ga hoshii
Quick, I need one!
hayaku hoshii
As I imagine a lovey-dovey future
love hidai na mirai
love
My expectations only go up
takamatta kitai
What should I try as the coefficient?
keisuu wa nan ni shiyou
There are too many variables
michisuu sugiru
To your feelings
kimi no kimochi
Rather than just work on the left-hand side
hidari yori mo daisuki
Look ahead to the other side of the equal sign
ikooru no saki wa
Although I'm not sure what it does
wakaranai kedo michibiku
It leads to the correct answer every time
kotae wa itsumo seikai deshou
I'll get over my worries and prove my love for you
nayande mo kono ai wo shoumei suru yo
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
Ooh, two pretty girls?
Wait, are those Holy Swords?!
Y-You're here to kill us?!
The Holy Sword is here
The Holy Sword Is Here!
Episode 2
Behold, boobs!