I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Over this past year, I've woken up
with hangovers in the following places...
Sometimes I might wake up in the
cabin aboard the torpedo boat...
...and sometimes the office
of a pirating company...
...but generally, this is my place of rest.
A cheap hotel room looking
down over downtown Roanapur.
For the first time in a year, I'm leaving
this country for a far away location.
A place that is too far removed
from the current me. That country...
Oh, is that you, Rock? Happy New Year.
Though it's hard to get
into that mood here.
There's nothing but the
Chinese setting off fireworks.
Yeah. Everything's decorated
nicely for the new year here.
How's Revy doing?
All she does is complain. She didn't
like the Tokarev she was given.
She was in a bad mood
over that yesterday, too.
You sure are a lady's man.
She went with you because she
was worried about you, right?
Yeah. I should be going now.
I'll call you again.
It's starting to snow.
It snows worse in New York,
but still, this is nostalgic.
It's been ages since I last saw snow.
Ever since I left that city.
- How do you like Japan?
- I've been hit on by a few guys.
When I talk back, they make a face
and repeat the word "gaijin".
This country pisses me off.
So, today, we meet face to
face for the first time.
Thank you for coming from so far away.
These guys are my men.
Now, how shall I address you?
Just Balalaika is fine.
I've been briefed by Laptev.
We've been eager to set up
base in Tokyo for some time.
I do appreciate your assistance.
If you join forces with us,
there'll be nothing to fear.
As you've heard...
...the Kanto Peace Council is
making an effort to keep foreigners out.
Mr. Laptev from Russia is one example
of someone who was thrown out.
So I was thinking... We could
reach out a helping hand.
But isn't the Washimine
clan a part of the Council?
We can only go so far in
meeting their call to duty.
We've gone to great lengths to fulfill
our obligation to the Kousa clan.
And I think we've done a
lot for the Peace Council.
But we can't stay at the bottom of the
pile forever, simply outta obligation.
Our interests are mutually
beneficial, Mr. Bando.
You expand your reach with our help...
...while we will set up a new
enterprise in this city.
You're quick to understand.
If you suppress the Kousa
clan with your power...
...then the Peace Council cannot
afford to go against us.
Our emblem will gain power.
I hear that among the Russians,
you're most used to being in a fire.
You're concerned about our forces?
Our forces are nothing
like those in this nation.
- We are a military force.
- Let me show you.
It's me. Are you in position?
- Very well.
- Mr. Interpreter?
She's now speaking in Russian.
Perfect. Go ahead and begin.
To start things off, we've blown up one
of the clubs owned by the Kousa clan.
Blown up?! You idiot!
What are you thinking?!
Intimidation with handguns
amounts to nothing.
We will make our strength very
clear with our first strike.
This is how Hotel Moscow
makes a show of force.
We will decimate anything... that
stands in our way, you understand.
That's why we have come here.
Fine by me. It's one hell of a firework
to start off the Washimine clan's fight.
I've taken a liking to you, Miss Balalaika.
All those yakuza guys were...
...paralyzed with fear.
That's a little much to return to,
after being away for some time.
I wish they wouldn't turn my
country into a battlefield.
The Sis was in a really good mood.
There hasn't been a big fight
in Roanapur lately, after all.
RESERVED
She's the type to give up fucking if
there's a war to be fought.
- There's something wrong with her.
- She's a war maniac.
She left a few important
screws back in Afghanistan.
Hey Rock. What's that?
Oh. They have a fair up.
It's for the new year season.
So it's a carnival. Looks
like fun. Hey, driver!
Thank you.
I don't see any Ferris wheels.
You won't find them at a
traditional Japanese fair, Revy.
- Here you go!
- Thanks.
Yeah, that's my third one!
You're living up to
the name of Two-Hands.
You got that right.
Who do you think I am?
I'm Miss Rebecca. Just give me a gun
and I'll show you why I'm the best!
That's my fourth. It's a shame
I don't have my Cutlass.
I could close this shop
down in three seconds.
Of course, this is the hardest country
in the world to have a gunfight in.
And you can't bribe the
cops here like in Roanapur.
I don't want to be thrown in jail.
- You remembering something?
- Like what?
What do you mean,
"Like what?" This is your country.
Don't you have anyone?
You know. Like, family.
It's not like you were born
from the crotch of a tree.
I thought snoops weren't well liked.
It's nothing. Just wondering
what you were thinking.
You looked like you were deep
in thought about something.
From the time you pulled
a gun on me, on that boat...
...a year has already passed. Time flies.
Yeah.
I don't understand it.
This is a place I knew well,
but I feel like I don't know it at all.
My family doesn't get along.
My older brother turned out
well and got a government job.
But I got into college a year late
and ended up in a normal company.
They didn't expect much of me.
I guess they really didn't care.
But your parents are alive, right?
At least contact them.
You haven't been arrested yet.
This is your only chance.
If you keep this up, one day you'll
never be able to see them again.
From our point of view, yours is a normal
home. Isn't it worth going home to?
You got this far without stealing or killing.
Don't misunderstand me. I'm just saying
you should at least go give them a visit.
Can't say I'm really normal. Hanging
around you guys is clear proof of that.
What?
Okay! One more and I get the top score!
Damn it! I bet it's weighed down!
Hey, hey!
All right! Hey, Rock!
Um, she says she scored enough points
for first place, so give her the prize.
No way. She can't cheat.
He says it doesn't count. Because
you poked it and pushed it down.
What?! You bastard! What
the fuck?! Bullshit!
I'm not gonna take this
kinda crap, you dickweed!
- What the hell?! Speak Japanese!
- What was that?!
- You just cussed at me, didn't you?!
- What the hell are you saying?!
- Revy, cut it out!
- Son of a bitch!
Damn you! We're in
Japan! Speak Japanese!
Gin.
Miss customer. Excuse me.
We're in the middle of the new year's
week. Why don't we all just have fun?
Please lay your aggression aside.
Who the hell are you?!
Revy! Let's go! We're being a nuisance.
Rock, baby. Are you taking his side?
If you're gonna be unreasonable,
I have a problem with that.
Life is short, so we'd all like to
just enjoy what we have left of it.
You had your fun...
...so please take advantage
of this opportunity to save face.
No way.
Revy! Let it go, Revy! Come on!
Um... Um, sweet sake...
Won't you join me for some sweet sake?
It's chilly, so rather than
standing around in the cold...
- Who the fuck are you?
- Miss.
Yes, I agree. I prefer not to
fight, so let's do it. Okay?
So, how did we end up like this?
Come on. There's nothing to gain
from making a big scene.
I'm not even in the mood any more.
Lost the buzz.
Well thank God Almighty.
I'm really glad things calmed down, too.
Ah, well, um...
- Oh, I'm sorry!
- Oh, please go ahead.
Well, um... Then sure.
You look like a student.
Or are you a vendor?
Well, yes. They're both correct.
My father was, um...
My father was a vendor. That man...
Ginji is like my father's student.
If there's an argument here,
everyone goes to Ginji.
He's big, right? His body.
Before he realized it, he was
like the arbitrator of Takamachi.
I see.
I thought I would help close shop today
after my college entrance exam classes.
So that was a little shock to me.
She's ultra-short tempered to the core.
I'm just glad she didn't
end up causing a big scene.
- Is she Japanese?
- Oh.
She's Chinese-American. How should
I put it... She works with me.
I came to translate for a Russian,
and she came with me.
An international occupation
is very impressive.
Not really. It's a small company and
we're always dealing with trouble.
It's a lot of hard work,
and it's dangerous.
- It's dangerous?
- Ah, well...
Yeah, something like that.
What's with him?
What are you laughing at, asshole?
Miss. You're not a
decent woman, are you?
There. Those eyes.
Those aren't good eyes.
Those are the eyes of a dog.
I have no fucking idea what
you just said, but... I can tell.
You're the same kind as me. You stink
of blood and guts. A smell I know.
Well, it's getting cold. Miss, sitting
out here isn't good for your body.
Yes. Goodbye.
That's how we met.
Oh, by the way, what's your name?
Oh. It's Yukio. Yuki, as in snow,
and O, as in sandal straps.
That day...
I still didn't know just how
powerful the underground world is.
0230 hours. We have assaulted
a Kousa clan office.
Confirmed result. Twelve kills,
no fatalities, no casualties.
All men left the scene by 0237 hours.
Shall I have them prepare Russian tea?
No, I don't want to make a fuss.
- Then some toast?
- Would you like some, Sergeant?
No, I'm fine.
Don't skip breakfast,
Sergeant. It's not healthy.
What's the situation with
police force intervention?
Right. They closed off
the scene at 0305 hours.
They're on heightened security status.
I had a member of the
Washimine clan...
...transcribe their
wireless communications.
We must wait for Rock's
translation for the details.
The reliability of information
could mean life or death.
- Have him translate it immediately.
- Right.
As I would expect from you, Balalaika.
I can see why Boss
Slevenin acknowledges you.
Who's ass do you think
I'm wiping, Vasily?
You've disgraced the reputation
of the organization.
You can't even take control
of a single playground.
I want to wrap up the operation
here and get back to Roanapur.
That place is full of gunpowder,
so I can't leave it unattended for long.
Goodbye. I'll see you in six hours.
Don't overstep your
boundaries, Balalaika!
Back in Moscow, I'm one
of the respected bosses!
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's hard to remember those who rose
up using money instead of skill.
I better write your name down on
a dollar bill so I can remember.
Apologize, you ex-military bitch!
I'm warning you. There are two
things in this world I can't stand.
One is cold blintzes, and the other
is dimwitted ex-KGB shit heads.
Live with your head low so
the bullets don't hit you.
Boss.
You know, kids nowadays would
rather have video games than these.
How much longer do you
plan on enduring this?
This is the true job of a vendor.
It's a lot better than
selling drugs or women.
Are you implying that I
do this because I like it?
When the old man died, he left us this
group that can barely get tribute.
The only reason we've
come this far is because...
...the old man and the Kousa clan's
last head took each other as brothers.
Now with that gone, those guys haven't
let anyone take the head of our group...
...even now, three years later.
We're the only ones left with any
sense of obligation to the old man.
He took care of me when I
came from the Kansai region.
So you see, we've gotta do something.
Gin-boy. You said that dealing with
low-lifes was a shame upon the yakuza.
But that only matters if we have a name.
That's not what the old man said.
I'm pulling off a big job right now.
Joining up with Russians to
take out the guys above us.
Boss. Do you realize what you're saying?
They tried to take us out first!
But, the Russians are Russians,
no matter how you cut it.
They don't have a shred of honor. So we
need to stay in control of certain areas.
What are you trying to say?
I want you to take it up again.
That white scabbard.
The name that still puts fear into
all yakuza: Man-slayer Ginji.
Won't you show that to me once more?
Boss. I'm grateful that you're
looking after the young lady.
I also understand what
you're saying. However...
What you're suggesting now
doesn't bear a shred of justice.
When I held the white scabbard for the
old man, it was because he had that.
Then I guess that's that. I'll come again.
Those Russians...
Did they bring their own interpreter?
- Yeah they did.
- What kinda guy is he?
Oh, just a young guy with a pretty,
but naughty, girl by his side.
He didn't look like anything
more than a normal guy.
If I had to make an analogy, he's like
a bird that arrives at the doorstep...
...with soup, onions, and even
the pot to cook himself in.
Okay. I won't be too long.
- Later.
- Shoo. Hurry up and go. Shoo, shoo.
I'll wait for you, but not for too long.
Just until I finish drinking this.
After that I'm leaving, Partner.
The sky looks the same
no matter where you are.
Here, or in Mott Street.
Hey! You God damn brats!
You wanna shoot each other up,
then head on out to Lebanon!
Hey now, so you're a
real gunman, aren't ya?
Just look at this sorry excuse for a gun.
Okay, brats! Now watch those cans
we got lined up there, all right?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
- Wow!
- That's amazing!
- Like magic!
- Just like Annie Oakley, right?
Jack McCall!
I'm here to avenge Wild Bill!
Can you defeat me, the
incredible Jane? Now, come at me.
I'm hit!
Hey, hey, wait a sec! No,
no, you got it all wrong.
The only place you'll see people go down
like that is in the movies or on TV shows.
Listen. I n reality, you suddenly lose
all your strength. Do you understand?
Like everything below your knees
disappears, and your feet stagger...
...and unable to position yourself,
you go down head first.
I'll show you how it happens. You.
You know, that's not
very cool looking, lady.
It's always like this when you die.
It's really not that cool.
- What are you doing?
- How long have you been watching?
Since about the time you charged
into the Deadwood saloon.
I noticed the scenario
changed part way through.
Calamity Jane didn't die at that location.
Damn it.
- My toy pistol!
- Listen up!
- Ow, ow!
- You tell Dutch or Benny about this...
...and I'll cut off your balls
and pole and feed them to you!
I won't! I won't say a thing!
So? Were you able to meet your folks?
W-Well, I did go to the house,
but I wasn't able to see them.
They weren't home.
What is it?
No, it's nothing. But we still have
a few more days here.
You're right.
Why doesn't he go home?
This place suits him so perfectly.
What is it with this guy?
Next Episode
Boss! The Russians aren't holding back!
They've b-blown something up
again today!