I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
So, today, we meet face to
face for the first time.
Thank you for coming from so far away.
These guys are my men.
Now, how shall I address you?
If you join forces with us,
there'll be nothing to fear.
As you've heard...
...the Kanto Peace Council is
making an effort to keep foreigners out.
Mr. Laptev from Russia is one example
of someone who was thrown out.
So I was thinking... We could
reach out a helping hand.
We can only go so far in
meeting their call to duty.
We've gone to great lengths to fulfill
our obligation to the Kousa clan...
You're quick to understand.
If you suppress the Kousa
clan with your power...
...then the Peace Council cannot
afford to go against us.
Our emblem will gain power.
I hear that among the Russians,
you're most used to being in a fire.
Mr. Interpreter?
I'm sorry, it's military code.
To start things off, we've blown up one
of the clubs owned by the Kousa clan.
Blown up?! You idiot!
What are you thinking?!
Fine by me. It's one hell of a firework
to start off the Washimine clan's fight.
I've taken a liking to you, Miss Balalaika.
RESERVED
Next Episode