Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
With high hopes, humans
leave Earth...
...to begin a new life in
the space colonies.
But the United Earth Sphere
Alliance gains military power...
...and in the name of
Justice and Peace...
...seizes control of one
colony after the other.
The year is After Colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
To counter the Alliance's
tyranny, rebel colonists...
...bring new arsenals
to the Earth...
...disguising them as
shooting stars.
But the Alliance headquarters
catches on to this operation.
The Shooting Star She Saw
Moving object confirmed
at Lagrange Point AX...
...moving in the GY position.
Estimated to reach Earth
in 600 seconds.
It's not just one.
No sir.
The radar's picked up
five metal objects.
Zechs is in the atmosphere;
let him know.
It's probably old satellite
parts or something like that.
Yes, sir.
Lieutenant Zechs.
Surveillance is reporting
a meteorite.
The satellite surveillance
guys are practically blind.
They think a meteorite
would ride the wave course...
...to enter Earth's atmosphere?
It's just as OZ
Headquarters said.
Mm-hm.
It's the colonies' Operation M.
How many can we catch?
Just one. The one headed
for Eastern Eurasia.
One would do just dandy.
A hired front line soldier
mustn't rush to battle.
That's quite the bold
statement, sir.
I told you.
I'm a true soldier.
All areas functioning.
Commencing operations
in seven minutes.
A civilian shuttle...
Mr. Darlian.
The shuttle will soon
enter the atmosphere.
Please be sure to fasten your
seat belt and remain seated.
What's the matter Relena?
Aren't you glad to be
coming home to Earth?
No, not a bit.
Sorry I couldn't spend
time with you.
Work keeps interfering.
Father, next time we go
out to space...
...how about leaving yourself
a little free time?
Father, what is that?
Relative speed to target, 01545.
Engaging auto lock.
Ready to shoot down obstacles.
Earth's assault carrier?!
We've caught up.
I'll bring it up on screen.
Just as I thought.
So that's their "battle seed"...
...all ready to sprout into
new battles.
Operation M.
He has to slow down; there's
a civilian shuttle ahead.
You don't think he'd shoot down
the shuttle and speed up?
I doubt if he'd shoot it
down right in front of us.
He's on a secret mission,
you have to remember.
The Alliance is onto me.
Figures.
He's entered the atmosphere;
we'll follow.
I'm finally here.
I made it to the Earth.
The capsule's changed course.
Is he trying to commit suicide?
The only way to keep a
secret is to destroy evidence.
Maybe that's his plan.
But the capsule's speeding up.
He's trying to break away.
Ridiculous!
He couldn't possibly
survive that heat!
Maybe he could.
Our enemies seem to be pretty
technologically advanced.
An atmosphere entry capsule?
Operation Meteor!
Huh?
Lieutenant Zechs, what is this?
The enemy's new weapon
is a fighter.
It moves just like a bird.
We've reached flight altitude.
We can proceed to attack.
Let's get him with
our machine gun.
No.
No machine gun for him.
Shoot him down!
But Lieutenant Zechs.
I thought our mission
was to bring in the weapon.
But the real target's obviously
the fighter pilot inside.
I'll escape no probs.
Alter mission?
That craft is carrying
OZ mobile suits!
Judging by its speed, there's
probably three suits on board.
Roger that mission.
I'll go back and shoot down
the OZ carrier.
Enemy fighter has turned
and is headed for us!
Is the Leo ready to use?
Yes.
You're going after him
with a mobile suit?!
Right.
Then wouldn't the Aries
light-speed mobile suit...
...be better than the Leo
land battle mobile suit?
My Leo is plenty fast enough.
Besides, if he wants to fight,
I should give him my best.
Lieutenant Zechs, I'll send
backup when the Aries is ready.
Roger!
What?! He's above!
Left drive system malfunction.
He's good!
Nice shot, Lieutenant Zechs!
So much for him.
That was far too easy.
Lieutenant, should we
pursue him with the Aries...
...once you return with the Leo?
We'll follow him with the
carrier and capture him on land.
It's our chance to find out
the purpose of Operation M.
What if he self-detonates?
He's made it all the way
to the Earth.
He won't commit suicide
before setting foot on it.
It transformed into a mobile suit!
Lieutenant Zechs, what kind of
machine is that?!
No idea.
I thought only the Alliance and
OZ could build mobile suits.
Lieutenant, leave him to us.
Thanks.
He's intense. Perhaps!
It moved!
Never mind; Just shoot!
One more to go.
He blew away two Aries
with just one shot!
Not too shabby!
Lieutenant Zechs,
are you all right?
Yeah.
Sorry to worry you.
I did everything I could.
We have complete data analysis.
Judging by the strength
of the mobile suit...
...it could only be made
from Gundanium alloy.
So, it WAS a Gundam.
The suit might be unharmed.
But that reckless pilot
won't have survived.
Lieutenant.
The Marina Mother Ship
is offering to salvage...
...the unregistered mobile suit.
Let them do as they wish.
Tell them it sank in the J.A.P.
Point of the Asia Area.
Yes, sir.
They offered to salvage it?
There's no bright future for
soldiers scurrying for a reward.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Mr. Darlian!
What issues were discussed
at the Colony Summit?
What are the colonies'
demands to the Alliance?
Any comments, Vice
Foreign Minister Darlian?
Here on Earth, people wonder...
...when the colonies
will attack.
What do you say,
Mr. Darlian?!
Please, Vice Foreign Minister!
Is it a hostile situation
with the colonies?
We've been waiting for you,
Mr. Darlian.
A military car's outside.
Please proceed quickly.
Right away?
That won't do.
I have things to prepare for
my daughter's birthday.
I've arranged for a separate
car to take your daughter.
Don't trouble yourself about me.
I'm capable of finding
my own way home.
Well, let's go then.
General Septem's expecting you.
Father, don't you realize my
birthday's coming up soon?!
The average girl would
probably flip over this.
A military plane.
This would've already
been a space harbor...
...if it weren't for them.
Guess it's time to head home.
A body!
A military uniform?
He's a soldier.
Better get help!
You're saying three of your
mobile suits were shot down?
Yes, sir.
It's unlike you to
be so careless.
It'll be hard to pacify
the Alliance big shots.
We were up against a mobile
suit made of Gundanium.
You're joking.
Just imagine if it was
made by the colonies.
Something like this would
never have happened...
...if we'd been in OZ
fifteen years ago.
So it WAS a Gundam.
Can't imagine otherwise.
Alliance's surveillance
was far from sufficient.
The Alliance's Marina is on
the way to salvage evidence.
Leave that business to my men.
I'll send my specialists in
undersea searches.
You take it from there.
Right.
I'm sure you're aware but
this is an important period.
Don't do anything to
anger the Alliance.
I understand.
Sorry I'm late.
Colonel Treize.
I hear your subordinate
lost three mobile suits...
...when they entered the
atmosphere.
Yes.
Your point being?
You wasted three mobile
suits to bring...
...a minor rebellion under
control!
And we were able to prevent
the rebellion from developing.
I'm not talking about the results!
You're wasting the military's
valuable combat resources!
Valuable combat resources?
Are you talking about
our soldiers?
Or are you talking about
mobile suits?
Are you ridiculing me?!
Calm down.
Colonel Treize, it could
happen again.
Be more careful.
Yes, sir.
Now, onto our main agenda,
which is obstructing...
...coalition between colonies.
The Alliance Military's getting
too complacent during peace.
The new future will be created
by my organization, OZ.
He's just a boy.
Be still; the ambulance
is coming.
Did you see?
See what?
Down there!
Hurry!
Hey, who are you?
What?!
Hey!
My name...
My name is Relena Darlian.
What's yours?
Are we under attack?!
This is Duo here.
I've destroyed the main motor!
Now I just have to slice
my way out of here!
Dover Base here!
We're under sudden enemy attack!
Enemy attack?!
Who's attacking?!
I dunno!
Now that you've seen me,
you must die.
The mission was to destroy
just the space port.
I'll demolish everything.
This is Battle 001.
Pilot name: Trowa,
for the record.
You're sure the rebel capsule
fell in this area, are you?
Yes, sir.
But there's nothing here.
Attack!!
What's happening here?!
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
We're surrounded!
Who are they!
Captain!
What?!
Drop your weapons and surrender.
Then I'll spare your lives.
Fire! Fire!!
Quatre reporting.
I've destroyed the leader.
I told you...
You should've surrendered.
My name's Wu Fei.
I'm not hiding anywhere.
This battle will be over
in practically no time.
The search unit isn't here yet?
They say they won't be
here for two hours.
What's taking them so long?
Don't get so flustered.
That Gundam's not
going anywhere.
And don't forget it's
quite deep here.
The Marina's search will take
a long time to complete.
But...
Why don't I show you
something interesting.
What's this?
An OZ observation craft
took these pictures.
Don't you think it looks
a lot like the one we saw?
So there are two of them?!
No, there seem to be more.
Reports state that OZ's mobile
suit factory, a space port...
...and troops searching for
the capsule like we are...
...have been attacked and
completely annihilated.
So there are four.
Five in total, if you include
the one that sank already.
Five?!
Five Gundams?!
We're very fortunate.
Because we made it out alive
after encountering a Gundam.
I'm surprised that Relena
isn't here yet.
It's still very early in
the school year.
You can't blame her.
She just returned from outer
space yesterday, after all.
I sure envy her.
I'd love to take a trip to
outer space, even just once.
Guess that's what being the
richest girl in school is like.
Oh that reminds me; isn't it
Relena's birthday tomorrow?
That's right.
I wonder who Relena's gonna
invite to her birthday party?!
- Miss Relena!
- Good morning!
Good morning.
Hey, that's him!
Quiet please.
I'd like to introduce a new
student to our class.
I'm Heero Yuy.
It's a pleasure.
I'm sure that's him.
Take the seat beside
Relena, Heero.
Feel free to ask her any
questions you might have.
Now, let's begin class.
Nice to meet you, Heero.
Um... excuse me Relena?
Here you go.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
I hope you'll be able to
make it to the party.
But... But why?
I'll kill you.
What kind of person is he?!
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The Alliance's Marina
sends out troops...
...to find the sunken Gundam.
But OZ's Zechs is
the first to find it...
...using the Cancer mobile suit.
Heero must destroy the Gundam
before anyone else seizes it.
But in the dark ocean depths,
another Gundam appears.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 2,
The Gundam Deathscythe
"The Gundam Deathscythe".