Maximum Titillation OVA Vol. 2
The Church Trio's Underwear, Amen!
Xenovia! When did you start
wearing such cute underwear?!
Irina. I'm not the
plain church girl I used to be.
Just look!
The clerk highly recommended
this as my "battle underwear"!
Hold on! Battle underwear is...
...supposed to be like this!
- Oh!
- Wow! That's cute!
What do you think?
It's the white of faithfulness!
White underwear is the best,
and the lace adds elegance!
Oh! This underwear is worthy of the Lord!
What underwear do you have, Asia?
- Huh?
- Hey! Pay attention!
Umm, I don't really--
Oh-ho...
Please don't stare so close-up like that!
Oh, sorry!
Your underwear's cute! It's perfect for you!
Huh. Pink's not so bad.
The president chose this
underwear for me. I really cherish it.
Ah! President Rias has a real knack for this!
She knew exactly what would suit you!
She said to use this as my "battle underwear."
That means all three of us
have battle underwear...
You both have nice underwear,
but mine's clearly the best.
White! Angel white!
Hmm. We should have a guy judge for us then.
Like who?
Well, there's Issei hiding
in that locker, for example.
Oh! Issei! I didn't know you were hiding there!
Sheesh. I can give you a peek
anytime you want, you know.
Eek!
I-I-Issei?!
Punishment! Divine punishment!
Amen!