I lost again!
Rossweisse-san, I can read the expressions on your face.
It's true, they're so obvious.
Even considering that it is your first time playing,
it's shocking how bad you are at Old maid.
It's been a while since we last visited Phenex house.
Eh? Yes, you're right...
Rias-sama,
I apologise for the sudden visit.
Actually,
I wanted to ask for your advice regarding my brother.
Riser...
so
no
mu
If you listen to the voice of your heart
You'll be born anew again and again
born
born
new
mo
u
ko
I can't hide it anymore
The purported salvation is but a mirror paradox
Trying to come to terms with myself
I realized my soul must lie with my wishes
The moment we met, the warmth of the tears
de
ta
shun
shun
ta
kan
shun
Falling off your palm ignited my heart
And we understood the DxD each other felt
I've been waiting
What's there to be gained amid all the despair?
It's not bliss but rather a good feeling
feel
feel
ing
so
no
mu
Until I reach deep inside your heart
I'll call out your name again and again
your
name
your
name
The Unresurrected Phoenix
You want to talk about Riser?
Yes.
I assume you've heard the stories about him.
Like, how he does nothing but mope about since that incident.
Riser?
I've heard the rumours, too...
Who is he?
He's from Phenex family
and Rias-oneesama's ex-fiancé.
Fiancé!? How romantic!
It sounds so noble!
Hang on. If he is her ex-fiancé, then...
You see,
Issei-san crashed their engagement party
and challenged Riser-san to a duel.
Issei-san won and he took back Rias-oneesama.
On the other hand,
Riser-san had never lost before, so...
Riser still hasn't recovered from that, right?
I probably shouldn't have come here, but...
I only have your place to turn to for this.
My place? What do you mean?
When I was asking for advise on how to help my brother,
I was told that he should learn the so called fortitude that Rias-sama's peerage possesses.
That is what your household is famous for.
Fortitude!?
Fortitude, huh...
A certain someone knows all about that.
More precisely...
He should be ashamed of himself!
I can't believe he's been sulking for half a year because of one loss.
He even says that he is afraid of Dragons!
Since then, he hasn't participated in a single rating game.
Gossip magazines have been writing whatever they want about him.
He got traumatized by one battle with Issei-sama,
and now he cannot touch anything that relates to Dragons.
I would understand if he was simply holding a grudge against Issei-sama.
He should man up and learn from the experience of that defeat and grow stronger.
It's really, really shameful!
But...
He's still my brother...
Don't worry, Ravel.
Eh?
I will do something about it.
Well, I am the reason behind it all.
He just needs to learn fortitude, right?
Leave it to me!
I'm all about fortitude.
So Ravel, don't worry about it anymore.
Well... If you absolutely insist...
I-I will accept your help Issei-sama.
Please work hard for a high-ranking devil.
I...
I would really appreciate it.
Understood.
Issei will be in charge of getting Riser out of his funk.
So huge!
I thought Buchou's house was big,
but it can't beat this one.
So, what does Riser... san...
What does he usually do all day?
He stays in his room all day running rating game simulations.
Occasionally he will summon people who are good at chess to play with him.
Onii-sama, you have guests.
Ravel?
I don't want to see anybody today.
I had a nightmare.
I don't feel like meeting anybody.
Your guest is Rias-sama.
R-Rias-dono!?
Riser, it's me.
Why have you come here after such a long time, Rias!?
Are you here to laugh at me?
Or maybe
you're here to brag about your
wonderful fulfilling life with the Sekiryuutei?
I want to talk with you for a bit.
Let me see your face.
What could you possibly want to talk about
with the man you rejected!?
Wha—!
Se-Se-Se-Se-Se-
Sekiryuutei!?
H-Hello. Good morning.
No!
P
Go home!
I don't want to be reminded of that time!
Such a miserable feeling...
I don't want to experience something like that ever again!
Is this really someone who has never lost a game since they was born?
For crying out loud...
Onii-sama!
Rias-sama took the time to come and see you.
Please stop hiding under your bed covers.
L-Leave me alone! Go home!
First of all, let's get him out of his room.
Stop! Stop!
What is this bullshit?
So, what's your plan?
He should be here any minute now.
It's been a while since I've seen you guys.
Old Man, thanks for coming!
Ta-Ta-Ta-Ta-
Tannin!
The ultimate-class devil and legendary dragon!
Riser Phenex, huh?
I used to watch you with great interest because I thought you were a promising king.
However, just looking at you now, you clearly have a serious problem.
Just like how we did it before,
can you help him with some training?
His family are saying that he needs to gain some fortitude.
Oh I see... Fortitude...
That's a good idea.
So you're coming to the mountains, huh?
N-No!
Stop running away!
If you are a man then prepare yourself.
Well then Buchou, we'll be going now!
Please make sure to contact me when you need help.
Yes, Buchou.
Take me with you!
I want...
I want to help with my brother's recovery!
Ravel...
That girl has good eyes.
Hyoudou Issei, why don't you take care of her in the mountains?
Issei, you have my permission.
Please take Ravel with you.
Rias-sama...
Okay!
Let's go, Ravel!
N-No!
Why do I have to go to the dragon's mountains!?
This is for your own good, Onii-sama!
Please go along with it.
No!
Wow, incredible!
D-D-
Dragons!
This area is the dragon's nest where my brethren live.
Tannin-sama, you called for me?
This is a high-level dragon who serves under me.
I've asked him to help take care of training Riser Phenex.
Wha—?
But, I can handle his training...
You won't be strict enough with him.
Riser Phenex, here in the mountains
we will train your body and soul from scratch.
Why is this happening?
Hyoudou Issei.
You should also do the training.
You'll start with running.
Of course...
Hey, hey! You're too slow!
You froze my fire!
Riser-dono, when you are running, you need to call out dragon!
Come on, say it! Come on, say it!
Onii-sama, you cannot give up at this level!
Dragon! Dragon! Dragon!
Come on, say it!
Dragon! Dragon!
itsP
Watching from here, he is just like an adventurer who is being attacked by a dragon in the mountains.
What the hell is happening!?
Hot springs are so nice.
I can feel the stress being washed away.
Why do you feel so much stress?
Well...
I devoted myself to my boss, yet he abandoned me and left me with nowhere to go.
I will never forget what he did.
My, my. So scary.
I wonder how Issei-san and the others are doing.
It seems we ended up letting Issei handle everything again, didn't we?
Well, I wouldn't worry just yet.
Maybe they're getting along just fine.
How fantastical it is to think about the Dragon and the Phenex training together in the mountains.
We can only hope.
I'm... I'm dying.
It hasn't been that long since we started training.
I am a pure high-ranking devil!
It's my duty to live by putting a higher value on my blood and my shrewdness!
That's how it is for high-ranking devils!
I simply cannot do boorish training like this!
Don't even think about running away.
Are... Are you trying to kill me!?
We are going to have a rocky road ahead.
It's been three days since the training started.
How's my brother doing?
Hmm...
I'm really not sure.
To be honest, I was just like him when I started training
with Old Man Tannin for the first time.
Oh!
I think he will be alright once he gets used to it.
You think so? That makes me feel relieved.
You must be cold.
Why are you wearing something like that?
I'm... I'm not cold at all!
It's only proper for a lady from a noble family to wear a dress to morning tea.
I-Is that so...
More importantly, these pancakes are delicious.
Do you really think so!?
I got everything from the dragons,
but there were some ingredients I couldn't find...
But I wasn't satisfied with how they turned out.
Yeah, why would I lie about that?
These are really good.
You make the best pancakes I've ever tasted.
O-Of course!
You can count yourself lucky that you get to eat my handmade pancakes.
You should be thankful.
Yeah, yeah.
What's with that attitude of yours?
Jeez, and I woke up so early this morning too...
Early in the morning?
N-No. I can make dozens of pancakes in a short amount of time.
I just happened to wake up early this morning.
Come to think of it,
I haven't properly thanked you yet.
Thanked me?
At the party, you gave me a vial of Phenex tears.
Oh that... That was just a token of our new acquaintanceship. It's nothing.
But without it, I would have been in serious trouble.
Thank you.
Is... Is that so?
Well, I'm glad to hear that it was useful.
Wh-What are you doing?
Hey, Ravel. If you went to a human school,
do you know what year you would be in?
Huh?
Fine, Just for you I will answer your question.
I would be a first year student if I went to a human high school.
First year!? You're my junior then!
Despite that, her body is already filling out nicely.
It looks like her breasts are even bigger than Asia's, who is in her second year.
At some point, I'd like to try on the Kuoh Academy uniform.
Eh?
Oh good idea! You should try one on.
I bet you'd look great in one.
Of course!
It is me that we're talking about.
C-Can I visit your clubroom again in the near future?
Of course! Please do!
Why don't you stop by my place along the way?
Th-Then, I will visit without any reserve!
After all, it is also a high-ranking devil's job to learn about the ordinary life of humans.
Oh by the way, I heard that Rias-sama and the others will be up here in the mountains tonight.
Buchou and the others?
Yes, apparently there is a nice hot spring around here.
A hot spring!?
A hot spring...
Buchou and others are currently bathing...
This means I have a chance to see boobs while on this mountain.
I must go! To the hot spring!
Given the situation, I need to be sneaky so that Riser won't notice.
He has been surprisingly quiet.
Usually he's always complaining...
Oh crap! He must have been listening to my conversation with Ravel while he was training!
Riser must be on his way to the hot spring.
I can't let him see Buchou's, Asia's, Akeno-san's, and everybody else's tits.
Damn it! Where is he!?
There he is!
Crap! He found me!
Were you planning to peek inside the hot spring!?
What's wrong with that!?
It's a gentleman's duty to peek inside a hot spring when there are women bathing!
Is that what someone from a noble family would do!?
Your attack is sharper than the last time we fought.
But do you think you can beat me in an aerial battle?
Stop being a hindrance Sekiryuutei!
I want to see Rias's tits!
I cannot stand the fact that only you get to enjoy them!
There's no way I'll let you see them!
Buchou's tits are mine!
I am her ex-fiancé!
Do you think I would give up before I could enjoy those big tits of hers!?
Put yourself in my position!
I understand how you feel.
No, no. That doesn't matter!
Just how perverted are you!?
You've managed to recover just from the idea of being able to see tits!?
Who said you lack fortitude!?
You have more than enough!
You have more fortitude at being a pervert than me!
Don't compare yourself to me.
By the way, Rias's queen should also be there...
I want to see the Priestess of Thunder's tits, too.
They're huge, aren't they!?
Akeno-san's tits!?
I will never let you see them!
Her huge tits are only for me!
Stop being ridiculous!
Let me see them too!
You stop being ridiculous!
You're being unreasonable!
You bird-brained idiot!
You're the one who's an idiot!
Akeno-san's tits are mine!
We'll relax in the hot spring tonight
and check in with Issei tomorrow.
My, my. Then we should clean our bodies really well.
I have heard that the water from this hot spring is really good for your skin.
Is that so?
My womanly power may increase even more.
Oh, we might be committing a sin by becoming even more beautiful.
Please forgive us Michael-sama.
Listen up everybody.
Don't get too carried away and neglect your homework.
A student's job is to study after all.
Everyone has such developed bodies.
We'll bloom soon enough.
You've become so much stronger.
I should have the advantage in an aerial battle.
I'm surprised to see how well you're doing.
It scares me to think of what you will become, Sekiryuutei.
Thanks for the compliment.
But that doesn't mean that I'm about to give up.
Oh crap, I didn't realize how close we've come to the hot spring.
I can't make a ruckus out here
or else I'll lose the chance to peak inside the hot spring.
Of course...
Ah! Buchou's bare breasts!
Breasts!?
Gotcha!
Damn it! I kicked him too hard!
Yes! I won, again!
Oh wait, wasn't I was supposed to help him get over his fear?
Oh well...
Protecting Buchou's boobs is more important!
Issei?
Buchou?
I heard a loud noise so I was wondering who it was.
So it was you.
My, my. Issei-kun?
Issei-sama, did you come to see us?
A-Asia!?
Have you come here to peek at us?
I'm impressed, Issei.
Peeping Tom! You're the worst!
I-Issei-kun!? You need to confess your sin!
I can't get married any more!
Onii-sama?
Issei-sama!?
I knew your body would be fully developed.
And your breasts are amazing!
Issei-sama, you...
Pervert!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
What a disaster.
It's lucky that you're immortal.
Of course, we're made of sterner stuff compared to low-ranking devils like you.
Oh, is that so...
Well, to be honest...
It was a good kick, considering you're a mere low-ranking devil.
Rias has a good pawn.
Riser-san...
I will give up Rias.
You're...
Therefore,
let me see Rias's tits just one time!
Don't be ridiculous, you damned Grilled Chicken!
I'm a high-ranking devil who is giving up pursuing a woman in exchange for one glance.
So, let me see Rias's tits!
You really are my enemy after all!
You stole my line!
What are you implying, you Grilled Chicken!?
You are such a cheapskate! Cheapryuutei!
Cheapskate! Cheapskate!
Riser Phenex. He looks fine now.
Yes.
Issei. Thank you.
sou daitai no koto nante
Well, yeah, I do think that
mou wakatte wa iru na tte
I've got this stuff mostly figured out
omou yo dakedo ne
But still, you know
kokoro wa bannou ja nai
Feelings on their own can only get you so far
daiji na koto bakka ishin fudenshin
The stuff that matter isn't getting across
saishuuteki ni wa analog tsuushin
So we have to rely on analog communication
dakara ima sugu
That's why, right now
motto chanto katachi ni shite yo
I want you to be more concrete
kimi ga
Do it
ijiwaru na voice
With your flirty voice
give me kikasete yo
Give me, just tell me
chotto dake de ii no
Just a little hint is fine
aimai na no wa yada na
Don't leave me hanging
no secret sansei
No secrets, yeah?
do you do you know
Do you know?
answer todokete ne
Give me your answer
kowaku nante nai shi
I'm not afraid to hear it
ienai kedo nee wakaru desho
I don't have to actually tell you, right?
wakatte yo
Take the hint
tell me heart tell me heart
Tell me your heart
subete wo kaeru no wa
If you want to take it to the next step
give me word give me word
Give me your word
itsu de mo kimi dakara
The power is in your hands