Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
With high hopes, humans
leave Earth...
...to begin a new life in
the space colonies.
But the United Earth Sphere
Alliance gains military power...
...and in the name of
Justice and Peace...
...seizes control of one
colony after the other.
The year is After Colony 195.
Operation Meteor.
To counter the Alliance's
tyranny, rebel colonists...
...bring new arsenals
to the Earth...
...disguising them as
shooting stars.
But the Alliance headquarters
catches on to this operation.
I'd like you to leave the room
now, Vice Foreign Minister.
Isn't it about time you
people realized...
...that you're posing the
greatest threat of all!
Silence! We've had enough!
Heero!
I'm right over here so
hurry and come kill me!!
Relena's Secret
Vice Foreign Minister Darlian.
I hope this'll be a very
successful trip for you.
Nothing wrong with a little
socializing is there?
I have nothing to discuss
with a Specials officer.
Pretty harsh words, Minister.
I'm just here on orders
from my superiors.
Don't take out your
frustrations on me.
Relena.
Look carefully.
Never forget how beautiful
the Earth looks from afar.
You'll never see it again,
Darlian.
What are you sighing about;
something bothering you?
The colonies are amidst
a beautiful sea of stars.
So why is it they don't
seem to sparkle?
Don't you agree?
No.
I don't agree with you at all.
Relena's in the colonies
this very moment.
They should be sparkling
much brighter than usual!
Target: North Pacific Ocean,
OZ supply base.
Roger that mission.
Mr. Darlian!
So rumors of Earth's chronic
financial crisis are false.
Otherwise you couldn't afford to
take a shuttle for yourselves.
I only wish that were
the only rumor.
The latest false rumors
throughout the Alliance...
...are much more grave.
The rumors that we're planning
an attack against Earth?
How absurd!
Nothing good could result
from our attacking them.
The purpose of this visit
is to find out for ourselves...
...whether or not those
rumors are accurate.
Let's hope there's no
truth to them.
How could Earthlings think the
peaceful, courteous colonists...
...would want to start a war?
How could they?
Excuse me, Miss Une.
You don't have diplomatic
authorization from Earth.
I really can't allow you
to sit in on this meeting.
I understand.
But I'd like to know the
outcome of the meeting.
- Of course.
- Fine.
Then I'll excuse myself.
Ten minutes.
That's when it all ends;
or rather when it begins.
It's Relena.
Yes?
I'm going out shopping.
Be careful out there.
I'll get you an escort.
No, don't bother.
It's much safer here
than it is on Earth.
She must've forgotten this.
These accusations are unjust!
We've never heard of this
Project Meteor...
...or the new type
of mobile suit.
Mr. Darlian.
Why does the Alliance find
it difficult to believe us?
Ten more seconds.
Excuse me, ma'am!
Here; I think you forgot this.
You idiot!
Father!!
That was a close call.
Go after the girl and kill her
if she tries to resist!
Right!
Father!
Where are you, Father?!!
Relena...
Father!!
Is Mr. Darlian okay?
Huh?
Well?!
No other survivors!
Who are you people?!
We'll just take Mr. Darlian!
Right!
Stop!
What're you doing?!
Move!
Someone's taken Darlian's
daughter and is escaping!
Block the exits!
Let go of me!
You'll come with us!
Otherwise you'll get killed!
I don't care if I do.
What're you doing
with my father?!
Just do as we say
for the time being.
Get in!
Are you hurt?!
This injection should
help you relax.
Get Father to the hospital!
Or else he'll die!
The hospital's too risky!
No!
They're probably already
guarding the hospitals.
We have good doctors
in our organization.
Who are you people, anyway?
Relena...
Father...
Listen to me, Relena...
Don't try to talk!
Lie still!
I'm not your biological
father.
Huh?!
Your real name is
Relena Peacecraft.
You're the daughter of
the Peacecraft family...
...who once advocated
Complete Pacifism.
What're you saying?
I'm a senator who served
their country in the past.
But long ago the kingdom was
demolished by the Alliance.
I took you in as my
daughter when I escaped.
That's not true!
Watch out for the
OZ organization.
Father...
Father!!
NOOOOO!
The medication's working.
She's asleep.
The mobile suit's repaired.
Thanks pal; I owe you one!
No problem, as long as
I get paid.
You're an excellent client.
We made it just in time
for my next mission.
You leaving?
I won't stop you.
But at least tell me
what your name is.
My name's Quatre
Raberba Winner.
I have no name.
But if you must call me
something, then Trowa.
Call me Trowa Barton.
Thank you, Trowa.
We'll meet again.
Master Quatre.
Should we let him go like this?
He knows the location
of this base...
I wouldn't worry.
He's not the talkative type.
He could attack!
I almost wish he would.
Then at least I'd be
able to see him again.
Nothing to report.
Roger.
What a drag; boring guard
duty for two whole hours.
Hey, is something wrong?
No problems.
Everything's in order.
Now to get to the target
point for my mission.
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
I'm counting on you, Otto.
Don't worry about a thing.
The staff here is skilled.
I'll make sure it gets completed.
Are you sure this 20 year-old
suit is gonna be useful to us?
It's probably more advanced
than any OZ mobile suit...
...that's currently available.
You're kidding.
No way.
It's true.
This Tallgeese suit is the
prototype for all mobile suits.
Even those Gundams were built
based on this Tallgeese design.
The Gundams?
Father!
You're awake.
I'm terribly sorry for
your loss.
If only we'd become aware
of the situation earlier...
...we could've avoided
this tragedy.
Lady Une, any comments on
this terrible accident?!
I'm saddened by what has
happened here today.
I had no idea there were such
evil terrorists in this colony.
We're told that Vice Foreign
Minister Darlian...
...and his daughter
were kidnapped.
We're investigating the
situation ourselves.
We're unaware of the
terrorists' true objectives...
...but if this reflects the
feelings of the whole colony...
...we'll be forced to take
military action.
W- Wait a minute, Lieutenant
Colonel Une!
Excuse me.
I'm conducting a terrorist
investigation.
Damn it!
She's made us out to be
a bunch of terrorists!
That's just what you are!
My father died because you
didn't take him to the hospital!
I told you, the hospital...
Enough already!
I'm terribly sorry for
what happened.
What?!
I'll get revenge for his death.
OZ did it, right?
OZ killed my father, right?
Don't be stupid!
You'll just end up
getting killed!
It's suicide!
I don't care if I do get killed.
I'll kill you.
Stop it!
Why do you wanna
shoot him?!
No need to apologize Father.
I'm old enough to understand
how important your business is.
Heero...I want to
see you, Heero.
Heero, you say?
Now!
Let me go!
You don't mean
Heero Yuy, do you?
Do you know him?!
That was some performance
by Lady Une.
What happened to Mr. Darlian?
He was killed.
Relena...
Still worried aren't you, Zechs.
Worried about what?
Open up your heart.
You're hiding too many secrets.
Commander!
We're detecting an
enormous heat...
...and two guard Leos
have disappeared!
Enemies?!
It might be a Gundam!
Prepare all mobile suits
for combat!
Yes, sir!
Visibility is poor.
I can't confirm anything.
A Gundam!
Please feel free to call me
Dr. J, young lady.
Believe it or not,
I'm a scientist.
Dr. J.
You're the one that sent
Heero to Earth, aren't you?
That's right.
But who in their right mind
would've thought...
...he'd end up in the same
school as Darlian's daughter?!
How's that rascal doing?
What a kid!
What are you trying
to get him to do?
That young lad is an
agent of ours.
An agent?
Since Heero was young,
we've taught him...
...a wide range of combat
strategies.
We brought him up as
a professional assassin.
Why do that?!
Don't you see?
For the peace of the colonies,
of course.
That's crazy!
Killing can't possibly
lead us to peace!
It leads directly to peace!
Wars are started by people
and they end with people.
Heero's ordered to attack
the dangerous, evil people...
...responsible for
starting wars.
But there must be more
peaceful solutions!
Twenty years ago, we
believed that ourselves.
We thought mankind
couldn't be so foolish.
That no one could possibly
wish for a war.
The colonies were started
by scientists like myself...
...and by laborers.
Our ancestors did everything
they could to form the colonies.
After over 100 years
of hard work...
...we enjoyed a normal
lifestyle.
And exactly twenty years ago,
we were living peacefully...
...under the ruler of
all colonies, Heero Yuy.
Heero Yuy?
His name still lives on
today as a legend...
...among the residents
of our colonies.
That's where we came up
with the lad's code name.
His code name?
Peaceful times in the colonies
didn't last for long.
They must've felt a leader
promoting peace was dangerous.
Heero Yuy was assassinated
by some organization.
From then on, communication
ceased between the colonies...
...and it became an excuse to
fortify the Alliance Military.
OZ was responsible
for the assassination...
...and wanted to wage
a war in the Earth Sphere.
OZ?!
Do you know OZ?
That was the last thing
my father said.
To watch out for OZ.
So who are you making
Heero fight?
All of OZ.
We must stop their ambitions...
...to take over the United
Alliance Military...
...and dictate the Earth Sphere.
But, why does Heero have
to take on that enormous task?
Why should he be responsible
for doing all that by himself?
We have no choice.
He understands the emotional
pains that the colony residents...
...have endured over the years.
Still!
It looks like we're after
the same thing.
Well, aren't you gonna
at least respond?
Locked on target.
Seems like the two of us will
have to fight it out after all.
They should be able to return
you safely to Earth from here.
Why did you help me out?
Is it because of my father?
Because I'm his daughter?
Not at all.
It's because you had the same
look in your eyes as Heero did.
That genuine expression.
Heero's actually a kind-hearted
young boy.
I know.
But Heero's very dedicated
to his mission.
Stay away from him
if you value your life.
I've returned the favor.
Damn you!
I'll get you!
Father...
I'll always be your daughter.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Thrown into a new,
uncertain destiny...
...Relena returns to the Earth.
What awaits her is
a school party...
...and notice of Heero's
transfer.
Knowing Heero's secret,
Relena figures out...
...that the transfer is related
to his next mission.
OZ assassins come for Relena,
and Heero ends up saving her.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 6,
Party Night
"Party Night".