I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Let's see...
Now, now, now... Okay.
My name is Takenaka.
Masahiro Takenaka.
What's your name?
Why do you want to know that?
It doesn't seem right
for you to stay nameless. That's all.
Though I don't mind
calling you "bro".
Hey, baby! I didn't know
you wanted to die so badly!
Volunteering for suicide,
are you?
Were you born in Tokyo?
Well, yeah.
I was born in Adachi.
Do you go to Shinjuku a lot?
Oh, is L'Etoile still there?
I heard they tore down
the Nichigeki theater.
I remember, after a demonstration
march we had at the JNR...
...I went there
to watch "Abashiri Bangaichi".
Do you know it?
It's a film starring Mr. Ken.
It was following our fight with
the riot police.
I went there as-is, in my black helmet,
war-stick outfit.
I was so young back then.
Do you miss Japan?
Well, let me ask you why you're
crossing this dangerous bridge, bro.
I don't imagine it's to put food
on your plate.
There aren't a lot of folks
who'd do this...
...seeing that Japan's full of
petit bourgeoisies these days.
If you ask me, at this point...
...you and I are both outsiders
of that country.
You know...
I feel empathy towards you.
I wanna know why you've chosen
to become an adventurer.
I'm... I'm different from you.
Please don't group me
with people like you!
Oh? How are you different?
I wasn't chased out or anything.
But you're different.
You were forced into a corner,
and you escaped.
I'm young,
but I know what you've done.
Bro, I left Japan...
...having gambled everything on
human activism...
...and complete,
worldwide revolution.
When you have a will and a mission,
it's not called losing.
Do you have anything about you
like that, bro?
If there's a difference between us,
that's where it is.
I have that sort of thing as well.
I wonder. A resolution
and a mission are synonymous.
Then what about you? You don't
have a mission any more, do you?
Or at least,
you no longer believe in it.
- Hey bro...
- Cut it out, Takenaka!
Even I understand that this
Japanese conversation...
...has nothing to do
with the interrogation!
Okay, listen up, Japanese guy.
I'm not as kind as this man.
We don't have time.
Where are the documents?!
- We're gonna walk from here.
- Can't we keep driving there by car?
I don't wanna charge in on them in this
piece of crap, with a junkie at the wheel.
How dare you! This is the
world's greatest four-wheeler, you bitch!
I'm already sick of being stuck
with a drunkard.
Listen up, you fucking Irish.
Wait here until you get the signal.
If you run away,
I'll hunt you down and kill you.
My! She says some good things!
I agree intensely.
Like hell I will!
Anyway, don't overdo it.
I don't want you drugged up
when we make a run for it.
It's unnecessary to worry about this guy
when it comes to that, yes it is.
Even with his brain off to Mars,
his driving is never affected.
Let's go, "yes it is" lady.
Do you prefer your ass
be split in four?!
It's not nice to make fun of others.
You rotten bitch.
I heard this story a long time ago.
It's about a man
who came to a city.
He went to a street corner,
and all alone, he began preaching.
"To make the world a better place"...
...that man kept preaching,
day after day.
At first many expressed interest
in what the man had to say.
Some even said they would
fight alongside him.
But then, gradually,
they all lost interest.
To them, it didn't matter
what happened to this world.
But the man didn't stop.
Even as he aged, with not a single soul
listening to him, he continued.
Then one day, a child who was
walking by asked him...
..."Why do you continue preaching
when there's nobody here?"
The man answered, " I thought I could
change everyone in the beginning."
"Then I realized that it was
a hopeless dream."
"But the reason
I won't stop preaching..."
The reason I won't
stop fighting is, bro...
Back then,
I gambled my whole life on that.
And I don't wanna have
that become a lie.
Well, well... It seems that you
and I really are different, bro. Sorry.
How much shall
we hurt him, Takenaka?
It won't be necessary.
He's not a soldier, just a delivery boy.
He has no reason to be loyal.
Leave him alone and he'll talk.
If he doesn't talk by morning,
well, we are soldiers, after all.
We'll have to pass an informal court
hearing and send him to the firing squad.
Tomorrow? Every minute that passes
is hurting us!
We're on the brink of determining
whether or not the plan goes ahead.
- Don't you understand, Takenaka?
- Don't be so tense, Ibraha.
If not him, we'll go after
the girl we left at the village.
She might just come waltzing in here
to save him. Right?
Three at the west gate.
Six at the east gate.
Only a 50-caliber at the front.
Any mines?
No. The camp is always moving.
That would be too much trouble.
We should hurry, though.
If your dumbass partner talks,
we'd suffer a great loss.
Don't worry.
He's tight-lipped.
He won't talk even if
the judge's trumpets sound.
Let's move in when the sun sets.
You ready, "yes it is" lady?
Absolutely. But remember,
when this is over...
...I'll carve some meat off your ass.
You whore.
Damn it!
Takenaka!
Oh, sorry for calling you,
but there's something bothering me.
I received the reports of the teams
investigating Thailand!
The other three were blanks!
That Japanese has the key!
Your actions are interfering with the plan,
you know! Takenaka!
You... You know very well
why this is so important to me.
Hey. What happened with the team
we sent into the city?
Don't change the subject, Takenaka!
I'm not changing the subject.
How many hours has it been
since the search group left?
- Why haven't they reported back?
- That's because...
And the surveillance team
at the government camp.
That woman hasn't been
found anywhere.
In that case,
where is she?
What? Feels so good
you can't pull the trigger?
Though men know all about stabbing...
...they usually haven't experienced
being stabbed.
I'm getting started, too!
Revy?
Revy! I'm in here!
Revy!
Baby, baby.
Have you been a good boy?
If you promise to behave
a little longer, sweetie-pie...
...I'll even buy you some licorice candy.
So, let's get the hell outta here.
- Oh? Is this the dumbass?
- Who the hell is she?
Here's your change.
Rock! Hurry up!
- Rock, come up with a strategy!
- What are you talking about? Just run!
Okay, that's a good plan!
Get going!
Whaaaat?
I have no plans to go anywhere.
It's your turn to do your job!
Now, get this damn thing moving!
Oh! I forgot!
I must go to Liverpool!
It's no use now.
He's super relaxed.
Jimi Hendrix is calling me!
He's telling me to defeat the Klingons!
C-Captain Picard!
Hey! Wait!
You're going the wrong way!
Stop being an idiot! You've brought us
smack into the middle of enemy territory!
Damn. Guess there's
no choice now!
Those crazy bastards.
All units! After them! Go after
those guys that just came through!
Make sure you get them!
Corner them and kill them! Follow me!
- Rash behavior won't get you anywhere.
- You shut up.
Anyway, seeing that Rock
hasn't snapped yet...
...I take that to mean the enemy's
not much of an opponent.
No.
Look at that. Those fools are
coming after us in herds.
Oh, that's perfect.
- Damn it!
- I understand how you feel, but Ibraha...
I have a mission I've been
trying to accomplish for years.
I won't let that damn gangster ruin it!
Damn. Damn. Damn.
What's with him?
Here they come.
Revy. I talked
to that Japanese guy. And...
Rock, paper, scissors!
I lost, damn it!
I get leftovers.
See you later.
It's my turn after you take out two cars!
Did you say something?
No, never mind.
Here I come!
I'm gonna fly now!
- What are you doing?!
- Look!
Hey! You idiot!
I said don't kill them all!
The left! I get the left,
you take the right!
Stop it!
There's no room up here!
Spread out! Watch out so you don't
hit any obstacles! After them!
Hey, look!
What?
Rachel Welch and Jane Fonda
are in a footrace!
- Oh. Really.
- Stay down!
- You're in my way!
- Damn you!
Where in the world
are you luring me to?!
Could it be... Could it be...
The legendary nudist beach?!
Dutch, there are only thirty minutes
until the time limit.
Are you able to keep
your ass relaxed in your seat?
Oh, I see.
No, not really. You're free to use any
means necessary. That's fine with me.
It's me, Mr. CIA. Yeah,
right on schedule. Don't worry.
Cut it out with your lousy jokes.
How about the money?
I don't take American Express.
Let me know when you get it. Later.
- What did Hong Kong say?
- Sir.
"You may take the law into your
own hands as deemed necessary."
"Just don't let things get too dirty."
In other words,
avoid fighting them head-on.
That's a tall order.
Well, for now all we can do
is wish the delivery boys luck.
We'll start over!
Rock, Paper, Scissors again?
We haven't got time for that.
Here they come!
Barbarella's holding up
an anti-war placard in the nude!
We'll kill them all!
But they have too much range on us
for your weapon. Stay back!
Guess I've got no choice.
Let's see what you've got.
Smartass.
This'll make your eyes roll.
Damn it!
Take this!
Oh, she's not all talk, I see.
Nice going.
If we had an M72 or a M242 this
would have been a lot easier to finish off.
Stupid. Cannons and guns
run out of ammo.
But the blade and body
never malfunction.
They're the best weapons
in the world.
Don't be dumb. Knives can chip.
Guns over swords.
Nuclear bombs over guns.
Now, if we had one of those,
it would be awesome.
But they're designed so that only
politicians can get their hands on them.
Shit!
There's something wrong
with your head, you know.
A bakery will sell you bread. Criminals
only use such weapons for criminal acts.
What?! Peace Work is only open
to the first three people?!
Gimme a break. Rock.
Have some of this. It'll calm you down.
Sure.
That's right! Go after them
with all the base's vehicles!
Even if you cross the DMZ border,
don't hesitate!
Charge in
and get the documents!
- Stop it! The troops will all die!
- Give that back!
Ibraha! We have a job to do! Ibraha!
Ibraha!
Shut up!
You know it! No matter what you do,
or how you do things...
...your son is never coming back.
DMZ, right?! The camp should be
visible any time now.
How are you feeling, Rock?
Having fun yet?
How should I put it? Running away
like this always makes it worse.
I feel like I've been running away
like this since kindergarten.
- It's over.
- Oh, it's affected him the wrong way.
Oops, I screwed up. He's such a
positive guy, so I thought he'd be okay.
That's not enough. The mood
at the time is just as important.
When I talked to the old guy
I acted high and mighty.
Now that I think about it,
I tend to blab all I want...
...then talk myself outta
the situation.
Hey, look!
Here we go again.
What is it this time?
Playmates! There are one hundred
Playmates, starting from 1990!
It's an attack of the Playmates Army!
Commander! An unknown vehicle
has entered the DMZ! Permission to fire!
Number Three Bunker!
That's a guest! Do not fire!
All bunkers and guards!
That is not the enemy!
Our job is not a profession.
It's our way of life, isn't it, Takenaka?
And there are times when
we cannot give in!
Ibraha.
The scoundrels in Jerusalem and
those that protect them...
...are all finally within reach!
I'll show them what the Red Cross
camp in Beirut was like in '87!
That's why I've come this far!
Commander! Orders, please!
Keep after the enemy!
Charge into the government camp!
We must retreat! Stop!
Don't lose focus on our goal
because of our cause!
"Because of our cause," Takenaka?
But isn't that the whole reason
we've been fighting?!
Isn't that why you came
to the Beqaa Valley?!
Answer me, Takenaka!
To all units. Retreat from
your present positions.
Do not return to camp. Make your way
to the secondary gathering point.
Roger!
You and I were both
only looking at our past.
As long as we kept doing so,
nothing ever changed. But...
Although none of it matters now,
you were a good comrade.
Such a tragic story,
don't you think, Ibraha?
Has the launderer's
delivery boy arrived yet?!
You're late, Langley boys!
Langley's been busy!
There are too many bastards
shitting on freedom and justice!
So, where's this thing
that's supposed to get us excited?!
- Crap! The briefcase!
- What?!
I don't have the briefcase!
Revy! We're in trouble!
Don't panic. If Harry Houdini
rubs the magic lamp...
Here!
Just like that!
What the...
Then why did we have
to save this dumbass?!
You guys wouldn't have agreed to come
unless I said he had it.
It's all wrinkled and sweaty.
Okay then! Thanks! Next time, deliver it
in a more decent manner, will ya?
Otherwise the boss will be pissed!
Oh, and Miss Rebecca!
If the chief at Buffalo Hill and the NYPD
27th Precinct heard about you now...
...they'd shit their pants!
Damn it.
Don't get me wrong!
Our job is to destroy enemies
of the United States!
We're not being paid
to chase criminals!
It's just a little something
for you to think about...
...for someday when we bring you
your next job! Bye!
Hey, Revy.
I haven't thanked you yet. Um...
Thanks.
You're being ridiculous!
There's no need to be so formal
with each other.
By the way, Rock...
Oh my...
What the hell are you
babbling about?!
I'm never doing you any favors
like that again, you pea brain!
All costs associated with rescuing you
are coming outta your paycheck!
If you wanna be saved again, next time
you'd better ask God to do the favors!
Gimme a break.
Hello, Mr. Ken.
What a coincidence.
Oh, hello, Mr. "Excuse Me".
How was your vacation?
We had a great time.
How did things go with you?
Boy, it was a pain. The trade
fell through, and I hurt my hip.
And then, I ended up leaving a
close friend after having a fight...
...and I even tried pushing what
I couldn't accomplish onto the young.
It was one unpleasant situation after
another. I feel like I'm getting old.
But there'll be a next time.
Of course, there'll always be
a next time, until I die.
There will always
be a next time. Bye.
By the way, mister,
what is it you do?
My job?
Let's see. Yeah, it's finally
clear to me now.
My job is to be
an enemy of the state.
Next Episode
Vampires?
Those words have something
to do with vampires.