Maximum Titillation OVA Vol. 6
Rossweisse's True Teaching Story!
Makeup Test
Underway
I can't believe an Occult Research Club
member needs a makeup test.
Err, well, things have been so crazy lately...
All the other members have top grades, though.
S-Sorry...
If he does poorly on this,
he'll be held back a year!
As his teacher, I have to make sure he passes!
You can do it, Rossweisse!
Oh, whoops.
"Eraser Grab"
"Upskirt Peek"
"Issei Aroused"
"Dress Break"
"Held Back a Year"
No!
I-I'll pick it up!
C-Can't breathe...
Wh-What's the big idea?!
You're the one who did this!
It's hot. I'm going to open a window.
All right.
"Window Open"
"Skirt Blown"
"Issei Aroused"
"Dress Break"
"Held Back a Year"
No! Opening windows isn't allowed!
Huh? But I already opened it.
No! Close it! Close it!
Oh no!
Aah! Pull me up!
Hold on, Ma'am! I'll help you up!
"Help Up"
"Dress Break"
"Held Back a Year"
- No! Don't help me after all!
- Huh?! Make up your mind!
- Hurry and get away from me!
- Don't move!
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Rossweisse. You have a thread on you.
Huh? Where?
Here.
See?
Uhh... Huh?
Oh!
No!
Oh, err, umm...
I'll never get married now
that I've been seen like this!
No, I don't think that's true...
I'll never get married!