Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
People in space have
lost all reason.
That's why I'm gonna
destroy everything.
Quatre.
I'm not leaving.
Here's a colony that
needs to be defended.
Trowa!
The five of us have become
redundant soldiers.
The Eternal Flame of the Shooting Stars
Carriers are in the
atmosphere and approaching.
Their target is obviously
this base!
Must be the new models.
Do you think they're
all mobile dolls?
Probably.
They're not sending many
to crush this base.
But we're the Treize Faction.
We can't be defeated.
Operation Nova.
Upon completion of their
mobile doll assembly line...
...the Romefeller Foundation
sends mobile dolls to Earth...
...to eliminate the
Treize Faction.
To gain complete control
on Earth...
...they attack areas with
any chance of retaliation...
...and force people to
obey the Foundation.
Get as close as possible...
...before they use their
beam cannons!
That's our only way to win!
Enemy approaching!
Charge!
Operation Nova!
Space has a bad habit of
sending menaces to Earth.
The Romefeller Foundation...
...produced the unmanned
suits called mobile dolls...
...to increase its power
as it took over the world.
However, a voice
within the Foundation...
...denounced the use
of mobile dolls.
The voice of OZ's leader,
Treize Khushrenada.
Duke Dermail.
I can't support the Romefeller
Foundation in its current path.
What?!
Tradition is a kind of history.
It's the history of sympathy,
built on people's true feelings.
I think fighting in wars
can indeed be beautiful.
I'd also like to express my
regret over the lost souls...
...by appealing to how
priceless man's life is.
Treize objected to battles
that employed mobile dolls...
...and therefore made humans
unnecessary.
So he thought to dissolve OZ.
However, with the desire
to maintain their force...
...the higher powers within
Romefeller...
...tried to resolve the
situation by confining Treize.
This resulted in encouraging
some OZ soldiers...
...who also disagreed with
the mobile dolls, to unite.
They called themselves
the "Treize Faction"...
...and rose against the
Foundation's plan to rule.
Is that so?
I see it won't be easy
dealing with the soldiers...
...who respect Colonel Treize.
Damn Treize!
We've got more important
things to do!
Tubarov.
We'll have to increase
production...
...of mobile dolls for Earth.
Not to worry.
Things are going smoothly
here in space.
We've managed to capture
the new Gundams...
...and their pilots.
I shall destroy them
here at the Lunar Base.
It's possible that the
Gundams are being used...
...as a symbol for the rebels.
Tubarov, get rid of them.
Yes, sir.
Things can only get worse
by confining Colonel Treize.
Our opposition must
be eliminated.
That's the easiest and
best way to deal with this.
Get out!
Stop!
Trowa!
I'm the one who did
this to you.
Forgive me, Trowa.
Damn you!
We have permission from
Commander Tubarov...
...to execute you Gundam
pilots!
Try that again and you can
kiss your butt good-bye!
Heero!
So you'd prefer to die here?!
The Treize Faction?!
He's caught up with
all the targets.
He's very rapid.
His reaction speed
surpasses all expectations.
Keep testing.
I'm increasing the
simulation level.
Lieutenant Trant.
Commander Tubarov
is on the line.
Right.
Commander!
This cockpit system penetrates
the pilot's brain waves...
...and increases his
combat abilities.
Our test pilot is reacting...
...as quick as the mobile dolls.
Then you haven't listened
to my orders, Trant.
The orders I issued were
to destroy that Gundam.
Because of Lady Une's revolt...
...the five Gundam engineers
are now hiding within the base.
I can't have you wasting
your time!
But sir!
I'm convinced this system
could be utilized...
...with the OZ mobile suits!
We could use this
Gundam's system!
Our purpose here is to
eradicate the Gundams!
What's the point of depending
on its system?!
Erase the Gundams from
the universe!
Follow my orders!
Commander Tubarov is betting
everything on the mobile dolls.
Our hands are tied.
What shall we do now,
Lieutenant Trant?
Scrapping it will be simple.
But first I'd like to have
one piece of data.
The data on the pilots...
...that can fight as well
as the mobile dolls.
Good.
His brain waves haven't
been affected.
What does this test determine?
We're checking how the
cockpit system of Wing Zero...
...influences the pilot's
brain waves.
No problem!
That system is flawless.
A decision was made by
the Romefeller Foundation...
...to confine Treize
Khushrenada.
As a result, OZ's forces
have split into two factions.
Lady Une has been shot.
We don't know whether
she's dead or alive.
But Romefeller regards
her as an offender.
The other two pilots, Duo
Maxwell and Wu Fei Chang...
...escaped during OZ's
internal unrest.
But both of their Gundams
are still only 80% complete.
They only need minor
adjustments, though.
With a little time those two
pilots can probably finish...
...the Gundams themselves.
How about Trowa Barton?
He's been MIA since
the Vayeate was destroyed.
Probably dead.
The possibility of his
surviving is very low.
Our force will be diminished.
But that can't be helped.
And that's our current
situation.
Did you get all that, Heero?
Got it.
Now I'll explain the Treize
Faction on this base.
Wait a minute!
Please look into Trowa
Barton's whereabouts!
I know he's alive!
There are lots of colonies
in that area!
I know he'd be able
to survive!
That's some personality...
A little questionable for
a soldier.
That's why the Gundam Zero
ended up in enemy hands...
...even with that system
installed.
What?!
The system amplifies
and controls...
...brain waves for fighting.
It also brings battle
results...
...greater than the pilot
could normally ever achieve.
It would've been okay if
the pilot saw OZ as the enemy.
But the mind-warping side
effects...
...caused a target error.
The pilot was incomplete
as a soldier...
...so he attacked his
very own allies.
Extremely regrettable.
Especially since the Vayeate,
Mercurius and new Gundam...
...could've demolished
the Lunar Base at once.
Because of your training...
...your athletic abilities and
tactical imagination...
...are brought to perfection.
But as soldiers you're
far from perfect, mentally.
This latest incident has
made that flaw very clear.
You must become
perfect soldiers!
Otherwise you won't survive...
...the golden age
of the mobile dolls.
Or if you'd rather, go insane!
That's what wars do to people!
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
What's your opinion of
the Wing Zero system?
I have no idea.
I never knew that unit
had been completed.
I was focusing on
the large beam cannon...
...and didn't pay attention
to the cockpit system.
The beam cannon hasn't
been retrieved yet.
The main weapons...
...are the beam saber and
wing vulcans on its shoulders.
Are you planning to
fight Heero?
In either case we can't leave
Gundam Zero...
...in enemy hands.
Heero.
I've been wondering
who our allies are...
...and who our enemies
are in this war.
I get confused thinking
about it.
Quatre...
The ones after your life...
...and the targets you try
to defeat are the enemy.
But what if you
were mistaken?
Quatre.
We're not mistaken.
But it's possible that this
period of war has gone nuts.
They've located the gates
to Blocks A and B!
A large number of soldiers
are headed this way!
Members of the Treize Faction.
We've surrounded your hideout.
I have reservations about
fighting former comrades...
...without talking things
over first.
We can avoid futile bloodshed.
We're completely surrounded.
So they want to negotiate.
Firstly, I can't promise
to release all of you.
However, I guarantee
that you'll live.
As long as we can cooperate.
I didn't know you doctors
were in there.
What are your demands?
We'd like you to hand over
the Gundam pilots.
Because we want to record
combat data on the Gundam.
Looks like they noticed.
The system is just as
attractive to OZ.
There's no choice.
We'll surrender the pilots.
I'm afraid I can't promise to
save your lives, doctors.
Headquarters was pretty adamant
about their decision.
We've survived this long.
But our lucky streak's over.
I'm prepared for the worst.
First they want us as hostages.
Good way to treat us.
But the fact that we're
hostages won't stop Heero.
Heero, is there a problem?!
Not really.
Tell them to start.
Right.
Make him fight the
mobile doll data!
Sir!
He's good.
He isn't a Gundam pilot
for nothing.
He's better than mobile dolls?
He hasn't reached his limit yet.
Check his fastest reaction.
A system that can beat
mobile dolls.
To say that humans are
unnecessary in a battle!
Heero.
It's human beings that
fight against each other.
But those humans now
depend on machines...
...for the strength to fight.
Heero, it's mistaken!
This Gundam is a mistake!
These combat abilities are
extremely high.
Incredible!
My...my enemies...
My enemies are the people
after my life!
What?!
Heero!!
Hey!
Remember, we've got hostages!
Heero!!!
Increase the number
of mobile dolls.
- That'll work!
- Right!
Heero...
No, you're not Heero!
My enemies are the people
after my life.
And the ones that toy
with my life.
They're all my enemies.
Hostages don't mean anything
to those guys.
Because we created targets
for Heero to fight.
It's OZ and ourselves that
aren't needed in outer space.
That system disrupts the
balance in the human mind.
The fact that we're using
it to beat the mobile dolls...
...proves that our minds
have already been warped.
Well, shall we go?
To get killed?
I wish they'd eventually be
defeated by this age of war.
Contact Commander
Tubarov for backup!
How can we tell him about
our blunder, you fool?!
What's that, Lieutenant?!
Stop!
What are you doing?!
Stop!!
You people don't want
to die here, do you?
I'll stop him from attacking!
What?!
He can destroy this entire base!
Trowa said there's no sense
having one pilot run amuck...
...in a mobile suit.
This war won't end...
...if people keep fighting
on their own!
Heero.
That cockpit increases
your combat abilities.
But you lose control.
If I lost control because
of that cockpit...
...then I've lost something
important...
...because of some worthless
machinery!
I don't want to lose anything
else that's important to me.
Quatre.
I've got a very clear view
of the enemy.
If you're going to be an enemy,
then I'll have to kill you.
That Gundam is all on its own.
But we mustn't fight alone!
You lose sight of the target
when you fight alone!
I can see my target!
I see my enemy!
There's still a self-detonation
system left in this suit.
If you won't stop fighting...
...I'll destroy these two
mobile suits right now!
These mobile suits are
the least needed things...
...in outer space!
There's one thing outer
space needs even less.
Outer space needs
the Gundams.
And I'll fight to defend
space!
We aren't...
We aren't needed in outer space!
What?
We mustn't fight each other.
Relena...
Heero...
Who are you?!
You're from Earth.
Am I right?
Heero.
Let's go to the Earth.
The Earth was kind to us.
We ended up surviving again.
And so did this guy.
Is it necessary for the future?
We'll let the next pilot decide.
Those boys are not about to be
defeated by this suit.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
The rise and fall of the victorious
repeats itself.
People get tossed around
by a history of disputes.
Caught within the flames
of war...
...the Gundam pilots wander
without a destination.
What did they lose, and
what did they gain?
And what words does Relena
have after observing them?
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 27,
The Locus of Victory and Defeat
"The Locus of Victory and Defeat".