Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
Nureta sono kata wo atatameruyou ni daita
I hold onto your wet shoulders to give you warmth and comfort
Furueteru yubisaka wa nani wo motomete samayouno
What are those shivering fingertips wandering after?
Anata no manazashi mamoritai
I want to protect the honest look in your eye
Kanashimi tsuyosa ni kaeru ai wo shinjite
Believing in the love that'll change sorrow to strength
Just wild beat communication
Ameni utarenagara
Standing in the lashing rain
Iroasenai atsui omoi
I want to show my passionate, undying feelings
Karadajuu de tsutaetaiyo tonight!
With my entire body tonight!
In the year After Colony 175...
...the leader of the colonies
was assassinated.
Five Gundams were sent
to Earth to take revenge.
However, since OZ's activities
in space...
...took the form of cooperation
rather than control...
...the colonies decided
to accept OZ.
The year After Colony 195.
As OZ moves to take over
both Earth and outer space...
...Gundams are labeled rebels
and are isolated from society.
With no place to return...
...the Gundams and
their pilots...
...must fight for a reason to
exist in the changing world.
What?!
They missed it!
Intentionally?
Milliardo, there's one other
person who understands me.
Her feelings toward me have
given her split personalities.
The actions you took
were justified.
And what I'm about
to do is also justified!!
Duo, the God of Death Once Again
We're adjusting the ballast.
Go slowly.
Easy does it.
Wait.
Get some light on those rocks!
There it is!
It's hardly damaged, considering
the battle it's been through.
Sally.
Vessels approaching.
This was just Heero's trick,
abandoning his Gundam at sea...
...while he goes to space alone.
It's a mobile suit submarine
carrier!
No surprise that OZ would
come here too.
It's a dangerous job...
Don't concern yourself
about us mercenaries.
We have expertise as the former
Alliance's Deep-Sea Unit!
Prepare to send out the Pisces!
Object at 1 o'clock.
Perhaps Zero One.
Right, send out the Cancers!
Yes, sir!
All units, open fire!!
Propeller sound confirmed!
Enemy mobile suits!
What?!
Cancer!
Come in! Cancer!
Discarding his Gundam
like that...
What was he thinking?
Heero.
The foundation of our future
will be built by these suits.
These are for mass-production.
But don't worry about
cost performance.
Resources in space are
unlimited!
He treats the Space Colonies
like old world colonies...
...to be plundered!
Let him be.
We'll give him something
to remember.
I'm counting on you.
Sure.
Where are you taking that?
It's the Gundam you took apart
to try stealing our technology.
We're honored.
You're still interested
even after it was trashed.
How dare you!
I don't need that!
Get rid of it!
As you wish, Chief Engineer!
Shall I start making a mobile
suit superior to the Gundams?
Get to work!
Calm down!
Quit rushing me.
I've got a lot of things
to take care of.
Sorry to keep you.
There's no point in
just rebuilding them.
You didn't used to have
any problems...
...with your principles
against war in space.
So why is there a need
for armaments now?
A hundred years have passed...
...since the colonies were
experimental.
We feel there's no choice...
...but to avoid battle
by arming ourselves.
This is Sally Po, formerly a
Major in the Alliance Military.
As a rebel organization
member opposing OZ...
...she's supported and led a
number of their maneuvers.
There are also signs that
she has the Gundams Zero One and Zero Four.
The Romefeller Foundation
that controls OZ...
...is the most powerful
entity on Earth.
I'd say there are problems
with that organization.
However, we wanted to
protect the colonies.
And that's why we've
accepted OZ.
We chose the option that
would give us more safety.
Armed struggle will continue
on Earth.
That's why we chose
this method of protection.
OZ is keeping the Gundam
engineers captive.
Those on Earth opposing
OZ think that OZ alone...
...is changing the world into
a dangerous place to live.
We've heard that the engineers
have already been executed.
We cannot maintain our
dignity as a nation...
...unless we augment
our strength...
...and eliminate the chance
of more rebels.
Our decision won't change.
Ambassador Peacecraft.
Please try to understand
our reasoning.
The engineers have been
executed?
That's impossible.
It's this kind of fabricated
rumor we must fear the most.
Also, natural resources
and parts...
...have been transported
from the plant colonies...
...as we begin mobile suits
production...
...on the Lunar Plant, together
with support from OZ.
We no longer have to fear
the possibility of an invasion.
With Commander-in-Chief
Treize and Colonel Une's help...
...this will mark the beginning
of a new era for outer space.
What a bunch of crap.
They're the ones who planted
the fear of war in everyone.
That's not true.
The colonies have suffered
a history of humiliation.
We aren't afraid of battles...
...that will allow colony
independence.
Who are you?
My name is Hilde Schbeiker.
I've volunteered my services
from this colony.
So you're an OZ soldier.
Anyone can be critical.
The work of the colony's
students speaks for itself.
Our volunteer work at the Lunar
Plant reflects our faith in OZ.
Huh...Is that so?
Then maybe I should
apply, as well.
The next military exam
is in one week.
Why don't you give it
a try if you like?
Count on it; I'll be there.
We're headed to the Lunar Base.
Are they using us as test pilots
for the new models?
Maybe as target.
Even OZ admits that we're
pretty psyched.
The objective of OZ...
...and its mother organization,
Romefeller...
...was to destroy the United
Earth Sphere Alliance...
...and take control of Earth.
Why don't they take over
the colonies?
Taking over the defenseless
colonies...
...would be like twisting
a baby's arm.
Maybe Zechs would be
able to understand.
Treize is getting hungry
for mortal combat.
And the overconfident
colonies will realize...
...just how much stronger
Treize is.
All soldiers prepare to board
ship on the double!
Here you go, sir.
Thanks.
Have a nice day.
You!
Stop!
You...
What?
You talking to me?
I told you, new volunteers
are to apply next week.
Give me a look
at that application!
Oh, this?
It's all filled out.
But it's a fake!!
You scum!
- He's taken the Leo!
- After him!
Everybody stay calm!
I don't want to start firing
inside the colony!
You won't get away!!
My goal is to destroy
the Lunar Plant...
...but it's too far away!
Stop!!
Her again...
If you retaliate,
I'll have to kill you!!
Warning shots are meaningless
against inexperienced fighters!
This one's for the peace
of the colony!
I'm fighting for the peace
of the colony as well.
Got him!
Moving in till it's in
target range!
Okay, fire!
Sir!
Hey!
We're both fighting for
the colonies!
Then why are we enemies?!
Are you pleading for your life?!
I'm telling you!
We aren't enemies!
I volunteered and pledged
my loyalty.
I'm prepared to die any time!
You're so intense it
makes me sick!
Hey, get outta here!
Mobile Suit Gundam Wing
Duo Maxwell...
Who would've thought
you were a Gundam pilot?
Why did you save me?
What are you talking about?
I'm prepared to sacrifice
my life.
I don't need sympathy
from my enemies.
Hilde, you say?
What "enemies" do you mean?
Since when is the colony
an organization fighting a war?
When the Alliance came from
Earth to attack the colonies...
...smiles disappeared from
people's faces.
I've been fighting to help
give back those smiles.
Then I come back to the
colony, and guess what?
People don't want their
smiles back.
Tell me something.
When did the colonies
get so twisted?
Outer space is affected by
the war on Earth.
We can't just sit back
and be taken over.
This is outer space's decision.
Your bravery's commendable.
So where are you taking me?
To the Lunar Base.
You'll be questioned on the
Gundam, among other things.
Saves me a trip.
You know I'm planning
to destroy the Lunar Base.
You don't stand a chance.
Why don't you see me
as an enemy?
I won't let you destroy it.
Hate to say this, but you don't
have the skills to be my enemy.
So it's foolish for you to
risk your life against me.
But you remind me of how
reckless I was...
...when I went to Earth
to fight all on my own.
Don't patronize me!
In fact, we're both foolish.
A soldier can get killed
at any time.
We'll see many friends in
the colony lose their lives.
Let's live our lives believing
in the paths we've chosen.
You've got to be at least that
foolish to make it as a soldier.
Did he tell you anything?
No.
I see.
Chief?
When we were fighting...
...couldn't we have
fired a warning shot?
We have orders to kill rebels
when necessary.
That's what wars are about.
Even if it means sacrificing
your own people?
Officer Hilde.
I feel bad about it.
But soldiers must always
be prepared to die...
...to fulfill their missions.
Unit Chief, we're about to
arrive at the Lunar Base.
Good.
We'll take the shuttle to OZ's
military establishment.
To deliver the prisoner.
Roger.
What happened?!
The third engine's on fire!
Someone on board did it!
Duo?
And now, the getaway.
Duo!
Hey, that was quick.
You've got good instincts.
I'm blowing up the hatch.
Step back if you don't
wanna get hurt.
You're gonna do what?!
Stop it, Duo!
Duo!!
What was that explosion?!
What's wrong?! Report!
The mass balance device
is busted!
I'll get seasick!
Mobile dolls!
Don't move!
I made it to the moon!
That's ironic!
Am I washed-up?
Not too bad a job,
if I do say so myself.
Hurry up and finish me off!
I hate the thought of being
killed by a machine!
What?!
You fool!
Give your code to prove
you're an ally!
You'll get killed!
I can't do that.
There's no telling who
my allies are anymore.
Duo.
Hurry up and do what
you want to accomplish!
Hilde...
I decided to live out my life,
believing in my chosen path.
Sorry, Hilde.
This time I'm not
bailing you out!
I told you, I'm already
prepared to die!
Yeah, I remember.
But Hilde!
Just don't die in vain!
Same goes for you.
What are you doing, Hilde?
Drop your gun at once.
I've got a serious problem
with your conduct!!
Interesting.
It's underground.
I'll get to the plant
through this duct.
There he is!
Don't lose him!
We believe the enemy
has entered Area B6!
We're in pursuit!
Captain!
What?
Call from a colony Unit Chief.
The enemy is attempting to
destroy the mobile suit plant!
What?!
Get security underground
and stop him from entering!
What the heck?
Who's there?!
The God of Death.
That's four of them.
Are you here to kill us, too?
Long time no see, Duo.
So it WAS you guys.
Then those are!
That's right.
They're new models.
Duo, how would you like
to operate one?
When's it finished?
In one month.
Make sure you live
until it's finished.
Then you'll have your
chance in the spotlight.
In here!
Hurry!
Duo, decide quickly.
We can't let them
find this place!
I understand...
Okay, we'll do it your way!
Hurry up and get started!
Could you do the honors?
As much as I hate to...
It wouldn't hurt as much if
you screamed out loud.
Yeah.
But I'm a real man.
Traitor!
Coming here and trying to
kill us, after all we've done!
We won't let anyone
interfere with our research.
Botched your mission?
You couldn't destroy the base...
...and you didn't kill
Dr. J and the others.
Don't rub it in.
I'm still glad I decided
to come here.
Good news.
Your Gundam and mine
are being rebuilt.
I can hardly wait!
Looks like OZ will be
keeping us alive for the time.
It's a good chance,
so don't die yet.
Don't worry about me!
I don't plan on dying
that easily.
There's the colonies
to fight for.
Just watch.
I'll be the God of Death again!
I will!
Well...
...good night...
I've completed my mission...
...to escort Ambassador
Peacecraft on his return.
Thank you.
I'm sure the Ambassador
realizes...
...how resolved the people
in space are.
How about from the eyes
of Zechs Merquise?
He has opinions about
this era as well.
We'll battle again.
We'll hear his decision then.
I don't think anyone
can stop the future.
Not even Treize.
But I'll try to direct things
toward Treize's ideal.
I can sacrifice my life
for that purpose.
I'll fight and win.
For Treize's future.
And for my own future.
Maeburemonaku yobidasuno tenki ga ii kara
I give him a call out of the blue, just because it's sunny...
Watashi wo machiboukesasete nanisama no tsumori
But he makes me wait, how dare he treat me this way!
Hashittekitano wakatterukedo
I know he's out of breath from running here...
Sonna koto wa atari mae yo!
But that's the very least he could do for me!
Just love! Kinikuwanai aitsu
Just love! He gets on my nerves...
Ijiwaru wo schichau no wa sukidakara yo
I only tease him because I actually like him...
Just love! Kininaru kara itsumo
Just love! I'm always thinking about him...
Murina koto itchauno chotto gomen...
Sorry I push things a little too far...
Just love...
Next Episode
Is destruction the only path
for an outer space gone mad?
A mobile suit resembling
a Gundam...
...attacks the colonies that
are arming themselves.
Trowa and Heero head out
to face this powerful new suit.
They find that the pilot of
this mobile suit is Quatre...
...cold with anger and
full of deep sorrow.
Next, on Gundam Wing, Episode 24,
The Gundam They Called Zero
"The Gundam They Called Zero".