I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Even though I'm offering
150 thousand?
Doesn't matter! Kill them...
...then don't forget to pick up the cash
on the ground when you're done!
Right. Do not move, guys!
Negotiations... have been broken off.
- Damn you!
- There they are!
Jodorowsky here!
Encountered enemy at Point Pskov!
Roger.
How dare you!
Stop it, Eda!
It's Hotel Moscow!
They've come out, big sister.
It's the Russians!
Yes!
Hey, big sister...
Let's confuse the Russians.
If we can randomly eliminate a few,
they'll return to their main base for sure.
Very well, big brother.
Let's take separate routes
and corner the Russians!
- I wish you success, big sister.
- Yes, big brother.
- I love you.
- Yes. I love you.
We lost the targets during combat.
But we've clearly shown ourselves
to the enemy.
Instruct them to proceed and assume
that the enemy has taken the bait.
Right.
All units,
continue with the plan.
Lavochek Unit, Lobosfski Unit,
complete level two preparations...
...and proceed to the final location.
Target Two located behind
Jodorowsky as he's retreating.
Confirm the number of targets.
At once!
Baronin to Okchabriagin.
I have only sighted Target Two.
I repeat, I have only sighted
Target Two.
Private Eugene here. We have located
the target that is following Jodorowsky.
We only see one body
from here as well.
Target Two is securely locked on
to Jodorowsky's ass.
I'll drag him along
to the planned location.
- So only Target Two has taken the bait?
- That's correct.
That's fine. Then make sure
to corner that one without mistake.
Don't take anything for granted.
They're extremely clever.
Let them believe that they
have the advantage.
With that in mind, proceed to
the next stage and stir up confusion.
I'll have my subordinates take them
on mafia-style.
Not to worry, we're almost at the
park entrance. We'll make the first shot.
Focus all your efforts on getting
the target disturbed and furious.
Frustration will dull the
target's senses.
That's when
we'll turn the tables.
Roger.
Sergeant, it's time.
- Take command of the final unit.
- Yes.
Best of luck to you, Captain.
Yeah. And you be careful, too.
Now...
Guess it's about time
we put an end...
...to this boisterous merrymaking.
How do you expect me to return
to the church empty handed?
We should've agreed to that offer!
You got too greedy!
How dare you!
Who do you think it was
that saved you...
...from getting your balls torn off by
those guys from Hotel Moscow?! Well?!
I was born without balls,
you monkey-girl! Idiot!
You're asking for it, you shit!
We'll have a duel!
Sounds like fun, Revy!
Of course, it will be more fun
after you get more holes in your ass!
You know...
I really don't care anymore.
I didn't get a penny outta this.
I'm going back to the office.
Call me if something comes up.
Hey, wait! What about me?!
- What do you mean?
- What do you think?!
I don't wanna walk into the
line of fire alone to go get my car!
Come with me, Revy!
We're friends, right?
You can go on your own.
You're not a kid.
Wha...
How could you be so cruel?!
Hi, miss.
How long have you been there?
I've been waiting until you were alone.
I didn't wanna face the two of you
all by myself.
There's something I want you
to help me with.
As soon as big brother kills
the Russian lady, we'll have to flee.
But we killed Verocchio and his men,
who were supposed to arrange all that.
You fool. You knew all that,
and yet you killed your guardian?
Besides, now you no longer have
an obligation to kill Balalaika.
So why continue? Why?
Why? Why, you ask? What a question.
That's so funny!
Because we want to. There's no other
reason at all. We want to, so we do it.
But that's not important right now.
I want you to introduce me
to an escape specialist.
I want someone who takes their job
seriously. Tell me, miss.
There's no need to hide.
Come out here.
You could tell I was here.
You're amazing, lady.
It's no wonder your subordinates
are so skilled.
I chased them all over,
but couldn't kill a single one.
Now, what do you suggest
we do, lady?
Shall we take advantage of
this opportunity and talk?
Perhaps we can talk about
that man we killed.
Anyone else would've died
a lot sooner...
...but that man lasted
for quite some time.
He kept yelling to the very end,
"Captain! Captain!"
Over and over,
while spitting out blood.
Is that so.
You're a cold person, lady.
But you know what?
You'll be like that man soon enough.
It's just a shame that you don't
have much time left.
That really is a shame.
I'm sorry to say this, little boy,
but this is the end of the road for you.
But before that.
You'll have to apologize for your
mischievous pranks. Hey, kid.
First of all, kneel there before me.
- You're not serious.
- Kneel!
It's the end for you, kid.
If only you had the ability to use reason,
you would've realized...
...that you walked straight into a trap.
You know, you're gonna die here,
as nothing but...
...a brat beyond repair.
Lady, you're funny.
What are you saying?
I will not die.
I'm not gonna die.
Because I've killed so many people!
We've killed many, many...
...many, many...
...people. Therefore we can live on...
...that much longer.
We can... We can add on to our life.
We will never die. Yes.
We'll live on eternally.
So that's your religion, is it?
That's a wonderful way of thinking.
But the correct answer is,
as the song goes, "no one lives forever".
There you have it.
Now...
I could kill you by torturing you cruelly.
It's the least I could do
to even come close...
...to what you did to my subordinates.
But unfortunately I'm not
as vulgar as you are.
So I'm just going to
watch you die from here.
Judging from your wounds,
you have ten minutes at the most.
I dedicate these few minutes
before you leave this world...
...to Saharov and Menshov's souls.
You probably wouldn't
be able to understand.
Don't cry, you fool.
Captain?
Sergeant.
I'm finished on my end.
That wasn't good, Captain.
I was chilled to the bone.
Sorry.
I had you stick with me
through all this selfishness.
Captain.
I'm getting too old for this.
I'm a little exhausted.
She's got a great singing voice.
It's hard to believe it's the voice
of a crazed, bloodthirsty murderer.
Yeah.
Her voice alone is that of an angel.
But this has really taken
an odd turn.
You can say that again.
The bloodthirsty murderer...
...that starred in the night of terror
in Roanapur is now our client.
Well, that's fine by me. She's a client,
just the same. So, where's Revy?
At first she was really pissed off
about that girl...
...but right now she's outside
guarding the cabin...
...just in case something
happens to Rock.
That's a beautiful song.
Where did you learn it?
I heard it on TV.
This song's one of my favorites.
But you know what? You're the first
person besides my big brother...
...that I've sung it to.
H-Hey!
You seem different from everyone else.
It's like you're in a different place.
A different world.
Guess I'm just not used
to this job yet.
You're a nice person.
You know, I'm really good at figuring out
who's good and who's not.
It's me. Balalaika?
- I presume you know why I'm calling.
- Yeah.
In fact I expected this call sooner.
Hey, Dutch. Do you realize
what you're doing?
Of course.
We're being paid extra
for the additional risks involved.
You're not doing this for some
obligation or sympathy, are you?
- Do I look like a philanthropist to you?
- Just checking.
It allows me to determine
the position I should be taking.
We both just gotta do what we gotta do.
Am I wrong, Balalaika?
- Dutch. We're swaying south.
- You're right, Dutch.
I've already taken a number of steps.
Yeah. I just noticed some guys
that may have something to do with that.
No regrets and no grudges.
Good luck.
Roger, Captain.
- Sergeant.
- Yes?
- Get me the E File of the trouble list.
- E?
Insurance with a good return.
- The Vietnamese Navy?
- Correct.
Quite impressive.
The power of Hotel Moscow...
- Are we gonna fight them?
- Don't be ridiculous.
We're a torpedo boat,
and we're up against missile ships.
Damn frustrating, but that eliminates
the Hainan Island route.
What about Brunei?
Where Mary Lee is.
No way.
It'll take too long.
Then the only remaining option...
...within the range this boat will take us
is Elroy in Pangkal Pinang.
Big Horn Elroy.
- Okay, that's where we'll go.
- I'll contact him at once.
We're out on the sea, but I'm not able
to see any of it. How disappointing.
Sorry about that.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
Have you never seen the sea?
Back when we were in Sicily...
...and at the orphanage,
all we saw were gray walls.
I was born in the rocky
Carpathian mountain range.
It was always cloudy.
A very lonely place.
A particular dictator prohibited
his citizens from having an abortion.
The purpose was to create more workers
for this poor country...
...but the fact was, if they were poor,
they could not raise their children.
Massive numbers of abandoned children
were taken in by state-run orphanages.
The children would become prime
candidates for the secret police.
The dictator was killed...
...and what remained were the countless
orphans who received no love.
Once we were handed
over to Sicily...
...we were continually surrounded
by blood and darkness.
We were kicked until we
no longer moved...
...and there were nights that
I'd have red pee all night.
Big brother and I would often ask
why God is so cruel to us.
But you know what? Both big brother and
I realized something. Other children...
...would be brought before us.
And then as they cried, they'd be beaten
with bats. You know what then?
The grown ups were laughing.
Big brother and I also laughed.
We thought as we laughed,
that it was all fixed.
Yes. If the world keeps turning because
of the people that are killed...
...then our purpose in this world
is just that.
People kill, get killed,
and kill again...
...and this creates a ring in this world.
But aren't you sad that your big brother
got killed because of that?
What are you saying?
I'm right here.
I'm always with big sister.
Because we will live eternally,
above this ring that continues forever.
We will continue killing,
and the world...
...the people and the two of us will
always exist so we can kill. That's why...
...we're no longer sad.
We've learned to love the smell
of blood, the sound of screaming...
...and the warmth of bowels.
No!
You're wrong. This world is really here
to make you happy.
Listen. Blood and darkness are only
very small fragments of this world.
It's far from everything
the world has to offer!
Hey. Don't cry, mister.
This is the first time I ever met such
a kind person like you! So...
Here. A gift for you.
- Rock?
- Benny!
Go check on him!
I'll take care of the kid!
All right!
Well, well... I see that the blood of your
kind is also red. Hey, stupid brat.
It's not only the Sis'.
I'm also really disappointed that
you're not already dead.
You know,
you have the same smell.
The smell of blood and rotten sewers.
You and I are the same thing!
I couldn't care less
about any of that.
You try teasing him one more time,
and I'll kill you.
Also, if you say
anything to piss me off, I'll kill you.
Damn it!
Damn it! Why? Why did all this
have to happen?
Everyone ganged up on her
and turned her into a tiger.
A man-eating tiger! Damn it!
Rock. You can't look
directly at these things.
This is that sort of place,
and it would be best.
- I'll... I'll...
- What? Adopt her? Impossible.
That kid can never stop killing.
If only someone was just
a little kinder to them...
...they might've gone to school,
made friends, and lived happily.
But that didn't happen, Rock.
So this story ends here, Rock.
Dutch. Long time no see.
Yeah, it's been a while.
- So that's your cargo this time?
- Yeah.
I hate to rush you, but were you
able to get her a passport?
I gathered everything she'll need,
as always.
See you again, mister.
I hope to meet
you again someday!
Next time, we'll put together a
lunch basket. Just the two of us.
Yeah.
That sounds wonderful.
That really would be wonderful.
How beautiful. The sky.
It's Hotel Moscow, Dutch. Who else?
You know you just trashed
your career as a getaway man.
Yeah, I'm done.
I have a son in South Africa.
I got a letter from his wife. He's only 34
but has been diagnosed with cancer.
In any case, I've grown tired of walking
the tightrope. This is my last job.
Hotel Moscow is paying me
a pretty attractive amount for it.
Well, see ya.
Her last words were, "How beautiful.
The sky." That's so unfitting.
Rock! Bring a canvas.
We'd better cover the body.
Someday I want to run away...
That won't be necessary. Dutch.
This is fine.
Just as she is.
...to the world of midnight...
She can look up at the sky and gaze
at the ocean as she sleeps.
Where the darkness fill the air...
Where it's icy cold...
Where nobody has a name...
Where living is not a game...
There, I'll hide my broken heart...
Dying to survive...
There, no one can see me cry...
The tears of my lonely soul...
I'll find peace of mind...
In the dark and cold world of midnight...
Midnight...
Next Episode
The reason I accepted this job...
...is because I was told I'd be able to
make perfect counterfeit money.