I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
Someday I want to run away...
...to the world of midnight...
Where the darkness fill the air...
Where it's icy cold...
Where nobody has a name...
Where living is not a game...
There, I'll hide my broken heart...
Dying to survive...
There, no one can see me cry...
The tears of my lonely soul...
I'll find peace of mind...
In the dark and cold world of midnight...
Midnight...
Next Episode