Hey, you! Wait!
Damn it, so agile!
Asia-chan!
Oh my.
Akeno-san!
My my.
Why is it targeting...
only my breasts?
B-Because you have big ones that stand out?
Oh my.
All right, he's cornered!
Good evening,
stray demon.
We've been ordered to exterminate you.
After abandoning your master,
you ran wild to fulfill your own selfish desires with no regard for decency.
Your crime warrants nothing but death.
In the name of Duke Gremory,
I'll blast you away.
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 13 "Boobs Bearing Fruit!"
It's futile.
Yuuto!
Roger, President!
Oh my, you're already done?
Akeno-san! Koneko-chan!
We're done too.
Good work.
It was weak.
So that was this guy's familiar.
Gross.
The bug kept coming at my breasts for some reason.
Your breasts?
It was a bug like Issei-senpai.
Well, I'm sorry I'm like a bug to you.
Everyone...
Are you all right, Asia?
Y-Yes.
The two of them protected me.
Now, stray demon, it's checkmate.
Or are you determined to continue fighting?
No, I choose to surrender.
I'm aware I stand little chance against the daughter of the famous Gremory family.
I see you have a fine pair of boobs.
Hey, don't be so rude to the president!
He's a demon like Issei-senpai.
Well, I'm sorry he's like me.
Akeno, restrain him and use a magic
circle to send him to the demon world.
Understood.
I really would've enjoyed it far more had you resisted.
Go and submit yourself to the verdict of the demon world.
Of course.
I've done everything I needed to.
I had no chance to shine last night.
Compared to Kiba and Akeno-san, I still have a ways to go.
“I've done everything I needed to,” huh?
Wh-What the hell is this?!
A research laboratory, it seems.
According to the report, he was performing a certain experiment here night after night.
Documents that seem important will be sent to the demon world.
The rest should be destroyed.
What on earth was that stray demon up to?
He was really fixated on breasts.
Did you say breasts?!
Hey, Issei!
Wh-What do you want?
Damn you!
You've accompanied Rias-senpai on the way to and from school so much recently!
Not just that! I heard you were walking with her arm in arm!
That is simply outrageous!
Hey, calm down, Matsuda, Motohama.
I-I can't tell them that both Asia and the president are living at my house!
Welcome back, Issei!
And that's not all!
We do things like that
or even that! I can't tell them about those!
Well, she's like a big sis to me, after all.
Damn, you're acting like a huge snob!
You've delighted in Rias-senpai's
voluptuous breasts, haven't you?
I never even mentioned the president's boobs.
Boobs?! I knew it!
You're the one who brought it up!
Speaking of boobs, Issei,
did you know?
A lot of girls have been skipping
school or leaving early recently.
Is there some odd disease going around?
No, they were only diagnosed with anemia.
Anemia?
Now here's the puzzling part.
The girls affected have one thing in common.
They all have huge boobs.
H-Huge boobs?
Indeed.
This is based on my data of every girl in the school.
There's no mistake!
At this rate...
...all big-breasted girls are going to disappear from this school!
A disease that only affects girls with big boobs, huh?
Here, open up!
It's good!
Is it?
This mouth-watering, savory taste!
The seasoning is just right too!
It's really good!
Is it?
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh my, you two look so lovey-dovey even though it's just lunchtime.
Since I'm staying at his house,
making lunch is the least I can do.
I prepared lunch too.
You also made some for me?
But since the president already...
I-I'll have your homemade lunch too, of course!
Oh, this is...!
It's good!
That's great.
Wait a minute.
This tastes like Mom's cooking.
Did you learn from her?
I did.
I see.
You learned from Mom.
I'm glad!
Practicing was worth it.
Not bad, Asia.
I-I don't want to l-lose to you.
I feel like I will, though.
I joined the race later than you,
but I'm not here to lose either!
Oh, President, isn't this...
Yeah.
Grayfia-san!
So that stray demon was an alchemist who was working with goblins?
Yes, and we've discoverd a related issue.
An issue?
It seems he's synthesized a chimera from a carnivorous plant and a demon world dragon in his laboratory,
and released it in this town.
U-Um, what's a chimera?
It's a monster made up of different creatures.
M-Monster?
The carnivorous plant aspect shouldn't be a big problem,
but the dragon aspect will be a pain to deal with.
Dragons embody powers unique to those of demons or angels.
I remember Grayfia-san saying something like that.
That's it for now.
I'll contact you again if there are any updates.
All right.
Thank you.
President, we've returned.
We're back.
Good work.
I can tell from your faces that you found something.
Yeah, we tracked it down.
It's most likely after the girls of this school.
Girls?
Then the rumor that many girls suddenly got sick is...
That's right.
The problem is that we picked up traces of magic in those girls.
Magic?!
It bothered me, so I had Yuuto and Koneko search in secret.
Is it a plant goblin?
No, this is...
A dragon?!
This must be the one Grayfia-sama was talking about.
That saves me some trouble.
Let's hide. Someone's coming.
Huh?
They're girls from my class, Katase and Murayama.
I-It's moving.
It's sucking out their life energy.
How dare—
Hold on, Issei.
But, President!
Judging from past cases, it won't kill them.
Indeed.
So let's wait and see for a bit.
They're unsteady, but they seem okay.
It seems it put a spell on the targeted girls
and made them come here every night.
And it sucks out their life energy for nourishment?
I-Is that really possible?
In any case,
since we've found it,
its luck has run out.
Issei-san!
Don't let your guard down.
Commence attack!
Okay, President!
I'll kick its ass.
A threat to the peace of the school needs to be brought down!
All right, here it goes!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
This creature's pretty smart!
There's no end to these!
It's recovering faster than we can damage it.
Its full potential has been brought out.
The air and soil of the human world
along with the life energy of the students
must provide the optimal conditions for it.
Will everyone be all right?
Asia!
President!
Shit!
Wh-What is this?
This again?
Oh my, these tentacles are perverted!
E-Even Akino-san and Koneko-chan?
I can't attack recklessly!
Damn it! What should I do?
Oh my, this is a problem.
I don't like this slimy stuff.
Slippery stuff is eating away my clothes!
This slippery...
slimy fluid...
It seems to melt clothes!
Can't you use your powers to fight back?
I can't!
I can't get my destruction spell to start!
I can't generate lightning either.
Koneko, can't you break free with your powers either?
It's just too slippery.
Oh my!
Is that gooey fluid making it impossible to use magic?
At this rate...
...everyone will become naked!
This is quite...
No, this is a really big deal!
Issei, don't just watch. You fight too!
Dragon!
Asia!
Why did it only let Asia and Koneko go?
I-It's focusing its attacks on my breasts.
It's extracting my life energy from them.
Wh-What an indecent movement.
No!
W-Wow!
This is such a wonderful—
I mean, lewd—
I mean, fearsome attack!
It attaches itself to women's boobs and sucks out their life energy!
But why breasts?
Don't ask the obvious!
I too would love to glue myself to President and Akeno-san's breasts and suck out their life energy!
Don't sympathize with the monster!
I'm not sympathizing!
I'm burning with jealousy right now!
You damned chimera!
That's no good either!
Now I remember.
The girls who were reported sick all had plump chests.
I see now!
So this monster only preys on...
big-breasted girls!
D-Don't stand there in awe. Do somethi—
You're a high-class demon lady.
Don't let out obscene screams like that.
Grayfia!
Just report any updates!
No!
Okay.
That chimera draws life energy out of big-breasted women.
I know that!
I'm being subjected to that as we speak!
And it has another special ability.
Special ability?
Women who eat the fruit produced by this chimera,
no matter how small their breasts are,
will develop voluminous breasts instantly.
What?!
That stray demon said...
If all women in the world get big boobs,
not only can they all live in comfort,
but men's true dreams can also take flight!
Small breasts are a cardinal sin!
I'll make the entire world big-breasted!
Boobs and peace!
End of quote.
Oh my!
B-Boobs... and... peace!
What a...
What a magnificent dream!
I can't believe he had such a wonderful ambition!
It takes the ultimate creature to save
women who agonize over their breast size!
So that's why that demon was
staring at the president's boobs.
Even his bug familiar went for Akeno-san's boobs!
His incredible attachment to
boobs gave him the courage!
He made his dream come true even if it meant defying his master!
I admire him!
Small breasts are a sin.
Small breasts are cruel.
Koneko-chan.
I'll crush it all.
Koneko-sama is enraged!
Yeah, I know my breasts aren't as great as President's or Akeno-san's.
I'll save the you both!
Wait, handsome guy!
President!
Wh-What is it?
Let this creature go!
I think this is a great chimera that will fulfill the dream of all men!
What are you saying?
I can't believe your perverted urges kicked in at a time like this!
Oh my, this is problematic.
Ouch!
With this, flat-chested girls won't have to suffer anymore!
And in line with what the stray demon said,
those big boobs will give men the strength to step forward!
Ouch!
I'm trying to defend you here!
Out of my way, please.
That chimera is my enemy.
Sh-She's scary!
But I won't give in!
Look, Koneko-chan!
That's it! If you eat that, you'll get big boobs in an instant!
Hey, Kiba, what are you doing?!
Issei, you're giving me so much trouble.
President, this is for the hope and future of every woman on the planet!
Just listen.
Yes, ma'am!
If we defeat that chimera,
you're free to do anything with Akeno's and my breasts for the entire night!
Oh my.
I'm free to do anything with them.
Was that...
Was that really what I just heard?!
What should I do?
Big boobs for every woman in the world...
Just the thought of it is fascinating!
But I need to be sensible!
Even if all the women in the world gain big boobs,
I'll probably only get to look at them.
And only momentary glances at that!
But, but...
I'm in!
I can't resist boobs right in front of me!
The right choice is not those boobs out of my reach,
but those within it!
I'm going to destroy you!
Prepare yourself, you damned chimera!
Issei-san...
Issei, lend me your power.
I got it!
Boost!
Not yet!
I still need more!
Boost!
One more count!
All right, this is it!
President! I'll send you this power!
Transfer!
Its power may indeed be able to resolve some women's agony.
However, other girls shouldn't have to pay the price.
Begone!
It's over.
Okay, let's head back.
Hold on!
President! Akeno-san!
As promised, your wonderful
breasts are mine for the night!
President or Akeno-san?
I'll see whose breasts are softer!
Ouch.
Nope.
Since you were fooling around,
I'm postponing it!
Th-That's ridiculous!
I can't believe you would side with a monster like that.
K-Koneko-chan.
You're terrible.
There.
Why?!
Reflect upon your actions for tonight.
Let's head back, everybody.
Asia, save me!
President said you really need to think about what you did.
Forget him. Let's go back, Asia-senpai.
Sorry, Issei-kun!
See you.
You bastard! You're gonna leave me behind with that charming smile?
I'll be saving my breasts for later, Issei-kun.
Don't leave me behind, everyone!
I apologize, President!
I won't do it again!
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Hey, handsome guy!
You just left while I was buried! That was so heartless!
What?
Wait, huh?
Who are you guys?
High School DxD second season announced!
TV Anime 2nd Season Announced!!
Let's boobs!
Let's Boobs!
TV Anime 2nd Season Announced!!