You sure you're okay?
An Infection Called a Stye,
a Hordeolum, or Perhaps Just Beauty
It's swelling pretty bad.
Worry not.
I acquired these from the hospital this morning.
Then why didn't you use them this morning?
Opened!
Unfurled!
Equipped!
Ker-chang!
And now you can't see.
Worry not!
The eye is but a vessel.
The Tyrant's Eye operates by that concept.
My eye may be covered, but I see all!
Observe!
Wow.
Good job, Rikka.
But try to keep the
eyepatch on straight, okay?
Yuuta, sound the alarm!
Emergency!
The Adminstration Bureau is interfering with the Tyrant's Eye's vision!
No cheating now.
Okay, enough playing around.
Just take that eyepatch off.
You'll hurt yourself.
I cannot do that.
This eyepatch is necessary to contain the power of the Tyrant's Eye.
To remove it is to expose this spatial axis to the powers of darkness.
Moreover, it may even corrupt
other spatial axes—
You're getting on my nerves.
Yuuta, that hurt...
Whatever. Just take it off.
Ease your heart.
That was but a farce.
Behold now the true power of the Tyrant's Eye.
I'm scared!
Yuuta!
Assistance!
You'll get yourself killed at this rate.
Do I truly have no choice but to open the Tyrant's Eye?
But releasing all the seals will take—
Take it off.
Tyrant's Eye, activate!
Oh, Rikka. Don't forget your eyedrops.
Can't do it.
Don't just give up!
Fine. I'll put them in for you.
Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
Y-Yuuta, I'm not ready yet...
Hold still. It won't hurt, I promise.
But I'm scared...
Hey, now. I can't do it with your eyes shut.
What are you doing?
But I'm not ready...
Come on, look at me. Chin up.
To Be Continued
O ye who (gen gen gen) consumes the abyss (ius ius ius)
shin'en wo (ten ten ten) kurau mono (sai sai sai)
It's time for the (ang ang ang) Dark Carnival (uish uish uish)
magamagashii (han han han) shanikusai (mon mon mon)
kecchaku wo tsuke ni kita zo
I'm here to settle our score
Just when I thought the wind seemed restless today
myou ni kaze ga atsumaru to omottara
See that?
That was my power!
It seems the Great Mother calls for my aid yet again
watashi wa futatabi mother ni michibikareta you da
Wow, I even
scared myself!
No common humans shall be harmed
ippanjin wa kizutsuke ya shinai
The Organization will take care of everything after
ato wa soshiki ga umaku yatteru
kisama no shiru watashi ga watashi no subete dewa nai
The "me" you see before you is not all there is to me
Enough of this foolish act; you can see, can you not?
kudaran shibai wa yose mieteru no de arou
kono karada ni mo naretekita koto da shi
How accustomed to this body I have grown!
It's about time we began our feast!
soro soro hajimeyou dewa nai ka
I just haven't
unleashed
my true power
watashi no ushiro ni wa
I have at my beck and call
yon no daitenshi to nanajuuni no akuma ga iru
Four archangels and the seventy-two demons
honki wo amari dasaseruna yo
Don't make me get too serious on you
I won't deal the final blow; you may live
todome wa sasanai de oiteyaru
watashi ni michi wo akesasetakerya
If you seek that I may open your path
Maybe you can bring a god or two with you
kamisama demo tsuretekuru to ii