Angel Summoning
Magick Circles: A Guide
That's enough to summon an angel?
I've seen elves before, you know.
That's, like, the tenth time
you've said that.
Mori Summer, this isn't some séance or ouija thing, right?
If it turns freaky, I'm outta here.
Worry not.
This magick circle is for summoning angels of the highest choir.
I see.
Then it'll be a worthy opponent for me,
Sophia Ring S. P. Saturn VII.
Our preparations are now complete.
However, we must take note.
We are summoning an angel.
Overexposure to holy energies
may damage your human souls.
So please, eat some of this.
It is an elixir.
Grass?
Okay.
Got it.
Looks like chrysanthemum to me.
Now, let us summon the angel.
O Holy Spirit,
we ask that You send us
a messenger on holy wings.
We offer this vessel.
Purify our sinful souls,
and sing: holy, holy...
holy!
An angel has descended!
Huh? Where?!
A wind blew, did it not?
Well, yeah, it would.
We're outside.
That was not the wind.
It was a wind brought about by the angel's wings.
Oho! It looks like a worthy foe!
You can see it?!
N-Naturally, I can see it too.
An angel, radiating holy light.
No way!
Wait, seriously?
What? You can all see it?
It has possessed the vessel.
Do not see with your earthly eyes.
See with your mind's eye.
I can't see it.
The vessel kinda went flying.
It seems it has left.
So it fled.
We may battle another day.
Looks like it.
Was there even one?
Yup.
That's what Mori Summer was like
back in middle school!
Oh, so that's what
Mori Summer-chan was like.
No!
The End
O ye who (gen gen gen) consumes the abyss (ius ius ius)
shin'en wo (ten ten ten) kurau mono (sai sai sai)
It's time for the (ang ang ang) Dark Carnival (uish uish uish)
magamagashii (han han han) shanikusai (mon mon mon)
kecchaku wo tsuke ni kita zo
I'm here to settle our score
Just when I thought the wind seemed restless today
myou ni kaze ga atsumaru to omottara
See that?
That was my power!
It seems the Great Mother calls for my aid yet again
watashi wa futatabi mother ni michibikareta you da
Wow, I even
scared myself!
No common humans shall be harmed
ippanjin wa kizutsuke ya shinai
The Organization will take care of everything after
ato wa soshiki ga umaku yatteru
kisama no shiru watashi ga watashi no subete dewa nai
The "me" you see before you is not all there is to me
Enough of this foolish act; you can see, can you not?
kudaran shibai wa yose mieteru no de arou
kono karada ni mo naretekita koto da shi
How accustomed to this body I have grown!
It's about time we began our feast!
soro soro hajimeyou dewa nai ka
I just haven't
unleashed
my true power
watashi no ushiro ni wa
I have at my beck and call
yon no daitenshi to nanajuuni no akuma ga iru
Four archangels and the seventy-two demons
honki wo amari dasaseruna yo
Don't make me get too serious on you
I won't deal the final blow; you may live
todome wa sasanai de oiteyaru
watashi ni michi wo akesasetakerya
If you seek that I may open your path
Maybe you can bring a god or two with you
kamisama demo tsuretekuru to ii