kono sekai no chiisana basho de
On that day that I came and I first found you
kimi no sugata wo mitsuketa ano hi
In a tiny place in this wide world
kaze wo ukete waratteita ne
The wind blew past you, and you were laughing
watashi no kokoro ga somatteita
In a moment it was burned forever in my heart
dore dake chikaku ni itatte
No matter how close I stay by you
omoi ga tsutawaru wake ja nai ne
My feelings still might never be able to reach you
dore dake hanaretemo
No matter how far apart we are
kono omoi kawaranai yo
These feelings I have will never change
unmei toka eien toka
Destiny and eternity
kowashite demo soba ni iru
I'll be by your side even if you destroy them
ashita yori mo ima daisuki da yo
I love this moment more than what tomorrow might bring
owari nante konai dakara motto...
The end will never come, so, please...
utsukushisa mo sutekisa mo
Everything wonderful and everything beautiful
nakute ii kara
Can just go away
kuruoshii hodo ni aisasete
I want to love you so much that it drives me insane
ano hi no kotoba wasurenai
I'll never forget your words on that day
wasurerarenai kimi he
I'll never be able to forget you
todoite hoshii
I want you to know how I feel
Tyrant's Eye - Daybreak
Good morning, Tomo-chan.
Good morning, Rikka-chan.
Did you finish your homework?
I did.
B-Be still!
What happened to your arm?
I had a close call yesterday.
No, never mind.
Don't worry about me.
Okay.
All right, what happened?
You see...
No, you wouldn't believe me if I told you.
They can't be seen by normal humans.
Never mind.
Nothing happened.
I must fight them alone.
Tomo-chan, forget I ever mentioned it.
If you don't tell me in the next three seconds, I'll never ask again.
One...
The Denizens of the Dark seek to destroy this world.
After yesterday's vicious battle,
I was able to seal one of them in my left arm.
Didn't you tell me yesterday that you hurt your arm at the station and couldn't use it?
I-It healed.
A Denizen of the Dark
attacked me right after.
I see.
And then you sealed it with those bandages, right?
Yes. I was created for the sole purpose of sealing the Denizens of the Dark within me.
But that means nothing to me.
All that matters to me is your safety.
I couldn't be any more grateful.
To repel the Denizens of the Dark is my fate.
There is no need to thank me.
She must really love saying "Denizens of the Dark."
Changing Room
Huh, you're taking it off?
It gets heavy when it's wet.
It's annoying.
What about the seal?!
The Next Day
Good morning.
Good morning...
The Day After That
Good morning.
A Week Later
Did you get hit by a truck?!
I had another close call yesterday.
You're overdoing it with this "seal" thing!
You don't look cool with that many bandages!
Sensei...
Takanashi...
Get your butt to the faculty room now!
From then on, Rikka-chan only sealed denizens in her left arm and right eye.
At the break (Doom!) of the dark dawn (Gloom!)
shikkoku no (ha) akatsuki ni (zetsu)
Cut through the heavens and cleave apart the world (Slash!)
kokuu wo kirisaite yo wo ugate (zan)
Now it's time to part (Ruin!) Here's a flower for your soul (Death!)
saa owakare da (metsu) hana wo tamukeyou (sou)
rinpyo-to-sha-kaijin rettsu go-!
Rin Pyou Tou Sha Kai Jin Let's Go!
(Fall and make fall, O light of the stars!)
(fure furase hoshi no hikari yo)
(Scatter and make scatter, march on the warpath!)
(chire chirase hadou wo susume)
...are you ready now?
...kakugo wa ii ka?
Quiver, and be still!
furuete nemure
Ugh... Not that dream again
uu... mata ano yume ka
My head is pounding like it might split in two
atama ga wareteshimaisou da
The full moon tonight is magnificent
koyoi mangetsu ga uruwashii
The eye which reflects all truth begins to throb
shinjitsu wo utsusu hitomi ga uzukidasu
(Dance! Dance! Jaoushingan!)
(odore odore jaoushingan)
I'm not off guard, I'm just bored, you see?
yudan de wa nai taikutsu na no sa
I've long forgotten all the gods to which you pray
inoru kami nado tou ni wasureta
fua~aa~aa saa utageja
Fwaa-aa-aah! Now let us feast!
(In Heaven and on Earth I alone am honored! Yay!)
(tenjoutenge yuigadokuson washo-i)
watashi nara koko ni iruzo
You know, I'm right here for you
But don't get too close, I can't control it!
dakedo chikadzukuna seigyo dekinai...
The Heavens cry, the Seas howl, I'm the strongest now!
ten ga naite umi ga hoe watashi ga saikyou da
Why don't you get it?
naze kidzukanai?
That's the problem with you foolish humans!
kore dakara ningen wa...
(Fall and make fall, O light of the stars!)
(fure furase hoshi no hikari yo)
(Scatter and make scatter, march on the warpath!)
(chire chirase hadou wo susume)
Are you ready now?
kakugo wa ii ka!