Good morning.
Good morning, Tomo-chan.
What are you doing, Rikka-chan?
Developing ESP.
Become
Psychic
Just
By
Reading
This
Book
That book looks really fake, Rikka-chan.
Clairvoyance, foresight, telekinesis.
I believe those faculties and the Tyrant's Eye are closely related.
Tyrant's Eye -
Before the Storm
By developing my ESP, I will
intensify the power of the Eye.
It's also another skill for my resumé.
You might get a laugh,
but they'd turn you down right away...
Draw cards at random.
I will determine what they are
with the Tyrant's Eye.
O-Okay.
Okay, what's this?
I see it!
It's a star!
H-Hold on. I wasn't relaxed enough for that one.
I couldn't focus properly.
It says to assume the position I find most natural.
You assume this position a lot during tests.
I can sense the entirety of the universe.
I can feel the twinklings of the stars.
That's nice...
Tomo-chan, next card.
Okay, this one.
I see it.
It's a circle.
I'm psychic!
At least get it right a second time first!
Next, I'll work on my foresight.
What happened to clairvoyance?
I have no need for it.
Foresight will be more
useful in the future.
You're foreseeing that it'll be, anyway.
Any day trader needs it!
Rikka-chan, are you
going to be a day trader?
I will see the enemy before he sees me!
Did she mistake "day trader" for "date raider"?
But anyway, how will
you develop foresight?
I will predict whether the next person to pass through that door is a boy or a girl.
Oh, I see.
Tyrant's Eye, activate!
Boy!
Girl!
Foresight Trials
I can't feel my intuition!
That's kind of redundant...
It didn't really make sense, either.
I-I'm not done yet!
I will now unleash the
true power of the Tyrant's Eye!
Boy!
Huh?
...friendless!
Takanashi...
No, I mean, because
you're a girl, not a boy, so...
Um...
Rikka-chan stopped trying to develop ESP after that.
To Be Continued
O ye who (gen gen gen) consumes the abyss (ius ius ius)
shin'en wo (ten ten ten) kurau mono (sai sai sai)
It's time for the (ang ang ang) Dark Carnival (uish uish uish)
magamagashii (han han han) shanikusai (mon mon mon)
kecchaku wo tsuke ni kita zo
I'm here to settle our score
Just when I thought the wind seemed restless today
myou ni kaze ga atsumaru to omottara
See that?
That was my power!
It seems the Great Mother calls for my aid yet again
watashi wa futatabi mother ni michibikareta you da
Wow, I even
scared myself!
No common humans shall be harmed
ippanjin wa kizutsuke ya shinai
The Organization will take care of everything after
ato wa soshiki ga umaku yatteru
kisama no shiru watashi ga watashi no subete dewa nai
The "me" you see before you is not all there is to me
Enough of this foolish act; you can see, can you not?
kudaran shibai wa yose mieteru no de arou
kono karada ni mo naretekita koto da shi
How accustomed to this body I have grown!
It's about time we began our feast!
soro soro hajimeyou dewa nai ka
I just haven't
unleashed
my true power
watashi no ushiro ni wa
I have at my beck and call
yon no daitenshi to nanajuuni no akuma ga iru
Four archangels and the seventy-two demons
honki wo amari dasaseruna yo
Don't make me get too serious on you
I won't deal the final blow; you may live
todome wa sasanai de oiteyaru
watashi ni michi wo akesasetakerya
If you seek that I may open your path
Maybe you can bring a god or two with you
kamisama demo tsuretekuru to ii