Kotatsnail
You guys here?
Asleep as always.
Sure, it is the Napping Club, but...
Didn't we all agree that we'd
clean the clubroom today?
Wake up!
You want me to drag you out—
Hey—
Fine, then!
I'll just lift this blasted—
1.5 liters.
Are you really asleep?!
I told you, she's Mongolian.
Cut it out already, will you?!
She's out!
Now to put the kotatsu
away before she can—
What's with this thing?!
Hi-ya!
To Be Continued
O ye who (gen gen gen) consumes the abyss (ius ius ius)
shin'en wo (ten ten ten) kurau mono (sai sai sai)
It's time for the (ang ang ang) Dark Carnival (uish uish uish)
magamagashii (han han han) shanikusai (mon mon mon)
kecchaku wo tsuke ni kita zo
I'm here to settle our score
Just when I thought the wind seemed restless today
myou ni kaze ga atsumaru to omottara
See that?
That was my power!
It seems the Great Mother calls for my aid yet again
watashi wa futatabi mother ni michibikareta you da
Wow, I even
scared myself!
No common humans shall be harmed
ippanjin wa kizutsuke ya shinai
The Organization will take care of everything after
ato wa soshiki ga umaku yatteru
kisama no shiru watashi ga watashi no subete dewa nai
The "me" you see before you is not all there is to me
Enough of this foolish act; you can see, can you not?
kudaran shibai wa yose mieteru no de arou
kono karada ni mo naretekita koto da shi
How accustomed to this body I have grown!
It's about time we began our feast!
soro soro hajimeyou dewa nai ka
I just haven't
unleashed
my true power
watashi no ushiro ni wa
I have at my beck and call
yon no daitenshi to nanajuuni no akuma ga iru
Four archangels and the seventy-two demons
honki wo amari dasaseruna yo
Don't make me get too serious on you
I won't deal the final blow; you may live
todome wa sasanai de oiteyaru
watashi ni michi wo akesasetakerya
If you seek that I may open your path
Maybe you can bring a god or two with you
kamisama demo tsuretekuru to ii