Faculty Room
A meeting of representatives?
Well, a lot of new hobby groups were formed this spring,
so we don't have enough rooms to go around.
I see.
Is this the start of the Sixth Great War of Magic for the Holy Clubroom?!
What a shocking development!
Keep it down.
So...
The Student Council wants representatives from each hobby group to present their activities.
Of course, they want your group
to participate, too.
So it's a meeting to take rooms away from groups without real activities?
I wouldn't say that...
It definitely is.
The meeting is after school today.
Make sure you send a representative.
Would that be you, Togashi-kun?
No.
I think it would be Rikka-chan.
l
I wanna fallin' love
yokan yume ga tsudzuku
The dream will go on and on
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
We made a promise, but deep inside,
I'm still scared it might all disappear
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
hitori ja nai tte shinjitai no ni
Even though I want to believe you'll always be there
omoitsudzuketeru dake de shiawase nante ienai ne
Being in love with each other isn't happiness all by itself
utsuro na jishin seotteitemo
Even if I pretend that it's all that matters
kimi ga warau
You just laugh
soshite watashi no yuuki ni naru
And you always give me strength
l
hitotsu no kotoba de kimi no sekai wo kaeraretara
But if one simple word can change your whole world
But if one simple word can change your whole world
l
futatsu no koi ga shinka suru
Then two loves will start to progress
Then two loves will start to progress
l
hontou da yo
That's the truth
That's the truth
l
meguraseta mayoi ga mitsuketa kotae wa
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
itsudemo kimi ni michibikareta
You always led me to the answer
Even if I can't work up the courage to do it
l
sunao ni tsutaetai
I want to tell you everything
I want to tell you everything
l
ko
ro
aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
kokoro aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
kokoro
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
l
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real
come
on
voice
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
Hobby Group Representatives Meeting
So this is where the Sabbath will be held.
The supreme decision-making body!
The world's very future will be decided here!
They all look kind of scary.
They're putting everything they've got
into getting or keeping a room.
Can you do it, Rikka?
Hobby Group Representatives Meeting
Dekomori.
Yes, Master?
Effective immediately, I hereby transfer the leadership of the Oriental Magick Society into your hands.
Hobby Group Representatives Meeting
But it's the Napping Society...
I am of the darkness.
To expose myself in public is to endanger everyone present.
So you don't want to go.
Yuuta, if I were to attend this meeting,
I would inevitably expose these civilians to the
dark energies which spill forth from the Tyrant's Eye.
You just don't want to go, right?
Hey.
Um...
The meeting's about to start.
Maybe you should've gone
with her, Togashi-kun.
I would if I could.
They said only one representative per club.
Master, you truly are of the darkness!
The Illusive... Siesta Labyrinth
With such a dark aura about you, none can even think to approach!
She's just nervous.
Next, the Oriental Magick...
Napping? Society in Summer?
That would be me.
I have arrived.
Right...
Tell us about your activities.
Unfortunately, that is information
I cannot give you.
What?
Learning of our society comes
with the risk of losing one's life.
Such an event will compel the Fallen Angels t—
You wrote her a script?
Well, she wouldn't be able
to wing it, you know.
The Oriental Magick Napping
Society in Summer is...
The poor rabble!
Not a word could they raise in response!
Victory!
That's my master!
Your dark aura overwhelmed them!
So she didn't manage to say anything useful
before getting kicked out?
Kicked out? More like she left on her own.
We explore historical resources of
cultural significance in order to...
Could you repeat that a little more clearly?
I feel sick...
The end.
Why didn't you go in with her?
They said one representative per group.
Fist, palm, knee!
You could've taken advantage of the fact that you two are dating.
To the depths of darkness with thee!
Like...
Rikka and I are of one body and soul!
Two, but one!
No one will ever be able to...
...separate us!
No, that's way too embarrassing.
But you guys have been like that 24/7 lately.
Right?
So passionate.
Maybe in your dreams!
Not to mention that would've gotten us kicked out for sure.
Hello!
Sensei?
Why the sudden visit?
We have an emergency?!
The Student Council did?
Well, they said it didn't seem like you were really using your room.
So they asked me what I thought.
Well, can't say I didn't expect that.
Hey! Give that back!
What happened after that?
What is wrong with you?
That's my cracker!
They asked me to check exactly
what you were doing and report back.
Hold it right there!
So what do you use the room for?
Give it back, you freaking first-year!
You don't know?
Where do you think you're going?
I don't.
Aren't you our supervisor?
Stop, will you?!
I know, right?
The Student Council asked me
the exact same thing.
Right...
You had a magic circle, so I said you
probably did things related to magic...
Give it back!
Mjollnir... Tornado!
But you're not.
Yeah, we're not.
But we do nap!
You were awake?
Yeah.
Napping?
Yes.
It's in the name, right?
"Napping Society in Summer."
Oh, it is! So you're a napping club?
Yes!
Well, it's not like "magick" turning into "napping" makes much of a difference.
No, it does!
Napping Contest
A napping club is more than okay!
There are napping competitions?
That's right.
There are some really major
tournaments in Europe.
How do you tell a good nap from a bad one?
Well, you get rated on how fast
you can fall asleep, your posture,
how deep you sleep, and how long
you can sleep, and the total is your score!
You knew about this, Kumin-senpai?
Yup!
I've been reading up on napping, you know!
And a friend of mine just happens to
supervise a siesta club at another school.
Siesta?
Magic?
Indeed, Master!
It means "nap" in Spanish!
Wait, so if we have a match
against them as part of our activities...
...the Student Council will have to
acknowledge our legitimacy!
That's right!
To
Subject
Maple Hill High School Siesta Club Supervisor
So should I send an e-mail to the
other school for a practice match?
Yes, please.
Though, actually, Kumin-senpai's
the only member who's been napping.
Jumping straight into a match
would be pretty rough.
Don't worry!
Napping isn't difficult at all!
I can teach you!
Really?
Yeah! Leave it to me!
The darkness falls!
Death!
Look out for trains now!
I never knew there was so much to napping.
There sure is!
It's actually pretty hard to nap well.
The way the top nappers do it is so beautiful, you can't help but be amazed!
Really?
Yeah!
Their posture, and the relaxed
expression on their faces...
They sleep at the perfect depth,
just short of what you'd call a deep sleep...
They almost look like...
Huh?
Huh?!
She's asleep!
But after hearing her talk about all that, you see her in a whole different light.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you from the
Ginkgo High School Napping Club?
Yes, we are.
My name is Nemuri Sui, and
I'm from the Maple Hill Siesta Club.
Siesta Club President
Nemuri Sui
What? The Siesta Club?
Wh-What's this?!
She has an aura of sleepiness
radiating from her entire being!
It's like she's made of the
very essence of sleep itself!
I can't fight it, Master!
I'm being drawn... in...
No! Dekomori!
Our supervisor told us that we were challenged to a match, which is rare in these parts,
so I thought to pay my respects.
Oh, thank you for coming all this way.
But...
"But"?
It seems you aren't deserving of them.
Huh?
As far as I can see, you do not
truly pursue the art of napping.
I assume you are just
another club that fools around.
B-Bullseye!
Don't worry.
Most of the so-called "napping clubs" out there are just like yours.
But our Siesta Club takes
napping very seriously.
Please refrain from requesting
a match just for fun.
W-We're very sorry.
I understand.
Well then, I will tell our supervisor that the match is canceled.
It's not just for fun.
We're not fooling around either.
Kumin-senpai?
The Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer is always serious about its activities!
Right, everyone?
Huh?
U-Um...
Togashi-kun!
Er... Uh...
Dekomori!
M-Master!
Huh? Wh...
P...
Precisely!
Oh?
Then should I take your challenge
as a duel instead?
Of course.
For the Tyrant's Eye,
all battles are fought to the death!
I am prepared to lose everything!
Hardcore, Master!
Should we lose this impending
battle, I hereby swear to...
disband our society!
What?!
Are you retarded?!
Quit being reckless and think before you act!
When locked in battle,
one must be able to adapt oneself—
It's ready!
So this is what they use in competitions?
Yep!
It meets the specifications of the
High School Napping Association of Japan!
Pro-sized beds are a little bigger.
"Pro"?!
Team matches are done five on five.
You're judged on how fast you can fall asleep,
your technique, and other rules.
Sounds complicated.
Well then, let's give it a try.
No need to think about your posture for now.
Just concentrate on falling asleep.
I have to go to Drama Club, you know.
If you go, our club'll get disbanded for sure.
Fine, whatever!
Falling asleep is easier said than done.
Just close your eyes for now.
Huh? What's that?
Is it Takanashi-san?
Y-Yuuta...
What on Earth is she doing?
Yuuta!
No way!
What are you doing?
Y-You misunderstand!
This is, um, well...
Yuuta...
I-I can't move...
It's just sleep paralysis?!
But of course!
Unlike you, Master does not think about evil and indecent things!
I never said anything.
And what exactly do you mean by "indecent"?
W-Well...
Gut-ter-brain.
Silence, Fake Summer!
Whoa—
Stop that!
PLACEHOLDER
I hate you, you little...
Hey, you should be sleeping!
Next, we'll nap outside.
It's important to be able to
sleep in any environment.
But here?
That's kind of hard...
Master!
The light! Agents of the Light are assaulting me!
Schwarzschild Prototype Mark IV!
Let's swim!
A little random, don't you think?!
Not at all.
It's the best way to get you
nice and tired for a good nap.
But why the pool?
It's way too cold to swim in right now.
Oh, I see. What a shame.
Nothing beats swimming.
You can crawl in the pool,
then crawl into bed!
That wasn't funny!
Hey, come over here!
Is that... Isshiki?
What's he doing?
My guess is that he caught wind of what Kumin-senpai's doing,
so he's trying to show that he can nap, too.
Let's head back.
Yeah.
Kumin-senpai!
Napping's a lot harder than I thought it'd be.
Yeah, forcing yourself to sleep isn't easy.
Worry not.
The Tyrant's Eye is omnipotent.
You are the best, Master!
This isn't the time for that.
We disband if we lose.
Then we simply need to win.
Go, Yuuta!
Me?!
We'll be fine if we do this together.
Where does all that confidence come from?
Nice timing, Dekomori!
Death!
What the heck is that rig?
Can we really win like this?
Shouldn't we come up
with some sort of strategy?
But this is a sleeping contest.
If only there were a reliable way to fall asleep.
I know!
There's a really simple way,
now that I think about it!
The Night Before the Contest
Until the darkness vanishes with the dawn,
we shall fight hand in hand!
Naturally.
If we stay awake together
without a wink of sleep,
we'll definitely be sleepy for the match.
I see.
It won't make for a very pretty nap, though.
It's not like we can control what happens
once we're sound asleep,
so shouldn't we shoot for points by falling asleep quickly?
You're right.
Good night.
Yeah.
Good night!
Why? Why?!
Give them up already, Super Pauper.
Take this!
Parallel Poverty King Explosion!
No! My fishcake factory!
Yay!
50-perfect combo!
I am...
a shining monochrome monster.
I found myself in a virtual world...
Yuuta...
Hero...
What the devil?!
Good morning, Hero.
Togashi-kun, does this mean...
That the Dark Flame Master
has fallen to the Dark Side?
No!
I'm sorry.
Old habits die hard.
I know the Hero and the Tyrant's Eye are bound by the contract of lovers.
Here, have it back.
What the heck?!
Seeya!
Hey, wait.
She's gone.
Salt, Kuzuha! Purify this space!
Wait, I thought you guys were going to stay up all night.
Crap!
I get it now!
It was all part of the Magical Devil Girl's plan!
No, it's our own fault for falling asleep!
Hurry!
Now then,
the Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer of Ginkgo High School
will face the Siesta Club of Maple Hill High School in a practice match.
Wait a minute here.
First
Siestant
Nasutaka Fujiko
Second
Siestant
Ichiba Parumu
Th-There's no way we can win this!
Third
Siestant
Tenbaku Youko
Fourth
Siestant
Utsutsutouge Toromi
Final
Siestant
Nemuri Sui
I can't even tell if they're awake or not!
They are residents of the
dream world, without a doubt!
Danger.
You will disband if you lose, as we agreed.
The world could do without a joke group that is a napping club in name alone.
N-Now what?
There's absolutely no way we can win!
We all slept so well that
we're practically glowing!
First
Siestant
Takanashi Rikka
Second
Siestant
Dekomori Sanae
The only thing we can do is...
Third
Siestant
Togashi Yuuta
...apologize right now and hope for the best.
Fourth
Siestant
Nibutani Shinka
No!
Final
Siestant
Tsuyuri Kumin
We won't lose!
Our club isn't so half-baked!
Kumin-senpai...
When I first met Rikka-chan, I felt that...
Oh, really?
Yes, really.
That is to say, our true goal is to discover the Unseen Horizon,
but our activities are not limited to that alone.
That is what our society is!
I felt that I could get along
with her and her club.
With her?
But she's got eighth-grade syndrome.
Yeah, but how do I put this?
Not many people understand her,
but the way she gives it her all and how serious she is about it
is exactly how our Napping Society is.
Kumin...
The Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
gave it their all having naps,
having fun,
and having vanishment!
That's why we won't lose.
We're the strongest!
Yes!
Reality, be rent!
Synapse, break!
Vanishment, this world!
This world of slumber is ours.
Leave at once!
Avalon Smasher!
Mjollnir Hammer!
Out!
I am the Dark Flame Master.
Be engulfed by the Dark Flame and—
Out!
Why me?!
Leg cramp!
Out!
And now...
...only two remain.
NREM Killer: Circadian Rhythm Disruptor!
NREM Killer      Circadian Rhythm Disruptor
Destiny Ring!
Destiny Ring
Why?!
With your power, you could stand atop the world if you wanted to.
But you see, I love that place.
Y-You...
That's why I'll protect it.
Three Parts Wake.
Kumin-senpai.
Kumin-senpai!
Togashi-kun... Everyone...
We did it!
We won!
Gratitude, Kumin.
Really?
What about them?
They left.
They admitted complete defeat!
Then we don't have to disband!
Of course!
I shall resume my fight with
Fake Summer tomorrow!
Can't you just give it up?!
What's so funny?
I had a fun dream during the match.
What kind?
I was with you guys, and...
But was it really a dream?
I release the power concealed within.
Lightning Blast!
With this, I am now able to use lightning-based attacks.
Let me try!
I want to try, too!
Freaking first-year!
Quit messing with our costumes!
fake
So you have come, Fake Summer.
It goes with everything!
fake
Quit messing around!
Don't you look away!
You little...
Looks like nothing changed in the end.
We don't even bother to nap.
Yeah, but being able to sleep here
makes me the happiest person in the world.
Good night!
Take this!
Yuuta, look out!
What was that for?!
Lightning, Dekomori!
Roger!
To Be Continued
Don't just ignore me!
mebuita yamiyo ga haran he to hakou
The night falls again, bringing with it conflict
wakuwaku suru nee
Isn't it exciting?
nanatsu no oto eigou yori hanatarete
The seven of the scales echo forth from the ends of eternity
dokidoki suru nee
Isn't it thrilling?
matsui no rakuin anshou ni hirameku
The mark of the Mighty Hammer glitters from the sunken depths
mada tsudzukeru ki na no
You still haven't gotten over it yet?
ai no setsuri ni kyokkou matataku
The Aurora flashes upon the Providence of Love
mou yamenasai
Cut it out already
bokura wa hitotsu ni nari
We converge and become one
ten wo kakete
Flying through the sky
hokori wo sakebi chiru
We scream proud and burst
hanabi no you da
Like a rocket
kagayaki wa setsuna ni hazeta
In an instant, the sparkling is rent away
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
gusha wa tsukikage ni kyomou wo idaku
The fool holds, of the moonlight, dark delusions
game ga bokura wo
If this game exists
oitsumeru tame ni aru naraba
only so we may lose all hope
semete kuchinu hodo no baka de aritai
Then may my foolishness never die so long as it goes on
reiki suru tamashi de hoeta
Charged with lightning, I screamed forth from my soul
Van!shment th!s world!!
Vanishment this world!