Come to think of it, a story where we both escape our deaths would've been nice as well.
Something like in Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid or Bonnie and Clyde?
Or a story where we both fight a common enemy.
But the strong point here is the battle of two comrades.
Maybe a battle for our homeland? For our families?
Something like Romeo and Juliet?
A setting like that would be a bit too predictable.
We could have you kill Yuuta by mistake.
So Dark Flame Master gets the deathly role of someone like Mercutio or Tybalt?
But wouldn't that be a bit far-fetched as our setting?
It's enjoyable precisely because situations like that can't actually happen.
You're right.
I really wouldn't want to come to hate him just because he's playing our enemy.
No, no, that wasn't supposed to mean I like him or anything.
That's it...
Dark Flame Master ignores his contract with me and falls in love with you.
You're talking about our setting, right?
Driven by anger I have to fight you!
And that's when the Dark Flame Master Robot, controlled by Yuuta, enters
to fight me!
What a complex development!
Just saying it out loud makes me sad for some reason...
Master, you're crying for real!
Please don't cry!
Something like that will never happen until my death!
Who knows...
You're cute, after all...
No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
No! No! No! No! No! No!
No way! No way! No way! No way! No way! No way! No way! No way! No way!
Schwarz Sechs Prototype Mk II!
Gungnir!
Gun Twinkle!
It tickles!
I'm never going to forgive you for stealing Yuuta!
Are you doing this on purpose?!
Stop it!
It tickles!