Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You looked this way
and saw me pouting with a frown ❤
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I was just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
matte miru no
That's all I really wanted ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
But the things I mumbled to myself
after "Nothing" were
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
hazukashii kara
Way too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask me what I said
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing us together
mou hajimatteta
Had already started then ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
Dandelion Kindergarten
Priestess of... the Melody
Hirakata
Missing Cat!!
Missing Cat !!
(
Name: Dodomen  Female
Breed: imxed breed with some Persian.
Breed: mixed breed with some Persian.
Age: 5 years. Fur color: gray. Size: Big.
Characteristics: Spunky, sleeps a lot.
Please contact us if you find her.
Contact:
Class 2-4,
Tsuyuri Kumin
To Be Continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?