For Sale
Reality, be rent.
Synapse, break.
Vanishment,
this world!
Avalon Smasher!
How long are you going to keep acting like this?
Is it fun?
Is it fun acting like a selfish little kid?
Gun Twinkle!
Do you hate Mama?
No.
Are you trying to make things
difficult for Grandpa and Grandma?
No!
You know well enough that
there's nothing you can do!
That you have to accept it!
What do you want?
There's nothing we can do.
Evil Eye.
Stop that!
No...
No!
Our house is gone.
Papa is gone too.
And your "Unseen Horizon"...
...exists.
The Unseen Horizon exists.
You...
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You looked this way
and saw me pouting with a frown ❤
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I was just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
matte miru no
That's all I really wanted ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
But the things I mumbled to myself
after "Nothing" were
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
hazukashii kara
Way too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask me what I said
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing us together
mou hajimatteta
Had already started then ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
I agree that she has to accept it, Touka-san.
Yuuta...
And I think she understands that she does.
She understands, and that's
why she's acting like this.
Accepting something is easier said than done.
There are so many things in this world that are hard to accept.
Some things happen so fast.
Before you can get your head around it, it's all over.
Togashi
You're not running from the truth.
You're not trying to ignore it either.
Third Period
Self-Study
But you wonder, "Does everything in life have to be so normal?"
Third Period
Self-Study
Self Notes
My Life
Everyone says that it does.
They say that's reality.
But does it have to be that way?
That is reality.
Everyone accepts it and moves on.
Because that's what it means to grow up.
Oh, I'm sure.
But for her...
Rikka!
The Exile... of the Two
Oh! Welcome back.
Where's Rikka?
She came back a minute ago in a taxi.
She might be at the beach.
Your friends said they were going there to light some fireworks.
Thank you very much.
The time has come to unleash the
Black Flame Dragon upon the world!
Wait! Wait!
What's wrong with her?
Oh, you tagged along?
You see this here? Want it?
Go fetch!
What the heck?!
These are fun to watch!
Y-Yeah!
Togashi-kun and Rikka-chan
sure are taking their time.
I wonder where they went.
Just think about it.
A boy and a girl on vacation with their
friends at the beach sneaking out at night...
They must have encountered
warriors from a parallel world!
Togashi-kun!
Where's Rikka?!
She isn't here.
That girl...
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Togashi-kun?
Ah, to be young!
Maybe it did turn into a bloodbath!
Bloodbath is a powerful barrier spell.
Fake Summer
Yuuta?!
Jeez. I almost didn't make it.
Why are you here?
I should be asking you that.
Where do you think you're going?
The Administration Bureau holds too much influence in this area.
The barrier is far too strong.
I'm retreating.
So you're going home?
dare ga kidzuketa darou
Did anybody notice it was there?
hikari no mukou de koku naru kage ni
The shadow beyond the light, growing ever darker
Yuuta.
Where did you find the power of the Dark Flame?
kako ga tooku de sakenda
The past was so distant, I had to scream
I told you, it doesn't—
senaka mukete wa mimi wo fusaideru
Turn around, and cover my ears
It came to me when my friends were talking one time.
They were all excited, talking about going out for fun.
sou naku kara tte yowai to kimenaide
Don't call me weak just because I cry
But I wasn't.
It was like I was different.
nakanai kara tte tsuyoi to omowanaide
Don't think I'm strong just because I don't
I felt like I was alone, like
I didn't belong in this world.
kimi ga nigiru te
The warmth of your hand
atatakasa wo
As you hold mine
Your dark mind recalled your
memories from another world?
shinjite mite mo ii ka na
Maybe I can try trusting it now
That's probably what I was thinking back then.
That's why...
yatto kidzuita
I've finally realized
Go away!
youyaku mitsuketa
I've finally found it
What's wrong? Is it interference from the Administration Bureau?
namida de boyaketa shinjitsu
The truth that was hazy through my tears
No.
Hey, why—
Our eyes met.
Huh?
boku wa boku de ii to
You said I could be myself
atama wo nadenagara
As you pat me on the head
nemuru kimi no yokogao ga ima
As I watch you sleep here next to me
atarashii kimochi wo terashita
A whole new feeling lights up in me
Now we are bound by an even stronger contract, Dark Flame Master.
Whatever you say.
arigatou soba ni itekurete
Thank you for standing by me
Be engulfed by the Dark Flame—
Stop that!
mebuita yo hajimari no tane ga
The seed has already started to sprout
Oh, a text from Togashi-kun.
What's it say?
"Takanashi-san wants to go back home. I'm taking her there."
So they're going back?
They're not even trying to hide it!
Hide what?
If you don't drop the cutesy act, I'm outta here.
Have you ever gone out with a guy?
Of course!
I went out with Takashi-kun back in kindergarten.
Oh, but then my family went with my
dad when he was transferred overseas.
I had private tutoring instead of going to elementary or middle school.
Does she really have no idea?
Ow!
Sorry!
It stings!
My body has been burned by the sun, just like Icarus's wings.
Wh-What do you want?
Stupid
mori
Oh, nothing. I just thought it would be nice of me to wash your back for you.
Stupid
mori
I happen to have this really nice sponge.
Y-You don't have to.
Come on, don't be shy!
Stay away from me!
Togashi Yuuta
No Subject
I'll be going home.
Rikka is with me.
Don't worry about her.
Togashi Yuuta
No Subject
I'll be going home.
Rikka is with me.
Don't worry about her.
Togashi Yuuta
No Subject
I'll be going home.
Rikka is with me.
Don't worry about her.
It's gotten pretty late.
Yuuta! I can't get into my room!
Takanashi
The code has been changed!
You just forgot to bring your key.
Man... Guess there's no other option.
I'm back.
No one's home?
Maybe...
An Administration Bureau raid?!
Stop! Anyone but my family!
Don't say things like that!
Oh, here we go.
Kuzuha and Yumeha are at summer camp, and Mom is at work.
Stay on your toes.
It might be a fabrication.
It's not.
Let's see...
They're all coming back tomorrow.
So that means...
We're alone tonight?
Huh?
Which way was the bathroom again?
Kumin-senpai?
You were awake too, Isshiki-kun?
Why are you up this late?
I thought the moon would look pretty when it got completely dark out,
so I was thinking of going on a walk.
Care to join me?
O-One second!
Just one second!
Huh? A walk?
If you want to go, then go. I'm hanging up.
That's the vaguest advice ever!
Did you stop caring about your
friends after you got a girlfriend?!
When did I get a girlfriend?
Did you already forget that I created an opportunity for you to talk to her before the entrance ceremony?
Huh?
Sorry, gotta go!
Wait, hold—
Leave my things alone!
Yuuta, what's this?
No idea.
That's enough. Put it away.
Is it an ultimate mechanism which
even the Tyrant's Eye mustn't know of?
No.
Whatever. Let me just show you.
You take this and put it here.
And if you bring your arm down like this...
Voilà!
Wow!
That's amazing, Yuuta!
Keep your tears to yourself.
I grant thee honor from the
bottom of my Tyrant's Eye.
Keep that to yourself too.
Anything in particular that you want to eat?
Just so you know, we don't have much in the way of groceries,
so I can't make anything like
what you get from Touka-san.
I'd rather fight the final boss
without equipment than eat that.
So you'd rather die.
Wanna go to the convenience store, then?
It's late anyway.
The convenience store?
We're getting rations from the convenience store?
What? You don't like them?
The Priestess forbids eating food from there.
She forces me to eat her cooking.
You should be thanking her for that, you know.
I want to try it!
Thank you very much.
Sure this is all you want?
Bonito
I saw you eating one at school.
I grew curious of their assembly.
You pull this down to split the skin...
Take both sides and pull them apart.
That's so cool.
That's cool?
It's good.
Touka-san'd kill me if she saw you.
Here. Have some fried chicken.
The taste of adventure.
What kind of taste is that?
What does yours taste like?
Wanna see for yourself?
Here.
Too spicy for you?
Yuuta!
Sorry, sorry.
Have some of these.
Red is dangerous!
Not falling for it this time?
Mana replenished.
All right. Let's go home.
Yuuta.
I don't want to go home.
I want to bask in the moonlight.
Hey!
What do you think?
It's night!
We're alone!
Is she trying to say, "Everything's
ready for you, so just confess already!"
Yeah, sure. How should I know?
Come on! Don't be cruel!
You owe me for being kind enough to talk to you before the entrance ceremony!
That again? I'm hanging up.
Please wait, good sir!
What now?
How're you doing with Takanashi-san?
We just had dinner.
She forgot her house key.
Wait, you mean you're alone together?
Yeah.
I knew something was up, but
I didn't know you'd gone that far.
What are you talking about?
Whatever you're imagining,
it's not happening.
Why not?
"Why not?" We're talking about Rikka here.
Eighth-grade syndrome alert, man.
But you're in high school!
But...
Yuuta.
Hello?
Hey!
Come on...
It sounded like you'd
be on the phone
for a while.
I'll go back first.
Kumin
Alone with Rikka...
No, no, no!
No way, no how!
Love's gotta be the last thing in that delusional head of hers.
Yuuta,
is this the Mjollnir Hammer?
No chance at all.
Stop doing that. You're stretching it.
Just fold the sleeves up.
How do you think these things up?
Come on. It's late.
You can sleep in this room,
so brush your teeth and—
It smells like Yuuta.
Stop!
Why?
It smells like Yuuta.
Just stop!
It's embarrassing!
I'm turning off the light.
Night is when the Tyrant's Eye is most active!
It is already—
Just go to sleep.
Seriously.
It smells like me?
I told you to sleep.
My heart is filled with unease.
They may be close.
We must be on guard.
Look...
I'm turning it off.
My heart is filled with unease.
It'll go away if you sleep.
My heart is pounding.
That'll go away too.
I'm excited!
This isn't a theme park commercial!
I'm gonna explode!
Why?!
I don't know!
Wh-Whatever. Just go to sleep.
Wait!
Hey...
Don't go...
No way...
She...
Yuuta, close your eyes.
Huh?!
Just for a second.
Just do it for a second.
A-Are you kidding me?
Does she...
Does she really...
A-Am I...
even okay with this?
No, wait...
But...
What's this?
A piece of powerful magic.
It's a symbol of our new contract.
Could you put it somewhere less conspicuous?
It's best here.
With this, your powers of darkness are multiplied.
You can unleash the Dark Buster, which is even stronger than the Dark Flame.
I'm going to bed.
Eighth-grade syndrome is eighth-grade syndrome, no matter the place or time.
But I guess this is okay—
Or is it?
Well, whatever.
My heart is pounding.
This presence...
Who goes there?!
Yuuta.
To Be Continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?