You're traveling light.
It's cheaper to just buy what I need when I get there.
Thanks for helping out.
It's okay.
I am the Dark Flame Master!
I wield the power of the flames of dark—
Here.
You can have it.
Thank you very much.
Also, there's something important I need to tell you.
I'm really grateful.
It's thanks to you that I can
leave without any worries.
Thank you very much.
It's nothing.
Sis...
Thanks.
Mama should be home soon.
If I don't leave now, I'll miss my flight.
Give her a hug for me, okay?
Sis...
Come on, Yumeha!
Bye-bye!
Let me see the children sometime!
Yumeha, what?!
I taught her that.
Sure, I will.
Well then.
Yeah...
I'll email you.
It's been three weeks since
Rikka took off her eyepatch.
She's been trying her best
to come to terms with that.
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Come on, why ginger roast again?
Less complaining, more eating!
One-Winged Fallen Angel
Ginger roast!
Kuzuha, help Yumeha change clothes.
Come here!
Ginger roast!
Yuuta, Takanashi's here.
Rikka!
Coming!
Go-Go... Good morning!
Good morning!
I'll go get Yuuta.
U-Um...
Yeah?
P-Please get Yuuta for me!
Sure!
You know, conversations
have this thing called "flow".
If the other person gets what you mean, you don't have to state the obvious.
But Nibutani said that I should have an answer to everything, even if it adds nothing.
Yeah, but still...
It's difficult.
This is what you get for hanging on to your eighth-grader syndrome for so long.
What now?
She also told me to change the way I talk.
Really?
Really, Yuuta.
May I be of your service?
You're not a maid.
What do you require?
Nor some rich girl.
What'll it be?
I'll pass.
What?
Yeah, I think you'd better stick to that one.
She said it's not good 'cause it sounds like I'm trying to brush you off.
Well, I guess so...
What you do want?
If you're gonna get it wrong on purpose,
be less obvious about it.
Stop in the name of death.
Morning.
Don't "morning" me!
Today is the day I free Master from the
deathly demon eating away at her soul!
Sanae.
I already told you that I'm over all that.
Don't call me "Sanae"!
Prepare yourself!
Hey!
I really thought I was about
to meet my death...
Be careful!
Sorry...
...Like death I am!
Rend reality!
Shatter synapse!
Vanishment... this world!
Master!
I told you.
Wake up!
I left that behind me.
Master... Master...
Uh, isn't it about time you—
Shut the death up! I'll never give in!
I'll crush the deathly devil
possessing Master and save her!
Rikka...
What?
Are you...
okay with this?
Never mind.
I guess it'd be irresponsible of me to say that.
She got scouted?
Yeah, her performance at the fair was quite popular.
Ah, the one she did with Dekomori?
They were looking for someone who was up for crazy acting like that.
I'm happy the fair turned out so well for you guys.
What do you mean? Nothing happened to me.
Huh? Nothing?
This, from the person who confessed to Takanashi?
Your face is creeping me out.
I heard you're like two lovebirds on the way to school every morning.
Oh well...
Then look at how hard I failed!
Kumin was just asleep, wasn't she?
That doesn't count as a reject—
Of course not! I'm not giving up just yet!
I'm not giving up!
I get it, I get it...
Um...
Takanashi?
What's up?
Please be friends with me.
Wait, what?
She's...
We'd love to!
That felt like a confession!
My heart's still racing!
Me too!
Library
Come on, it's our lunch break!
Isn't this the librarian's job?
Library
Yeah. Is this all of it?
Yep. I don't even know what
the teachers were thinking.
Library
The class reps aren't there to do all their work!
Oh, I heard you got scouted by the Drama Club.
Yeah, kinda.
What're you gonna do?
Dunno. Why do you ask?
Dunno.
Togashi...
Do you regret it at all?
Regret what?
What happened with Takanashi.
Why would I?
No reason.
Now that she's overcome
her eighth-grader syndrome,
Tooka doesn't have to worry for her anymore.
She's getting along better with her mother too.
There's nothing to regret.
That's right...
That's right.
I see.
Oh, did you see them too, Takanashi?
Yeah.
Aren't they awesome?
Yeah, I kinda liked it.
Didn't expect that!
Then let's go to their next show together!
That sounds great!
A cold wind blows.
Dekomori sways in the deathly breeze.
Left and right...
Thinking of Master.
Master...
Hey.
MIKAN
What's up, junior high schooler?
You seem down.
Don't talk to me, commoner.
Don't call me that!
Besides, you're one too.
MIKAN
I'm different! I'm the
wielder of the Mjolnir Maul!
Oh. Well, if you've got the energy to do that, you should be fine.
MIKAN
What the death are you doing?
Can't you tell?
It's a love letter!
To Kumin
Isshiki Makoto
You still haven't given up on that?
What're you doing?
Nothing.
Master, I've been waiting for you!
Deko—
Sanae...
I discovered something amazing today, so I couldn't wait to show it to you!
Look at all these enchanted gems!
Which would you like? C'mon, which?
They all house top-grade enchantments!
Dekomori...
Wait a moment!
They'll look even prettier like this!
Master!
Dekomori...
Yes?
I have something important
to talk to you about.
Yes?
Could it be the Overseers' new—
No.
This society...
I mean,
this club...
is disbanded as of today.
Master?
I think we should each focus on what we want to do in the future.
You too, Dekomori.
What's wrong with you, Master?!
This society was formed to find the Ethereal Horizon and cross over to the other side!
Master!
Enough.
You heard her.
Now give me back the Mabinogion and go graduate junior high.
C'mon, this way.
Let go!
You know,
I think you're just sticking to your guns.
You and Takanashi too.
Let go!
Be quiet!
Let go of me!
It's okay.
No one deathly asked for this.
Wow, that's a lot of stuff.
We don't have much time.
Huh?
I promised Mom I'd clean it all up before she gets home today.
What?!
She'd start worrying again if I didn't.
I don't want to make her worry.
I see.
So, what are we cleaning up?
Let's start with everything on the floor.
Roger.
Whoa, you had one of these too?
This...
Are you taking that down?
Why?
Well...
I don't know what I'm meant to put away and what I'm not.
Okay. Let's take it down.
Yeah. Thanks.
Are you really okay with cleaning up this much?
Yeah. This should put her mind at ease.
Yuuta!
Hm?
Aren't you hungry?
Sure am!
Your mom's gonna be late, right?
Wanna come over?
Can't we go to the store?
We can, I guess...
Are you really sure about this?
Yeah, I am.
Hold the bottom, Yuuta.
You like that, don't you?
It's so cool!
What's cool about that?
Here.
Pretty, huh?
Yeah. But they're just cars.
It's just their headlights shining.
Of course.
Yuuta...
What's up?
Mom wants to visit the grave with me.
Huh?
Dad's.
What do you think?
Well...
I think Mom'd be happy if I went.
Then that's okay, right?
If that's what you wanna do.
Your pinky.
Thanks.
I'm going home ahead.
Hey! Hey, Rikka!
Hey, Rikka!
Ah, Kumin...
Dodomen?
He had a little accident.
Hey, don't scratch at it!
What's wrong?
Thanks...
No way...
The train just left, so sit down.
Okay...
Here.
Thanks.
You've been saying thanks a lot lately.
Hey...
You'll be back, right?
You'll come back after visiting the grave, right?
Yeah. I've got school too.
Yeah. That's right.
Stop!
I told you I wouldn't give up!
Not until my death!
Dekomori...
I'm Master's servant!
I'll stay by your side, even if I must
follow you to the depths of oblivion!
Rend reality!
Shatter synapse!
Vanishment... this world!
Destiny Mjolnir Impulse!
Secret technique!
Dekomori...
Don't touch me!
Rikka.
Rikka...
Why didn't you tell her?
Why didn't you tell her not to go?
Master wanted to hear those words from you!
"I'll look for the Ethereal Horizon!"
"Don't go!"
But she's...
Master said that she was able to protect the
Wicked Eye thanks to the Dark Flame Master!
You were her emotional support!
When the Dark Flame Master told her that the Ethereal Horizon existed, she called me!
When you made your lovers' contract, she called me again!
She was crying! Master was crying!
My Master! The strongest there has ever been!
She trusted you!
Why won't you tell her that the
Wicked Eye's power reigns supreme?!
Why won't you engulf her
in the flames of darkness?!
She's been waiting for that for so, so, so long! All this time!
Why?! Why?!
It hurts.
What if I told her?
How would telling her what she wants to hear make anything better?
Of cours—
There's no Ethereal Horizon.
Her father's dead and buried!
I can't do anything about that!
No matter how much she wishes I could.
Shut up!
No matter what fantasy she invents for herself.
No matter how much power she believes she has.
If something's not real, it's not real!
Shut up!
Have any of your "special attacks" ever worked?!
They don't work on people,
but they work on monsters!
Has your weapon ever materialized?
It...
...never has.
No matter how much you want it to,
or believe it will.
It doesn't exist!
I... I...
I know...
I know!
No...
That wasn't what I wanted to say...
To be continued
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?