Staff Room
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
The Cram Time... of Crucifixion
Cast the spell of 9×7!
Cast the spell of 9×8!
Evil Clown
Revised
edition
Mathematics I
Staff Room
Revised Edition
Mathematics I
Email address
Address book
Takanashi Rikka
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Black Power
Japanese
Mathematics I
Social
Studies
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Incoming mail
Sub
Engrave it upon your soul
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Sub
Engrave it upon your soul
Thanks
To be continued
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?