Media lab
Movie screening area
Far Eastern
Magic Nap Society
of Summer
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Pandora's Lunchbox...
of the Holy Mother
nani mo iwanai senaka ni taishite
When I see you there, walking right in front of me
nante ieba ii no kana
What should I say to make you turn around?
suki ni naru no ni riyuu wa nai no ni
It doesn't take a reason to fall in love with someone
yuuki no nasa ni iiwake bakari
But I need excuses because I'm too shy
ryuuseigun wo nagameteitara
As we looked up to watch all those shooting stars
kirakira tte oto ga suru mitai
I felt like I could almost hear them glittering
sou iu kimochi no yoin sura
I've got a feeling that even that feeling
kimi to nara wakachiaeru
Is something that we can both share
koi no kakera ga ima hitotsu ni
These bits of love are coming together now
yasuppoi kotoba de kazattemo
Even if I dress them in all sorts of fancy words
kimi ni todokanai kamo shirenai
They might not be able to reach your heart
demo nani mo iwanai mama da to kimi ga
But if I don't say anything then you just might
kiechau kamo shirenai
Disappear into the night
ano hoshi mitai ni
Just like a shooting star
ima doko de naiteru no
Where are you, and why are you crying?
doushitara waratte kuremasu ka
What do I need to do to make you smile?
ten wo tsunaide seiza ni shitai
I wish we could be joined together, like a constellation
sono yubi de
By our hands
senaka awase ja nakute kocchi wo muite
Don't walk with your back to me, look this way
soshite tonari wo arukitai yo
And let me walk beside you
Ginkgo Festival
Eastern Magic Napping Society in Summer
miagete goran yoru no hoshi wo
Take a look up above, see the stars out at night
chiisana hoshi no chiisana hikari ga
All those little stars, all those little lights
sasayaka na shiawase wo utatteru
Singing about little, happy things
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
To be continued