I can do it!
Today my foe shall finally meet its death!
Good luck! I know you can do it!
It's so sticky and stinky and lukewarm...
How can people possibly enjoy this?
Hey, has anyone seen my pompo—
Huh? It's gone!
You're amazing, Deko!
Now I can conquer even death itself!
I drank it all!
You didn't drink any of it!
Ah, if it isn't the fake Forest Summer.
I've overcome the barrier known to mortals as "milk",
so by this time next year I'll be looking down on you physically as well!
It stinks!
It's not too late to kneel before me,
unless you want to face your death!
Your nose is dripping.
Staff Room
Your grades in math have been so bad that your teacher came to speak with me personally.
He's been blaming it on me having approved your circle.
I apologize. I have grown too accustomed to the Otherworld's base 0 numerics.
Even so, how could you have only scored two percent on the first year midterms?
Two percent?!
Nana, you're so mean.
Sorry! It just slipped out accidentally.
Accidentally, huh?
You're doing okay in your other subjects, so could you please put some more effort into math?
Rest assured.
From tomorrow I shall unleash my full potential.
Really?
It shall be done.
Great! Then you won't have to worry about me disbanding your circle if you fail your finals.
I'll let your math teacher know the good news.
I'm so glad you're giving it your all!
Excuse us!
Yuuta...
What?
Wh-What should I do?
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
The Cram Time... of Crucifixion
Geez...
I missed club practice all because of you!
You live down to your standing, fake Forest!
You reek of the stench of milk!
Yeah, it really smel—
I'm your senior!
Then behave like one!
Hey!
Master, I've been awaiting your return!
What deathly challenges did you face in the staff room?
I proclaim a state of emergency.
Could it be code blue?
Don't complicate it even more!
And spare me the BGM!
Hey, what happened?
What smells like milk?
Never mind that! Just tell me!
Math?
Yeah.
If she fails her next set of exams, the circle will get disbanded.
Who cares? It's not like we do anything here.
No! This is the Nap Club, beloved by all!
We must use all of our youthful energy to protect it!
Is she sleeping?
I think.
Use your own youthful energy, not mine!
Forest Summer's way more plump than she looks at first.
Is she suffering from brain death?
I don't want to hear that from you!
Well, that's how it goes,
so hopefully they'll calm down and study until fi—
What are you doing?!
I'm divining the answer.
O wise spirits who rule this world and guard all its secrets...
Obey my eye and answer my call!
You still have that set up?!
Dekomori, nice timing!
So, what's the answer?
82 degrees.
Or thereabouts.
You're just guessing?!
This one's wrong too!
You're doing it the right way, but you messed up the multiplication.
Seven times four, huh?
This is quite a discovery.
Four times seven isn't particularly remarkable,
but its palette swap, seven times four, is really powerful!
You get surprised when it casts a high-level spell on you.
That kind of feeling.
I get it!
The difficulty of the sevens row is much higher than you'd expect from a boss of that level!
That's true...
You get fifty-six when you multiply seven by eight.
It makes an ascending sequence, like climbing to the top.
And when you overcome that, you reach the final boss at the nines row.
The first form is seven times nine, sixty-three!
Cast the spell of 9×7!
The second form is eight times nine, seventy-two!
Cast the spell of 9×8!
And then the final form is nine times nine! Eighty-one!
What exactly are you doing?
Anyway, the point is that if you can avoid making such careless mistak—
Okay, let's give them names!
Seven should be the Evil Clown.
It should be something that sounds a bit weaker.
Stop that!
Evil Clown
In the name of the Wicked Eye, I command thee.
May my body and spirit crystallize into pure concentration,
so I may avoid failing my math exams.
Deathly so.
So now you're begging the gods all of a sudden?
I don't beg.
I command by the authority of the Wicked Eye.
Deathly so!
Stop it! You'll bring divine retribution!
Not to mention you're still in junior high!
Why are you praying with her?
I'm my Master's faithful servant.
I must remain at her side, no matter the conflict.
Shouldn't you be worrying about your own entrance exams?
I've already been chosen as one to struggle with death in your high school division.
You?
Oh please, there's gotta be a limit to your delus—
It's true.
I heard that her grades are among the best in her year level.
No way....
She? The best in her year level?
Something's...
...very wrong here!
I hold dominion over all numbers from junior high level and beyond.
Math problems at introductory high school level are nothing for me.
Really? Then how about this one?
Let me take a look.
I see, I see.
Revised
edition
Mathematics I
The answer is x-cubed minus eight.
She's right!
This is the most basic of the basics!
This much must be easy for you, Mas—
You managed to pass your entrance exams at that level?
You're amazing, Master!
You used your hidden powers, didn't you?
She can't recover from that, huh?
It's like getting up to 300% damage in Sm**h Br**hers.
May I somehow avoid failing miserably.
So you are begging the gods after all!
You'll be fine, Rikka!
Ah, Kumin! Do you have something for me?
Whenever you're not sure about the answer, use this!
This pencil has been my faithful
companion through many battles!
I'll lend it to you!
Question one! What is the size of each angle?
Four! The answer is—
Three!
May Rikka pass miraculously.
They're hopeless.
Now my only chance is...
Staff Room
Work?
Indeed. Our Society is currently treated as a mere circle.
It's at the lowest level of the school hierarchy.
However, our goal... and purpose is to contribute... and serve the school...
Don't just read off that thing!
So you're looking for something you can do to help out?
Exactly.
Something that'll make the teachers think that our circle is worth having.
She just wants to avoid studying at any cost.
Well, I guess there are a few things...
Really?
It's hard work, though.
Are you sure?
Perfectly.
We have Yuuta!
Hey!
Prepare to meet your death!
Mjollnir Accel!
Let me explain!
Mjollnir Accel is a technique that overloads the nerves of the lower body with concentrated magic,
boosting physical power up to 3.88 times higher than normal and enabling high speed movement. Deathly so!
Witness the power of my acceleration!
Witness its deathly power!
I'll pretend to panic as I hurtle toward the wall,
and then stop a second before my death!
Come on!
Do it properly!
And why do I have to help too?
Because Nana said every member of the club had to help.
I don't recall joining anything.
Didn't you fill out a club entry form?
That was only to get closer to that brat!
I'm still a member of the cheerleaders first and foremost!
Excuse me. My hand slipped.
But didn't you say that your seniors at the cheerleaders are always complaining,
so you're slowly getting tired of it?
Why did you bring a pillow to the pool?!
Is that true?
Well, not exactly...
But I wasn't that enthusiastic about it in the first place.
Then why did you join?
Isn't being a cheerleader and class rep the exact opposite of having eighth-grader syndrome?
I thought it'd be the best way to change my character.
Why do you want to change so much?
Eighth-grader syndrome looks like a lot of fun.
It's not fun!
Huh? Why?
It's embarrassing!
It's a stain on the carpet that is my life!
A furball of embarrassment I can never quite cough up!
I couldn't agree more!
Really?
Those girls look like they're having fun to me.
Dropping off a few pearls of "wisdom" doesn't entitle you to sleep!
You can work like everyone else!
Schwarz Cutter!
Come on now!
Align to G*ldolva!
Target: G*ldolva!
I shall wash off that expression off your rotten face!
You fake!
Disappear! Embrace your death and begone!
You little...
Who do you think you are?!
Is this... the Genesis?!
It's a battle of new school versus old school! To the death!
What are you even talking about?
Just put down that hose already!
I won't let you have your way!
Leave it to me, Dekomori.
I shall help you.
Oh, Master!
Evil Eye... shoot!
I can feel the power bursting forth!
Tally-hose! Geronimo!
Dodge! Dodge!
Staff Room
So you spent three hours there,
but you just played in the pool instead of cleaning it?
That's not exactly it either...
Either way, the PE teacher wasn't pleased that you didn't manage to clean the pool one bit.
But at least we volunteered, right?
The Society's rating must've risen.
Sadly, it's the opposite.
When I told the math teacher about our deal,
he said that just passing shouldn't be enough.
He wants you to at least match the class average.
The average...
Excuse us.
Yuuta...
What?
What... What should I do?
Huh?
Where's Yuuta?
At Rikka's place.
Oh? You're curious, right?
Wanna go peeking?
Why would I? I don't care that much.
Why not? They're both teenagers!
Aren't you worried that smug thief will steal your brother away from you?!
Not one bit?
Not really, no.
And Dad'll get mad at you if you keep saying weird things like that.
Nah, I just called him in Jakarta,
and he said you should totally go and peek!
Why are my parents so hopeless?
I'll ask you just one more time.
You really do intend to study, right?
Of course.
Let me make this clear: our school's quite high-level,
so if you want to match the class average, you'll need to study very hard.
I am ready.
Okay, then let's get started.
First, a basic problem.
You throw two dice at the same time. What is the
probability that the sum of the rolls will be three?
Can you do it?
Easily.
By the way, your room's still a mess.
You should clean... up...
I have no idea.
I thought that if I could understand the person behind the dice roll I could work it out,
but it's a lot harder to guess what he's thinking than I thought!
So this is all you can do?
No! I have yet to unleash my full potential.
You just wanted to say that!
Okay then, let's start from a bit earlier.
Revised Edition
Mathematics I
That's quite a bit earlier... Are we covering all that?
Revised Edition
Mathematics I
You have to start with what you understand and build on that. That's the rule.
Who's there?!
Nobody's there.
No, I'm sure someone was!
Yuuta, watch out!
That won't work.
By the way, have you heard about the
magical properties of the number eigh—
That won't work either.
Hmph.
I clearly heard you say "hmph"!
Sit down!
I thought you said you were serious about this.
I am.
I thought you asked me to help because you were trying your hardest.
I did.
But I'm just hopeless at math!
I've got no idea what they're thinking!
What point is there in knowing the probability of the results when throwing dice, anyway?!
Why are you arguing with me?
I don't get it!
Her persona's in ruins.
Then let's...
Take a break!
I'd love to.
I'll be able to work seriously after a break!
I'll make you tea as well!
Geez...
Your sister isn't home yet?
Nope.
What would you like to drink?
Yuuta?
Whatever.
There's chameleon plant tea, noni juice and chaga tea.
That's a hell of a lineup.
If you don't run some water over these, it'll be harder to scratch the stains off later.
I'm using some detergent.
Why are you washing them?
Why not? They're dirty and I don't really have anything better to do.
What's that pose supposed to mean?
Thanks.
Oh? You were just too embarrassed to say thanks?
Stop that!
What happened?!
It's from the Priestess.
Oh, Tooka?
What happened?
They observed an extraordinary magical phenomenon at the Overseers.
Without the embellishments.
She'll be late.
As usual.
As usual?
On weekdays, she's late pretty much every day.
Oh!
I haven't asked you for your electro protocol code yet!
You mean my email address?
Some call it that.
Quick! Initiate infrared data communications!
You mean the IR port?
Some call it that.
Sending it now.
Yuuta, your code's pretty cool!
Huh? Cool?
It's just your usual...
Email address
Oh, crap.
I haven't changed it since junior high...
Divine Exseed Freya Magna!
Don't say it loud!
I'm changing it right now, so wait a moment.
Don't!
Address book
Takanashi Rikka
Mine's too ordinary.
I'm changing mine.
All right, Yuuta!
Define my new code!
You should be able to come up with something great.
I think your current one's just fine.
Then I'm using your code.
Not that!
But can you really just change it like that?
Why not?
You know, if you change it, you'll have to tell all your junior high friends and your family...
It should be fine if I just tell the Priestess and Dekomori.
Really?
In this dimension, they are the only ones who acknowledge my existence.
But if you come up with a new code for me,
I'll give it to you, Nibutani, and Kumin too.
Come here for a moment.
But the chameleon plant tea...
I'll teach you as much as I can until the exams.
So you need to study as much as you can too.
Yuuta...
You want to keep your circle together, right?
If you can match the class average,
I'll think of a protocol code you might like.
You're late.
Wh-What are you doing here?!
When I got home, you two were
totally absorbed in your studies.
I figured I'd just be disturbing you, so I left.
Here, I wrote it down!
Now it's over between us.
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
I'll raise our children.
Don't forget you promised that I could see them once a month.
What are you doing?
Yumeha, what are you doing?!
Just playing house is so unrealistic.
This is too realistic!
Problem?
No...
Well then, I'm off.
What about her?
She fell asleep at her desk, so I let her continue sleeping.
I see.
I envy you.
After a week of that...
If you can solve this, I'll give you some chewing gum you'll like.
Black Power
I can feel it replenishing my mana!
I used a wide variety of tricks to made Rikka study,
Japanese
Mathematics I
Social
Studies
and thus we faced the exams.
We're starting the mathematics exam now!
No looking until the bell rings, okay?
I can see it...
I can see it!
Ready...
Start!
I can...
Rend reality.
Shatter synapse.
Vanishment... this world!
There!
I can see it!
I can see it! I can finally see it!
The light I've been seeking for so long!
The answer!
I can...
not.
And a few days later...
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Crap. I didn't do that well myself.
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
No good, huh?
This time, everyone did quite poorly.
The class average was only 50 percent.
Study harder next time!
What an amazing miracle!
Would it kill you to walk like a normal person once in a while?
Oh right, I forgot!
Yuuta, my new protocol code!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Just kidding! I thought of one!
I'm only doing this today, okay?
Heed my words, wielder of the Wicked Eye!
I have witnessed your struggle and your achievements.
I, the Dark Flame Master have crystallized that Dark Power
into a new code befitting of you!
Engrave it upon your very soul!
Protocol code, thy name be carved!
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Sub
Engrave it upon your soul
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Sub
Engrave it upon your soul
Black... raison d'etre...
Its true meaning is "Black Reason for Existence".
It should befit you well.
So cool...
It's so cool, Yuuta!
But of course.
I guess that should be enough.
H-Hey!
Wait a se—
Thanks
To be continued
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?