A Christmas party?
Yeah. You and me and Takanashi...
and Kumin.
You still haven't given up on her?
What do you mean? She approved of me as a friend!
Then why not invite her yourself?
That'd be a bit too much...
Too close!
See, a guy asking a girl somewhere on Christmas has all these connotations...
You're such a drag. No thanks!
Thought so.
Yeah, I figured you'd be going on a date with Takanashi.
That's no surprise. It's Christmas, after all.
Where do you get these ideas? I have no such plans!
Why not?
What do you mean, "why not"?
Aren't you going out?
Uh...
Did you break up?
Where'd that come from?!
Did you get dumped?
I'm not you!
Then why?
Well...
After all that, Rikka came to school, just like before.
We went to class together, just like before,
and she's back at club, just like before.
However...
Nothing's changed from before.
Far Eastern
Magic Nap Society
of Summer
A kotatsu?
Master, you mustn't!
Kumin!
Where am I?
Don't worry.
It's neither the Underworld nor the Otherworld.
What a shame!
This deathly heat field has caught my soul in its unrelenting grasp!
Who the death could have dragged such a dreadful device here?
You seem to be enjoying it enough.
It's pulling me in!
Oh no! I've got no deathly chance!
I'm using the same kotatsu as Kumin!
What'd I just touch?!
Oh, the chimera was under there too?
I'm bleeding! Bleeding!
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Christmas
Special
Date
Master!
Christmas
Date
Special
Christmas
Date
Special
Christmas
Date
Special
Christmas
Date
Special
Christmas
Date
Be careful!
Its temptation is deathly indeed!
What's the situation?
Buzzcut and Kumin are unconscious.
Show me the way.
Yessir!
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa hazukashii kara
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after being so evasive
kikanaide kureru?
So please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
A
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no yuku mama ni yukou yo
My heart seems to hop with glee, so I'll let it guide me
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
So you're going out, but nothing's changed?
Glittering... Slapstick Noel
The contract is stronger now than ever.
Therefore, it matters not if the flow of our everyday lives is not altered.
Then who cares?
But...
What?
Yuuko
Daiki
It is traditional that those bound by such contracts
Yuuko
Daiki
perform a special ceremony at Christmas time.
Yuuko
Daiki
Do you want to?
Yuuko
Daiki
I have long distanced myself from ordinary people.
Nothing could be further from me than such unenlightened celebrations.
Then just let it go on like this.
But...!
Which one is it, then?!
Well, what do you want to do?
What do I want?
For example,
do you want to spend more time with Togashi,
or always hold hands with him,
or have him caress your head...
Sliding Volt!
What's wrong with you?!
What a fearsome psychological assault!
She's such a pain...
Oh well. I think I know what you really want.
There is no way a mere commoner like you could
possibly perceive the true intent of the Wicked Eye!
Then I'll be going.
Wait, O wise one of the light!
Let go of me, you moron!
Listen. Christmas is just around the corner, right?
You should make use of that.
You can't do anything by yourself anyway, so we should—
Party!
We're throwing a Christmas party!
Eh? I can't allow that.
Just in the club room, please.
We won't stay late, either.
But the school's closed on the 24th.
Will there be a Bloody Christmas here?
Yes, indeed.
I knew it.
Deathly so.
Stop teasing us, please!
They take it seriously!
I can't believe the clubroom's out.
But this is such a good opportunity, so how about we hold it at someone's place?
Very well. Let's get together at mine and—
Nope.
Why?
I can only imagine how much of a mess your room must be.
That's total prejudice!
Yeah, I think Togashi's place would be best.
My place? Not a chance.
My dad's coming home from Jakarta.
Then how about Takanashi's?
Well...
Yeah, no.
Looks like I have no other choice.
I shall show you the deathly might of my stronghold.
Really?
Won't your parents object to a bunch of high schoolers barging in?
No problem!
It's been so long since Master and I last had a
chance to investigate the source of Dark Matter!
Rikka, you've been there before?
Just once.
Dekomori's house is a fortress with defenses that can withstand any and all attacks.
A fortress?
Indeed. It should prove most fitting for our gathering.
This is Dekomori's house.
You're kidding me.
Just how rich is she?
Look, a doggie!
Wait, what did she do to that expensive-looking dog?
Huh?
C'mon, why is it always me?
Dogs really love Forest Summer.
Quit it already! Get away from me!
More like hate her.
Whatever, just help me!
Wicked Twinkle!
Welcome to my castle!
Looks like... this really is... her house.
And with her grades, she can get into any high school she wants.
A total winner.
I don't want to accept... this reality!
Your dress looks really nice, Deko.
Mother made me put it on.
She said it's important to death up properly for a party.
Oh. But I came in my usual clothes...
You're more than cute enough already!
Naturally, I have made sufficient preparations
for any combat situations that may arise.
That's my Master!
I brought one for you too!
No, thank you!
I'd swear I just heard Santa Claus scream in deathly agony!
Master!
Hey!
They're hopeless.
What is this place?
It's all too perfect!
Her mom's hot too!
Seriously?
Watching that stuff on this would be way too exciting!
Watching what stuff?
Merry Christmas!
They had a whole lot of spare costumes, so they let me borrow this one.
Bad choice?
No, it looks great on you.
Yuuta.
There comes a time in every man's life...
where he's happy simply to have been born!
That much?!
Yay, a soft, fluffy sofa! Sweet dreams!
That was fast.
Don't do it.
Just one! Just one!
Where is that fool?
You're up next?
Well, I—
I do believe I asked where she was.
How would I know?
Don't put it on if you don't want to.
They took my clothes away!
Fake
She sure is persistent.
Following this pattern, Takanashi's up next, right?
Well, I have a rough idea what to expect.
It'll be the usual—
No way!
Huh? Gym clothes?
What happened to the dress you brought?
Nibutani told me to put on these instead.
That girl...
Tell me where you hid them!
Let go!
This is my stronghold! I won't let you have your way so easily!
That hurts like death!
I'm getting tired of this.
Nibutani.
What's the meaning of this?
Isn't she cute?
But why gym clothes?!
Because I heard that was your fetish.
Who told you that?
Tooka.
It was her?
She's underestimating us high schoolers!
Rikka! Go and change.
Right! My clothes!
I get it!
In that case, fight me!
Fight?
I'm not playing along with one of your pretend battles.
What are you talking about?
At times like these, there's only one way to fight.
The cards of death!
It sure is surreal playing cards in such a posh room.
Why does she have to be the president?
Give me two cards already, scum!
In this environment, it feels so realistic...
Hmm, not deathly bad.
Here, take these in return.
Come on!
Say "thank you," or meet your death.
Thank you.
That hurt just to watch.
I need to get her back for that.
Here it is!
The time for uprising has come!
I'll bring down that fat Presideko!
Let me!
Then let's begin!
From the scum...
Know regret!
If you believe your victory is
assured, you'll lose your footing!
Revolution?
What?!
Don't underestimate the power of the common folk!
Stop!
Counter-revolution?!
Does that even exist?
Hey, what are you doing?!
I just had those!
Deathly done!
Didn't I tell you waking her up would be trouble?!
Trouble?
I get the feeling this is turning into less and less of a game.
You're incapable of reading between the lines! Just sleep!
You're so mean, Forest Summer!
Right, Rikka?
Rikka?
Where did she go?
Yuuta!
Rikka?
Rikka, what are you doing up there?
Hey, your face is red...
No way!
Ouch!
Yuuta!
Hold your horses!
Don't tell me...
I guess this is why. She ate three of them, too.
They had quite an effect on her.
Geez, just sit down!
Yuuta, there's a sword master there!
The ceiling...
Just sleep.
Yuuta...
What is it?
Hey!
Give back my Master!
Don't tell me even you—
Mjolnir Hammer!
Give me a break.
You're cheating!
How dare you play with Master's heart?
She's a deathly delicate soul, you know!
You should show some gratitude!
I'm not playing with her...
Yes you deathly are!
It's only you my Master talks about!
You laughed. You got angry. You looked away.
I hear nothing else!
Wait!
Why are you bringing that up now?
Get away, Dekomori.
Yuuta lacks decisiveness as the Dark Flame Master.
If all happens in accordance with that decided by the Wicked Eye,
the final battle at the unavoidable end of the world will commence again.
What are you even talking about?
Point is, you piss me off, Yuuta!
Master!
Rend reality!
Shatter synapse!
Vanishment... this world!
You're not getting away.
Mjolnir Lightning!
You're gonna kill me!
Avalon Smasher!
Mjolnir Striker!
Gimme a break!
I feel sick.
Huh?
What are you even doing?
The world's spinning...
Just lay flat for a while.
I'm sorry.
I said I'd help you find the right time to be alone with Togashi at the party.
Hm?
No need for that.
Really?
The Wicked Eye has already seen through it all.
No problem.
Well, it's really hard to make a move if you're a girl.
I also have—
Experience with Yuuta?!
You sure bit on that one quick!
I don't. I just meant it can be hard to think of what to say sometimes.
That's why I think Christmas is the best possible time.
I see.
Right? Doesn't Christmas have all these connotations?
Like bloody massacres?
What's going on inside your head?
I'm talking about lovers! Couples!
And bloody massacres?
Well, some couples are like that.
Wait, that's not it! The point is,
it's a time for couples to hold hands and kiss!
I think Togashi's considered this stuff too to some extent.
He hasn't.
You think so?
The Wicked Eye told me!
Are you done changing?
Yeah. You can come in.
How is she?
Calmed down a little. She's sleeping.
Okay. Then I'll carry her home.
She lives just above me, after all.
Right.
Sorry, but we'll be heading back then.
Sure.
What was that?
Nothing. Go and wake up Kumi—
Where is my Master?!
She went home with Togashi.
He can't abduct Master, for death's sake!
Now I have no choice but to—
Yeah, whatever. We're going inside.
Let go! Get your deathly hands off me!
What the death?
You've been so deathly mean to me recently.
Even though I'm always trying my best to attack you.
Huh? Is it my turn now?
You took this more seriously before!
You always chased me around!
Yet... Yet...
Now I'm abandoned not only by Master but you as well...
Give me a break!
Don't cry.
Then...
Take me to where Master is!
Why does it come down to that?
Maybe we can still make it.
Hey, Rikka.
What?
I bought these, since it's Christmas and all.
I thought they'd go to waste since we were having a party and all.
Yuuta...
Wanna go?
If you're feeling up to it.
I'm fine.
Whoa, Yuuta! This is amazing!
Yeah.
It's so pretty.
This your first time on a sightseeing ship?
Yeah.
And you?
I went once when I was very little.
Look, that's our town over there.
Oh, I see the barrier is already up!
But that town there looks strange.
Could the seal be broken?
You really are the same as always.
Hm?
Listen...
I've given this a lot of thought.
You know, about us.
But I guess I still don't really get it.
Maybe we shouldn't try so hard.
It's just like with eighth-grader syndrome.
Time will naturally sort everything out for us.
So I thought... How do I put this...
It's kinda cold. Wanna go downstairs?
Yeah.
Stop right there!
Dekomori?
I tried to keep my cool, but what the death was that?!
Are you still drunk?
Get lost!
I can't leave Master in your hands!
Hey!
I told you to leave them alone!
Sorry!
What are you all doing here?
Deko insisted on coming.
She promised she'd just watch.
Oh, did she now?
Sorry!
Give back Master!
Mjolnir Hammer!
Rikka!
Don't worry. I won't let her hurt—
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Huh? What was that kiss sound just now?
What the death are you doing?!
I should be asking you that!
How dare you steal my first kiss?!
Thus, my relationship with Rikka didn't really change this Christmas.
There isn't the slightest hint of a
relationship between Kumin and Isshiki.
You just looked at me with deathly lust in your eyes!
Because you did!
You're saying it's my deathly fault?!
Just those two.
A new flag—
Don't say "flag"!
Damn it!
Death it!
I'm home.
Bro's
I guess this is for the best right now.
Merry Christmas!
Which reminds me, wasn't the world supposed to end?
To be continued
. . . maybe?
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?