M-Meow...
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Ah, this feels great!
The water gets deeper that way, so be careful.
You okay?
Yeah.
What do you think you're looking at? There's a damsel in distress here!
Sorry! Sorry!
Togashi, you perv!
Aw, stop it!
Stop it!
You perv!
Stop it, please!
Stop it!
You've finally come back to us.
What's that you're holding?
Heilige Wasser!
Pressure rising in the mana chamber.
Energy charging, 120%...
So that was you?!
What happened to your forehead?
My forehead?
I was caught up in a fierce battle last night, and—
Ah, it'd be safer for you not to know.
Eighth-grader syndrome is a real pain to deal with.
A cat?
Meow!
A chimera?
You mean the monster from Greek mythology and video games?
Yeah. Last night I was investigating the Ethereal Horizon, when suddenly...
I caught it!
You want to keep it?
Yes.
This beast will serve as my familiar.
A chimera from the depths of oblivion should prove invaluable in my search for the Ethereal Horizon.
But there's one problem.
What problem?
The priestess of the Ethereal Horizon Overseers displays immune hyperreaction to chimeras.
You mean your sister is allergic to cats?
And thus I enlist the help of my comrade, the Dark Flame Mas—
Not a chance.
A week has passed since I started high school.
All right, thanks in advance.
Hey, Dark Flame Master...
Dark Flame Master!
Shut up!
Over time, I got used to dealing with this serious case of eighth-grader syndrome.
Priestess... of Melodies
Yuuta...
No means no!
Kuzuha and Yumeha both love animals,
and Mom wouldn't object either,
but doing what you want is against my principles.
Yuuta, you're so mean.
By the way, where's your dad?
He's working in Jakarta.
I see...
I must be careful not to let anything slip about my past,
Did you know that Jakarta is the origin of the Japanese word for "potato"?
but at least for now I've managed to blend into my class without any problems.
Well then, Hirakata, you're class librarian.
I somehow ended up as one of the class reps after Isshiki nominated me as a joke,
but that might not be such a bad thing at all.
All right, we're finished.
Thanks! Well done.
Homeroom's over.
Nice job, man.
It's tough work being a class rep.
And whose fault is that?
Yeah, yeah. Oh, who're you gonna vote for?
I'd like to open the poll soon.
What poll?
The cutie poll!
I told you about it, didn't I? We guys are gonna vote to decide who's the cutest in the class!
Who're you going with?
Are you sure that'll be all right?
The girls won't be impressed if they find out.
Don't worry, they won't!
At times like these, nothing's stronger than the bonds we share as men!
Togashi!
Yeah?
Could you come to the science lab during lunch break?
Remember? The science teacher asked us for help.
We gotta check the equipment.
Seven, eight, nine, ten... There's twelve of these.
Okay, twelve it is.
All right, that's it for this shelf.
This aroma... is it Asience? Petal Sassoon?
Have you gotten used to being a class rep?
It's all pretty new to me still.
If you notice anything, please let me know.
I tend to forget stuff, you see.
Really? You didn't strike me as absent-minded.
I pay special attention to making sure I don't come across that way.
I'm a class rep, after all.
R-Really?
You always seem so calm and collected.
You've been class rep a bunch of times before, right?
Yeah, kinda.
But you got recommended.
You must have experience too.
Me? Not at all.
I might've done it once back in elementary school,
but mostly I preferred not to stand out.
Really?
When we first met, I was thinking how alike we were.
Remember? It was at the station, on the day of the entrance ceremony.
You remember that?
Of course! Why wouldn't I?
But you didn't even know my class or name then.
Yeah, but when I got to class and saw you,
I thought "Oh, it's him!"
R-Really?
Calm down! It's too early to get nervous!
But at least her opinion of me isn't bad, right?
Could it be that if I go down this path,
I might actually get a life?
Let's do the rest tomorrow.
Should I make a move?
Why don't we walk home together?
Wait, let's simulate it first.
Predict her reaction!
Why don't we walk home together?
What's the occasion?
Not a chance!
Wh-What's wrong, Togashi?
Nothing, I just—
Togashi?!
What the hell?!
You scared me!
It was you? Again?!
Yuuta, my head's spinning...
Takanashi?
Why are you two here?
We're doing some work for the teacher.
Just ignore her, okay?
So many drugs for such a simple school.
The arm of the Overseers is long indeed.
Could you just quit this charade and take off the coat?
It's not even yours, is it?
Take it off?
Yeah, take it off! Right now!
How bold... Telling me to undress...
You did that intentionally, didn't you?!
And don't play with the chemicals!
Sadly, the chimera lacks the mana to manifest itself in the real world.
I must supplement it by artificial means.
Chimera?
Ah, it's nothing.
Just a gray cat with a mark on its forehead.
Takanashi picked it up yesterday.
Don't call me Takanashi. It's Rikka.
A gray cat?
That reminds me...
Is it really Dodomen?
Have
you
seen
this
cat?
Answers to Dodomen
I'm not sure,
but it pretty much fits this description.
It's about this big.
Its behind is like this.
It has wings—
Nowhere.
Yeah, my cat's about that big too.
You mean its wings?
Just shut up.
When did she get lost?
About a week ago.
Do you want to come and see it?
Can I?
Sure, uh...
May Seventh?
Contact Tsuyuri Kumin,
Class 2-4
Tsuyuri
Kumin,
Oh, it's pronounced "Tsuyuri".
I'm Tsuyuri Kumin. Nice to meet you.
Oh, um... I'm Togashi Yuuta.
Stop that!
I live on the second floor,
and Takanashi lives right above me.
Call me Rikka.
Shut up.
You get along so well.
You guys must go way back.
Nah, she just moved in recent—
Magic code unlocked.
Just open it already.
It opened... It opened!
You really are a pain.
Wait a moment.
I must check my room for anomalies in the fabric of spacetime.
My bad for trying to barge in.
We girls have our secrets.
Come in.
Excuse me!
This is amazing!
Welcome to the Dark Side,
to the twirling world of chaotic chaos.
You realize you said it twice?
Ah, you like cute plushies, don't you?
That's the Black Tortoise of the North.
That's a military Mauser!
That's cooler than I thought you ever could be!
It's a sacred gun that can exorcise devils.
Yeah, I can totally see that!
Can I see?
Go on.
The Mauser really is awesome!
Actually, you know, the original model of this gun was made a century ago,
and it's pretty awesome, called the M712, and...
You love stuff like that, don't you?
By the way, all objects in this room are
placed according to the laws of astrology.
Moving anything is strictly forbidden.
Therefore, cleaning is unnecessary.
Emit.
And where's the cat?
You can't see it? Well, I wouldn't expect normal people to.
She's our senior. Show some respect.
Don't worry about it.
She blended in so well!
You can see it?
Could you give it a rest?
So, is this the right one?
I'm afraid not.
Its chin looks different.
I see.
Whose cat is that?
Whose is it?
Airtight blast doors, lock!
Activate radiation barriers!
All personnel, evacuate!
What?!
My room?
What are you doing? This isn't even your room!
We'll be done in a moment.
Are they going to fight?
Don't get so excited.
This time, I will overcome this barrier!
Schwarzschild, full power!
Avalon Sm—
You're Togashi Yuuta, right?
I'm Takanashi Tooka, the sister of this freak.
We should talk.
She's still going on about her
"Wicked Eye" or whatever it's called,
just like when she was back in junior high.
It's quite a nuisance.
Not to mention that she knows I'm allergic to cats,
and yet she takes one in just like that.
She doesn't care how much trouble it causes.
I'm sorry, but could you take care of it?
That cat. I can't get rid of it myself.
Please do something about it.
I don't care if you give it to someone or leave it on the street,
just get rid of it.
That's all.
But... why me?
You don't want to?
It's not really about whether I want to.
Then thanks in advance.
But...
I have a record of what was said on this apartment's balcony two years ago.
This is no charade! No fantasy!
This world shall be conquered by darkness as of the year 2012!
Togashi, what's wrong?
What's wrong, Yuuta?
I'm not Yuuta.
I am the Dark Flame Master!
I wield the power of the flames of darkness!
Hey, that's your voice, Togashi!
Stop it, please!
Stop! Please, stop!
I can feel the winds of change!
I don't want to hear that again! Please!
What are you talking about? There's no wind at all.
I can feel... I can feel the power overwhelming!
Don't shout things like that! People will laugh at you!
What care have I for the foolishness of mortals?
I like uploading stuff to video-sharing websites.
Listen, my beloved sister.
Don't let me down.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry, but...
Okay.
She got away.
Dad, Mom, I'm sorry I didn't respect you!
Togashi, let's run away together! Let's run to the ends of the Earth!
I'll hold you to those words.
The ends of the Earth are all around us!
Our world is round, after all!
Why did you do that?
Your sister was really mad!
We must escape, and quickly.
She's a high-level priestess of the Overseers.
We must not take her powers lightly.
Your blood shall be a sacrifice to these chains!
Bloody Prison!
Nice try.
She can even teleport. It's truly frightening.
Weren't you just being careless?
She's here!
This is so much fun! Like a horror movie!
It isn't fun at all!
I saw something sparkle in the distance!
Tsuyuri!
Yuuta, hurry!
How should I put this... I feel like my life is in danger.
Sadly, I have no means to defeat the priestess in this time space.
But I will eventually have to confront her.
It's dangerous to go by yourselves. Take this.
Let's live together once this battle is over.
Stop tripping death flags!
Yuuta, you must run!
I'll buy us some time.
You go on ahead!
I must find the Ethereal Horizon.
No matter what.
Takanashi...
I told you to call me Rikka.
The chimera!
So that's where they are.
I'll stop her!
Catch the chimera, Yuuta!
Come forth, Schwarz Sechs Prototype Mark II!
Rend reality!
Shatter synapse!
Vanishment... this world!
Heed the call of blood.
I summon thee!
Königin der Nacht.
Dark Matter Blaze!
Takanashi...
She's... actually holding her ground?
Nergal Blast!
Come on, Takanashi!
Wicked Twinkle!
Enough is enough!
That's quite enough of your delusions.
Anyway, keep that cat away from me.
That's all I want for now.
Ouch.
Use these.
I don't get it.
That should have ended with my Wicked Twinkle.
How did I lose?
It only works that way in your imagination.
It still stings.
Dark Matter Blaze.
It was like a fighting game.
I guess I can keep a model gun.
Sorry, but I can't let you return to your former home.
I don't want to get hurt anymore.
Mom, can I keep a cat?
Wow, what's this all of a sudden?
Look, a kitty! It's so cute!
Kumin's cat was found unhurt soon after.
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?