Just why doesn't she lose her weight again?
A Wandering Chimera
Doesn't one usually lose it after giving birth?
That's what I thought as well, but now that's over and her weight hasn't gone down at all.
I'm even giving her less to eat.
Maybe she isn't feeling well after all.
She looks fine, though...
Just let her keep her fat.
It increases her attack stats.
You're part of the reason her staying fat as well.
You keep feeding her those cat snacks.
Jeez...
Sophia!
Evening, Satone.
When did you sit down over there?
Around when you said, "I'm going to protect Rikka even if it costs my life!"
I don't remember saying that.
But anyway, how about a fight to refresh our memories?
Challenge accepted.
Stop!
You're at Togashis' dining table.
It's a demilitarized zone.
You were one step away from death.
Not any closer than you.
Huh?
There, there...
Oh no!
S-She took control over Chimera!
Are you betraying me, my servant?!
She seems pretty attached to you.
Have you always been this close?
Well, lately she comes around every day to play with me.
Oh no!
C-Chimera...
Do you have any complaints about me?
I've been wondering where she kept going out sometimes.
So it was to your place, Shichimiya?
Right.
She comes every day and keeps begging for food.
What a troublesome fellow.
Food?
You feed her as well?
I have to.
She keeps purring until I give in and give her some in the end.
Then Chimera's been...
Really not easy being here...
Touka!
When did you arrive here?!
Around when you said, "I'm willing to die for Rikka's sake."
I did not say that.
Did you come in using the veranda as well?
Don't be ridiculous.
I used the front entrance of course.
But I'm not telling you how I opened the lock.
Please refrain from just entering someone else's home in the future.
How rude.
The owner gave me her permission.
See?
I lent her our spare key so she can see how things are going at any time.
I thought she'll be worrying about Rikka.
I didn't expect for Kuzuha to change sides to the enemy as well...
Who's the "enemy" here?
I can't take this...
Now listen, Chimera.
I'm not working at that Japanese restaurant anymore.
So stop dropping by to get food from the head chef every day.
Got it?
I'm not sure if you did or not...
Are you saying Chimera comes to your place as well?
Yeah, she comes to the restaurant I used to work at.
Seems like she makes the head chef there feed her every day.
Then the reason why Chimera can't lose weight...
It's just because she's a huge glutton!
Tune in again!