Togashi-kun's place?
Yeah!
I mean, they're living together!
Living together!
Don't you want to see?
Life together with your wife, to get her!
That joke's dead.
Master is sharing a base with the
Dark Flame Master only under contract.
She is not living the sort of
rotten life that you imagine.
That's right.
And Togashi-kun said not to
talk about it at school.
I know.
But they're high schoolers!
And they're dating!
And they're living together!
Aren't you curious?!
Only rotten, fake mages
such as yourself would be.
Now silence. I am busy.
What are you doing, Deko-chan?
I am writing an adventure log for a comrade who has
temporarily withdrawn from the battlefront.
Adventure log?
She's copying notes for a sick classmate.
Well, you can stay here.
What about you, Kumin-senpai? Interested?
Think about it! Lovers, living together!
Their hearts race when they make eye contact!
When no one's around,
they might hug and stuff!
They might even kiss
when his sister's not looking!
What? Really?
Yes, really!
Kiss
Silence!
Silence! Silence! Silence!
See? You're curious.
I am not!
I wanna fallin' love
yokan yume ga tsudzuku
The dream will go on and on
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
We made a promise, but deep inside,
I'm still scared it might all disappear
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
hitori ja nai tte shinjitai no ni
Even though I want to believe you'll always be there
omoitsudzuketeru dake de shiawase nante ienai ne
Being in love with each other isn't happiness all by itself
utsuro na jishin seotteitemo
Even if I pretend that it's all that matters
kimi ga warau
You just laugh
soshite watashi no yuuki ni naru
And you always give me strength
l
hitotsu no kotoba de kimi no sekai wo kaeraretara
But if one simple word can change your whole world
But if one simple word can change your whole world
l
futatsu no koi ga shinka suru
Then two loves will start to progress
Then two loves will start to progress
l
hontou da yo
That's the truth
That's the truth
l
meguraseta mayoi ga mitsuketa kotae wa
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
itsudemo kimi ni michibikareta
You always led me to the answer
Even if I can't work up the courage to do it
l
sunao ni tsutaetai
I want to tell you everything
I want to tell you everything
l
ko
ro
aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
kokoro aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
kokoro
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
l
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real
come
on
voice
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
The dark waves are too thick here.
Master's presence is virtually undetectable.
I cannot see her.
Master!
Where are you, Master?
Yeah, "not curious" my foot.
She did finish copying those notes really quickly.
Oh, there's Togashi-kun!
Really?
What's he doing?
Is he reading the wind?
Or is he declaring war anew
on the forces of darkness?
I think...
he's taking the laundry in.
Sorry, I forgot to bring it in.
Don't worry. It was supposed
to be Rikka's turn today.
Yeah, but I don't mind.
Cleaning
Breakfast
Laundry
Dinner
Door
Trash
Rikka
Kuzuha
Yuuta
Rikka
Kuzuha
Yuuta
I've been doing it all along anyway.
Dolphin Ring... Striker
It's not okay.
Rikka said she'd help with the chores.
It is complete.
Evil
The Tyrant's Dark Stew of Unpremeditated Chaos!
So you admit you don't know what you're doing.
Rikka-san, Onii-chan and I can make dinner from now on.
Understood.
Then I shall perform all other missions!
But she didn't, so now we're taking turns.
Is she home?
Yeah, she just got back.
You! How are you still alive?!
What happened to cleaning?!
Sheesh, will you quit screwing around—
Wait, did you buy that?
I-I did not.
The Fates dictated that
it should fall into my hands—
It's so cool! Let me see!
Here.
Thanks!
Wow!
You can play Ghostbusters with this!
Yuuta, you're so cool!
Yuuta!
I'm not cleaning for you.
This thing looks pretty expensive.
Where'd you get the money for it?
Yoridori Bank
Ms. Takanashi Rikka
Didn't you say Touka-san sent you living expenses the other day?
Rikka—
No, the Tyrant's Eye!
Will you show me your gold ledger?
It is the greatest secret of the Tyrant's Eye!
I mustn't show it to anyone—not even you, Yuuta!
Show me, Tyrant's Eye!
If opened, all the evil sealed within its pages will be unleashed upon the world!
Enough. Just show me.
No, Yuuta!
What... is the meaning of this?
His power level is over 150,000?!
That's even higher than the Priestess!
Apologize...
to Touka-san!
You! Little!
Please stop!
They're just like how they are at school.
We don't know that for sure yet.
Can't expect a couple to be
lovey-dovey all day long.
Someone already moved in upstairs?
Fresh Market
Pachira
Were you seriously going to ride out the month on less than 1,000 yen?
Relieve Void: one of the
Tyrant's Eye's passive abilities.
By living off the Eye's mana within my body,
I can maintain biological function
without sustenance for many years.
Would you like to try one?
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
New!
Coarse-Ground
Sausages
But you're still starving.
Sorry, could we have two bags?
Shopping for dinner together?
Now that's something a couple would do.
Let's move.
You're heavy.
And didn't you see the sign that said no skates?
The enemy may strike at any moment.
When that happens...
I'll knock over that snack rack to block their path!
Right after that, I'll take out the lights!
Then, having blinded them, this...
is both sword and shield!
Enough already! Cut that out!
Whoa, it's getting late.
Let's go.
Wait.
Cumin!
Yuuta, I want this.
Cumin.
We don't need that.
Put it back.
But Yuuta!
I want it!
It's cumin!
Please?
Rikka-chan's so cute!
What about me?
I'm going to look for some decomori!
That doesn't exist, silly!
And this is cumin seed.
It can put monsters to sleep.
You use cumin to make curry powder.
But we don't make curry from scratch.
Roux cubes are good enough.
So you don't like cumin?
I never said that.
Come on, let's go.
It looks like they split up.
What's she so focused on?
Today, I'll have...
a blue crystal.
Picked one out yet?
Let's go.
Yuuta.
It is necessary that I investigate the status of the singularity.
I shall withdraw.
Right now?
Be home by dinnertime.
I swear on the Tyrant's Eye that I will.
Master summons me!
I must go.
Duty beckons!
It's great that they get along so well.
You wouldn't think they were going out, though.
That's a problem.
Huh?
They've been dating for six months!
That's supposed to be when passions burn their hottest!
Really?
But they aren't doing anything passionate.
That can only mean one thing.
Relationship fatigue.
This fried chicken isn't that fatty—
That hurt, Mori Summer-chan!
I'm your senior, you know!
I don't care. We're talking about fatigue!
But what about it?
How do you feel about Takanashi-san?
What do you mean?
You're dating, right?
You've confessed your love for each other, right?
W-Well, yeah.
Doesn't your heart race when you're with her?
Don't you hold hands and gaze into each other's eyes and stuff?
That's none of your business.
Come on! Just tell me!
We've moved up a grade,
but she hasn't changed one bit.
And you're just as dumb
as you were last year, too.
H-Hey!
We tailed you yesterday, and you were
more like father and daughter than a couple.
Or maybe like grandfather and granddaughter?
Who are you calling a grandfather?!
And what? You tailed us?!
You don't like Kumin, huh?
What are you talking about?!
You're living together, Togashi-kun.
Living. Together.
Where's the "I love you"
and the "I love you too"?
Well, I don't think you can call it fatigue.
And why not?
Well, fatigue would mean the flame's gone out,
but Rikka and I have never even held hands.
Seriously?
Really?
Yeah.
So how can it be fatigue if nothing's happened?
Togashi Yuuta.
Whoa, why are you so angry?!
When did you start dating?
L-Last fall.
When did you go on a date on that boat?
Christmas.
You've had New Year's and Valentine's Day,
and you still haven't held hands?!
I can't breathe, Nibutani!
Come with me!
Wait! Wait, Nibutani!
Togashi, look at me...
Outta the way!
Meet Kannagi Kazari-chan.
I'm Kazari. Nice to meet you!
Hi...
Kannagi-san is an expert on relationships.
I'm sure she can give you great advice!
Wait, what the heck?!
Didn't I tell you to keep my
living together with Rikka a secret?
Yeah, I know.
I didn't tell her about that.
All I told her is that your relationship isn't going too smoothly.
Your girlfriend would be Rikka-chan, right?
Huh?!
Well, um...
No need to hide it.
The whole class knew since last year.
I see.
Trouble with Rikka-chan.
This might be a good opportunity.
You see, I'm into girls.
And right now, I'm in love with Rikka-chan.
Except I haven't told her because my love
might be snuffed out like a candle in the wind.
We're rivals?!
Blow harder, wind!
Just kidding.
That wasn't funny!
Anyway, your phone, please.
Here.
You should invite her on a date, get a good mood going, and see how she reacts.
Wait, what are you doing?!
Texting her.
"Would you like to go on a date this Sunday?"
What?
"I have something important to tell you."
Wait! No!
And sent!
Stop!
That was almost like confessing to Rikka-chan!
My heart's pounding so hard!
How could you?!
They might not show it, but girls are always waiting for the boy to take the initiative.
Even Rikka?
I think so.
It's just even harder for her to be clear about it
thanks to her eighth-grade syndrome.
You need to take the lead!
Well, I guess you're right.
Understood
Takanashi Rikka
Message
And so, on Sunday, Rikka and I are going on a date neither of us asked for.
Good water dragon.
Morning.
Rikka-san, that's so cute!
It is a robe reserved only
for the most solemn of rituals.
Oh, are you doing something special today?
All right. Let's go.
First, answer me.
What is our destination?
A place you wanted to go to.
Me?
You were reading my thoughts?!
No.
Well, you'll see when we get there.
Got a good grip?
Releasing magic lock.
Unit prepared for launch.
Yuuta, all systems green.
Go!
Keep it slow!
Yeah, I know.
How're you doing?
Hanging in there?
I am fine, poor visibility aside.
I'm afraid the view isn't gonna get any better.
I'm keeping this ride safe.
Don't worry.
When you die, I die.
You're scaring me.
And...
The Tyrant's Eye is the strongest!
Even with its view blocked, it sees all!
Even what is in your heart!
Never knew it could do that.
Right now, you're thinking,
"Whoa, I'm faster than the speed of sound!"
"Limit break: My Celerity/Alacrity!"
I know I'm right!
You're completely wrong!
Look!
Oh, windmills.
What are you doing?
I will use the powers of darkness
to make them spin.
Assist me, Yuuta!
They're not going to spin.
Don't worry!
With our dark powers combined, we can do it!
Like this?
Tyrant's Black Dragon
of the Darkness Hellflame!
Sure, sure. Just hold on tight.
Oh, I saw a video of a windmill
getting destroyed the other day...
Sazanami
Aquarium
A reconstruction of R'lyeh.
Didn't you say you wanted to see a real dolphin up close?
Kairu-kun is a genius.
He appears to be a typical dolphin,
but I suspect he is actually
a dark warrior in disguise.
Haven't seen him in a long time.
O, Great Old Ones.
They might not show it, but girls are always waiting for the boy to take the initiative.
Rikka.
Um...
We're here together and all, so...
Want to hold hands?
We don't have to if it's too embarrassing.
It's just that we've been dating for so long, and I've only ever touched your pinky.
Look, penguins!
Nautiluses!
No, no. "Nautili"!
I was seriously thinking of applying to Miskatonic University.
The so-called "lost continent of Mu"
was never actually a continent, but...
By the way, Kairu-kun only came with the Japanese version.
What? Seriously?
Amazing! What speed!
He even sunders darkness!
Whale anyone from the audience
help us ask the dolphin to do tricks?
Me! Me!
Okay, the girl right there!
Yay!
Can you tell us your name and age?
T-Takanashi Rikka!
I-I'm...
I'm in sixth grade!
What are you saying?!
Look into his eyes and
move your head back and forth.
C-Calm down, dolphin!
Are you okay? Need a towel?
I'm fine.
Now, the trainer will teach us
how to ask the dolphin to jump!
First, point to the sky with your right hand.
Next, put your finger on your left shoulder.
Finally, on the count of three,
swing your finger up and to the right.
Okay, then!
One, two, three!
The dolphin does my bidding!
Hey, that's enough! Stop it!
Please, a diving beetle!
Wow, a Japanese giant salamander!
Not much change from our usual routine.
You need to take the lead!
I'm sure she's right, but...
Here you go.
A shakey shake!
And you can have this too.
It comes back from the machine every time:
The chosen 10-yen coin!
Don't just assume anything will amuse me.
You don't like it?
Oh, it's a ridged 10-yen coin, so I guess it's kind of special.
The ridges are worn off
because it's so old, though.
How sad.
You have been rejected by the world.
No, it's just been rejected by
the world's vending machines.
You can use it anywhere else.
But then it's not "chosen" anymore...
Which is it?
Today sure was fun.
You sundered darkness!
We finally held hands, too.
Y-Yeah.
Hold.
All you want.
All you can hold!
But I still don't know what to think.
We are bound by the contract of lovers.
Thus, we are lovers.
However, I have yet to understand what lovers are.
When I think about it, I am filled with confusion.
Rikka...
Under the contract of lovers,
physical contact between contractors is inevitable!
Y-Yeah, you're right!
B-But...
What now?
I don't know.
I researched what lovers are.
But I still don't know.
The information on the 'Net was unintelligible.
"A couple may or may not be called lovers if they are living together"? Which is it?!
It's completely different from the contract with the Tyrant's Eye.
So you're unhappy with our contract?
No!
Not in the least!
I'm overjoyed!
But I don't know what to do.
Something was supposed
to change, but nothing has.
There's one thing I'm sure of, though.
It's the end of another fun day.
I will soon head home.
To the same home as you.
Nothing could make me happier.
In fact, I'm so happy that
I wonder if I've raised a death flag.
They're spinning!
Our powers combined
have caused them to spin!
The Tyrant's Eye really is the strongest!
The Dark Flame Master is the second strongest.
Yuuta?
Sorry, I'm not laughing at you.
Well put, Tyrant's Eye!
Such is why I, the Dark Flame Master,
have chosen you!
Our contract is not what the lowly masses
call the contract of lovers!
It is the Tyrant's Eye Contract of Lovers!
Consequently, we have no need to follow the
filthy traditions and senses of foolish, normal humans!
We need only to construct
our own unique relationship!
Ease your heart, for we are destined to do so!
As the Dark Flame Master and the Tyrant's Eye!
Yuuta...
Does... that work for you?
You spun windmills and went home?
That makes zero sense.
And you're fine with that?
Yeah.
I think Rikka should just be herself for now.
It feels like a weight's off my shoulders.
Well, if you're okay with it, then whatever.
But remember what Kannagi-san said.
If you keep dragging it out,
you can bet something troublesome will come between you two.
Do you want to see my magic?
To Be Continued
mebuita yamiyo ga haran he to hakou
The night falls again, bringing with it conflict
wakuwaku suru nee
Isn't it exciting?
nanatsu no oto eigou yori hanatarete
The seven of the scales echo forth from the ends of eternity
dokidoki suru nee
Isn't it thrilling?
matsui no rakuin anshou ni hirameku
The mark of the Mighty Hammer glitters from the sunken depths
mada tsudzukeru ki na no
You still haven't gotten over it yet?
ai no setsuri ni kyokkou matataku
The Aurora flashes upon the Providence of Love
mou yamenasai
Cut it out already
bokura wa hitotsu ni nari
We converge and become one
ten wo kakete
Flying through the sky
hokori wo sakebi chiru
We scream proud and burst
hanabi no you da
Like a rocket
kagayaki wa setsuna ni hazeta
In an instant, the sparkling is rent away
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
gusha wa tsukikage ni kyomou wo idaku
The fool holds, of the moonlight, dark delusions
game ga bokura wo
If this game exists
oitsumeru tame ni aru naraba
only so we may lose all hope
semete kuchinu hodo no baka de aritai
Then may my foolishness never die so long as it goes on
reiki suru tamashi de hoeta
Charged with lightning, I screamed forth from my soul
Van!shment th!s world!!
Vanishment this world!