It was the first time I'd ever hugged a girl.
I could feel a slight heat beyond the soft sensation.
She was so fragile, I felt like she'd break if I held her any tighter.
So lost and sad...
Rikka...
Rikka?
Media lab
Movie screening area
Forget it! Forget it! Forget it!
Far Eastern
Magic Nap Society
of Summer
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Students are to leave the school by 8pm at the latest.
Pandora's Lunchbox...
of the Holy Mother
Master!
Do you dare design to draw forth the deathly night of devils from this darkness?
Master?
You're still as death!
Did you freeze yourself in time?!
It doesn't seem that you have.
Master?
What the death are you doing? Master!
Could it be that Master finally accepts me as...
Master, we mustn't!
I'm your servant! We mustn't give in to our emotions like this!
Though, of course, they do say that
..forbidden passions are the most exciting...
Master?
I hugged Yuuta.
I love Yuuta.
Master?
No way... Are you just a
fake copy of Master?!
So now we not only have a fake
Forest Summer, but Master as well?!
I'm the real one.
But... does that mean...
Master, you f-f-fell in love
with the Dark Flame Master?
Master, I am needed for an urgent matter of life and death! I must take my leave.
Dekomori...
Don't try to stop me!
As your servant, it's my duty to cast the one who stole your heart into the darkn—
What should I do?
You said that you were able to protect the Wicked Eye for this long thanks to the Dark Flame Master.
I'm sure he'll be able to realize your heartfelt feelings as well.
I wonder.
I've been serving under you
for a little over two years.
It's the duty of the servant to know everything about their master.
Dekomori...
There's no need for you to worry.
The Wicked Eye's power exceeds death itself!
You'll be saying "'Til death do we part" in no time.
Then, you and Takanashi...
Yeah.
What should I do?
About what?
Am I supposed to confess?
You love her, don't you?
I think so...
But it's not because she's cute or hot!
She's way beyond help with
her eighth-grader syndrome,
but there's more to her than just that!
She has her problems,
and I feel sorry for her, but...
I mean... I'm not just doing it
out of pity, of course...
Say no more, dude.
You don't need a reason to fall in love.
What an expert you must be.
Good luck!
Same to you.
That's damn creepy!
How dare you treat me this way
after I listened to your troubles?!
No one asked you to!
You mess up everything by
spreading half-true rumors in class!
But darn, you're lucky.
Takanashi's got the potential to place 4th on the cutie poll.
With a girl like that...
With a girl like that?
One day, you'll...
We'll what?
Yuuta, I regret to say that I have no prior
experience regarding bodily interactions.
Regrettably, neither do I!
Don't even suggest that! Are you nuts?!
Well then... I've got something of my own to sort out, so I'll catch you later.
Kumin!
What?
Would you come with me
to the school fair afterparty?
Sure!
Really?
Cut!
Why do I always have to
endure your two-bit acting?
We're not acting!
And why are you even here at all?!
We need to get ready for
tomorrow's performance.
Where are Togashi and Takanashi?
Do not utter those names in my presence.
My mood is deathly foul.
We shall fight.
You think we have time for that?
We need to find those two and—
They already left, for death's sake!
The Dark Flame Master said they had something to discuss of deathly importance—
Um...
Follow my orders as bound by your pledge...
What's that?
An enchanted gem. It fulfills wishes.
I got it from Dekomori.
Wishes?
I can't go into details!
That's okay, I don't need to know.
You dropped it.
It's warm.
Strong wishes cause the gem to emit heat.
Which means—
Don't!
Ouch...
It started raining...
Do you have an umbre—Of course you do.
What did you want?
Oh, right.
I have something too.
Something highly confidential
I must discuss with you.
I-I see.
I wanted to talk about... But not here.
This can't go on.
Hey...
Schwarz Sechs Prototype Mark II!
How can you say its full name so fast?!
Hey!
Good thing it didn't fall into the river.
What's up?
The lights...
The lights... are moving.
nani mo iwanai senaka ni taishite
When I see you there, walking right in front of me
Rikka...
I love you, Yuuta.
nante ieba ii no kana
What should I say to make you turn around?
suki ni naru no ni riyuu wa nai no ni
It doesn't take a reason to fall in love with someone
yuuki no nasa ni iiwake bakari
But I need excuses because I'm too shy
I love you, Yuuta.
ryuuseigun wo nagameteitara
As we looked up to watch all those shooting stars
kirakira tte oto ga suru mitai
I felt like I could almost hear them glittering
Wait, I was gonna say it first!
sou iu kimochi no yoin sura
I've got a feeling that even that feeling
No. The Wicked Eye is destined to always be first.
kimi to nara wakachiaeru
Is something that we can both share
koi no kakera ga ima hitotsu ni
These bits of love are coming together now
I'm the Dark Flame Master!
yasuppoi kotoba de kazattemo
Even if I dress them in all sorts of fancy words
The Wicked Eye's the strongest of all.
kimi ni todokanai kamo shirenai
They might not be able to reach your heart
Geez, whatever.
It took me ages to come up with this,
so I'm saying it anyway.
demo nani mo iwanai mama da to kimi ga
But if I don't say anything then you just might
Thou who art surrounded
by the flames of darkness,
kiechau kamo shirenai
Disappear into the night
I, the Dark Flame Master,
beseech thee to forge a lover's—
ano hoshi mitai ni
Just like a shooting star
ima doko de naiteru no
Where are you, and why are you crying?
Okay, screw that. The point is—
Continue!
Yuuta!
doushitara waratte kuremasu ka
What do I need to do to make you smile?
Thou who art surrounded
by the flames of darkness,
ten wo tsunaide seiza ni shitai
I wish we could be joined together, like a constellation
I, the Dark Flame Master, beseech thee to forge a lover's contract between us.
sono yubi de
By our hands
Okay.
Shouldn't you be leaning on my chest?
senaka awase ja nakute kocchi wo muite
Don't walk with your back to me, look this way
Is it embarrassing?
Then, your hand?
soshite tonari wo arukitai yo
And let me walk beside you
My pinky.
Your pinky, then.
I'm home!
You're late!
Sorry, Kuzuha.
Demandant, do you possess feelings of love for the respondent?
No.
All I feel is that I want to be divorced from the respondent as soon as possible.
What are you doing?
We have to talk.
Huh?
This one's lost its taste too.
You can have it.
Can't we discuss this at home?
I can't allow Rikka to hear it.
It's from the head restaurant in Italy. They invited me there for training.
I have no reason to refuse.
You really are that good, huh?
Did you doubt me?
Not at all!
Whatever.
But isn't that nice?
I'm sure Rikka will be—
You get it, don't you?
I can't let her live there by herself.
So Mom's moving in in my stead.
Rikka's mother?
What do you think?
I don't—
Do you think it's gonna work out?
Rikka doesn't hate her mother, right? Then—
Mom...
Mom tried to talk with Rikka a number of times.
She apologized for not telling her about Dad.
But...
What's wrong, Tooka?
Please help me!
I'm sure she'd listen to you!
You just need to tell her to grow up!
She's grown up enough.
I think that eyepatch is the armor by which she protects herself.
I'm sure she understands... all of it.
But she can't deal with the gloom in any other way.
Acting like that is the only way she can protect...
Protect what?
I don't know.
But I'd say she still wants to hold on to it.
If she listened to you or your mother and swallowed the bitter pill, it'd be all over.
She doesn't want that.
What's wrong with it being over?
There's no Horizon or Wicked Eye!
No matter how much she looks for Dad, she'll never find him!
Well...
How is affirming what she says better in any way?
She's never gonna get what she's looking for!
But...
Encouraging her like that...
is just irresponsible.
Ginkgo Festival
Here's your cheese potato!
Thank you very much!
Wow, it's really popular.
That's just on the outside!
Inside, it's a cruel, backstabbing gang!
That's why I don't want anything to do with them anymore.
So it's golden on the outside, slimy on the inside, just like a cheese potato?
Spare me your smart comments!
And where are Takanashi and Togashi?
They said they were going to change.
Hurry up!
Just you watch!
Our impromptu performance will take all your customers away!
Oh look, it's Forest Summer!
Don't call m—
Sato! Suzuki!
Hey! Haven't seen you since junior high!
How old are you this year? 716?
Are you still catching lizards?
Don't bring that up!
Didn't you paint your lips purple
to feign sickness, Sato?
Oh, you were into stuff like that too?
You too, Suzuki!
I remember you claiming you'd found fairies!
I just...
Fairies?
You never know what'll be unearthed next.
Mining for eighth-grade memories is a dangerous job.
Yesterday's business is still far from over!
Today I've increased my powers fourfold!
Ugh, it's heavy!
You seriously are nuts.
Eastern Magic Napping Society in Summer
How is affirming what
she says better in any way?
Encouraging her like that...
is just irresponsible.
Yuuta, you're so cool!
You don't have to look that impressed!
Your move!
"Be engulfed by the flames
of darkness, and begone!"
Yuuta, do it!
I don't wanna.
But you'll have to do it soon anyway.
Yeah, I guess so.
Be engulfed by the flames
of darkness, and begone.
There was no power in that.
Can there be any power in it?
Of course. Open your legs, bend your knees, and flap the tail of your coat.
Yeah, yeah.
Be engulfed by the flames
of darkness, and begone!
No pictures!
Next, together.
It's almost time to begin our mission.
Let's proceed to our positions.
Yeah... I'm not really feeling it, though.
Rikka!
What?
Nothing.
Your pinky.
Excuse me...
Yes?
Would a girl named Takanashi
Rikka happen to be here?
She's...
She's not here right now.
I see.
Could you give her this?
Um...
It's okay. I'm leaving right away.
I think she still doesn't want to meet me yet.
Am I really being irresponsible?
Yuuta!
Why are you spacing out there?
It's about time we started!
We've got so many visitors too!
Rikka...
Take off your eyepatch.
It's time for our long-running talent show!
Ad-lib entries are welcome too!
Let's start then! Number one, on stage!
I'm number one, class 1-3, Haruno Shinya! I'll be doing impersonations!
First, the principal!
Are you done with the performance?
Yeah. The brat and I managed to pull it off.
She came at me with killing intent, you know!
Sorry.
I didn't expect ...
you to say something like that.
That lunchbox, you know...
It was still warm.
It had a good heft to it, too.
It was stuffed.
With love?
With reality.
Number two! Class 1-4, Isshiki Makoto!
I'll shout!
Tsuyuri Kumin!
Please go out with me!
Sorry...
What about Takanashi?
I'll go look for her.
Togashi!
I think you did the right thing.
Okay, let's welcome the next person on stage!
Class 1-4, Takanashi Rikka.
Thanks.
I'll sing.
miagete goran yoru no hoshi wo
Take a look up above, see the stars out at night
What is she doing?!
chiisana hoshi no chiisana hikari ga
All those little stars, all those little lights
Dad...
Dad liked this song.
sasayaka na shiawase wo utatteru
Singing about little, happy things
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
That was Takanashi Rikka from class 1-4!
Rikka...
Thank you very much!
Does this song bring back memories for you, or something like that?
To be continued