M-Meow.
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You looked this way
and saw me pouting with a frown ❤
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I was just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
matte miru no
That's all I really wanted ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
But the things I mumbled to myself
after "Nothing" were
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
hazukashii kara
Way too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask me what I said
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing us together
mou hajimatteta
Had already started then ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
This feels wonderful.
The water's a bit deeper over there. Be careful.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Hey! What are you looking at?
I nearly drowned, you know!
Sorry!
Togashi-kun, you're such a perv!
Hey, cut it out.
You perv!
Quit it!
Perv!
Stop!
So you've finally returned.
What's that in your hand?
Heilige Wasser!
Magic chamber pressure rising.
Energy charged to 120%.
So it's your fault!
What happened to your forehead?
My forehead?
There was a ferocious battle last night, and...
No, you're better off not knowing.
Dealing with people with eighth-grade syndrome's a real pain.
A cat?
Meow.
Chimaera?
Like those monsters in games and in Greek mythology?
Yes.
I encountered her last night while searching for the Unseen Horizon.
And I caught her!
Are you keeping her?
Yes, I'm making her my familiar.
As creatures that dwell in the Dark Realm, chimaeras should hold the power to detect the Unseen Horizon.
But there's one problem.
Which is?
The Unseen Horizon Administration Bureau's priestess's eyes
react violently to Chimaera's mana.
So your sister's allergic to cats?
And so, Dark Flame Master,
my comrade in arms, I come seeking your assis—
Not happening.
Dandelion Kindergarten
A week has passed since I started high school.
Please make sure she behaves.
Hey, Dark Flame Master...
Dark Flame Master!
Stop that!
I've managed to adjust to my class,
Priestess of... the Melody
and I've gotten the hang of handling this extreme case of eighth-grade syndrome.
Yuuta.
No means no.
Sure, Kuzuha and Yumeha like animals, and my mom probably wouldn't mind,
but I don't want to do anything you ask me to.
You're so mean.
By the way, where is your father?
He moved to Jakarta because of his job.
I see.
I still need to be careful that
no one finds out about my past,
Did you know that "Jakarta" is the root
for the word "potato" in Japanese?
but other than that, everything's going great,
Hirakata
and I'm blending into my class just fine.
There we have it. Hirakata-san will be the volunteer librarian for our class.
Well, I did get elected class rep thanks to one of Isshiki's pranks,
but as far as the job goes...
Can't complain.
And on that note, we conclude.
Okay, thank you.
Homeroom is over now.
Nice job.
Must suck to be class rep, though.
Who got me elected, again?
My bad.
Anyway, know who you're voting for yet?
I want to get a running tally going.
On what?
On who's the cutest girl.
I told you, the guys are voting on who the cutest girl in class is.
Who're you voting for?
You sure you want to do that?
The girls'll kill you if they find out.
Like that'd happen.
Guys know how to keep a secret
when it comes to this stuff.
Togashi-kun.
Yes?!
Could we take care of the science lab at lunch?
The science teacher asked us to check the supplies, remember?
...seven, eight, nine, ten...
Twelve in all.
Twelve...
Okay. That's it for this shelf.
I recognize this scent!
It's either Asience or Petal Sassoon.
Used to being a class rep yet?
Yeah, I guess.
Can't really say I know what I'm doing, though.
Feel free to tell me if I miss anything.
I can be pretty forgetful.
Really?
You look really responsible to me.
I'm just pretending to be responsible.
I'm a class rep too, you know.
R-Really?
You look like you're used to it, though.
You've served as class rep a lot in the past, haven't you?
Well, yeah.
But only because I was nominated.
You've been one too, right?
Me?
No way.
Maybe once in elementary school.
I didn't really stand out.
Really?
When we first met, I had the feeling that we were kind of similar.
Remember? We met at the station on our way to the entrance ceremony.
You remember that?
Of course.
Why wouldn't I?
Yeah, but...
We didn't know each other's name or class.
Yeah.
That's why I thought, "Oh, it's him!" when I saw you in the classroom.
O-Oh...
Get a grip, man.
You can panic later.
But at least I haven't made a bad impression on her.
Is this a sign?
Am I finally going to get a life?
We can check the rest tomorrow.
Should I ask?
Want to go home together?
Wait, hold on.
I need to simulate this.
Response prediction!
Want to go home together?
Why?
No! I'll die!
Wh-What's wrong, Togashi-kun?!
No, nothing. Just a little—
Togashi-kun!
Wh-What the heck?!
You scared me.
It's you?!
It's you again?!
Yuuta, I-I'm getting dizzy.
Takanashi-san?
Why are you two here?
The teacher asked us to come here.
You can just ignore her.
What are these chemicals doing here?
It seems even this place isn't out of the Administration Bureau's reach.
Who cares? Just take off the lab coat.
It's not yours, is it?
Take it off?
Yeah, take it off.
Right here and now.
Take it off right here and now?
You said it that way on purpose, didn't you?
And don't play with the bottles!
Sorry, but there isn't enough mana in this world to support Chimaera.
I need to create some artificially to replenish her mana.
Chimaera?
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's a gray cat with a weird mark on its head.
Takanashi-san picked it up yesterday.
I told you to call me "Rikka," not "Takanashi."
A gray cat?
It might be...
Did you really find Dodomen?
It might not be her, but she fits the description on here pretty well.
Missing Cat!!
Missing Cat !!
(
Name: Dodomen  Female
She's about this long and this wide.
She has wings on her back too.
No, she doesn't.
That does sound a bit like my cat.
The wings?!
Enough already. Just be quiet.
When did she go missing?
About a week ago?
Want to come see her?
Can I?!
Of course.
Um... May Seventh-senpai?
Oh, it's read as "Tsuyuri."
Breed: imxed breed with some Persian.
Breed: mixed breed with some Persian.
Age: 5 years. Fur color: gray. Size: Big.
Characteristics: Spunky, sleeps a lot.
Please contact us if you find her.
Contact:
Class 2-4,
Tsuyuri Kumin
I'm Tsuyuri Kumin.
Pleased to meet you.
Um... I'm Togashi Yuuta.
Don't.
My apartment is on the second floor, and Takanashi-san's is right above.
Call me Rikka.
Be quiet.
You're such good friends.
Did you grow up together?
No.
Takanashi-san just moved in last week—
Shh!
Magic code: unlocked.
Stop being dramatic and open the door.
Shh!
It's open.
It's finally open!
Dealing with you is giving me a headache.
Wait here.
I must ensure no distortions are present in my room.
Sorry we invited ourselves over just like that, I guess.
Every girl has her secrets.
You may enter.
Thank you.
Wow, your room looks amazing.
Welcome to the Dark Side.
Welcome to the Pandemonic Chaos.
I hope you know that's redundant.
You have a lot of cute stuffed animals.
That's Genbu, Guardian of the North.
It's a Mauser C96!
You've got some good taste!
It's a holy gun with the power to vanquish evil.
Yeah, that's definitely the vibe it gives.
Can I touch it?
Yes.
Man, Mausers are so cool!
Ba-ba-ba-bang!
Ba-bang!
Um... The original model for this gun was made over 100 years ago, and it's really famous!
This is the M712 variant, and...
Togashi-kun, you like those kinds of things?
By the way, placement for all objects in this room was determined by astrology.
Do not move anything.
There's no need to clean this room.
Fire.
So where's the cat?
I've made it invisible to the eyes of humans.
You're speaking to an upperclassman.
Show some respect.
No, that's okay.
She blended into the room!
You can see her?!
Stop making this harder than it has to be.
So is she yours?
Unfortunately, this isn't the cat I'm looking for.
Her whiskers are different.
I see.
Whose cat is it?
Whose is it?
Closing airlock!
Flooding anti-radiation shield!
Everyone out!
What?!
Are they in my room?
What are you doing in my room?!
I'll make it quick.
Is this a duel?!
What are you getting all excited about?
I needed to defeat you eventually, anyway.
Schwarzschild, full power!
Avalon Schwarz!
You must be Togashi Yuuta.
Yeah.
I'm Takanashi Touka.
Her sister.
We need to talk.
This "Tyrant's Eye" or whatever—she's been going on about it since middle school.
Frankly, it's a problem.
And she keeps bringing cats home
even though she knows I'm allergic.
She's going to be the death of me.
Sorry about this, but could you take care of it?
Huh?
The cat.
I can't touch it.
Do something about it.
I don't care if you give it away or throw it out on the street.
Just get it out of here.
That's all.
Um, but...
Why me?
You don't want to?
I can't say that I don't...
Then do it.
But...
The audio in this voice recorder is from two years ago.
It was recorded on the balcony of this apartment.
This is neither an act nor a dream!
In 2012, in accordance with the Mayan prophecy,
this world shall be engulfed by the darkness!
What's wrong, Togashi-kun?
Onii-chan, what are you doing?
I am not your brother!
I am the Dark Flame Master!
Wielder of the Dark Flame and
He who shall reduce the world to ash!
Oh, is that your voice, Togashi-kun?
Stop it!
The winds feel magnificent today.
I'm begging you!
I don't want to hear anymore!
What are you talking about?
The wind isn't blowing at all.
The power... I can feel the power!
Stop shouting. Everyone's laughing at you.
Foolish mortals would never understand.
Just so you know, I like uploading things to video-sharing websites.
Listen well, my beloved sister.
Do it.
What now?
My body...
Yes, ma'am.
She got away.
Mom, Dad, I'm sorry for everything I've done!
Togashi-kun, let's run to the ends of the Earth together!
I might just take you up on that.
This is the end of the Earth!
Because the world is round!
What do you think you're doing?
Touka-san's really mad.
We need to get out of here.
She's the Administration Bureau's strongest priestess!
She's a force to be reckoned with.
Thou shalt sacrifice thy virgin blood to these chains!
Bloody Prison!
Very nice work.
Teleportation is just one of the
many abilities that she possesses.
Sure you weren't just careless?
She's here.
This is so much fun!
It's like a horror movie!
This isn't fun.
I just saw a flash!
Tsuyuri-san!
Yuuta, hurry!
Why do I feel like my life's actually in danger?
I'm afraid I don't have the means to defeat the Priestess at this point in time.
However, I absolutely must defeat her one day.
Take her and escape.
Once this battle is over, let's live together.
You're raising your own death flag.
You escape too, Yuuta.
I'll hold her off.
Use that chance to get out of here.
I must find the Unseen Horizon.
One day, I shall.
Takanashi...
Call me Rikka.
No, I mean look at Chimaera.
There you are.
I'll distract her!
You get Chimaera!
Come forth, Schwarzsechs Prototype Mark II!
Reality, be rent!
Synapse, break!
Vanishment, this world!
By the blood contract, I summon thee unto this world.
Königin der Nacht.
Dark Matter Blaze!
Takanashi!
She's... kind of winning?
Nergal Blast!
You can do it, Takanashi!
Gun Twinkle!
Cut it out!
Try to keep your delusions in check.
Just keep the cat out of the apartment,
and I'll let you off the hook this time.
Ow...
Here.
Impossible!
I'm sure I hit her with the Gun Twinkle!
So why?!
Maybe you did. In your head.
It still stings.
Dark Matter Blaze!
Life isn't a fighting game.
Guess I could keep a model gun.
Sorry, but you can't go back to your old home.
I don't want another bump on my head.
Mom, can we keep a cat?
What? That's a bit sudden.
A cat!
It's so cute!
Kumin-senpai's cat was found, safe and sound, soon after.
To Be Continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?