For Sale
Rend reality.
Shatter synapse.
Vanishment... this world!
Avalon Smasher!
How long do you plan to continue this farce?
Do you enjoy it?
Do you enjoy babbling this childish nonsense?
Wicked... Twinkle!
Do you hate Mom?
No...
Do you just want to cause trouble for Grandma and Grandpa, then?
No!
Don't you get it? We can't change the past!
There's nothing we can do about it!
When will you be satisfied? We have no choice!
Evil Eye...
No...
No!
There's no house here anymore. Dad's gone too.
The Ethereal Horizon doesn't even—
It exists.
The Ethereal Horizon exists!
You?
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
I think you're right, Tooka.
Yuuta...
I think Rikka's doing this because she knows it too.
You can tell her to accept reality,
but there are many things that none of us are able to accept.
She had no time to prepare for what happened,
and it was all over before she knew it.
Togashi
She isn't running away.
She isn't even trying to look the other way.
3rd period
Study hall
She just wonders if it's okay to sum things up with the usual platitudes as if that was all there was to it.
3rd period
Study hall
My Notes
Togashi Yuuta
And yet, everyone tells her, "that's life." "That's reality."
Is that really right?
That's what reality is.
Everyone has to live with it.
That's what it means to become an adult.
Maybe so, but for her...
Rikka!
The Exile... of Two
Ah, welcome back!
Where's Rikka?
She came back in a taxi not too long ago.
I guess she's on the shore.
Everyone else left a while ago to light fireworks.
Thank you very much!
The time has come for the Black Dragon to be unleashed on its deathly rampage!
Wait! Wait!
What's wrong with you?
Here you are.
Come on, boy! Fetch!
Go get it!
Why?!
Isn't this fun?
Yes, it is!
Togashi and Rikka sure are late, though.
Where could they have gone?
Where do you think they'd go after sneaking out to the beach together during summer vacation?
Don't tell me they encountered a warrior from the Otherworld!
Ah, Togashi!
Where's Rikka?!
We haven't seen her!
Damn...
Togashi!
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Youth at its finest!
Could this be the battlefield of love?
Battlefield of Love is a powerful barrier spell!
Fake Summer
Yuuta!
Geez, I barely made it!
But why?
That's my line!
Where do you think you're going?
The Overseers' power in that location is overwhelming.
Their barrier is just too strong.
I must retreat.
So you're going home?
Did anybody notice it was there?
dare ga kidzuketa darou
The shadow beyond the light, growing ever darker
hikari no mukou de koku naru kage ni
Yuuta...
Hm?
Yuuta, how did you first come to realize the power of the Dark Flames?
The past was so distant, I had to scream
kako ga tooku de sakenda
I never even had it...
Turn around, and cover my ears
senaka mukete wa mimi wo fusaideru
Well, I first realized when I was talking with my friends.
They were excited about going somewhere to hang out.
Don't call me weak just because I cry
sou naku kara tte yowai to kimenaide
I felt left out, as if I was something different.
Don't think I'm strong just because I don't
nakanai kara tte tsuyoi to omowanaide
It felt odd, a weird loneliness like being left behind by the world.
The warmth of your hand
kimi ga nigiru te
As you hold mine
atatakasa wo
So your dark self awakened to its memories of another world?
Maybe I can try trusting it now
shinjite mite mo ii ka na
Even that seems like a better
explanation than the truth.
That's why...
I've finally realized
yatto kidzuita
Damn me!
I've finally found it
youyaku mitsuketa
What's wrong? The Overseers' curse?
The truth that was hazy through my tears
namida de boyaketa shinjitsu
No...
Anyway, do you—
Our eyes met.
You said I could be myself
boku wa boku de ii to
As you pat me on the head
atama wo nadenagara
As I watch you sleep here next to me
nemuru kimi no yokogao ga ima
A whole new feeling lights up in me
atarashii kimochi wo terashita
Now we're bound by an even stronger contract, Dark Flame Master.
I told you...
Thank you for standing by me
arigatou soba ni itekurete
"Be engulfed by the flames of darkness—"
Stop it!
The seed has already started to sprout
mebuita yo hajimari no tane ga
It's from Togashi.
What's it say?
Takanashi's going back home,
so he's going with her.
So they left?
They're so bold!
Bold?
That cutesy act of yours is really off-putting.
Have you ever dated a boy?
Of course!
Takashi, from kindergarten! We were in the same class together.
But then we had to move overseas for my dad's work,
and I was homeschooled until high school.
It's been a while since I last met a real airhead.
Ouch!
Sorry!
It stings!
My body was seared by the Sun, like the wings of mighty Icarus before he fell to his death!
Wh-What do you want?
Well, I thought since we're all here, I might as well wash your back.
I found a nice, soft sponge too.
I-I'll pass...
Please, it's no trouble at all!
Get away from me!
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Untitled
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Untitled
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Untitled
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
We're going home
ahead of you.
Rikka's with me. Don't worry.
Darn, it's gotten quite late.
Yuuta! I've been barred from my room!
The passcode was changed!
You just forgot your key, didn't you?
Damn. I guess that leaves one option.
Huh? I'm back!
Huh? No one's here.
Wait a moment.
Could the Overseers have invaded?
Stop! Please, spare his family!
Don't jinx them!
Oh, right.
Kuzuha and Yumeha are at summer school
and Mom's got a night shift.
Watch out! They might be hiding in camouflage!
No.
They're all coming home tomorrow.
Which means...
We're alone tonight?
Uh... Which way was the bathroom again?
Huh? Kumin?
Ah, you're up too, Isshiki?
What are you doing?
It's so dark outside that the
Moon must be really pretty,
so I thought I'd go for a walk.
Want to come with me, Isshiki?
Just... Just a moment!
A walk?
If you wanna go, just go.
I'm hanging up.
That answer's no answer at all!
Just because you got a girlfriend,
now you're abandoning your friends?!
When did I get a girlfriend?
Did you forget I was the one who talked to you on the day of the entrance ceremony?
Sorry, gotta go!
Hey, wai—
Quit going through my stuff!
Yuuta, what's this?
Dunno.
Just put it away already.
Could this be some ultimate equipment you couldn't tell even the Wicked Eye about?
No!
Geez, you're so hopeless.
You put it on like this, then this here.
Then you swing your arm...
like this!
Amazing! Yuuta, that's amazing!
You don't have to appreciate it to tears.
With the full power of the Wicked Eye,
I look at you with respect!
You don't have to do that.
Feel like anything in particular?
Though there isn't much left,
so I can't make anything like Tooka.
I'd rather challenge the final boss than eat something like that.
That's some determination.
Then do you want to go to the store
and grab something?
It's getting pretty late.
The "store"?
Could you possibly be referring
to a "convenience store"?
What? Is that a problem?
The Priestess always forbade the use of such
stores, saying we should make our own food.
Well, if anything, you should thank her.
So I wanna try it!
Thank you, come again!
Is this really gonna be enough?
Tuna
Its structure has piqued my interest
since I saw you eating one in school.
You tear it open here,
then split the packaging.
Take the two sides and pull them.
That's so cool!
It is?
It's good.
Tooka would be red-hot furious
if she saw you now.
Here, have some fried chicken.
Quite a smart taste.
How can something taste smart?
What about your rice ball?
Wanna have a bite?
Here.
Spicy, isn't it?
That's mean!
Sorry, sorry.
Here, have this to make up for it.
Red means danger!
Not taking the bait, huh?
Replenishment complete.
Then let's go home.
Yuuta!
I don't wanna go home!
I'll bathe in the moonlight!
Hey!
What do you think?
It's night! And we're alone!
Could the message be "I set the stage, now confess to me!"?
How should I know?
You're so cold!
Did you forget I was the one who talked to you on the day of the entrance ceremony?
Didn't you say that already?
I'm hanging up.
Wait, please!
What?
How are things with Takanashi?
We just had dinner.
She forgot the keys to her place.
What? So you're alone with her?
Yeah.
I thought it all seemed suspicious,
but this is beyond my expectations!
What are you even talking about?
Can you really imagine things
going that way for us?
Why?
Do you need to ask? It's Rikka!
She's eighth-grader syndrome at its finest!
But you're high schoolers!
So?
Yuuta!
But...
Hello?
Hey!
Geez.
It sounds like
you'll be on the phone
for a while,
so I'm heading back.
Kumin
It sounds like
you'll be on the phone
for a while,
so I'm heading back.
Kumin
With Rikka...
Not a chance!
She's so deep in her syndrome, does she even understand the concept of love?
Yuuta...
Is this the Mjolnir Maul?
Nope, no way.
Stop that. You'll stretch it out.
Just roll up the sleeves, okay?
You're good at making references, huh?
Anyway, it's getting late.
You can sleep in this room,
so brush your teeth and—
It smells of Yuuta.
Stop that!
Why?
It smells of you.
Stop! That's really embarrassing!
I'm turning the light off.
The Wicked Eye is even more active at night, so I alread—
Whatever. Get some sleep.
Geez, talking about my smell...
Didn't I say to get some sleep?
I got butterflies in my stomach.
She must be close by. We must be on alert.
Come on, why—
I'm turning it off.
I got butterflies in my stomach.
It'll get better if you sleep.
My heart's racing!
That's the same thing.
I'm excited!
What are you, some theme park commercial?!
I'm explosive!
Why?!
I don't know!
J-Just go to sleep already.
Wait!
Hey, wh—
Don't go.
No way! She's...
Yuuta, close your eyes.
Just for a moment.
Just for a moment, please.
N-No way... Is she... really...
C-Can I... really do this?
No... But...
What's this?
A fragment of a spell that
contains the ultimate power.
Proof of the new contract we formed earlier.
Could you draw it somewhere less noticeable?
This is the most effective location.
It will amplify your powers of darkness many times.
As well as the Dark Flames, you can now use the even more powerful Dark Buster.
Get some sleep.
Eighth-grader syndrome will always be eighth-grader syndrome, huh?
Well, this ended quite well... I guess.
Whatever.
My heart's racing!
This aura...
Who's there?!
Yuuta.
To be continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?