Received Message
Takanashi Rikka
The water mage's offensive
grows stronger. Backup.
l
I wanna fallin' love
yokan yume ga tsudzuku
The dream will go on and on
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
We made a promise, but deep inside,
I'm still scared it might all disappear
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
hitori ja nai tte shinjitai no ni
Even though I want to believe you'll always be there
omoitsudzuketeru dake de shiawase nante ienai ne
Being in love with each other isn't happiness all by itself
utsuro na jishin seotteitemo
Even if I pretend that it's all that matters
kimi ga warau
You just laugh
soshite watashi no yuuki ni naru
And you always give me strength
l
hitotsu no kotoba de kimi no sekai wo kaeraretara
But if one simple word can change your whole world
But if one simple word can change your whole world
l
futatsu no koi ga shinka suru
Then two loves will start to progress
Then two loves will start to progress
l
hontou da yo
That's the truth
That's the truth
l
meguraseta mayoi ga mitsuketa kotae wa
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
itsudemo kimi ni michibikareta
You always led me to the answer
Even if I can't work up the courage to do it
l
sunao ni tsutaetai
I want to tell you everything
I want to tell you everything
l
ko
ro
aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
kokoro aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
kokoro
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
l
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real
come
on
voice
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
Full Moon Ragnarok
New Message
Release Seal
Water and Column
To Be Continued
mebuita yamiyo ga haran he to hakou
The night falls again, bringing with it conflict
wakuwaku suru nee
Isn't it exciting?
nanatsu no oto eigou yori hanatarete
The seven of the scales echo forth from the ends of eternity
dokidoki suru nee
Isn't it thrilling?
matsui no rakuin anshou ni hirameku
The mark of the Mighty Hammer glitters from the sunken depths
mada tsudzukeru ki na no
You still haven't gotten over it yet?
ai no setsuri ni kyokkou matataku
The Aurora flashes upon the Providence of Love
mou yamenasai
Cut it out already
bokura wa hitotsu ni nari
We converge and become one
ten wo kakete
Flying through the sky
hokori wo sakebi chiru
We scream proud and burst
hanabi no you da
Like a rocket
kagayaki wa setsuna ni hazeta
In an instant, the sparkling is rent away
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
gusha wa tsukikage ni kyomou wo idaku
The fool holds, of the moonlight, dark delusions
game ga bokura wo
If this game exists
oitsumeru tame ni aru naraba
only so we may lose all hope
semete kuchinu hodo no baka de aritai
Then may my foolishness never die so long as it goes on
reiki suru tamashi de hoeta
Charged with lightning, I screamed forth from my soul
Van!shment th!s world!!
Vanishment this world!