Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
Takarabayashi
Anju
Sword of Winter  2
That was really interesting.
Yuuta!
Here. It's what you asked for yesterday.
Yeah, thanks.
Something up, Rikka?
Not really.
That is suspicious.
Perhaps it's encrypted data from the Mage's Alliance.
Are we witnessing the beginning of the Eighth Magical War?!
Of course not.
She's right.
I don't think he'd hide that from you, Rikka-chan.
Indeed, that is true.
Then it's something he wants to keep hidden from me even though we're bound by contract.
We're talking about Isshiki here, I'm sure it's nothing good.
Like when he tried to rank all the girls' cuteness.
I wonder what it is.
Sup.
Togashi-kun, come take a seat.
No, I have a bad feeling about this so I won't.
Yuuta, I question your loyalty to our contract!
Huh?
l
I wanna fallin' love
yokan yume ga tsudzuku
The dream will go on and on
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
We made a promise, but deep inside,
I'm still scared it might all disappear
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
hitori ja nai tte shinjitai no ni
Even though I want to believe you'll always be there
omoitsudzuketeru dake de shiawase nante ienai ne
Being in love with each other isn't happiness all by itself
utsuro na jishin seotteitemo
Even if I pretend that it's all that matters
kimi ga warau
You just laugh
soshite watashi no yuuki ni naru
And you always give me strength
l
hitotsu no kotoba de kimi no sekai wo kaeraretara
But if one simple word can change your whole world
But if one simple word can change your whole world
l
futatsu no koi ga shinka suru
Then two loves will start to progress
Then two loves will start to progress
l
hontou da yo
That's the truth
That's the truth
l
meguraseta mayoi ga mitsuketa kotae wa
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
itsudemo kimi ni michibikareta
You always led me to the answer
Even if I can't work up the courage to do it
l
sunao ni tsutaetai
I want to tell you everything
I want to tell you everything
l
ko
ro
aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
kokoro aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
kokoro
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
l
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real
come
on
voice
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
Cut this out!
Come on, untie me!
Settle down, it'll be over soon enough.
How many times have I told you it's just homework?
Then why won't you show us?!
Well...
You leave us no choice but to check for ourselves.
Fortunately, we were able to prepare a magical analysis device.
Only for a little while though.
You're helping them too, Sensei?!
Why do you seem so worried?
It must really be something you don't want us to see.
I'm telling you it's not!
I don't really mind if you guys see it, but...
Kumin-senpai, open it.
Stop, idiot!
I feel sorry for Togashi-kun.
I'll do it.
You're unusually motivated, Rikka-chan.
This bag is emitting dark energy.
Not the usual response from the Tyrant's eye.
Stop! Hold on a minute.
Nibutani...
Have you double-crossed me?!
No, I haven't!
We're talking about something secretly passed between boys, right?
Seeing how much he doesn't want us to see it...
You know, it could be...
Y-You mean it's...
It's what?
Well, it's...
Come on. Spit it out already!
You do it! You brought it up!
Dekomori.
Well, you know...
In other words, it could be a collection of the female Homo sapien's primitive form.
Primitive?
What are you even talking about?
Don't make me say it, you started all this!
No, I didn't!
What's going on?
Look at you blush!
Sure you aren't talking about yourself?!
We're at school. Who would bring that kind of thing?!
Togashi-kun!
You immoral Guerzoniansus!
Stop! It's not whatever you're imagining!
I don't understand any of this.
Stop!
Wait!
Removable Disc (E)
General Options
Open the folder and play all files
Show automatic booting advanced settings
A woman?!
Close it, Master! That is something unsightly!
Yeah! If you look at that here—
A swimsuit?
Really?
A woman. Another. Here. Here! Here too!
Yuuta!
An idol?
Yeah.
I followed her when I was in middle school.
Since she's already retired,
I asked Isshiki to give me the pictures he had.
So Togashi-kun likes idols, huh?
So what if I do? I shouldn't have to talk to you guys about this.
I thought Guerzoniansus had fallen to the dark side for a moment.
You really let your imagination run wild.
What do you mean?
I didn't even say anything!
Your "primitive" blushing face spoke for itself.
Be silent!
We know what's on it now, so it's okay.
Yeah.
No, it's really not!
Rikka-chan.
Master...
This is a serious violation, a breach of our contract.
It is unforgivable that he secretly admires this kind of thing while we are bound together by our pact.
Are you angry?
I'm sorry for trying to hide it,
but looking at an idol isn't violating our contract.
It is. This must be disposed of.
It's someone else's!
Then return it.
Okay, I get it. I'll return it tomorrow.
No, return it now.
There's no rush, tomorrow's fine.
Today. The Netherworld demands it.
That's right! Do you really want to see it that badly?
Not really, but...
You said this some time ago, Togashi-kun:
"Rikka, I only have eyes for you!"
Don't say that out loud!
Besides, she's an idol!
She doesn't even know who I am!
I might as well not even exist to her!
Really now?
So you wouldn't mind if Takanashi-san did the same thing?
This man isn't too bad.
The Dark Flame Dragon within me refuses!
See? It's no different for women.
If you understand, hurry up and return it.
I agree with Mori Summer-chan.
Are you sure?
Yeah, thanks.
But you haven't had a chance to look at it yet.
Don't get busted this time!
Later!
Hey!
Bye, Kumin-senpai!
Really, just how much trouble are you going to cause us.
Aren't you glad Togashi-kun kept his promise, Rikka-chan?
No different for women, huh?
Is it really?
So that happened.
Sophia, did you know about this girl who stole Yuuta's heart?
Yeah, I think I remember someone like that.
He would never admit it though.
I've long since abandoned worldly emotions such as love!
Yes, it's all beyond the Realm of Chaos.
That means nothing to me. N-Nothing...
Dark Shameless Master.
All he did was look at photos every once in awhile.
Hero or not, he's still a boy.
Even now he reads dirty magazines, right?
That's a different matter.
That woman captured Yuuta's heart before we formed our contract.
Is that a problem?
It is.
He's in a contract with you now, so isn't it fine?
It's not. It makes me feel this strange tightness in my chest.
The Tyrant's Eye sure is selfish.
Really?
Well, that might be a good thing.
A good thing?
Yuuta...
I only have eyes for you, Rikka.
Yuuta.
Fret not. I only have eyes for you.
Yuuta!
Does he have more in here?
ImageFolder
Nothing strange.
Our contract is intact.
I'll show you in case something happens.
Togashi Yuuta usually hides his important things here.
Somewhere around here...
I brought it with me...
I-I'll confirm it to be sure.
Do your teeth hurt or something?!
You're a bad influence on our contract!
Rikka, are you still up?
Oh, she's asleep.
I thought I heard something.
Wake up, Rikka. We're gonna be late.
Hurry up or you'll miss breakfast.
You should clean your room more.
Something wrong?
N-No, I'm fine.
Is something wrong?
Like what?
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Be engulfed by the flames of darkness and begone!
They got into an argument?
Looks like it.
Wash your
hands after
going outside!
Togashi-kun told me Rikka-chan broke that flash drive from yesterday.
She snuck into my room in the middle of the night and stole something.
She's a thief! A criminal!
And she doesn't seem to understand that.
Then Rikka-chan told me...
Yuuta said he would return that drive but didn't.
An outright violation of our contract.
I did not break it.
The forces of darkness delivered him his punishment.
So that's why they're acting like that?
What should we do about it?
Who knows? I'd just let them be.
What? It's your time to shine, Mori Summer-chan.
What gave you that idea?
Are we really going to leave them alone?
Not like we really can.
I know, right?
Okay, you two.
Look over here.
What do you want?
Stay out of it this time.
You're not leaving us a choice.
Somebody needs to sort this out.
You guys don't act like a normal couple.
What does that mean?
Exactly as it sounds.
I'm sure some nonsense like the forces of darkness came up,
and the conversation went absolutely nowhere.
It's not nonsense. The Tyrant's Eye—
Yeah, okay. I hear you.
You're blaming Togashi-kun, right?
Don't worry.
I agree with you.
Why are you blaming me?
Your lie started all this.
You told us you'd return that drive, but you took it home anyway.
That's entirely unrelated.
It's entirely related.
This only happened because you broke your promise.
I kept my promise.
I went to return it. I never said I actually did.
You're unbelievable!
What kind of twisted logic is that?
It's the truth.
You're pathetic.
Mori Summer-chan, stop arguing with him.
This is why we shouldn't leave anything up to this impostor, she'll just make it worse.
Deko-chan.
What are you doing here? You're going to make this harder.
Silence!
As a servant myself, I understand the pain of being betrayed by someone you entered a contract with.
Dekomori!
Guerzoniansus should be taught the value of the contract which binds him!
That's what I'm trying to do.
You should stay out of this!
Ow! What the hell are you doing?
Words alone cannot teach someone the value of a contract.
You need...
magical power!
Magical power?
Have you forgotten?
Ever since you showed Guerzoniansus the power within your Tyrant's Eye,
you two have been bound by an unbreakable contract!
That's true, which means...
What are you doing?
Yuuta, I'll force you to understand how I feel using the power of the Tyrant's Eye!
Reality, be rent!
Synapse, break!
Vanishment, this world!
Königin der Nacht!
Here I come!
Avalon Smasher!
Mjollnir Tornado!
I'm not playing along.
Master, we can't give up!
Apocalypse Hammer!
Giga Inferno!
Stop it already.
Your tenacity is admirable!
Dekomori!
Now it's come to this, let's combine our attacks!
Purgatorial Fascination!
Lunatic Mjollnir Crusher!
I told you I'm not playing along.
What incredible strength...
He saw through everything.
Of course I did.
How many times have we fought before?
Then why won't you fight back?
Here I thought Guerzoniansus had finally been true to himself recently!
Like hell I have!
Rikka, I have no intention of forgiving you until you properly apologize.
I've been too easy on you recently and it's showing.
You're so full of yourself!
Magical Oriental Napping Society of Summer
I'm not going to budge!
You shouldn't! That's the spirit!
Sorry to bother you like this.
I don't really mind.
Why is Mori Summer with you though?
She couldn't contain her curiosity.
Don't put words in my mouth.
I just can't leave them alone.
So where's Togashi-kun?
Looks like he's just getting back.
I'm home.
Onii-chan, you're back late today.
Were you good kitties today?
Onii-chan, this isn't the time for that!
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
This says she's not coming home, right?
I won't come home
until you apologize
Rikka
Don't worry about it.
She'll be back soon enough.
No need to make her dinner tonight either.
Wait, seriously?
Yuuta...
Are you sure about this?
I really think we should go look for her.
She'll be fine.
It's already late, let's get some sleep.
If you say so, good night.
He's really going all out with this.
He really seems angry this time.
This can't be real.
His girlfriend hasn't come home at this hour
and he isn't worried in the slightest!
Has the love really disappeared?!
Well, that's because she's always out and about at this hour.
Oh, really...
Even so, he's usually a little more concerned than this.
Yeah!
Guerzoniansus once traveled all the way to the great beyond for Master!
Guerzonaiansus's love burned that brightly!
Well, things can't stay that way forever.
Does that mean...
Yuuta no longer wants to be in a contract with me?
The lights turned on.
That looks like...
A midnight snack?
I imagine it's for you.
Yuuta...
What will you do now?
I'm not sure.
I don't want to fight with Yuuta, but...
I can't stand leaving things the way they are now.
Master...
That's why you said you weren't coming home and came here, right?
I think you should tell him that.
Kumin.
I mean, you two have been together for over a year now.
I'm sure he understands how you're feeling.
You understand each other's feelings,
so it's frustrating when you can't agree on something
and it makes you think the other's being selfish.
Kumin...
I bet he wants to talk to you, too.
Although talking might result in you fighting,
I think it'd be good for you.
Good for us?
Yeah, something really good.
So you were at Shichimiya's place?
Good for us?
Yeah, something really good.
A fight, huh?
The more you fight with someone, the closer you are.
I hope you're not thinking that we're friends or anything.
Of course I'm not.
I'd decline even if you wanted to be.
Who'd want to be friends with you?
You two really do get along well.
No way!
Yuuta!
No, Guerzoniansus.
I must speak with you.
What is it?
It's my fault I took something of yours without permission,
but you're also at fault for failing to honor your promise!
You're right.
It's my fault that I broke our promise,
but that doesn't excuse you taking my things!
I understand.
In that case,
let the battle begin!
After spending the entire night arguing,
this is how it all ends, huh?
Master...
Leave them be.
Yeah.
This is for the best right now.
Couples need their alone time.
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Kbi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
Chuunibyou demo
Koi ga Shitai! Ren
is over
mebuita yamiyo ga haran he to hakou
The night falls again, bringing with it conflict
wakuwaku suru nee
Isn't it exciting?
nanatsu no oto eigou yori hanatarete
The seven of the scales echo forth from the ends of eternity
dokidoki suru nee
Isn't it thrilling?
matsui no rakuin anshou ni hirameku
The mark of the Mighty Hammer glitters from the sunken depths
mada tsudzukeru ki na no
You still haven't gotten over it yet?
ai no setsuri ni kyokkou matataku
The Aurora flashes upon the Providence of Love
mou yamenasai
Cut it out already
bokura wa hitotsu ni nari
We converge and become one
ten wo kakete
Flying through the sky
hokori wo sakebi chiru
We scream proud and burst
hanabi no you da
Like a rocket
kagayaki wa setsuna ni hazeta
In an instant, the sparkling is rent away
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
gusha wa tsukikage ni kyomou wo idaku
The fool holds, of the moonlight, dark delusions
game ga bokura wo
If this game exists
oitsumeru tame ni aru naraba
only so we may lose all hope
semete kuchinu hodo no baka de aritai
Then may my foolishness never die so long as it goes on
reiki suru tamashi de hoeta
Charged with lightning, I screamed forth from my soul
Van!shment th!s world!!
Vanishment this world!