Let's talk about love!
Dekomori's Wife Under the Heated Table
But the only one in here with a boyfriend is Takanashi, so...
How is it going with Togashi?
T-The bond between the Wicked Eye and Dark Flame Master is unshakable.
Which means... normal...
So no trouble but no progress either, huh?
Are you going to talk about Master and Dark Flame Master until my death?
Well, what else are we supposed to do?
Or do you want to tell us there's someone you like?
A contractor?
For crying out loud: someone you like!
So someone worthy of forming a contract with me...
A servant with such a huge amount of dark power...
I can't think of one.
Listen to me!
She's not listening at all.
A contract can only be made with a compatible being.
To put it differently, to find one is difficult.
Yeah, actually finding one yourself is pretty difficult.
I do have a worthy woman!
You? You really have one?
What is she like?
First thing that comes to mind is her being huge.
Well, that's just because you're tiny.
I'm not tiny!
Any other personal data?
She's really strong.
A delinquent!?
Are you telling us she even surpasses the Dark Flame Master?!
I'm not sure about that.
Let's make them fight to death sometime.
I'll tell him.
That's not something you decide without those two being around.
And she's dark-skinned.
A sportsman?
But most importantly, she can breathe fire of death.
A street performer?
What?! That's amazing!
And there's more.
Hey, hold on for a second.
What the death is it?
Tell us her name.
It's Níðhöggr!
She's the black dragon of death who survived Ragnarök.
Just a lizard?!
She's not a lizard, she's the dragon of death!
Same difference!
Nibutani, you're wrong.
Lizards resemble salamanders.
Whereas dragons are a completely different species.
Salamanders are–
I don't care! I don't care!
What do you like about little Níðhöggr, Deko?
She has the highest attack power of all familiars I control.
I wish to always be with her.
What a waste of time to listen to you seriously.
I'll think of something too...
Don't worry, you have little Chimera!
Chimera! My dear familiar!
Just how stupid was I to expect her to behave like a normal girl?
Tune in again!