eighth grader syndrome
Are you familiar with the phrase "eighth-grader syndrome"?
8th grader syndrome
A decade ago it
bwas still considered
blahto be part of the rebellious
blahage of puberty...
A decade ago it
bwas still considered
blahto be part of the rebellious
blahage of puberty...
SAMPLE VIDEO
Children are most prone to it around the end of the eighth grade.
It's an adorable, yet dreadful disease
resulting from newfound self-awareness
mixing with an overly active imagination
that results in the peculiar behavior
we're all quite painfully familiar with.
Like the guy who only read weekly manga mags up until yesterday,
then suddenly starts reading the
original English versions of books.
Or someone who has absolutely no idea what coffee tastes like,
but still tries to develop a
taste for drinking it black.
And then there's those who believe that they possess special powers,
and become obsessed
with the occult overnight.
During his junior high days,
this boy was a textbook example of eighth-grader syndrome.
He named himself the Dark Flame
...Master, and his catchphrase was...
"Be engulfed by the flames of darkness, and begone!"
That's so, so, so, so embarrassing!
I wanna forget it! I wanna forget it!
Merely remembering this embarrassing condition
makes one want to disappear from the surface of the Earth.
Did you see?
No! Not at all!
Do you want to?
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Hey, Kuzuha!
What is it now?
What do you think?
You look normal.
Yeah! Normal, right?!
Yeah...
Hell yeah!
You're weird.
What's all this trash?
That's mine.
I'll throw it all out later, so don't worry.
Sure is a lot.
But you bought this one with the
...money you got from New Year's...
Can you just leave it alone?
I remember you declaring you would rule the world with this, though.
You remember wrong!
You did!
You used to wear that weird coat a lot back then too.
Shut up! If I can live without
remembering that, so can you!
Good morning!
Mom, it's Yuuta's entrance ceremony today.
Encounter With... the Wicked Eye
Remember?
Oh, right!
Don't worry about it.
Parents don't usually attend high school entrance ceremonies anyway.
Sorry!
I'm sorry.
Please, you first.
Thanks!
Judging from her uniform, she goes to the same high school as me.
It's her! That girl from yesterday!
It opened?!
For some reason I got on a later train!
I don't know anyone here.
Well, that's no surprise.
I intentionally chose a different high school to everyone else from my junior high.
The first impression is the most important!
Don't be over-conscious!
Just blend in smoothly!
I'm Togashi Yuuta.
I can never loose this cursed bandage from my arm, and for good reason.
Doing so would unleash the Black Flame Dragon on this world.
That memory pains my heart.
I've been on my own in that class ever since.
Whatever! Don't worry about the past!
No one here knows me from back then!
I am the Dark Flame Master!
Perish, enveloped by the flames of darkness!
Contained and sealed!
A
Togashi
This is mine?
Hey, hey.
Could you spare me some pencil lead?
Oh, sure.
Which junior high are you from?
Ishiyama.
That's quite far from here.
Yeah, there's no one else from my old school here.
Ah, thanks.
Yeah, I hardly know anyone too.
Nice to meet you, man.
I'm Isshiki Makoto.
I'm Togashi Yuuta.
Yeah, yeah! Just play it straight!
Hooray for my high school debut!
Say, how do you like the girls in this class?
The girls?
Nice collection of hotties, don't you think?
Pretty sweet, if you ask me.
I don't really know...
Oh, she's in my class?
Oh? Aiming high, aren't you? Nibutani, huh?
Nibutani?
Yeah. Nibutani Shinka.
She's easily in first place on my list.
Could this be fate?
I have finally found you.
My eye... My eye is reacting!
Friend of yours?
I don't know her!
I crossed the pits of Hell to meet you here!
Dude, she just confessed to you! I'm so jealous!
No, you're getting it all wrong!
She's... Yeah, I'm sure she's...
She's... She's got eighth-grader syndrome!
My eye... My eye!
My eye...
Me?
The bottom shelf... The bottom shelf...
Ah, this one?
The nurse had to go somewhere, so I was told to give you these eyedrops.
Hurry up or we'll be late for the opening ceremony.
You were the one on my balcony last night, right?
What do you want?
It reacted...
My eye.
Indeed, our paths once crossed,
measureless eons before this age.
The moment I saw you, my Wicked Eye revealed to me our destiny.
That's why I sought the chance to meet you once again.
This bitter taste...
Doubtlessly, this is the work
of the Cult of Darkness.
I must seal this away.
Do I need any more proof?
The Wicked Eye wields darkness
tamed by the power of a pure heart.
As it itself is defiled by darkness, it cannot endure anything pure, such as holy water.
Definitely eighth-grader syndrome.
She's a textbook case.
We almost fell victim to the enemy's schemes.
We must be more careful from now on,
Dark Flame Master.
Eh?
Be engulfed by the flames of darkness!
Stop!
How do you know that?!
Where did you hear about it?
My Wicked Eye is perfectly clairvoyant.
I know everything about level seven
warlocks and their powe—
Where did you hear about it?
The entirety of the future and the past is but an open book before—
Yuuta, that hurts!
I asked where you heard about it!
I can't see! Yuuta, I can't see!
It was at the gym earlier!
At the gym?
I thought no one was listening...
Not a word to anyone about this, got it?!
I know!
The principles of the Ethereal Horizon and the composition changes in—
Not that!
I'm talking about my past!
No "Dark Flame Master"!
No "wielder of the flames of darkness"!
Why? That's so cool.
It's not!
Listen! I decided to leave all that behind me!
Every single tiny little bit of it!
Really?
Yeah.
So you're now a level eight warlock?!
No!
I'm talking about eighth-grader syndrome!
I'm not the Dark Flame Master or any kind of warlock!
I'm just a normal high school freshman!
Could you look less shocked?
Let me tell you a secret: you're an
average high school freshman too!
I have my Wicked Eye.
No one asked about that.
Not that it even exists in the first place.
It exists.
It does not.
Want to see it then?
Do you want to see my eye?
Could it... No way. That's impossible.
Yeah, show me!
N-No way...
You've gotta be kidding me!
D-Don't come any closer!
Just a moment. I'll put it back in.
It's just a colored contact?!
Oh no... I can feel it... inside me...
Stop saying weird things.
An afterimage...
You listening?
I'll tell you one more time: I left that crap behind me.
So don't come anywhere near me!
And shut up about the past!
But you've seen my eye.
The contract between us is complete.
We share the heart of darkness. We are spiritual soulmates.
That's so deep.
I'm going on ahead. You should hurry too.
And now for the freshman address.
Freshman representative, Nibutani Shinka.
Yes!
If that weirdo latched onto me like that,
there must still be something off about me.
This beautiful spring day with all the cherry trees in full blossom
is the day we join the community of this school.
Representing all freshmen, I would like to give words of gratitude for this grand ceremony.
She's the freshman representative?
Now that we're done with the
introductions, let's call it a day.
Health
Checkups
Formal
Address
Please be sure to check your schedule when you get home.
Hey, Togashi!
Got some time after this?
A few of us were talking about going for lunch together.
You're... inviting me?!
Yeah.
But is that really okay?
Why wouldn't it be?
Ah, is it Takanashi?
Takanashi?
The girl you took to the nurse's earlier.
Did you promise her you'd walk home together?
I didn't!
I want nothing to do with her! Nothing at all!
Oh? You don't swing that way?
It's not that!
I just don't want weird rumors to spread.
Really?
Isshiki, you coming?
Yeah, I'm coming!
Let's go!
Okay.
Togashi!
Come here for a sec.
She's lost her wallet.
She just moved here, so she doesn't know the town.
Could you walk her home?
Why me?
It looks like you live very close to each other.
Look!
You live on the floor above me?
I get it now.
Thank you!
I'm really sorry! I'll come next time for sure!
Yeah. Later.
So when did you move in?
I thought the only person up there was some office lady living on her own.
I changed residences the day before yesterday.
Takanashi Tooka is my sister.
I see.
So you moved in with your sister.
Or rather, that's what we lead others to believe.
But she's actually a powerful sorceress who oversees the Ethereal Horizon.
An enemy.
Oh, please.
When she awakens her powers, I'm no match for her.
Even if I use my Wicked Eye.
She's scary!
How scary can she be?
Fear not, Rikka! Victory is ours!
I'm not surprised she gets mad at you with all the nonsense you keep going on about.
Help me, Yuuta.
With the power of the Dark Flame Master,
we could break through the Overseers' barrier and find the Ethereal Horizon!
Forget that name!
I've come up with a new attack for you!
Judgment Lucifer!
How was it?
You're wearing roller shoes? What are you, five?
They have superior mobility.
And if I'm wearing these and the enemy attacks...
I broke a few of my ribs... But it works!
And it's cool!
Stop it! We're in public!
Which would you like? My treat.
Wait.
Up! Up! Down! Down!
Hey, Takanashi...
Left! Right! Left! Right!
The train...
Okay! Insert the coin now!
Huh?
And now B, A!
What do you mean, "B, A"?
A mana potion.
The Overseers have surreptitiously stashed them in various places.
The train already left, dammit!
Free drink!
You win! Yay!
Do you accept my powers now?
Nah. You looked pretty surprised too.
Beetle Movers
By the way, B and A stand for banana and apple.
It differs by the season, so be careful.
Yeah, whatever.
We finally made it.
Could you stop wasting my time?
Yuuta!
Come and see this!
They meant to deliver these to Ms. Takanashi,
but she wasn't at home, so they
asked me to take care of it for her.
And they call themselves movers?
Are these all yours?
I returned home late due to the Overseers' interference.
I should've been home by three according to pl—
Yuuta, who is she?
Ms. Takanashi's little sister.
They'll be living together.
I see...
Why do you have so much stuff?
It's way too much for one person.
They are all precious treasures.
Don't tell me it's all junk like that!
I'll go and get dinner ready.
There are many useful items here.
Oh, it's spring-loaded.
It can be used as a weapon...
Gungnir!
And for defense...
Schwarzschild!
All right! I get it!
Here.
Take your stuff with you.
Understood.
That's the last one.
Thanks. I appreciate your help.
As you should.
Where's your sister?
She's always late.
Ah, another Takanashi?
You're just as pretty as your sister!
Good luck, Yuuta!
What for?
Umm, what happened to your eye?
Don't worry about it.
There's nothing wrong with it or anything.
The Wicked Eye harnesses darkness using sacred powe—
Spare us the backstory, please.
Very well.
Perish!
Yumeha, don't take that out around h— Ow!
It's so cool!
Is not!
If you slung that over your back, it'd be perfect!
Perfect?
Yuuta used to do that.
He wore a black coat, had that sword on his back...
Kuzuha!
He certainly had some strange ideas back then.
Always chanting spells or whatever those were before meals.
Mom, isn't it time you left for your night shift?
Yessir...
Oh, jeez.
I told them it was trash, and they just go rummaging through it anyway...
Trash?
Yeah.
That's the life of the Dark Flame Master.
Like I said, I left that all behind me.
Why?
It's embarrassing.
It's cool.
It's not. Not even slightly.
That stuff's all totally pointless.
There's no such thing as the Flames of
Darkness or the power of the Dark Dragon.
It's all so stupid.
No. The power is real.
It isn't.
It is.
Come on—
So please,
don't throw it away.
Be engulfed by the flames of darkness, and begone!
Don't get me wrong.
I just thought they'd be too valuable to just throw away.
I'll make some money by putting them up for auction instead.
Okay.
Let's go inside.
You'll catch a cold if you stand out here too long.
Okay.
Though I said that,
spring was actually quite warm this year.
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?