Hot Pot Discussion under the Heated Table
I want to eat hot pot.
Sounds good.
I'd like one with meat.
I like how light the ones with chicken taste.
Dark hot pot here.
You really want to eat one?
Shall I cook one for you?
A being of light cooking it would cleanse it of the darkness element.
And light hot pot is nothing but poison for us who dwell in the darkness.
The whole point of dark hot pot is serving stuff that's not edible at all.
But it's the coolest one.
You just chose it because of the name anyway, didn't you?
What sort of hot pot do you like, Deko?
Me?
Let me think...
I love those with pufferfish or crabs to death.
Those with groupers are nice too.
Those with marbled beef aren't too bad either.
That being said, I prefer medium steaks to a hot pot with meat.
This damn bourgeoise...
Dekomori, I believe it is a master's duty to know about the current life of her servants.
The Wicked Eye is telling me that next time we should gather at your house to hold a day of hot pot.
Trying to profit, huh?
Oh well, can't blame you for wanting to eat those.
They sure sounds delicious.
No problem.
You're all welcome until death.
Are you sure?
Keep our count in mind.
We received another bunch of snow crabs just yesterday which should be enough for us all.
Snow crabs...
Their claws will become my dual swords!
Do that in front of Togashi or me and you'll get in trouble.
I'm really thankful for those but I'd prefer if they kept in mind what variety means.
What do you mean?
Eating crabs everyday is tiring me to death.
She really is irritating me...
Oh right, I'd feel bad for just eating so I'll treat you to a hot pot of mine.
You, Fake Summer?
You're not going to put in crab sticks and call it "crab hot pot" or something, are you?
That's only for fakes like you.
Why would I?
It'll be a hot pot I'm sure you're going to love.
What kind of hot pot?
It'll be something called "cheese fondue!"
Just die to death!
So cheese fondue?
That sounds delicious as well.
I should've never tried to listen to your sweet talk of death.
Are you that stupid to put ingredients into a hot pot poisoned with rotten milk?!
Are you?!
Oh my, no need to be that grateful.
Don't worry, I'll make sure to fill the hot pot from top to bottom.
Just brew your poisoned hot pots forever like a witch is supposed to!
Tune in again!