Today, we will be be summoning objects from our dimension one after another.
I wish to regain my previously lost honor.
Gulp...
You're talking about All Times All Places, aren't you, Master?
All Times All Places on the Beach
How did you get what that was about again?
And we did something similar just a while ago: the word chain game.
Somebody of the light element kept using sneaky tactics.
That didn't count.
Didn't I tell you they were all correct answers back then?!
Seems like she didn't take losing that often very well.
The Wicked Eye got overpowered for once...
But as long as light exists in this world, the darkness won't bend to death!
Well said, Dekomori.
That sounded cool!
Just leave such matters to me, Master!
All right...
So, what's the topic?
"Cool things of darkness."
All Times All Places, yay!
Hold on.
Don't "yay" me yet.
What is it?
What's with that stupid topic?
There are plenty of others to chose from.
Like spell names?
Now listen...
Then you'll just say whatever you want to.
Something with a smaller scope of words.
Stop being so selfish, Nibutani.
It's as clear as death.
You're the incarnation of selfishness.
Well, let's try playing it anyway, Forest Summer.
Don't call me that!
And sure.
But the topic has to be something normal that we both can take part in too.
No other choice then...
Affirmative.
All Times All Places, yay!
Fruit names, yay!
Come on...
What about "tangerine" or "apple?"
No way, those aren't cool!
You don't even know yourself what those
"fruits with cool names" are supposed to be.
How is losing now going to help you?
Durian.
And you think that one's cool?
Cool fruits, huh?
Sounds difficult...
What'd be a good fit?
What about star fruits?
If you cut them open, there's a star shape inside.
Now that does sound cool!
Will eating them make me invincible?
No, it certainly won't.
What else...
Dragon fruits and miracle fruits are as cool as death as well!
Those are also cool!
They're fruits of the underworld without a doubt!
You're never going to win at this rate.
Tune in again!