Staff Room
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
The Cram Time... of Crucifixion
Cast the spell of 9×7!
Cast the spell of 9×8!
Evil Clown
Revised
edition
Mathematics I
Staff Room
Revised Edition
Mathematics I
Email address
Address book
Takanashi Rikka
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Tooka
Yumeha
Yumeha and Tooka
have divorced.
Black Power
Japanese
Mathematics I
Social
Studies
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Mathematics I
Spring term final exam
Togashi Yuuta
Incoming mail
Sub
Engrave it upon your soul
Incoming mail
Togashi Yuuta
Sub
Engrave it upon your soul
Thanks
To be continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?