Yuuta...
Yuuta.
Wha—
Wh-What are you doing?!
Hey...
Contract.
Yuuta, let's form a contract.
Yes, I know very well that
this has to be a dream.
But that would mean that,
subconsciously, I want this to happen!
In other words...
Ow...
I knew it.
May I ask what you're doing?
Producing a zero-g field using
the power of the Tyrant's Eye.
The gravity in this room is under my—
Y-Yuuta! Are you okay?
What on Earth is going on?!
We've got an emergency!
Yu—
You little...
Em... Emer...
Enough is enough!
Yuuta, that hurts!
I wanna fallin' love
yokan yume ga tsudzuku
The dream will go on and on
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
We made a promise, but deep inside,
I'm still scared it might all disappear
yakusoku shitemo kokoro ga dokoka de obieteru mitai
hitori ja nai tte shinjitai no ni
Even though I want to believe you'll always be there
omoitsudzuketeru dake de shiawase nante ienai ne
Being in love with each other isn't happiness all by itself
utsuro na jishin seotteitemo
Even if I pretend that it's all that matters
kimi ga warau
You just laugh
soshite watashi no yuuki ni naru
And you always give me strength
l
hitotsu no kotoba de kimi no sekai wo kaeraretara
But if one simple word can change your whole world
But if one simple word can change your whole world
l
futatsu no koi ga shinka suru
Then two loves will start to progress
Then two loves will start to progress
l
hontou da yo
That's the truth
That's the truth
l
meguraseta mayoi ga mitsuketa kotae wa
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
Every time I got lost and asked myself what I should do
itsudemo kimi ni michibikareta
You always led me to the answer
Even if I can't work up the courage to do it
l
sunao ni tsutaetai
I want to tell you everything
I want to tell you everything
l
ko
ro
aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
kokoro aru ga mama koe ga kirameku
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
kokoro
All that my heart feels, with a sparkling voice
l
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real
come
on
voice
Let it out, and let it ring loud
real come on voice hibikiwataru yo
With my mobility reduced, I won't be able to evade their attacks.
The Magical Devil Girl... Strikes
My very life is at risk.
No roller shoes for you for a while.
Your punishment for drilling holes in my ceiling.
That can't be right!
I received permission from the Council!
What council?
No... Is this all part of their devious plan?!
I must make haste! The world is in danger!
It's like her eighth-grade
syndrome's gotten worse...
Or should I say it's back
with a vengeance?
We need only to construct
our own unique relationship!
Maybe I shouldn't have said that.
Then...
Yuuta.
No, no, no!
Not that, not that, not that!
Rikka and I aren't like that!
We aren't, and that's why I said—
Mobility test complete.
Was that even necessary?!
What now?
Tyrant Hero Motive Blast!
It worked!
No, it didn't.
And what? We're enemies now?
No.
Huh?
I am rousing the Dark Flame Dragon inside you from its slumber.
Dark Flame Dragon?
Yes.
The Dark Flame Dragon came to be when the
Black Flame Dragon obtained the powers of darkness.
It is the source of your power,
and together you share the same soul.
So why do we need it now?
An enemy draws near.
I believe her to be a powerful magician.
Magician?
Wait, you mean Touka-san?
No.
The Priestess has been banished to
the Vatican by my powers of darkness.
Careful with your words.
This magician's strength
eclipses even the Priestess's.
She may be among the strongest in Hell.
Thus...
We must summon forth the Dark Flame Dragon.
Hey, that's my shirt!
I have channeled my mana into it.
In the name of the Tyrant's Eye, I command thee!
O, Dark Flame Dragon which sleeps within Yuuta,
appear now before us—
Cut it out!
Why'd you go and draw a pentagram on it?
Damn. It looks kind of cool.
Yuuta!
Equip it!
Not a chance!
Well, maybe I shouldn't say that.
I mean, you did make it for me.
Really?!
But I don't want to wear it just like that.
Okay, how's this?
If you score higher than me
on the next test, I'll wear it.
If you don't, the Dark Flame Dragon will be sealed away forever.
Did you just suck your teeth at me?!
Damn...
I let my guard down.
How foolish of you, Dark Flame Master.
Behold the power of the Tyrant's Eye
and burn it into your soul!
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
It's just three points!
Silence!
You are now the servant of the servant!
You're so cool, Master!
I've fallen for you all over again!
Good job, Rikka-chan!
Naturally!
Now present the Dark Flame Dragon which sleeps within ye to Master!
Who are you trying to be now?
And so, you will wear this.
What is that?
Obviously, a magical girl outfit.
What happened to the T-shirt?!
Stop being so nitpicky.
Why is it a magical girl outfit now?!
The Dark Flame Dragon has
a strong affinity for mana.
We shall draw it out by enveloping your entire body with mana.
I designed it to suit you.
Dekomori and I made it, nice and new.
It's a masterpiece, that's true!
Ease your heart.
I have measured your three sizes
with the Tyrant's Eye.
But I'm a guy.
Unfortunately, there were no
examples of male magical girls,
so its design was fraught with difficulties.
As such, I've also prepared this.
Twin tails?!
Also, your transformation phrase
is "Yuuta, brave up"—
No way!
Now, transform! On the double!
Yuuta.
Kumin-senpai!
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Togashi Yuuta
Name
Takanashi Rikka
Okay, fine!
You won, I lost!
Why are you stripping?!
Transform!
Like I can do that!
Why did I agree to this?
Let's see...
Hey, I look pretty cute...
As if.
Hey, everyone!
Wish along with me!
Magical—
Wow, what a perfect parabola!
Yeah...
but you didn't have to throw it, you jerk!
Whoa! Nibutani savaging up
a crossdressing Togashi—
Kiss your memories goodbye!
Outta the way.
Ooh, you have completed
your transformation!
You look very pretty. I am glad.
And I am not.
Yuuta! Recite a spell!
I will not.
You look so cute, Togashi-kun!
Not you too, Kumin-senpai?!
Deko-chan said she made this
as a sample, so I wore it.
Want to try this one on too?
No, thank you!
Oriental Magick Napping
Society in Summer
Angel!
I am here for battle!
Come out, you—
It seems I am being summoned.
How'd you come to that conclusion?
Because I am an angel.
Specifically, a fallen angel of darkness.
So I was serving a fallen angel all along?
I like this revelation!
It's so cool!
We depart for battle.
Be on your guard, Yuuta.
Behold our angelicosity!
Tyrant's Eye radar mode, activate!
They are near the PA booth!
How are they angelic at all?
Wait, that voice...
PA Booth
I shall search this way!
Very well.
Spatial Rift!
Should be around here.
Who are you?!
So you were the Angel.
Are you a remnant? Or are you new?
Well, doesn't matter.
I am Sophia Ring S. P. Saturn VII.
You may know me as the Magical Devil Girl, Sophia-chan. I'm quite famous around here.
They also call me "The Devil, the Girl Who Rules Over Seven Magical Sacred Lands"!
Remember that, 'kay?
I am the Tyrant's Eye.
The Fallen Angel of Darkness, Takanashi Rikka!
The Tyrant's Eye?
A worthy opponent, I dare say.
Now, shall we begin our battle?
My pleasure.
Tyrant's Eye, activate!
Opening field!
Devil Magic Confinement Ring!
Acknowledged: The Devil.
Releasing magic lock.
Reality, be rent.
Sing, cherubim.
Synapse, break!
Descend, seraphim!
Vanishment, this world!
Physical linkage!
You unleashed quite the ability there, and we've only just begun.
You're as powerful an Angel as I thought.
I sense something ominous from you.
So I will destroy you!
Rift! Gates of the Abyss!
Open now and unleash thy darkness!
Shatter the illusion before thee by
the power of the Lord of Extinction,
A final summoning already?!
and guide it to its ultimate fate!
Schwarz Aschenputtel!
Vulcanus Shield!
Through a makeshift shield, yes,
but more damage than predicted.
I should have expected as much from the Fallen Angel of the Tyrant's Eye.
Looks like Sophia-chan
will have to do her best!
Your efforts are futile.
Unfortunately for you,
I'm the Magical Devil Girl,
so I'm not quite your
typical, cute magical girl.
One thousand phoenixes.
How many of them can you dodge?
Shield, full power!
Dark Phoenix Flash!
You underestimated me.
A marionette?!
Infinity System, online!
O, Flames of Crimson.
Burn black and be transformed into the Dark Flame!
An incantation?!
Inter my enemy in the Abyssal Darkness!
Black Flame Cannon!
Nullification Shield!
Shichimiya.
Hey, Shichimiya!
Oh, if it isn't the Hero!
What?
You know better than that.
You aren't a student here, so
you can't just walk in like that.
Sorry.
Allow me to explain.
Shichimiya Satone and I attended the same middle school for our first year.
What's more, she was the reason why I contracted eighth-grade syndrome!
Togashi
I found Shichimiya's speech and constant "fighting" super cool,
so I copied her.
Both "Dark Flame Master" and
"Be engulfed by the Dark Flame and begone!"
were taken from Shichimiya, by the way.
Wow! Is this your base, Hero?
Yuuta, she's dangerous!
Get away from her!
Still haven't given up, Fallen Angel of Darkness?
It seems Shichimiya decided
that Rikka was an angel,
You will regret ever picking
a fight with Sophia-chan!
figured out her school from her uniform, and came to meet her properly.
You shall witness the power
of the Magical Devil Girl!
I will take you on anytime, anywhere!
Who knew she'd still have a case of that?
You haven't won yet!
I shall defeat you next time!
Quit it.
Sorry, but I'll be going home now.
Nana-chan told me to see Shichimiya home.
Let us share a cup of afterlife wine,
arms linked, to celebrate our reunion!
Too close!
Yeah, yeah. But juice.
See you.
You seriously haven't changed one bit.
So the Agency is still searching for us here.
You'd best be careful.
Here.
Let us drink!
To be perfectly clear, I graduated
from that along with middle school.
Graduated?
Yeah.
So you're not a level 7,
but a level 8 hero now?!
No!
I quit all of that stuff!
The Dark Flame and
Dark Flame Master and all that!
I get the feeling I've said all this before...
Hero, is it because you
looked into the Angel's eye?
No!
I'm not a hero or anything anymore!
I'm a normal second-year high schooler!
You are?
Yeah.
Heck, it's been three years
since anyone's called me "Hero."
I see.
Well, that's stupid.
Stupid? What's stupid?
It's stupid, so it's stupid!
Just look! There's a whole world out there!
What the heck?
Now let's get you home.
Which way is it?
Well...
Take this train?
Yeah.
Get off here?
Cross this bridge?
Yeah!
And we're here?
Wait...
Shichimiya
This is the apartment above mine!
Oh, so the Togashi downstairs is you, Hero?
Stop calling me that.
And might you be living with the Tyrant's Eye?
How'd you know that?!
O, Flames of Crimson.
Burn black and be transformed into the Dark Flame.
Inter my enemy in the Abyssal Darkness!
Black Flame Cannon!
Tyrant's Eye ultimate spell:
Purgatorial Fascination!
Um... What do I do now?
Purgatorial Fascination is one of the
Tyrant's Eye's eight ultimate techniques.
It's the most powerful attack.
Because you are a magical girl by virtue
of attire alone, you have no defense against it.
O-Okay.
Then...
Master, you're amazing!
No, she's not.
Honestly, "magical girl"
isn't even remotely close.
More like "battle girl," I'd say.
Wh-What now?
And anyway, magic is for making people happy.
The faeries, who govern all magic,
possess hearts of incorruptible purity!
So don't just rely on brute force—
Gotta write this down...
Mori Summer-chan sure knows a lot!
This will be useful against the enemy.
Better write it down!
No, don't do that!
But why a magical girl?
That is a secret society's base.
Ooh! What a big factory!
How suspicious! How suspicious!
Shichimiya?
Yeah.
Shichimiya... Shichimiya...
Where have I heard that before?
She's an old friend of Togashi-kun's, apparently.
She suddenly challenged Rikka to a fight.
An old friend...
Maybe she's his ex-girlfriend?!
I don't think so.
No, it's totally suspicious.
She goes to a different school, but sneaks
into ours and goes home with Togashi-kun.
Something's definitely going to happen!
What do you mean?
A love triangle! A bloodbath!
You really like imagining those things, Mori Summer-chan.
N-No, not really.
And don't call me that!
I don't know what's going to happen,
but I don't think it'll be like that.
I swear upon the Tyrant's Eye!
I shall not yield to the Devil!
Death!
Satone-chan?
Who are you?!
It's Kuzuha. Don't tell me
you've forgotten her.
Oh, Kuzuha!
Kuzuha!
Wow, you've grown so much!
It's been three years.
You haven't changed very much, though.
Just, wow!
You'll grow up as big as a demonic anarthrous worm at this rate!
"Anarthrous"?
Yuuta!
Reporting back to base!
Requesting rations im—
To think you would infiltrate our base so easily!
Did you think such a
flimsy barrier could stop me?
Don't you underestimate Sophia-chan's magic!
Quit it.
Why only me?
Rikka, put your bag in your room.
Shichimiya's parents will be working late,
so she'll be eating dinner with us.
You don't mind, right?
If you do, we can decide who's the
stronger magical girl here and now!
She doesn't. Now cut it out.
That hurt, Hero.
Jeez. You never change.
You stuck to Onii-chan like glue back then, Satone-chan.
I needed the Hero's power
to find the Samsaric Circuit.
But I never imagined I'd find his base here.
So you didn't know where I lived?
You said, "Never may a soul know its whereabouts, be they friend or foe."
I tailed you every day,
but you always shook me off.
Oh right, I remember that.
Onii-chan warned me
every morning before I left.
Something like, "Use your utmost caution to ensure you are not followed."
So why is the Tyrant's Eye staying here?
I have no obligation to tell an enemy.
Look here...
Rikka-chan used to live in
the apartment above ours,
but she lost it because of a little mishap.
What?
So you wander this world
without a base of your own?
That's so cool!
O-Only natural for one of the darkness.
In fact, I spend most of
my time outside this world.
I reside within this space solely
because of my contract with Yuuta.
It is but temporary.
Big talk for a freeloader.
Contract?
A contract by the Tyrant's Eye.
Formed only after aeons
of searching this sphere.
Really?
Well, I dunno if you can call it a contract...
They're dating.
K-Kuzuha!
I-It is a contract!
I-It is not what the lowly masses call "dating"!
Yeah!
Kuzuha, you're way out of—
That's awesome, Hero!
Too close, I said!
You've found a partner for your journeys!
And it's the strongest, the Tyrant's Eye!
Yes, I know.
I know, so get off me.
Tyrant's Eye!
Wh-What?
What do you and the Hero seek?
What is your objective?
Our original objective was to uncover the Unseen Horizon.
But this was accomplished
by our powers combined.
And so, we now seek to awaken the
Dark Flame Dragon which sleeps within Yuuta.
Dark Flame Dragon?
Though I've got no reason to awaken it.
Yes, you do.
Your spirit soul begs for it.
Look...
The Dark Flame Dragon, huh?
I see.
You have my support, Tyrant's Eye.
Hero, I'm going home now.
Huh? Already?
Yeah.
Sophia needs to prepare for
her battles against the Angels.
What the heck?
Hero.
Wait! Shichimiya!
Hey! Hold up!
Dinner was great. Thanks.
Thank Kuzuha for me too.
Look...
We're in high school now,
so don't do that anymore.
Why not? We used to
nuzzle noses all the time.
Just don't, okay?
See you.
That's right.
Huh?
You never said "bye" or "see you."
Yeah.
You transferred away and disappeared,
without saying a word about it to me.
Because that would mean we'd have to part.
The moment you say a word of parting,
you've already parted.
That's how it is?
So long as you and I are both somewhere in this world, we haven't parted.
So long as you don't say it, you haven't parted.
That is the way of the world:
The Law of Linkage.
You never change.
I won't change for all eternity!
And that was how I reunited
with Shichimiya Satone.
It was just an old habit of hers.
It's like saying "hello" for her.
With her nose?
Yeah, with her nose.
Okay, fine.
We'll form another contract here.
I won't get close to any girls other than you.
Really?
Yeah.
And so, despite my uneasy feeling that
new troubles awaited us in the near future,
I let myself bask in the joy of growing just a tiny step closer to Rikka.
To Be Continued
mebuita yamiyo ga haran he to hakou
The night falls again, bringing with it conflict
wakuwaku suru nee
Isn't it exciting?
nanatsu no oto eigou yori hanatarete
The seven of the scales echo forth from the ends of eternity
dokidoki suru nee
Isn't it thrilling?
matsui no rakuin anshou ni hirameku
The mark of the Mighty Hammer glitters from the sunken depths
mada tsudzukeru ki na no
You still haven't gotten over it yet?
ai no setsuri ni kyokkou matataku
The Aurora flashes upon the Providence of Love
mou yamenasai
Cut it out already
bokura wa hitotsu ni nari
We converge and become one
ten wo kakete
Flying through the sky
hokori wo sakebi chiru
We scream proud and burst
hanabi no you da
Like a rocket
kagayaki wa setsuna ni hazeta
In an instant, the sparkling is rent away
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
douke wa seigi no tategami wo hashirasete
The pierrot rides upon the mane of justice
gusha wa tsukikage ni kyomou wo idaku
The fool holds, of the moonlight, dark delusions
game ga bokura wo
If this game exists
oitsumeru tame ni aru naraba
only so we may lose all hope
semete kuchinu hodo no baka de aritai
Then may my foolishness never die so long as it goes on
reiki suru tamashi de hoeta
Charged with lightning, I screamed forth from my soul
Van!shment th!s world!!
Vanishment this world!