It's so hot...
Yeah.
Morning!
Good morning!
What are you staring at?
What's with those clothes, anyway? Is she some pop star from the '70s?
You're being stupid.
Unlike you, Kumin's a pure, straightforward person untainted by this day and age!
Big words for a grade schooler.
Don't call me that!
Oh, Isshiki! You sort of look like a grade schooler.
The bursts of sunlight and gamma rays are threatening me with death!
Dark Limited Unknown Shield, equip! Yeah!
Her eighth-grader syndrome is more like second-grader syndrome now.
Did you say something, Fake Summer?!
Huh? I didn't say a word!
Oh, really?
It sure sounded like you lumped me together with that crew-cut kid!
Who're you calling "crew-cut kid"?!
The grade schoolers have two options: silence or death!
Come with Rikka on our summer vacation.
I need you.
Hear that, Fake Summer?!
Summer's here.
You wanna fight? I won't hold back!
Punish her!
Summer vacation's here.
Good luck!
Let's look for a
sparkling daydream...
shibaraku mitsumeatte kara
We looked into each other's eyes for a while
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no?
What did you think of while it lasted?
ki ni naru
I want to know that
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
Look at me as I now pout my lips
dou shita no tte kiite kuru no?
Will you ask me what's wrong?
matte miru no
I'm waiting
gomakashita haato no hitorigoto wa
I'm embarrassed by what I mutter after
hazukashii kara kikanaide kureru?
being so evasive, so please don't pay it any attention
ato ni hikenai hodo hikareau koi
Our love is so strong we can't run away
mou hajimatteta
It's already begun
yume nara takusan mita
I've dreamed of our meeting so often
sameta mama
Now I'm awake
demo mada aitai
And still I want to see you
kimi ga sou saseta
You did this to me
koi ga
yokubari da ne
Love is greedy
koi ga yokubari da ne
tobihanesou na kokoro no
My heart seems to hop with glee
yuku mama ni yukou yo
So I'll let it guide me
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
My ideals, delusions, and reality
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
Are all about you
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
A
atarashii sekai he
Changing into a new world
Motion sickness? Seriously?
Paradise Lost... of Memories
Told you she's like a grade schooler.
Shut up!
Just look out the window!
Watch the trees in the distance!
Shut up!
At times like this I must summon the wisdom of the Mabinogion
to purge myself of this malady!
"The soul is th—"
That'll make it worse!
Nibutani, there's a restroom that way. Could you?
Why me?!
I think a guy going there with a girl would raise a few eyebrows.
I'd sooner face death than accept help from a fake!
Oh, geez...
D-Don't touch me!
Hang in there. We don't have long to go.
Aided by my enemy in my
greatest moment of distress.
This could be deathly cool.
Don't talk.
Isshiki, you help too!
Isshiki?
A mole!
It's obvious as hell where you're looking.
Come along.
Okay.
Just a little longer.
Hey.
Rikka.
What?
Aren't you gonna react in some way?!
Or have you got motion sickness too?
I'm fine.
I have trained myself well.
Then why are you so quiet?
I'm worried too.
You're awake?
Did something happen, Rikka?
Not that I know of...
The world is spinning like a carousel of death!
Mjolnir Tornado...
I told you to shut up!
Geez.
Why do I have to take care of her?
You make a good class rep.
You're good at taking care of others.
Doesn't mean I like it!
This is all 'cos you had to barf all over us!
By the way, is she all right?
Takanashi did invite us.
"I'm going home. Want to come along to hang out?"
No one invited you, though.
Maybe there's something here for her.
How do you mean?
You know, the usual kind of thing!
Maybe her sweetheart from junior high went to a different high school,
but they waited for each other in a kind of long-distance relationship...
In other words, a battlefield of love?
Battlefield of Love is a powerful barrier spell...
Nobody asked you!
Love, huh?
My Wicked Eye...
is yours.
No way.
Look!
Who's that?
Tooka. Rikka's sister.
What's going on?
It's such a big house!
Takanashi, you're rich?
Thank you for coming all this way.
Oh, no!
Takanashi always does so much for us,
and now you've even invited us into your home.
I'm still worried that we're imposing on you.
Not at all.
So, Rikka's still pretending to be a pirate?
The things kids do these days.
I hoped she'd have grown up a little...
Dear!
Grandmother,
let's give them the Dark Brown Liquid!
Rikka!
Hey, Rikka!
Please accept this small token of our appreciation.
Thank you for having us.
Ah, please, don't worry about it.
Just enjoy your stay.
Thank you very much.
Wow, you're polite. Like an old lady.
Shut up!
What's that?!
A canine familiar?!
Deathly good! Send her to her death!
Come in.
You don't have much stuff here.
What's that?
I'm engaged in communications with
the other side of the Ethereal Horizon.
Where did you find that? It's quite unusual.
I found it last year.
I attempted to move it to my current base,
but the Priestess denied me permission.
No surprise there.
What's wrong?
With?
Oh, well. Let me say it in your language.
I sense an unusual aura around here. What is it?
This isn't a real base of mine either.
I used it only because of the Overseers.
Two years ago...
I was brought here.
Two years ago?
A lone house where nothing ever happens.
However, there's a barrier here that negates the existence of the Ethereal Horizon.
Mental assaults and pressure were extensive.
That's why I ran away.
I don't really get it, but does that mean something happened?
To break down this barrier, I needed...
the power of the Wicked Eye.
Are you in there?
Yes.
Are you going this year?
I'll leave your luggage here.
Also, your friends are going to the beach.
Please don't make them worry.
That's quite the bikini, Forest Summer!
Seriously? Even your swimsuit is white?
This was the only one I had, so I thought I'd give it a try.
It's perfect!
Thanks.
You're annoying!
My eyes! Seawater's blinding me!
There's a monstrous kraken in this sea!
We should test the power of our marine
magical gear by bringing its death upon it!
Watch closely!
With that equipment, you get a 3.88 movement speed multiplier until you reach the water.
You can move 3.88 times faster.
What's wrong? Go on in!
I'll remember this!
She really is fast!
We should go swimming too!
Kumin!
She's asleep!
You haven't talked much, ha—
What?
Sic 'em, Cerberus!
Why are you listening to her?!
I won't forget this!
Yuuta!
Hey, why are you following me around? Stop it!
Hey! Hey!
Point
What's this supposed to mean?
Yuuta, hurry!
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
On
anti-crime
patrol
What's that?
Rad Zwei Hellblau.
I couldn't care less about its name.
It's time we traveled to the Ethereal Horizon's cluster point.
Get on.
Dressed like this?
This camouflage is necessary to escape the Priestess's watchful eyes.
I knew it.
Hey!
So it comes down to this?
Togashi Yuuta!
Yes?
Go with her.
Where to?
To her father.
My whole body aches like death!
That sacred light got the better of me!
That's because you went running around all day
without even putting any sunscreen on.
But at least my Black Seal is now complete!
Whoa, lame.
They said we should eat this together.
What's that?
Perfect, isn't it?
Fake Summer
It sure is.
Takanashi
family
It was exactly three years ago.
Rikka was so little that
Dad didn't want to tell her.
So for her, he passed away suddenly and without warning.
It's probably because of that that she still doesn't even try to accept his death.
She stubbornly refuses to come here.
Come on, Mommy!
And your mother?
She left us with Dad's family.
Grandpa's a really serious man,
so he couldn't accept Rikka no matter what.
I had to leave because of my work as well,
so for the past two years, nothing's changed.
I must find the Ethereal Horizon. No matter what.
To overcome this barrier, I needed
the power of the Wicked Eye.
Amazing!
You made all this, Tooka?
It's what I do for a living, after all.
Now that you mention it, Takanashi's boxed lunches always look delicious!
Yeah! They've been the talk of our class!
You work in such a great restaurant! I'm jealous of Rikka!
Really?
I can't wait!
Let's eat!
Let's!
This has cheese, deathn't it?!
You hate cheese too?
Who could eat that stuff?
It stinks like dirty rags!
It's made of milk! Rotten milk!
How could it be any worse?!
Eat it.
M-Milk...
Yessir...
You're a hero, Deko!
I should've expected this from the Priestess even my Master fears!
Her powers of commandment are amazing!
That reminds me, where's Rikka?
I'll go take a look for her.
Is she not well?
Uh, well...
Are you there?
What's the password?
The Wicked Eye is the strongest.
Wrong.
Wrong?!
It seems you have suffered the Priestess's mental assaults.
You aren't yourself anymore.
So that's what you feared?
Well, rest at ease. I'm still the former Dark Flame Master, you know.
Are you okay with this? I thought you
wanted to look for the Ethereal Horizon.
Really?
Why would I lie?
B-But...
Mom and Tooka and Granny and Grandpa all...
That's why I'm here.
Yuuta...
T-Too—
I mean, the Priestess must be on high alert.
It won't be easy to escape.
Then you're giving up?
When do you wanna go?
N-Now!
Now?
Yeah, right now!
Once you make it to the tree, go around the right so that it conceals you.
I don't even have shoes, you know.
Don't worry. I do.
Reassuring.
What was that?
No idea.
Huh?
Death.
It caught her?
Ouch...
That's Tooka for you.
I didn't expect you would help her.
What are you planning?
Who knows? I'm not sure myself.
That was pretty cool!
You stay out of this.
Typical. I guess you really are...
a dangerous element.
Yuuta!
Rikka!
Over here!
Come on!
Rikka!
Jump!
You okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go to where I hid Rad Zwei Hellblau!
You just had to, didn't you?
How far is it?
About ten kilometers.
Th-That far?!
Don't worry.
The Dark Flame Master's the greatest!
The greatest?
Yeah, the greatest!
The Dark Flame Master's the greatest!
I told you not to call me that.
Let's go faster!
But the Wicked Eye is even greater.
Yeah, yeah.
Rikka and Togashi didn't come back in the end.
Tooka went somewhere too.
The things people do for love.
Who does what for what?
Oh you, Deko!
I'd say it's just a matter of time.
What is?
What the death?
Who knows?
Ah... Kumin...
You saw him? Three years ago?
Yeah.
Dad was gone.
But I saw him that night.
I could see Dad beyond the horizon.
I could see him.
That's why I'm sure he's still here.
He's watching over this place, and me as well, from the other side of the horizon.
I couldn't agree with that, but neither could I deny it.
Just...
Stop.
Are we there?
Yeah.
My base, where Dad and I and
everyone else were all together.
Land for Sale
This is reality.
Dad's gone.
This is the present.
Rend reality.
Shatter synapse.
Vanishment... this world!
To be continued
inside identity ibasho wa doko
Inside identity! Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji ka douka
Getting it wrong is a shame?
sunaosa ga itai toka
Being honest hurts?
dare ga nanto iou to tadashisa nante wakannai ze
Whatever people say, they don't know what's right
futsuu ni nagareteku nichijou ni
The boring river of time drifts on
muri shite najimaseta
We tried to fit in with the flow
shizunjimatta kouseitachi wo
And our uniqueness sunk in the mud
kande nonde haite warau
So chew it, swallow it, spit it out and laugh
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I wish you understood me"
iitai kedo ienakute
That's what I want to say, but I can't
nande daremo wakatte kunnai no to
"No one ever understands me"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kana
Is it selfish to think that? Is it? Is it?
kanjouteki na taiyou wa
The emotional Sun in the sky
netsu wo agesugite dounika narisou
Overheated, reaching its limit
sakebitakute shou ga nai
Of course I want to shout
gamushara ni mo tometeru identity
My fast and furious identity
inside my feeling
Inside my feeling
inside my justice
Inside my justice
jama shinaide
Don't get in my way
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?