Words of ancient times...
Word Chain Game Under the Heated Table
People say each one of them had magical powers.
Those words went on endlessly, connecting to each other.
I suggest fortifying the barrier around this society using them.
Gulp...
You're talking about the word chain game, aren't you, Master?
I'm impressed that you got that after that explanation.
I wouldn't be exaggerating if I called the deep bond between Master and me "one in body and soul."
Which leads us to...
"The Wicked Eye"
"...is all-powerful."
"Uriel."
"Louis XIII."
"Stone."
"The deadly Wicked Eye"
"...was sealed"
U-Um...
"...with a lost artifact."
Keep it real!
I am.
That was cool!
Death would come get Master if she wasn't at least this witty!
Let us continue with "the locked up castle of darkness."
"Royal Warrant."
"Whetstone."
How cowardly of you to keep ending them with "shi," Nibutani!
I really don't want to hear that from you!
Chuckle.
You're full of cowardice up to the top of your fingernails.
Iron Claw!
That hurts like death!
Shi... shi...
Okay, five seconds left.
Four.
Three.
M-Master...
Two.
"Don't miss the Wicked Eye calling Death's powers!"
As if that TV-promo-like answer is a legit answer!
Yes, it is!
Do you plan on taking over a TV station to make that show?
I'm trembling with fear of death thinking about that plan of yours.
You're going to advance the plan by advancing into the station, right?
And you're irritating me.
So it's my turn?
Um...
"Antiquity."
"Edelweiß."
"Sushi."
A-As I thought, you are of the light element.
And the enemy of the Wicked Eye.
Seriously, what a gutless girl.
Call me whatever you want.
Come on, it's "shi!"
Shi...
Shi... shi shi shi...
Okay, five seconds left.
Shi... shi shi...
"D-Don't miss the Wicked Eye escaped death!"
Let that rest already!
I-It works.
As if.
And shouldn't it be "escaping"?
T-T... T-This is all your fault anyway!
Using the ancient word "shi" more often than you'd ever find it in the Infinite Corridor...
I have no idea what you're talking about.
She's really our enemy, Master!
Tune in again!
Another peaceful day.