eighth-grade syndrome
Are you familiar with the term "eighth-grade syndrome"?
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
it may have been
lumped in with
"teenage rebellion"
at one point in time...
Reference Image
It refers to a frightening, yet charming "condition"
that eighth-graders are said to catch as they enter puberty.
As their self-consciousness grows while their childish imaginations remain intact,
they may adopt strange mannerisms.
You know. Those.
They only read the weekly comic magazines—until yesterday,
when they picked up foreign classics in their original languages.
They had never drunk coffee before,
but suddenly they love it, and black.
They one day declared that they were psychic,
and turned into one of those occult freaks.
Reference Image
Now, when this young man was in middle school,
he had quite the case of eighth-grade syndrome.
He called himself the "Dark Flame Master,"
and his catchphrase was...
Be engulfed by the Dark Flame and begone!
The shame! The shame! The shame!
Go away! Go away! Go away!
As you can see, it's a condition so embarrassing
that the slightest recollection of it
makes you want to shrivel up and die.
Ow...
Did you see?
No!
Do you want to see?
Huh?
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You looked this way
and saw me pouting with a frown ❤
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I was just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
matte miru no
That's all I really wanted ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
But the things I mumbled to myself
after "Nothing" were
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
hazukashii kara
Way too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask me what I said
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing us together
mou hajimatteta
Had already started then ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
Hey, Kuzuha...
What's up, Onii-chan?
How do I look?
Normal.
Totally normal, right?!
Yeah.
All right!
You're so weird, Onii-chan.
What's with all this junk?
It's mine.
I'll take it out later. Just walk around it.
Wow, there's a lot.
Onii-chan, didn't you spend all your New Year's money on this?
I don't care! Just put it down!
And after you bought it,
you shouted, "Now the world is mine!"
No, I didn't!
Yes, you did.
You used to wear this weird coat and—
Shut up already!
You can stop bringing it up now!
Good morning...
Mom, Onii-chan's entrance ceremony is today.
An Unforseen Encounter...
With The Tyrant's Eye of Truth
Did you forget?
Oh, that's right!
It's okay.
They did say parental attendance wasn't mandatory.
I'm so sorry!
No, excuse me.
Um...
Go ahead.
Thank you.
That uniform... We're in the same school?
Her again?!
It opened?!
What the heck?! I missed my train!
Entrance Ceremony
Wow. I don't know anyone here.
Well, it's only natural.
I did pick a place where no one
from my middle school would go.
You only make one first impression!
Calm down!
Just ease your way in!
Togashi Yuuta.
I can't take off this bandage for one reason:
The Black Flame Dragon should rampage elsewise!
My heart's breaking, Mommy.
Thanks to that, I was a loner.
Well, whatever!
Can't dwell on the past!
And no one here knows mine, anyway!
I am the Dark Flame Master!
Be engulfed by the Dark Flame and die!
Sealed for all eternity!
Togashi
This is my seat?
Hey there.
Sorry, but could I borrow some lead?
Oh, sure.
Which middle'd you go to?
Hishiyama Middle.
Wow, that's pretty far.
Yeah, so I don't know anyone here.
Oh, thanks.
I don't know too many people here, either.
Anyway, nice to meet you.
I'm Isshiki Makoto.
I-I'm Togashi Yuuta.
Yes! This is the "normal" I was hoping for!
High school's gonna be great!
So, what do you think?
Of the girls in our class, I mean.
The girls?
We've got a lot of cuties among us.
I'd say they're pretty good.
Well, I kinda just got here, so—
We're in the same class?
Ooh, good catch.
Checking out Nibutani?
Nibutani?
Yeah. Nibutani Shinka.
Can't say for sure yet, but I got a feeling she'll be number one.
Could this be the red string of fate at work?
So we finally meet.
My eye!
My eye! It resonates!
Do you know her?
No, I don't!
For aeons have I searched this sphere, solely to meet you.
Did she just confess to you?!
Damn, I'm jealous!
No, she clearly didn't!
That's right. This is eighth...
Eighth...
Eighth-grade syndrome!
My eye!
My eye...
Huh?
Me?
The bottom shelf...
Is this it?
The nurse had to step out for a bit,
so they said to put some eyedrops in for now.
If we don't hurry, we'll miss the ceremony.
You were on my balcony last night, weren't you?
What was that all about?
It resonated.
My eye.
Yes. We have met before, in ages long past.
The Tyrant's Eye of Truth revealed this to me the moment you entered its sight.
I awaited my opportunity to make contact with you.
This bitterness!
The agents of the darkness!
And so, it is sealed.
She really does...
The Tyrant's Eye of Truth is realized by controlling the powers of the darkness with a pure heart.
As such, contact with both the corruption of darkness
and the purity of holy water must be avoided.
No doubt about it.
She's got eighth-grade syndrome.
I nearly fell into a trap set by my enemies.
Don't let your guard down,
Dark Flame Master.
Huh?
Be engulfed by the Dark Flame and—
Stop!
How do you know about that?!
Where did you hear that?!
The Tyrant's Eye sees all truth.
All things about you, Yuuta, level 7 mage.
Where on Earth did you hear that?!
With but a glimpse, your past and future—
Where did you hear that?!
Yuuta!
That hurts!
I asked, where did you hear that?!
I can't see!
Yuuta, I can't see!
I heard you say it behind the gym!
The gym?!
I didn't think anyone was listening.
Listen, you'd better not tell anyone about it!
I know.
I know the laws that govern distortions on the Unseen Horizon
and the structural changes that such phenomena—
No!
I'm talking about my past!
About me being the Dark Flame Master
and wielding the Dark Flame!
Why? It's so cool.
It's not cool!
Listen, I graduated that along with middle school!
Completely done! Never going back!
Really?
Yeah.
You've finally advanced to level 8 magehood?!
No!
Eighth-grade syndrome!
I'm not the Dark Flame Master or a mage!
I'm a normal kid starting high school!
Don't give me that look.
Just so you know, you're a normal kid starting high school too.
I have the Tyrant's Eye.
Doesn't matter.
And whatever it is, it doesn't exist in the first place.
It exists.
No, it doesn't.
Do you want to see it, then?
Huh?
My eye. Do you want to see it?
Does she really...
No, there's no way.
Yeah. Show me.
No way...
No freaking way!
S-Stay away!
Ow...
Hold on a second. I'll put it in again.
A color contact?!
No! It's coming inside me!
Don't say things like that.
Afterimage...
Look, I'll repeat myself all day if I have to.
I'm done with that stuff.
So just stay away from me,
and don't tell anyone about my past.
But you saw my eye.
As such, our contract has been made.
We are of one dark soul.
Soulmates of the soul.
That's a lot of "soul."
I'm heading out.
You should hurry up too.
Now, on behalf of the new students,
a word from their representative, Nibutani Shinka.
Here.
Having someone like that following me around...
Honored faculty, staff, and now fellow students.
Maybe I need to keep working on the normal?
We would first like to thank you
for preparing this wonderful entrance ceremony for us.
Today, we begin a new chapter in our lives
She's our representative?
with the spring sun and cherry blossoms smiling warmly upon us.
Well, now that introductions are over,
Physical
Examination
One-on-One
with a Student
we're all done for today.
Make sure you look over your class schedules when you get home.
Hey, hey, Togashi.
You doing anything after this?
A few of us were thinking
of grabbing a quick bite.
Huh?!
Are you... inviting me?
Yup.
But is it really okay for me to go?
Why not?
Oh! Because of Takanashi-san?
Takanashi?
The girl you took to the nurse's office!
Takanashi-san.
You two promise to go home together or something?
No, we didn't!
I have nothing to do with her!
Absolutely nothing at all!
Wait, don't tell me you swing that way.
I don't!
But, like...
It'd be bad if people started rumors.
You really think so?
Isshiki-kun! Are you coming?
Yeah, I'm coming!
All right. Let's go.
O-Okay.
Togashi-kun!
Do you have a moment?
It looks like she lost her wallet.
Takanashi-san only moved here recently, so she doesn't know her way around yet.
Togashi-kun, could you take her back home?
Huh? Why me?
She lives really close to you.
See?
That's the floor above mine!
That explains everything.
So could you please?
I'm really sorry about this.
I'll go with you next time.
Yeah.
See you.
When'd you move in?
I thought there was an
office lady living alone above us.
My transmigration occurred two days ago.
Takanashi Touka is my elder sister.
I see.
So you moved in with your sister.
So it would appear.
But Touka is actually a mage with the Unseen Horizon Administration Bureau.
An enemy.
Hey...
Once she awakens, there is no fighting her,
even with the Tyrant's Eye.
She's terrifying!
She's that scary?
Don't give up, Rikka! Stand your ground!
I can see why your sister'd be angry.
You keep spewing weird stuff like that.
I request your assistance, Yuuta.
With the power of the Dark Flame Master,
we can break through the Administration Bureau's interference and find the Unseen Horizon!
I told you not to call me that!
I thought up a new attack for you.
Judgment Lucifer!
Well?
You're wearing roller shoes?
What are you, a kid?
They provide superior mobility.
And with these, if I'm hit by an enemy attack...
"Looks like they broke two or three ribs."
I can do this! It's cool!
Don't do that in public!
What do you want?
I'll treat you.
Wait.
Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right...
Hey, Takanashi-san... the train...
Now put the coin in!
Huh?
And now, B, A!
"B, A"?! What?!
A drink to restore magic power.
The Administration Bureau has secretly stored them in various places.
We just missed the train!
Free Drink!
You win a free drink! Isn't that great?
Now do you see my power?
No, you looked surprised, yourself.
Kabutomushi Movers
By the way, "B" and "A" stand for "banana" and "apple."
They change with the season, so be careful.
Uh-huh.
We're finally here.
How short is your attention span?
Onii-chan!
Get up here, quick!
They were supposed to move these into Takanashi-san's place,
but they said she was taking too long and asked us to hold on to them.
What kind of movers are they?
Are these yours?
My return home was obstructed by the Administration Bureau.
I intended to return home by 1500 hours—
Onii-chan, who's this?
You know Takanashi-san upstairs? It's her younger sister.
She moved in with her.
Oh...
How much stuff do you have?
Isn't this a bit much for one person?
They're all very important.
I really hope they're not all junk!
Onii-chan, I'll go buy dinner.
Some of it is useful.
Oh, it's an automatic.
It can serve as a weapon.
Gungnir! Ha!
And for defense...
Schwarzschild!
Enough! I get it!
Here.
Just get them out of here.
Fine, I'll help.
And that's the last one.
Thank you.
I'm grateful.
Yeah, you'd better be.
Where's your sister?
It seems she always comes home late.
Oh, Takanashi-san's sister?
You're both so pretty!
Yuuta, you need to work hard!
At what?
Um... Your eye...
Just ignore it.
There's nothing wrong with it at all.
The Tyrant's Eye of Truth is realized by controlling the powers of darkness—
And you don't need to explain.
Understood.
Begone!
Yumeha, don't just bring that thing in here!
Ow!
It's cool!
It's not cool!
If you equipped that on your back, it would be perfect!
Perfect?
Onii-chan used to do that.
He wore this weird black coat
and strapped that on his back.
Kuzuha!
Yuuta acted so funny back then.
He'd chant weird spells or something before he ate and stuff.
Mom!
Don't you have to go to work tonight?
Fine...
Honestly...
I told them not to play with it because it was trash.
Trash?
Yeah.
Even though it means everything to the Dark Flame Master?
I keep telling you. I'm done with all that stuff.
Why?
Because it's embarrassing.
It's cool.
It's not cool.
Not in the least.
There's no point in acting like that in the first place.
The Dark Flame and the power of the Black Flame Dragon don't even exist.
I was just being stupid.
They exist.
They have power.
They don't.
They do.
Look...
So...
Don't throw them away.
Be engulfed by the Dark Flame and begone!
Don't get me wrong.
I just thought it'd be a waste
to throw them all away.
I'll sell them and get my money back.
Let's go back in.
You'll catch a cold if you stay out here too long.
That's what I said.
But the rain this spring is actually kind of warm.
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
But no matter who says what
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
You can't know if it's really true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Fit in and act "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Killing off everything that ever made them unique,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to say it, but I just can't
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why can't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Turning the heat up so high, I think I might just blow
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
I
den
ti
ty
Identity
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?