Supplementary Lessons in the Clubroom
Master, don't give in to death!
I'll always be with you!
Takanashi didn't do well in the last pop quiz at all, so...
Just how bad did you score?
22 points...
You scored so bad you failed?!
You're hurting me, Yuuta!
Has Rikka always been bad at English?
I took quite a lot of damage from the attack of the Magicians' Society the day before it.
This time, it won't be a problem at all.
I see.
Then this problem will be as easy as pie, right?
R-Right now, the wicked thoughts of the United Kingdom Doctrine struck my body!
M-Master!
Dekomori...
Ms. Nanase...
Get away from here...
Come on...
If you say "United Kingdom Doctrine," they must've been in English, right?
Yes...
Hello!
By the way, what do you do on the weekend usually?
I like cooking and reading books, so I always do on my day off.
Do you wanna join?
In Japanese please...
All right, time to solve the problem now!
What an intense déjà vu.
Don't you always chant those English and German-like spells, Takanashi?
German is cool!
As cool as death!
That's it?
Chinese characters are cool too, aren't they?
There's "darkness."
There's "beheading."
There's "disgrace."
And there's "judgment!"
You really love Chinese characters, huh?
No, this has nothing to do with the eighth-grader syndrome at all!
I was just thinking about how glad I am to have been born in Japan.
And I was showing my respect for their 4,000 year-old use in China...
As expected from the Dark Flame Master
who's been blessed by the Dark Flame Dragon.
Didn't you get that I was desperately trying to deny it just now?!
But thinking about how the Wicked Eye is the Jet-Black Fallen Angel,
both English and German should be fine.
It somehow feels like I got the title of a useless person right now...
That reminds me, your pocket umbrella had a weird name as well, hadn't it?
This is not a pocket umbrella.
It's Schwarz Sechs Perfect Customize Guerzoniansus.
As I told you, stop putting "Guerzoniansus" in there!
It's the artifact of a new world that combines offense and defense.
As you can see, it's both the strongest lance and the strongest shield.
By the way, it also protects me from rain water.
So just an umbrella after all.
Okay, then let's hear your explanation about that "Schwarz Sechs Perfect Customize Guerzoniansus" again.
Keep the English parts in Japanese and the Japanese ones in English.
Nana is the devil!
J-J-J-Jisu izu notto ei poketto unburera...
What an idiot.
Yeah, truly an idiot.
And how would you call "Schwarz Sechs Perfect Customize Guerzoniansus" in Japanese?
Now come on, you named it, didn't you?
Ugh... O-Of course!
Um...
The Mechanical Something of the World's Vainglory - New Version!
Seriously...
A-And...
It's a very efficient w-weapon...
Yuuta, what do I do?
I completely forgot it...
Do you have the head of a bird or what?!
I'm getting dizzy, Yuuta!
The correct answer is "The 6th Black Perfectly Customized..."
But what is "Guerzoniansus?"
Please forget that part!
So cool!
The End