By the way, there's something I've been wondering about for a while.
Bun Discussion Under the Heated Table
What's inside those hair buns of yours?
Deko?
I assume it's morning stars.
This
No way that's true.
She did use morning stars as her hammer in her battle with Forest Summer a while back, though...
Their usual content really is a mystery.
A real mystery.
And it doesn't look like all there's inside is hair.
I've been wondering about it for a while.
Just what is inside them?
So, what is inside those buns on your hair-ends?
Will not knowing it accelerate your death?
If you want to know that badly, I might just entrust you with my secret.
I do!
Please tell us, Deko.
How could I decline now?
You too, lower your head to the floor and beg as if you're trying to avert your death.
I don't want to know it that badly.
I'm sure it's something stupid anyway.
It's not stupid!
You want to see it for sure!
Not really.
Show it to those who want to know.
Just say "show me!"
All right, show us then.
Okay, here it goes!
That's really all you wanted?
All right, pay close attention!
What the heck...
So there were sweets inside.
They're sweet buns!
The basic ingredient of my buns is candy of death.
They work as snacks and increase my attack stats as well.
An exemplary case of hitting two birds with one stone!
No surprise it hurts when you hit me with them.
Not bad, Dekomori.
You combined food supplies with attack power!
Just you saying that makes is worth being your servant, Master!
I'd been putting cookies in there a while ago,
but that didn't turn out well.
So after that I've been using candy of death.
Cookies aren't that sturdy, are they?
Tune in again!