I have a big gun, I took it from my Lord...
Sick with Justice, I just wanna feel you...
I'm your angel, only a ring away...
You make me violate you, no matter who you are!
It's all up to you, no one lives forever...
Been burn in the hell, by all those pigs out there...
It's always been hell, from when I was born...
They make me violate them, no matter who they are!
Get down on your knees! Get a good head on your shoulders!
If it's for your guys, go to the end of the Earth...
Do what you think, give it with dedication...
I'll put out your misery!
You made a mess! For Christ sakes, this rotten world!
Shit out of luck! Go with my vision!
Light up the fire! Right on the power!
Weapon... I have it all!
It's a big difference.
This wild, dirty place is far different
from my hometown.
I'm sorry. This isn't a city that
a child like you should have to see.
Roanapur at night.
I'm all right.
You believe in your people
from home, right?
Of course I do. I believe in her...
that she'll come and save me.
You're lucky. To be able to feel
that in your heart.
That the maid who you believe in
will come for you.
I don't know whether
it'll happen or not...
...but you must have a good family
for you to have such great faith.
Well, I tend to wonder how
my family feels about me.
You mean...
No, it's nothing important.
Do you miss your mommy?
Do you think so? If I did, I might've
said goodbye to this place long ago.
Rock. That's a pointless story.
That's a story some brat
would come up with...
...who chases after his mommy
when it's convenient.
We're just talking about ideals.
To see if you hold something
in your heart that you believe in.
Then, if I'm ever kidnapped,
would you come save me...
...waving around that
Cutlass of yours?
I wouldn't forgive you for being
stupid enough to get kidnapped.
If that happened, you'd have
to bite off your navel...
...and beg forgiveness of your comrades
for causing such trouble 'til you die.
That's the kind of world this is.
See? These are the kinda friends
I hang out with.
But just the same,
they're worth sticking around.
Kid. I really hope...
...that the woman you talk about
is as strong as you believe.
This hasn't seen much action lately.
This Cutlass.
Just kidding.
I guess there's no point in wishing.
Not while I'm dealing with...
...a maid-obsessed brat
from the countryside.
Did you hear that? "Be rude,"
she says. This bitch!
- She makes me laugh!
- What are you gonna do?!
What's this?
A fight?
I am afraid I will not be able
to hold back. Please pardon me.
Well then, enjoy yourselves.
What's this, didn't the bar
just reopen?
She's sure blasting
something flashy.
H-How dare you!
You damn bitch!
Guys! Don't hold back!
Kill her!
Please do as you wish,
if you can.
Shut up!
Roberta!
Damn you!
I-It's not working, Bro! Why won't
she fall? Is it made of kevlar?
Damn it!
You better pay for all of this!
Quite unexpectedly, we've walked
right into a very bad fight.
But the fact that they're going at it
works in our favor.
How about we take off
while they're busy?
Take off? To where?
We can go fishing at Phuket beach
until this cools down.
I'm not in the mood for drinking
with a gunfight on the side.
I'm no Giuliano Gemma.
Hey, will you hurry up and decide
if we're gonna shoot or not?
Good call.
I vote not to shoot.
Kid stays here. Don't wanna go for
a walk with a claymore landmine.
But he's worth something, Dutch.
The exit became a war-zone
while we were talking.
There's no way out over there.
Anyway, this kid isn't money anymore.
We'll leave him here, okay?
But that's...
We've got no choice.
Damn, damn, fuck.
Now, then.
Garcia. Listen.
Don't move from this spot
until the gunfire dies down.
When it gets quiet,
leave this place...
...and go home to Venezuela
with your maid.
I... I didn't know.
That Roberta is...
She's not someone capable
of killing. But...
Why...
Garcia...
Rock! What are you waiting for?!
Ten thousand dollars for
the bottles of booze...
...fifteen thousand
for the furniture...
...plus twenty thousand
for the building.
Now the problem is figuring out
who to send the invoice to.
Revy!
Y-You bitch!
Revy! Is this your doing again?!
How many times do your friends
need to tear up my shop?!
They're not my friends! I have
nothing to do with this, you idiot!
Foul timing to quiet down,
you assholes.
Lagoon Company!
What are you guys doing here?!
What happened to the cargo
you were delivering to us?!
Hold your horses!
Don't jump to conclusions, Abrego!
What's the cargo doing here?!
Did you ignore our contract?!
Like I said, don't jump to conclusions!
We'll talk about the payment later!
Young master.
Roberta.
I didn't expect to see you here,
young master.
Master has been very worried
about you. Now, come.
It cannot be helped
if you are afraid.
I shall explain myself later.
Who are those people?
This isn't good. Their eyes met.
No, Roberta! Don't!
Stand back, Maid.
Everyone here would
rather be alive than dead.
You too, right?
Don't be crazy!
You're being the enemy!
Shut up!
As long as you don't start shooting...
...you'll get the young master
home in one piece.
Without his brains getting splattered
on the floor. Get what I'm saying?
I am thinking.
We're not done with you!
I have finished thinking.
Una bendicion para los vivos.
Un ramo de flores para
los muertos.
That's Spanish.
A blessing for the living.
- Con una espada por la justicia.
- Flowers for the dead.
- Un castigo de muerte...
- Wield a sword for justice.
- ...para los malvados.
- Asi Llegamos al altar de los santos.
- The punishment of death for the villains.
Like this we join
at the line of the saints.
The Loveless family creed.
I cannot agree to your request.
I will get the young master
home in one piece.
However, I must work
in accordance to this creed.
In the name of Santa Maria.
Those words...
The hammer of righteousness
to all injustice!
That... that bitch!
Now! Let's go!
Hey! Stay away!
Stay away!
Revy!
It's about time you die!
You Bloodhound of Florencia!
What a crazy bitch.
This makes the Battle of Khe Sanh
look like a picnic in the park! Hey!
Is Revy all right?!
Her injuries are minor,
but she has a concussion.
Revy! Say something!
Hey!
Please stop.
Please stop, Roberta!
Stop it!
Garcia...
Rock!
Don't just stand there!
We're leaving!
Run!
Take me with you.
Young master.
I can't. I can't deal with this.
I don't like this Roberta!
Hold it!
Now I remember,
those words of yours earlier.
El perro de cassa de Florencia.
The Bloodhound from Florencia.
I can't believe you're alive.
Not even Jesus would've noticed.
These four years since you left
the Colombian Revolutionary Army...
...everyone from the drug cartels
to Interpol have been after you!
The cartels put a 400 thousand dollar
bounty on your head. Dead or alive.
Luck is finally on my side!
If I bring your head back,
I'll be a lieutenant of the cartel!
I no longer have a reason
to keep you alive.
If you will excuse me, I must be
on my way. Please accept this.
Now, everybody.
Farewell.
Damn. She's unbelievably thorough.
Rock, you bastard.
I told you to leave the kid behind.
I couldn't help it.
I can't leave him in there.
Do you think that killed her?
Get in the car!
I shouldn't be able to hear anything,
but I feel something.
I feel her footsteps getting closer.
Her black maid's outfit
will appear from that fiery exit soon.
Then hurry up
and get in the car!
- Where should we go?
- The question is, is there any place to go?
Not likely!
I believe it.
That's a killer robot from the future!
The only thing different
from the movies...
...is that Schwarzenegger
doesn't star in it.
There's nothing funny about it.
I'm having trouble seeing
the humor in this.
We've got her precious
little boy with us.
Anyway, we'll head for the port!
Hurry to the Lagoon!
Bad news has a way of gathering easily
without much effort.
She's pretty famous.
Her code name is "Bloodhound".
It's because once she's locked
onto her prey, she always kills.
This is gonna be a pain.
They're calling, Sergeant.
It's probably the worst possible news.
You're right. She's coming.
Rock! Wake Revy up!
- This is no time to be comfortably asleep!
- Revy! Revy! Revy!
Damn it!
Shit!
Corporal Menshov,
what is the situation?
Ma'am!
The Yellow Flag is totally destroyed!
The Bloodhound and Lagoon are gone!
However, a Plymouth was seen...
...heading to the city on the main street
ten minutes ago!
Do not leave that spot, Corporal.
Continue gathering information.
Roger. What should
I tell the owner of the bar?
Tell him not to worry
about insurance.
I am heading
to the city with a squad.
Captain. Are we going back to war
after so long?
Playing mafia is not good.
It dulls your body.
We'll see. But you can never
be too prepared.
We owe Lagoon.
Or rather, Dutch.
We can't leave this as is.
Let's go, comrades.
Cock your hammers.
Die, will you?!
Let go of me! You bitch!
Damn it!
Okay, now's our chance!
Hang on, Dutch!
We'll head to the port
using these back alleys.
Once we're out to sea,
it doesn't matter who she is...
Damn.
This isn't good, Benny.
We'll lose speed this way.
But her radiator's shot.
Her car won't run.
You should've paid more attention
to Rock's joke, Benny-boy.
Imagine her as an invincible
killer robot or something.
We're gonna push it!
Rock, do whatever you can
to wake Revy up!
We'll need her gun
if we get into a shootout.
Revy! Revy! Wake up!
Benny, turn at the next curb! Get onto
the main road and go at full speed!
Roger!
Are you all right, Benny?
Wake up!
Shit. The engine won't start.
Hurry, Benny!
Get down!
Young Master.
Roberta.
Next Episode
Those are no doubt the three
most terrifying women in the world.
This feels like Ground Zero.