Koneko-chan?
Gya-kun, hide yourself.
You're humans?
Correct...
We are humans with a specific talent
who have formed a pact with devils, we are...
magicians.
Well, you devils are said to be able to use magic,
but we are superior.
Hand over the vampire.
We know he is here.
What do they want?
You can't escape, give up.
A magic seal?
They were seeking shelter, but now they are trapped.
Just as we hoped.
We should be safe for now.
Stay calm,
President and the others will soon come.
K-Koneko-chan...
Koneko-chan!
We have you now...
These seals will restrict you from moving.
Resistance is futile.
Stop what you're doing! Let us go!
Gya-kun, I'm sorry.
Gya-kun...
This stand-off that we're in...
is nothing but bad news for this world.
Don't you think?
Takaga shireteta terai ga uzumaite
My puny arrogance came back to me
Oisugaru koto mo dekizu ni ita yo
and I couldn't go to you for help
Namida no wake kimi ni ienai mama de
I couldn't tell you why I was crying
Kuchibiru wa itsumo sora wo nirande ita
and always frowned up to the sky
Uzumoreteta yami yori kimi ga koete kita kyoukaisen
You dug through the darkness to cross this line
Sekai system wa kakumeigire
The world's out of changes to make
Kaikan itami hakai souzou
Pleasure, pain, destruction, creation
Kaete yuku watashi no yowasa wo
I'm going to change my own weaknesses
Ima oshiyoseru kanjouron
All I can make are appeals to emotion
Inochi gake no ai wa amakunaiwa
Love's not easy with my life on the line
Tsuyoku motto tsuyoku
Stronger, even stronger
Donna uso ga matteita to shitemo
No matter what lies I face
Eranda michibiki shinjite
I've already chosen which signs to follow
Furumau koto wa nai to yasashii akuma no hohoemi wa
The devil smiles at me, telling me to be myself
Hakanaku subete wo terasu no
and shines a faint light on the world
Episode 11
The Leaders' Summit Begins!
The ones who started the war,
God and the Satans, are gone, after all.
Irina...
So you also know...
That's why we've got two guys here who, although not part of our stand-off,
have the power to change the world.
Emperor of Red Dragon,
and Emperor of White Dragon,
I'd like your input on this.
I just want strong guys to fight.
You don't need a war to find tough guys.
Thought you'd say that.
Well, Emperor of Red Dragon,
what do you think?
Wha-
U-Uh...
That's a little too much to process...
In that case, let me to break it down for you.
Hyoudou Issei,
if we're at war,
you can't sleep with Rias Gremory.
Wha-
But...
if we declare peace,
survival and propagation of the species become the priority.
Propagation...
of the species?!
That's right.
Every night, you and Rias Gremory could be making babies.
What are you saying?!
Peace lets you spend every day making babies,
and if there's war, there wont be that opportunity.
How's that?
Makes it nice and simple, right?
Making babies...
Making babies every night...
with President?!
Issei!
So, if we have peace,
I can have sex with the President?!
Wait, do I even have the right to do that?
But if we're at peace...
it really could happen one day!
I want peace!
Make peace, not war!
I want to make love with the President!
Issei-kun,
Sirzechs-sama is present.
Jeez...
You pervert.
My, my.
Crap!
I can't believe I said that out loud!
A-Anyway...!
I'm only going to use my power for Rias-sama and my friends!
That's absolute!
Emperor of Red Dragon,
you mentioned that you
wanted to ask me something.
You remembered our promise?
Of course.
It's about Asia.
Why did you exile her?
Asia was so faithful,
so why was she exiled?
Issei...
After God died,
only his System remained.
You could call it a force that controls protection, mercy, and miracles.
I am just barely keeping it running,
so I had to remove all those who could cause it to malfunction.
So it was because Asia could
heal Devils and Fallen Angels?
We are maintained by the
devotion from our adherents.
We must remove any elements that could possibly harm our System.
And is that why an adherent who was accidentally told of God's passing
is also at risk of doing so?
I suppose it is.
We had no choice but to exile you and Asia Argento.
I beg your forgiveness.
She wasn't a traitor?
There is no need for that, Michael-sama.
Being a faithful Christian for most of my life,
I had some regrets,
but now, as a Devil,
I am happy with my life.
My apologies to the other people of God present.
I, too, feel happy with my life.
I've found so many great people here.
I cannot thank you enough for your forgiving hearts.
Oh yeah,
I heard one of my girls tricked and killed that girl over there.
Don't say that like it's none of your business!
Some Fallen Angel woman
killed Asia to try to impress you!
I am responsible for what my subordinates do,
so I'll pay you back with something only I can do.
What?!
Issei.
Wh-What the...
Did someone... stop time?
Looks like it.
We weren't affected due to our immense power.
And we had our Dragons.
It appears those guys were
protected by their Holy Swords.
What's going on?
I'm all right, thanks to you.
Who the hell are those guys?!
Those are magicians.
Magicians?!
Hey, I'm the magical girl here!
What's causing time to stop, then?
I take it they forced the half-vampire's ability into Balance Breaker state.
You mean Gasper?!
Very few people possess the ability to stop time.
He is most likely in the hands of the enemy.
President...
There's nothing more insulting than
having my family used by some terrorists.
Our guards...
Is that transport magic?
Somebody has connected this barrier to a gate.
Conversely, they have disabled our transport magic circles.
They got us good.
Yes.
Not only their timing, but their tactic of using Rias Gremory's family as a weapon against us.
There's a traitor?
We can't just stand here and watch this happen.
If Gasper-kun's power becomes any stronger,
even we could...
Even Sirzechs-sama?
He's that powerful?
He's a "Mutation Piece."
"Mutation Piece?"
It's a piece that can cause all sorts of anomalies.
The bishop piece I used for Gasper
can contain power that would
normally take many pieces to store.
It was a "Mutation Piece."
I didn't know he was so powerful!
He has unfathomable potential.
That's why we had no choice but to seal him away.
Anyway, we've got to do
something about that half-vampire.
It's too risky to fight back
with his powers on the loose.
Onii-sama.
I left an unused Rook in the old building.
A Rook?
You're going to castle?
Castle?
It's a special move that can switch the King and Rook's positions in one turn.
We can't send you alone, though.
Gasper is my family.
I will take him back personally.
If we could borrow Sirzechs-sama's power,
we would be able to send one more person with you.
Let me go, then.
I will protect my President!
I wish you luck.
Thank you!
All you have to do is kill the terrorists and the half-vampire in one shot.
Want me to do it?
Why you-
Read the mood here, Vali.
We're trying to make peace here.
I just can't stand doing nothing.
Then, why not go screw up our friends outside?
They ought to panic a little when they see the Emperor of White Dragon.
All right.
Balance Break!
Vanishing Dragon.
Balance...
Breaker!
That easily?!
I had to sacrifice my left hand
to do that for just ten seconds!
Damn...
That guy is crazy strong.
However, his strength reeks of trouble.
President, let's bring Gasper back in one piece!
Oh, hold up a sec.
I'm counting on you to protect Rias,
Issei-kun.
No problem!
Koneko-chan!
Gasper!
Let's search the other rooms.
All right.
Take these.
You can use them as a sacrifice.
A sacrifice...
to go into Balance Breaker?!
Only as your last resort.
You'll still burn through your stamina just as fast.
I know...
I tried that and failed once.
Give the other one to the half-vampire.
It'll keep his power under control.
Heed my words, kid.
You've gotten lucky every time so far,
but you aren't much stronger than an average human.
If you can't control your power,
you'll die.
You're your Sacred Gear's own weakness.
You don't have to tell me...
Once those two get hold of Gasper,
we'll begin our retaliation.
Sirzechs-sama.
This magic circle...
Is it...
Good day,
Satans Sirzechs-dono and Serafall-dono.
Wh-What are you doing here?!
The descendant of the previous Leviathan,
Katerea Leviathan?!
Chaos and ruin to the world...
That was from the new building!
Onii-sama!
The leaders of the three factions putting up a protective barrier together?
How pitiful!
What are you trying to achieve, Katerea?
To do exactly what this conference sought not to do.
If God and the Satans are gone,
this world will be ready for revolution.
Stop this, Katerea-chan!
Why are you...
Serafall...
You are the one that stole the
position of Leviathan from me!
I...
Don't worry.
I'll kill you right here, right now,
and take back the title of Satan Leviathan from you.
Good heavens.
I thought this was a big coup by the Devils...
But you are after the whole world, aren't you?
Yes, Michael.
This world is caught up in making up for the death of God and the Satans.
We are going to rebuild this rotting world,
and cause a revolution!
Azazel...
What are you laughing about?
"Rotting"? "Revolution"?
Like I've never heard that before.
Whoever says that always dies first.
How dare you insult me?!
May I, Sirzechs, Michael?
Katerea, do you have no intention of backing down?
No, Sirzechs.
You were a very good Satan...
but I'm sorry to say you were not the best!
I see.
That's too bad.
A descendant of the Leviathan
and a beast of the apocalypse...
You're not bad as an opponent.
Let's see how Armageddon looks, shall we?
Puny general of the Fallen Angels...!
Azazel...
and someone else.
Why is she...
President?
Katerea Leviathan...
You've heard that when the old
Satans passed on in the Great War,
the new ones took their place, haven't you?
Yes.
Your brother and the Student Council Chairwoman's sister did.
The Devils were in disarray after the long fighting...
to the point where continuing the war may have put them at risk of extinction.
However, since the descendants of the old Satans wanted to battle until their last breath,
they were exiled to the edges of the Underworld.
Then...
Katerea is one of them,
a descendant of the old Leviathan.
Let's go, Issei.
But President...
the others...
There's no time.
This is our priority.
Promote yourself to Queen, Issei.
Yes, Ma'am!
What was that?!
A devil?!
It can't be!
We disabled their transfer magic!
Gasper...
Koneko...
President Rias...
Issei-senpai...
We're outnumbered.
We can't let this become a battle of attrition.
Grayfia is analyzing the enemy's gate as we speak.
We have to buy time until she finishes.
We will keep the enemies at bay.
You three?
Naturally.
I'm here to guard Michael-sama in the first place.
I hope Azazel makes it.
It's nothing to worry about, Michael-sama.
Our comrades are with us.
Yes.
They will succeed.
Xenovia...
Irina...
Thank you.
Why..?
Why didn't you tell me?
You were exiled for finding out the truth.
You wanted me to tell you that God died?
I couldn't break your spirit like that.
Irina?
I want these peace talks to succeed.
If we attain peace, then even
a devil is no longer an enemy.
God's disciples would be allies.
Let's fight, for our future together.
Yeah...
I'm sorry, President.
It's all right.
I'm just glad the two of you are safe.
I don't know what tricks you used,
but move an inch, and...
President...
Please kill me.
The hell are you talking about?!
You're all better off with me dead!
I'm a coward, and I'm useless.
And my power's just...
causing you more trouble!
Don't be silly.
I told you when I made you my family...
Live for me,
and find a life that will make you happy.
You are my servant and my family.
I will never abandon you.
President... Rias...
Are you prepared to die, Azazel?
Snakes?
I want some answers first.
This aura you have...
it ain't something any regular
descendant of a Satan could pull off.
Who's backing you?
I have no need to answer you...
for you will die here and now!
Fool.
You should've brainwashed this
monster and made it into your tool.
I'm sorry, but unlike you lot, I care about my servants.
Shut your mouth!
You're a Devil!
Quit playing the innocent!
Gasper, cause me all the trouble you want.
Huh?
Time after time I'll scold you... and console you.
I'll never let you go.
President...
President...!
I...!
President...
You're the best, President Rias!
Gasper!
Don't run away!
Don't be afraid!
Don't cry!
Me, President,
Akeno-san,
Asia,
Kiba,
Koneko-chan,
Xenovia...
We're all your friends!
We're never gonna abandon you!
Boost!
Ascalon!
Blade!
Fighting back?
What are you doing?!
Issei?!
What are you doing?
But remember, Gasper...
you've got to take the first step!
You're a Gremory!
Show us that you're a man,
Gasper!
He disappeared!
No, he stopped time!
But we sealed his Sacred Gear!
The vampire changed form!
You...!
Don't be afraid!
Die!
It's sucking our blood!
It's sucking our power out too!
Is this...
It's part of the power hidden within him.
Just a part?
Your blood must have unleashed it.
But Issei, where did you get the idea?
Well, uh...
That guy...
President!
He stopped...
just my magic?!
It's useless.
I can see your every move.
Issei-senpai,
finish them!
Gotcha!
Dress...
Break.
It's like a showroom of awesome nudes!
Gasper, we're invincible if we're together!
Yes, Issei-senpai!
At last...
At long last...
my dream has come tru-
No.
I'm sorry.
You're the worst.
That should keep it under control.
Thank you!
All right...
let's go!
Yes, President!
What do you want to do?
churuchuchu doushitai
Hey, girls
churuchu hey girls
chu
ru
hey
girls
Lovely devils
raburi debiru
ra
girls
bu
ri
girls
de
bi
ru
You know what we wanna do! Yes!
churuchuchu aa shitai yes
They've descended upon us again
yes
kyou mo kourin
kyou
mo
kou
yes
rin
Girls are always greedy for more
shoujo wa shinkakei ni yokubari na no desu
I want this, I want that
are mo kore mo
They won't be content with what they had yesterday
kinou to kuraberun ja manzoku dekinai
Uh-oh
arere
a
i
re
Let's have a strategy meeting on how to upgrade
appugureedo sakusen kaigi
Agreed!
sansei
san
sei
I'm sure you have at least one of these
daredemo hitotsu kurai motte iru desho
You too, and you too
kimi mo kimi mo
Original magic words that protect your heart
orijinaru no jumon kokoro no omamori
Uh-huh
aruru
a
ri
ru
Positive thoughts that give you strength
purasu shikou taishitsu kyouka
Never compromising our love or dream
koi mo yume mo totteoki wo ne te ni ireru tame ni
Everyone
minna
mi
ni
n
na
We want to follow our heart
fiiringu juushi de
risaachi
de
Research
ri
saa
de
As we grow up
seichou shitai na
You see, girls are lovely devils
onna no ko wa ne raburi debiru
Deep down in their hearts, so treat them with great care
mune no naka kakushiteru no toriatsukai youchuui
They're only interested in having fun
tanoshii koto shika kyoumi nai no yo
Their whimsical temper makes them cute
wagamama ni kawaiku narun da
Promise!
yakusoku
ya
ku
so
Next Episode:
Hey, I'm Hyoudou Issei!
As the fighting grows more intense, I finally
battle Vali, the White Dragon Emperor.
I definitely can't lose for the sake of
the world... for the sake of the breasts!
Last episode, "Clash of the Twin Sky Dragons!"
Clash of the Twin Sky Dragons!
Episode 12
Defend the boobs!